<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent RB Jamaal Williams is visiting the Dolphins on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</link>
      <description>Williams has now met with two teams since the weekend, as the veteran running back was also brought in by the Bears on Saturday. Williams blew up for 262-1066-17 in 2022 but has totaled just 470 yards and two touchdowns on 154 carries since 2023 despite playing in 27 games. Williams’ workout comes a day after Alexander Mattison suffered a neck/shoulder injury in preseason action against the Bears. Now entering his age-30 season, Williams won’t have much to offer outside of a rotational and/or short-yardage role, which would make him unreliable for fantasy wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Alexander Mattison underwent neck surgery on Sunday and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99e1-d45c-a7fc-9bfbca940000</link>
      <description>Mattison left the field under his own power in Sunday’s game, and it was reported after the game that the veteran running back had suffered a neck injury. We now know that Mattison was taken by ambulance to the hospital after the injury and underwent surgery the same day.ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reportsMattison had a full range of motion, but he will now land on season-ending injured reserve after reportedly carving out a role for himself in camp. It’s a tough end to the season for a player who was hoping to bounce back following a disappointing 2024 season with the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99e1-d45c-a7fc-9bfbca940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Alec Pierce is day-to-day with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99eb-df63-a199-d9ebe9f20000</link>
      <description>Groin exited Sunday’s practice with an apparent leg injury that has now been diagnosed as a groin injury. Per Fowler, Pierce’s injury is not expected to be serious, and the day-to-day diagnosis suggests he could return before the end of the week. Pierce is being pushed in camp by second-year receiver Adonai Mitchell for a role as the team’s primary deep threat, and can ill-afford to miss time as Mitchell continues to impress in camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99eb-df63-a199-d9ebe9f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarShawn Lloyd (groin) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99f7-df63-a199-d9ff079a0000</link>
      <description>Per Packers beat writer Matt Schneidman, Lloyd and fellow running back Emanuel Wilson (knee) both practiced “in some capacity.” It doesn’t sound like either back got in a full workload, but it’s an encouraging sign for a backfield that was down its top two backups last week. Wilson is currently listed as the team’s RB2, with Lloyd backing him up as the RB3. Assuming both backs are back in 11-on-11s soon, look for the battle for the RB2 role to ramp up over the final few weeks of camp and the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99f7-df63-a199-d9ff079a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) was spotted in street clothes during Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</link>
      <description>Stafford threw upwards of 60 passes on Saturday in preparation for his return to the field on Monday. Instead, his much-anticipated return has again been delayed due to a back injury that required an epidural last week. Head coach Sean McVay said last week that Stafford was feeling well enough to play in games, which may still be the case, but the decision to hold him out on a day he was set to return is somewhat alarming. Hopefully, we’ll get more clarification on his status after practice, but this remains a story to monitor with Week 1 less than a month away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Rachaad White is day-to-day with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a17-d90d-a5bd-ba5f694c0000</link>
      <description>White did not practice on Monday after suffering a groin injury in Saturday’s preseason game against the Titans, but it doesn’t sound like the third-year back is going to be out for too long. White led the Buccaneers’ backfield on Saturday with Bucky Irving held out, and rushed six times for 28 yards in the outing. While his calling card has been in the passing game, White is at risk of losing more work to Irving, who has reportedly impressed as a pass-catcher in camp. He remains a decent handcuff to Irving for the time being, but may not have the standalone value he still carried even after Irving stepped into the RB1 role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a17-d90d-a5bd-ba5f694c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said the team will “be flexible and fluid” with Matthew Stafford as he continues to recover from his back injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a4e-df63-a199-db6fff6f0000</link>
      <description>It’s an incredibly vague response from McVay, who indicated over the weekend that Stafford would return to the field after going through a successful workout on Saturday. Instead, Stafford was spotted in street clothes on Monday and was also seen walking into an Ammortal chamber that specializes as a “wellness device that aims to optimize human performance and promote holistic health through a combination of non-invasive technologies.” So there’s that. McVay said surgery has not been talked about as an option for Stafford, but said his quarterback “didn’t feel good enough” to be on the field on Monday. There’s no way to know at this time if Stafford will or will not be available for Week 1, but there’s certainly reason to be skeptical. Like the Rams, we will also remain “flexible and fluid” with all news involving Stafford, and will check back in with any updates as they come. In the event Stafford is unavailable for any part of the regular season, Jimmy Garoppolo would be the favorite to draw starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a4e-df63-a199-db6fff6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart was “Efficient, effective, aggressive, and confident in the pocket” in his preseason debut against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a39-d90d-a5bd-ba7b31500000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan said that Daboll was “uncharacteristically effusive in his praise of Dart before adding disclaimers that it was only one game.” The Giants likely will not turn the quarterback position over to Dart early in the season, but the better he looks in the preseason, the easier it would be for them to pull the plug on Russell Wilson. Dart’s 154/1 passing debut on 19 attempts probably helped the rookie’s odds of appearing sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a39-d90d-a5bd-ba7b31500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Eagles LG Landon Dickerson “is thought to have suffered a meniscus injury to his right knee.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a76-d90d-a5bd-ba7fa4870000</link>
      <description>We still don’t know the full extent of Dickerson’s injury, but Schefter also adds that “Dickerson is getting additional options to determine the next course of action and how long he might be sidelined.” It could be nothing, but it’s possible Dickerson is looking at other options after receiving less-than-stellar news on his initial diagnosis. We’ll have a clear answer soon enough, but the three-time Pro Bowler could be on the verge of missing significant time, or at least the start of the season. If he were to be sidelined, former 2022 first-rounder Kenyon Green could be the favorite to replace him. Green was acquired earlier this offseason in the trade that sent C.J. Gardner-Johnson to the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a76-d90d-a5bd-ba7fa4870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed RB Ameer Abdullah (ribs) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a79-d90d-a5bd-ba7bfb3c0000</link>
      <description>As always in preseason, it’s possible an injury settlement is worked out to make Abdullah a free agent. The veteran hurt his ribs in preseason Week 1 action. We would only be speculating on his return to play timeline from the injury listing, but rib injuries are not often season-enders and it’s possible he could return at some point in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a79-d90d-a5bd-ba7bfb3c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
