<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 3-of-4 targets for 30 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 1 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1835-dbe3-a9bb-3877f16b0000</link>
      <description>It was a typically eventful night for Pickens in his Cowboys debut, as he also committed a personal foul and drew a 34-yard DPI. Never a dull moment. Pickens’ four targets were nine fewer than CeeDee Lamb, but you could see how the interplay between the two wideouts might work. Lamb was soaking up short-to-intermediate looks while Pickens went to work deep. Big gains are undoubtedly coming, especially considering how impressively Dak Prescott was spinning the rock this evening. Pickens will remain a top-30 option for Week 2 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1835-dbe3-a9bb-3877f16b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 3-of-3 targets for 16 yards in the Eagles’ Week 1 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1839-d332-a1fd-9e3f10b50000</link>
      <description>One of those “targets” was a measly receiver screen. For whatever reason, Jalen Hurts couldn’t get the ball to his wideouts in OC Kevin Patullo’s play-calling debut. If you thought Smith’s night was bad, it blew A.J. Brown’s out of the water, as AJB’s lone look/catch came at the 1:51 mark of the fourth quarter. Not good enough, but Hurts and Patullo now at least have 10 days to go back to the drawing board ahead of a Week 2 Super Bowl rematch with the Chiefs. Smith will find himself in the WR24-30 range for that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1839-d332-a1fd-9e3f10b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-6 targets for 23 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 1 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-183c-db7b-a5dd-b83c9d010000</link>
      <description>Ferguson’s box score doesn’t show his most eventful play of the game, a third quarter end zone hospital ball from Dak Prescott that managed to draw a personal foul on Eagles DB Reed Blankenship. Ferguson is lucky he avoided a concussion. It wasn’t the only time Ferguson was put in harm’s way by Prescott, but it was the most vivid. Despite the horrific yardage total, PPR managers will take the five grabs. That’s a number Ferguson should hit fairly frequently in an offense destined to be pass-heavy. He will be a high-end TE2 for Week 2 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-183c-db7b-a5dd-b83c9d010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 7-of-7 targets for 44 yards in the Eagles’ Week 1 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1840-de13-afdd-5ecbfc5f0000</link>
      <description>Goedert’s seven looks surprisingly led the team on an evening where Jalen Hurts attempted just 23 throws. Seven targets is a number Goedert only reached twice during his abbreviated 2024 regular season. The Eagles are going to do a better job of getting the ball to A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith going forward, but Goedert easily confirmed he remains the team’s No. 3 receiving option. He will be hanging around the TE1/2 borderline for Week 2 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1840-de13-afdd-5ecbfc5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders rushed four times for 53 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 1 loss to the Eagles, also losing a fumble.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1843-de13-afdd-5ecb5f3a0000</link>
      <description>Sanders “added” a -3 yard reception. As usual, Sanders’ good was all too vividly accompanied by the bad. Third quarter patience and explosiveness allowed him to find then hit a huge hole on the perimeter for a 49-yard gain, but he followed it up five plays later with a soft red zone fumble. The game then went into a lightning delay and Sanders wasn’t heard from upon the contest’s resumption. With Jaydon Blue a “healthy scratch” following an injury-marred training camp, Sanders was getting a looksee as the No. 2 back, but he might not get another opportunity in Week 2 against the Giants if Blue is ready to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1843-de13-afdd-5ecb5f3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahan Dotson caught 3-of-3 targets for 59 yards in the Eagles’ Week 1 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1848-db7b-a5dd-b84c1f300000</link>
      <description>Confusingly, No. 3 Dotson drew as many looks as DeVonta Smith and two more than A.J. Brown. He led the team in receiving, with his roasting of Kaiir Elam 1-on-1 for a 51-yard gain going down as the game’s longest play. The solid performance confirmed training camp buzz that Dotson was the unquestioned No. 3 wideout, but he’s still going to remain the fourth or fifth option in the passing game more weeks than not. That includes Week 2 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1848-db7b-a5dd-b84c1f300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley rushed three times for 26 yards in the Eagles’ Week 1 win over the Cowboys before departing with a rib injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-184a-dbe3-a9bb-385bf5e20000</link>
      <description>Mixing in as a change-of-pace back behind Saquon Barkley, Shipley was the only Eagle to notch a 20-yard run before going down. He was announced as “questionable” but never returned following halftime or a lengthy third quarter weather delay. Not great, though he does have 10 days to get healthy for the Eagles’ Week 2 Super Bowl rematch with the Chiefs. Shipley has at least confirmed he’s the unquestioned No. 2 and in line to see a few weekly breather touches when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-184a-dbe3-a9bb-385bf5e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the league is “reviewing last night’s spitting incident for potential additional discipline against Eagles DT Jalen Carter.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19d6-d332-a1fd-9ff60e1f0000</link>
      <description>This was expected. Carter’s decision to spit on Dak Prescott in last night’s season-opener led to an immediate ejection of the third-year lineman. Carter didn’t log a snap in Thursday’s contest, which could mean the league will effectively view his ejection as a one-game suspension, but we’ll know where things officially stand once the review concludes. Prescott, who was also seen spitting in Carter’s direction beforehand, is “unlikely to face any (discipline) for his role,” per Pelissero. He also notes that historically, the league has dealt more fines than suspensions toward players who were ejected for spitting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19d6-d332-a1fd-9ff60e1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said “I do not get the sense, based on the conversations I have had so far, that there are alarm bells going off about Christian McCaffrey (calf).”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19dd-db7b-a5dd-b9ddf4cf0000</link>
      <description>Pelissero noted that he is making these comments “cautiously” before pointing out that McCaffrey is a player with whom a team will exercise extreme precautions due to his value to the team and the nature of the injuries he dealt with last season. McCaffrey has had a healthy camp after dealing with multiple calf and Achilles injuries last season. After being activated from injured reserve in Week 10, McCaffrey landed on season-ending IR following a Week 13 game against the Bills in which he suffered a PCL injury that would sideline him for over a month. Fantasy managers are understandably panicking over McCaffrey popping up on Thursday’s injury report, but those concerns could be diffused before the weekend if he’s able to log a full practice on Friday. In the event McCaffrey is unable to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks, Brian Robinson would become a volume-based play with top-24 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19dd-db7b-a5dd-b9ddf4cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed C Ted Karras to a one-year, $5 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a0c-d332-a1fd-9e3ed4dc0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals did something similar with Karras last offseason when they signed him to a one-year extension in June. The veteran lineman was set to enter the final year of his deal with the Bengals before this extension, but now will be under contract through the 2026 season. Karras earned a PFF grade of 64.1 last while playing on over 1,100 offensive snaps. A pillar of health for most of his career, Karras has missed just one game since joining the Bengals in 2022 while starting in every game he’s appeared in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a0c-d332-a1fd-9e3ed4dc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
