<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:01:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns will interview Ravens offensive coordinator Todd Monken for their head coaching vacancy a second time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1b9-d35e-a1bf-d5fb7e1b0000</link>
      <description>Monken will have an in-person interview with the Browns on Tuesday. Making it to the second round of interviews is a good sign for his odds of landing the job. Even if he doesn’t, Monken is a highly coveted offensive coordinator who will have no issues finding work for 2026. He is already considered one of the leading candidates for the Giants’ OC job. Browns defensive coordinator Jim Schwartz is also getting a second interview for their head coaching vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1b9-d35e-a1bf-d5fb7e1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Titans will interview Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy for their head coaching vacancy a second time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1bd-dc7a-af9b-dfbff20d0000</link>
      <description>The Titans already conducted a virtual interview with Nagy. They will now meet him in person later this week. They are also pursuing Packers DC Jeff Hafley, who is likely their first choice. If Hafley doesn’t take the job, Nagy could get a second chance at leading a team. He went 34-31 with the Bears after a successful run as the Chiefs’ quarterbacks coach and eventually offensive coordinator. His latest stint as the Chiefs’ OC has not gone as well. With the best quarterback on the planet at his disposal, Nagy’s Chiefs have topped out at 15th in points per game over the past three years. It’s hard to see him doing better with Cam Ward under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1bd-dc7a-af9b-dfbff20d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Steelers “are expected to speak with former Cowboys HC Mike McCarthy about their head coach vacancy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1c5-dc7a-af9b-dfff4f380000</link>
      <description>As Schefter notes, McCarthy was born in Pittsburgh and worked under Steelers GM Omar Khan during his time in New Orleans in the early 2000s. For a team that just moved on from Mike Tomlin because of his recent lack of playoff success, McCarthy would be a bit of an odd choice. He made the playoffs three times during five seasons in Dallas but managed to win just one postseason game. McCarthy was, however, more successful in Green Bay. He won a Super Bowl over the Steelers and made the NFC Championship three other times. His track record in the postseason is a mixed bag at best, but the Steelers could do worse in this head coaching cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1c5-dc7a-af9b-dfff4f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports, “The Eagles and special teams coach Michael Clay have agreed to terms on a new deal.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1cf-dc7a-af9b-dfff47540000</link>
      <description>Rapoport didn’t have the specifics of the deal, but Clay’s contract was set to expire and the team allowed him to interview for a lateral move in Tampa Bay. After exploring other options, the two sides reached a deal to keep Clay in Philly for the foreseeable future. Clay has held the role of special teams coordinator in Philadelphia for five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1cf-dc7a-af9b-dfff47540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Eagles are expected to interview former Giants head coach Brian Daboll for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1f3-d56e-afff-f7fb2dc70000</link>
      <description>Daboll also has an interview for the Chargers’ vacant OC gig lined up. The Titans met with him to discuss their head coach opening, but the team has started their second round of interviews and he hasn’t been called back. We will assume for now that he isn’t in the running for that job anymore. Still, Daboll shouldn’t have any issues landing a coordinator job given the initial interest he has received. Previous reports have Daboll at the top of the Eagles’ wishlist of OC candidates, along with Mike McDaniel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1f3-d56e-afff-f7fb2dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Michael Silver reports Bills offensive line coach Aaron Kromer is expected to retire.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</link>
      <description>Kromer has been with the Bills for four seasons. He has been in the NFL for over 20 years, primarily as an offensive line coach, no matter the team. Pro Football Focus graded the Bills’ line as a top-10 unit in both run and pass protection this year. With Kromer hanging up the clipboard and multiple starters on expiring contracts, Buffalo’s line could look drastically different in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports former Titans offensive line coach Bill Callahan is “likely” to join new Falcons head coach Kevin Stefanski in Atlanta.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d221-d968-a19b-daf1a2c80000</link>
      <description>Callahan previously held the same role in Cleveland under Stefanski. The team let him go to coach under his son, Brian Callahan, with the Titans. That lasted less than two years and Bill ultimately resigned after the team fired Brian. Callahan is still considered one of the league’s best line coaches, even though the Titans stint didn’t work out. We fully expect him to reunite with Stefanski in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d221-d968-a19b-daf1a2c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns have requested a second interview with Jaguars offensive coordinator Grant Udinski for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d22a-d968-a19b-dafbf9270000</link>
      <description>Udinski previously discussed the opening with Cleveland via a virtual interview. He will not meet with the Browns’ bigwigs in-person, meaning he is one of the leading candidates for the job. Browns DC Jim Schwartz and Ravens OC Todd Monken are also scheduled for in-person interviews. Udinski is undoubtedly the highest-ceiling hire Cleveland could make. The 30-year-old offensive mind just helped Trevor Lawrence post career-high numbers across the board, including 38 total touchdowns. Udinski is also the least proven of the finalists, having only held his current role for one season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d22a-d968-a19b-dafbf9270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Nico Collins, T Trent Brown, RB Jawhar Jordan, QB Graham Mertz, and WR Justin Watson inactive for the Divisional Round against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d261-d968-a19b-daf1ce040000</link>
      <description>Collins, who sustained a head injury in the Wild Card round against the Chargers, did not practice this week and was ruled out on Friday. It’s a massive blow to the Houston offense. Christian Kirk, who had 144 yards and a score last week against LA, and Jayden Higgins will profile as the team’s top two receivers with Collins out. Brown tried to play but was unable to fight through an injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d261-d968-a19b-daf1ce040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is active for the Divisional Round against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d267-d968-a19b-daf7e6950000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez was removed from the Patriots’ injury report on Friday following his Wild Card Round concussion and subsequent placement in the league’s concussion protocol. He’ll join a solid New England secondary going against a Texans offense that will be without Nico Collins (concussion). Patriots declared CB ﻿Kobee Minor,﻿ LB ﻿Bradyn Swinson,﻿ OT ﻿Marcus Bryant﻿, DT ﻿Eric Gregory,﻿ G ﻿Caedan Wallace,﻿ TE ﻿CJ Dippre, and﻿ QB ﻿Tommy DeVito﻿ inactive against Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d267-d968-a19b-daf7e6950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
