<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts DT DeForest Buckner (neck) will play in Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce4-d35e-a1bf-7de6a8a10000</link>
      <description>Buckner hasn’t played since Week 9 due to a neck injury. The 31-year-old defensive tackle began practicing again last week. Colts coach Shane Steichen told reporters Saturday that Buckner will play. His return could be important for the Colts’ defensive line as they look to get after Brock Purdy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce4-d35e-a1bf-7de6a8a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts ruled out CB Sauce Gardner (calf) for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce8-dc7a-af9b-ffff546e0000</link>
      <description>Colts coach Shane Steichen answered in the affirmative when asked Saturday if Gardner would play again this season. That bodes well for the 25-year-old cornerback, who so far has avoided injured reserve despite a calf injury. Gardner will be out for Week 16’s matchup with the 49ers, but the Colts clearly believe he’ll return for at least one of the last two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce8-dc7a-af9b-ffff546e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed RB Dameon Pierce to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cf8-d35e-a1bf-7dfa64b10000</link>
      <description>The team waived running back Elijah Mitchell in an associated move. Mitchell had been active in only once game this season, whereas Pierce can contribute to special teams on game day. The Chiefs enter “evaluation mode” for the first time in over a decade after being eliminated from postseason contention in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cf8-d35e-a1bf-7dfa64b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns placed T Jack Conklin (concussion) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cfe-d35e-a1bf-7dfeaff80000</link>
      <description>The move ends the veteran tackle’s season in what amounts to an evaluation year. The Browns continue to experience multiple injuries along an aging offensive line, something they could look to address in the coming offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cfe-d35e-a1bf-7dfeaff80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports TE Gunnar Helm (toe) and WR Van Jefferson (back) are expected to play in Week 16 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d07-d35e-a1bf-7dc71af40000</link>
      <description>Both entered the weekend listed as questionable but it appears as if rookie quarterback Cam Ward will have his normal supporting cast available for a marquee matchup with the Chiefs on Sunday. Neither player is overly enticing in a fantasy setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d07-d35e-a1bf-7dc71af40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed K Charlie Smyth to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d11-d35e-a1bf-7dd3ea360000</link>
      <description>The kicker from Northern Ireland made his NFL debut just last month and now sticks with the Saints for the next three seasons. Smyth is 4-fo-5 in field goal attempts and has hit all five point after tries. The specifics of the contract are not yet available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d11-d35e-a1bf-7dd3ea360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated CB Trevon Diggs (knee) ahead of Week 16 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</link>
      <description>The team also placed fellow cornerback DaRon Bland (foot) on injured reserve in an associated move. As has been the case for most of the season, the Cowboys continue forward without pieces from their secondary. Diggs pushed his return up to the limit, meaning we might not see him play a full allotment of snaps in his first game in over two months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders delared QB Jayden Daniels, RB Chase Edmonds, T George Fant, T Laremy Tunsil, TE Colson Yankoff, and DT Eddie Goldman inactive for Week 16 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d26-d35e-a1bf-7de62ff20000</link>
      <description>The Commanders will be without both starting offensive tackles in a game started by backup quarterback Marcus Mariota, potentially opening the door for defensive dominance from a relentless Eagles defense. Expect a reliance on the ground game to start while getting back Chris Rodriguez from a one-game absence, but that stance could quickly shift should the Commanders fall behind early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d26-d35e-a1bf-7de62ff20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared OLB Josh Uche, QB Sam Howell, CB Mac McWilliams, RB A.J. Dillon, TE/FB Cam Latu, T Lane Johnson, and DT Jalen Carter inactive for Week 16 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d77-da28-afbb-fd7f9cff0000</link>
      <description>The team gets back G Landon Dickerson, which could benefit Saquon Barkley and the run game against a far inferior Commanders roster. Philadelphia can clinch a playoff berth with a win over their divisional opponents, eliminating the Cowboys in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d77-da28-afbb-fd7f9cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers elevated OLB Jason Pierre-Paul ahead of Week 16 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</link>
      <description>The appearance will be the first regular season game for the soon-to-be 37-year-old veteran in a over two years. It’ll come in a must-win, divisional showdown with the Panthers. The two teams play twice in the final three weeks of the regular season to decide who will represent the NFC South in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
