<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Terry McLaurin (quad) is “very much in doubt” for Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7bbf-dca3-a9fb-7fbfafbc0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin sitting for Week 4, according to Rapoport, would “not be a surprise” after he left Sunday’s win over the Raiders with the quad issue. McLaurin is seeking medical opinions about the injury, which could mean he’s facing an extended period on the sideline. If he misses Week 4, look for Zach Ertz and Deebo Samuel to see an uptick in targets. Luke McCaffrey, who had three receptions for 56 yards and a touchdown in Week 3, could be a deep league option if McLaurin is sidelined. McLaurin has been an iron man of sorts, starting 72 consecutive games for Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7bbf-dca3-a9fb-7fbfafbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said he’s “fully confident” in RB Trey Benson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7bd5-d6e9-af9d-fbd543280000</link>
      <description>“I’m fully confident in Trey, I really am,” Gannon told reporters when asked about the Arizona backfield following James Conner’s season-ending ankle injury. “I think the more he plays, the more comfortable you see him getting and the better he’s going to be.” Kyler Murray, meanwhile, said he has the “ultimate confidence” in Benson as the Cardinals’ top back. Benson, who’s impressed with a limited workload so far this season, will function as the Cardinals’ lead back for the remainder of the season. Emari Demercado, who had two rushes last week against the Niners, will be the team’s RB2. With enough pass game involvement, Benson could shape up as a top-10 weekly fantasy option, starting with Thursday night’s matchup against a tough Seahawks defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7bd5-d6e9-af9d-fbd543280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7be6-deb6-a7fd-7bff6cd30000</link>
      <description>Pierce remains in the league’s concussion protocol after sustaining a brain injury in Week 3 against the Titans. He caught four balls for 67 yards in that game, operating as Daniel Jones’ primary downfield threat. If he’s sidelined for Week 4 against the Rams, look for AD Mitchell to see a major increase in snaps and pass routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7be6-deb6-a7fd-7bff6cd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (ankle) was seen participating at Bucs practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c65-deb6-a7fd-7fff73e60000</link>
      <description>Fox Sports’ Greg Auman said Godwin could return as soon as Sunday against the Eagles. This comes after an ESPN report in which Adam Schefter said there was a “strong chance” Godwin makes his return to game action in Week 4. The Bucs will need Godwin with Mike Evans sidelined for the next 3-4 weeks following a hamstring injury in Week 3 against the Jets. While Godwin might not see a full complement of snaps and routes against the Eagles, he should be in fantasy lineups if he suits up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c65-deb6-a7fd-7fff73e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Michael Penix will start Week 4 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c71-deb6-a7fd-7fff91a10000</link>
      <description>Morris said the team wasn’t close to benching Penix following the team’s Week 3 meltdown against the Panthers. Penix against Carolina completed 18-of-36 passes for 172 yards and two interceptions. Penix was the week’s second most inaccurate quarterback, trailing only Trevor Lawrence. Kirk Cousins came in last week for fourth quarter mop-up duty, but appears far from seizing the starting gig from Penix, who has one touchdown pass over the season’s first three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c71-deb6-a7fd-7fff91a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) could return in Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c78-deb6-a7fd-7fff9ce50000</link>
      <description>Morris said there’s a chance Terrell, who’s been out since Week 1, could suit up in Week 4 against Washington. That seems like a remote possibility, however, considering the seriousness of the injury. With Terrell sidelined, Atlanta’s secondary has struggled to stop opposing passing attacks. If Terrell is out this week it would be a boon for Washington’s pass catchers and whoever starts at quarterback for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c78-deb6-a7fd-7fff9ce50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (concussion) is out for Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c83-dca3-a9fb-7d9b95860000</link>
      <description>Jones will miss Thursday night’s game against the Seahawks after sustaining a head injury in Week 3 and entering the NFL’s concussion protocol. Greg Dortch could see an increase in playing time with Jones sidelined. He won’t be fantasy viable as the team’s fourth or fifth option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c83-dca3-a9fb-7d9b95860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rob Demovsky reports Packers RT Zach Tom (oblique) is unlikely to play in Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c88-dca3-a9fb-7d99a1b70000</link>
      <description>Tom exited Week 3’s loss to the Browns after aggravating an oblique injury he had been dealing with headed into the matchup. “It was somewhat of a surprise Tom was active against the Browns, which in hindsight, coach Matt LaFleur said was a mistake,” Demovsky said of Tom, widely considered the Packers’ best offensive lineman. Green Bay could miss Tom against a Dallas defense pressuring the passer at the NFL’s sixth highest rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c88-dca3-a9fb-7d99a1b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) did not practice Wedneday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</link>
      <description>Brown exited Week 3’s win over the Texans with the shoulder injury and did not return. In his absence, Parker Washington functioned as a full-time wideout and four of 11 targets for 34 yards, leading the Jaguars in targets somehow. Brown would have to get in at least a limited practice by Friday if he has any hope to suit up in Week 5 against the 49ers. Washington would be a deep league option if Brown is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said QB Jaxson Dart will start for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</link>
      <description>Daboll said it was his decision to bench Russell Wilson and install Dart as the rest-of-season starter. He refused to explain his thinking when asked about Wilson’s benching, which came after a disastrous performance on Sunday night against the Chiefs. Dart will get his first NFL start in Week 4 against a stingy Chargers defense that last week stalled the Broncos passing attack. Dart should bring more aggressive downfield passing to the mix and will likely take off and run more than Wilson. He’ll be viable in superflex formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
