<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 19:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury said Jayden Daniels (knee) is “preparing mentally” on Thursday, but Marcus Mariota “is taking the reps.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d91-d6a5-adff-ffd5a5b30000</link>
      <description>It’s a long-winded way of saying Daniels won’t practice on Thursday. Head coach Dan Quinn said earlier this week that Daniels won’t practice until Friday at the earliest, so his absence today doesn’t come as much of a surprise. All signs point to Mariota getting the start in Week 3, but the Commanders are at least leaving the light on for Daniels right now. Daniels will be all but guaranteed to miss Sunday’s game versus the Raiders if he doesn’t return to practice tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d91-d6a5-adff-ffd5a5b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Burrow (foot) is expected to undergo surgery on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d9c-d6a5-adff-ffdde6810000</link>
      <description>Rapoport noted that the procedure could be pushed back if the swelling in Burrow’s foot doesn’t allow him to go under the knife. Burrow is facing a three-month recovery, meaning the Bengals are going to be without their star quarterback for most of the season. It’s possible Burrow is ready right at three months and is able to return for a playoff push, but that hinges on both his health and the team staying in the hunt with Jake Browning under center. For fantasy purposes, managers can proceed under the assumption that Burrow is done for the year. Browning is a must-add in all Superflex and 2QB formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d9c-d6a5-adff-ffdde6810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed OG Shane Lemieux, formerly of the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dcf-d93f-ad9d-5fcf53ae0000</link>
      <description>Lemieux played in six games with the Saints last year, earning a 42.1 PFF pass-blocking grade and a 58.8 PFF run-blocking grade. He allowed 10 quarterback pressures in those appearances, tying for the second-most among Saints offensive linemen during that span. Lemieux is now on the Seahawks’ practice squad. It is unclear whether he will be called up to the active roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dcf-d93f-ad9d-5fcf53ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dde-dfde-a1bd-5fdffe650000</link>
      <description>This is fantastic news. Likely returned to practice last Friday, practicing in a limited capacity, but he was ultimately unable to suit up for Week 2 against the Browns. His continued participation indicates he remains setback-free. Late last week, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport speculated that Likely could play in Week 3 against the Lions on Monday night. The game’s late kickoff makes banking on Likely a bit risky, but the fact that he is participating in this week’s first practice, which is often a day of rest for injured players, is promising. The Ravens chose not to put Likely on injured reserve to begin the year, which indicates they expect him to return before Week 5. He is currently on track to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dde-dfde-a1bd-5fdffe650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Nate Wiggins (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dfc-d6a5-adff-fffd38630000</link>
      <description>Wiggins returned an interception for 61 yards in Week 2 against the Browns, prompting an exuberant response from teammate, CB Chidobe Awuzie, who “jumped on Wiggins’ back and accidentally took him to the ground.” ESPN’s Jamison Hensley said, “Wiggins did not appear to be full strength the rest of the game,” and began exhibiting a limp in-game after that. Ravens OLB Kyle Van Noy (hamstring) could miss multiple games and DT Nnamdi Madubuike (ankle) is also hurt. Neither player practiced on Thursday. Madubuike leads the team with 10 quarterback pressures and two sacks. They face the Lions on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dfc-d6a5-adff-fffd38630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LG Joel Bitonio (back) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e1b-d1b3-a5dd-5f7b47100000</link>
      <description>Bitonio has now missed back-to-back days to start the week with this new back listing. It’s possible he misses Cleveland’s Week 3 game against the Packers on Sunday, but linemen usually get more leeway on not practicing, particular veterans like Bitonio, when they are hurt. We’d be unsurprised if he was listed with a questionable tag on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e1b-d1b3-a5dd-5f7b47100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (ankle) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e20-d6a5-adff-fee5b3cb0000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if it was more than a limited session, but this should get Downs back in the Week 3 fantasy conversation after missing Wednesday’s practice. The Titans defense has been something of a pass funnel in their first two games of the season and it makes sense for Downs to be in the FLEX mix after his eight-target Week 2 result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e20-d6a5-adff-fee5b3cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts TE Tyler Warren (toe) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e27-d1b3-a5dd-5f777f190000</link>
      <description>It’s a very encouraging sign that he’ll be able to go on Sunday, though by no means a definitive one. Warren went for 79 yards on seven targets against the Broncos last week and should remain an easy TE1 start in Week 3 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e27-d1b3-a5dd-5f777f190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e05-dfde-a1bd-5e8d4c7f0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez returned to practice in a limited capacity yesterday. The Patriots have smartly slow-played their star cornerback’s recovery, so it may be another week before we see him take regular season snaps. It’s a positive overall development for the young cornerback, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e05-dfde-a1bd-5e8d4c7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapaport reports Steelers OL Max Scharping (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e29-d1b3-a5dd-5f79bb100000</link>
      <description>Scharping has bounced around as veteran depth since playing out his four-year rookie deal with the Texans and, later, Bengals. He’s played just 20 snaps the last two years. He’ll likely be on the practice squad/end-of-roster shuttle again in 2026 if his knee cooperates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e29-d1b3-a5dd-5f79bb100000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
