<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adonai Mitchell caught 3-of-9 targets for 22 yards in the Jets’ Week 17 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6741-dc7a-af9b-efffef580000</link>
      <description>Mitchell easily led the Jets in targets, racking up a 26 percent target share. He undoubtedly saw plenty of air yards as well, but Brady Cook was unable to connect with him on many of their deep shots. Cook’s only interception of the day came on a heave to Mitchell down the left sideline. Cook simply didn’t have the arm to get it to Mitchell and a New England defender fielded the ball like an outfielder. Mitchell will get one more shot at converting his air yards to receiving yards in Week 18 versus the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6741-dc7a-af9b-efffef580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Geno Smith did not return after suffering an ankle injury in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674a-dc7a-af9b-efff1cda0000</link>
      <description>Smith was injured via an illegal block during an interception return on the Raiders’ seventh drive. A Raiders offensive lineman hit the ground on the play, pinning Smith’s right foot as Giants CB Rico Payton hit Smith from the left, twisting and stressing the inside of Smith’s right knee and ankle joints. It was Smith’s second interception of the day. His first occurred on a red zone play, when he errantly threw the football to Giants LB Bobby Okereke while attempting to lead TE Michael Mayer. If Smith can face the Chiefs next week, he will be a low-end QB2. Raiders backup QB Kenny Pickett could get the start. Before exiting, Smith completed 20-of-28 passes for 176 yards, one touchdown and two interceptions. He rushed once for one yard and took three sacks for 24 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674a-dc7a-af9b-efff1cda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Williams caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards in the Jets’ Week 17 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674d-d56e-afff-e7ed6efb0000</link>
      <description>Williams has seemingly overtaken John Metchie as the Jets’ No. 2 receiver. He has 14 catches over the past three weeks to Metchie’s eight. Williams’ late-season surge has been impressive, but it’s more impactful for his future earnings than it is for fantasy managers. He is buried in the WR5/6 range heading into the final week of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674d-d56e-afff-e7ed6efb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 1-of-3 targets for six yards in the Seahawks’ Week 17 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674a-dc7a-af9b-efffb9ea0000</link>
      <description>One of Kupp’s missed connections was a ball he coughed up for a near-interception following a mammoth hit. Held under 50 yards in seven straight appearances, Kupp is not percolating ahead of Week 18 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-674a-dc7a-af9b-efffb9ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audric Estime rushed 14 times for 94 yards and a touchdown in the Saints’ Week 17 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6752-dc7a-af9b-efffb1110000</link>
      <description>Estime ceded the first carry of the day to Taysom Hill. After Hill easily out-carried him last week, it looked like that would be the case again versus Tennessee. The Saints quickly threw in the towel on Hill and handed the backfield over to Estime. He punctuated a solid day with a 32-yard sprint into the end zone in the fourth quarter. The touchdown gave New Orleans an eight-point lead that Tennessee never erased. Estime should hold this role into Week 18, giving him some RB2 juice versus the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6752-dc7a-af9b-efffb1110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (illness) is active for Week 17 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-675f-d968-a19b-7fff5b8f0000</link>
      <description>Moore was one of many Chicago players to come down with the flu that has been ripping through the league this week but he ultimately felt well enough to suit up for Sunday Night Football. The same can’t be said for wide receiver Olamide Zaccheaus, who is inactive. Also inactive for the Bears are QB Case Keenum, WR Rome Odunze, CB Dallis Flowers, OL Luke Newman, DB Nick McCloud, and LB Ruben Hyppolite II.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-675f-d968-a19b-7fff5b8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) is inactive for Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6762-d968-a19b-7ff3815b0000</link>
      <description>Kittle was though to be “highly unlikely” to play after injuring his ankle a week ago, ultimately unable to suit up against the Bears. Wide receiver Ricky Pearsall will make his return to the lineup after missing Week 16. Also inactive for the 49ers are WR Jordan Watkins, DL Robert Beal Jr, RB Isaac Guerendo, DL Kevin Givens, CB Renardo Green, and LB Curtis Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6762-d968-a19b-7ff3815b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard rushed four times for 12 yards in the Panthers’ Week 17 loss to the Seahawks, adding three catches for six yards while losing a fumble.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6761-d56e-afff-e7e9588a0000</link>
      <description>With the game tied 3-3 in the third quarter, Hubbard’s fumble came one play after Sam Darnold tossed a red zone interception. He touched the ball only two times thereafter, but it would be a stretch to say he was benched. For the game, he was out-touched 15-7 by Rico Dowdle. Rico should remain the 1A back for next weekend’s colossal tilt with the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6761-d56e-afff-e7e9588a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker caught 2-of-2 targets for 16 yards in the Panthers’ Week 17 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6767-d968-a19b-7ff755250000</link>
      <description>Coker led the team in receiving, if you want to know how today went for the Panthers’ passing attack. Although he’s attained clear No. 2 status in the offense, Coker is still struggling to post meaningful fantasy lines. That could change for Week 18 vs. the Bucs’ pass-funnel defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6767-d968-a19b-7ff755250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Austin caught 4-of-5 targets for 52 yards and a touchdown in the Saints’ Week 17 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6761-d56e-afff-e7e930200000</link>
      <description>Mason Tipton was out with a groin injury this week, freeing up some extra routes for Austin and Dante Pettis. Both players posted solid box scores, but Pettis fumbled the ball at the goal line, coughing up his chance to find the end zone. Austin cashed in late in the fourth quarter with a touchdown grab from 10 yards out. Austin will have some WR5 life in Week 18 if Tipton remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6761-d56e-afff-e7e930200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
