<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports “if the Jets can’t sign Breece Hall by Tuesday they will use a tag.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a064-dbf6-abdd-ee75aa280000</link>
      <description>What kind of tag the Jets place on Hall remains up in the air. Regardless, it doesn’t sound like the veteran running back will be hitting the open market when free agency opens next month. Hall rushed for 243-1065-4 last season while adding another 36-350-1 through the air. Once tagged, the question shifts to whether or not Hall would be willing to play on the tag and/or sign a new deal with the Jets, or if he will try to force his way out of town via trade. There’s been some belief that Hall would like to move on from the team that has gone 22-46 since drafting him in 2022, so it will be interesting to see how things develop once he is tagged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a064-dbf6-abdd-ee75aa280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team is “not putting any time frame” on getting a new deal done with George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a074-d629-a1bc-b07d36ad0000</link>
      <description>Perhaps even more importantly, Jones added, “the most important thing is live in the present.” Inspirational words from the co-owner of a team who seemingly botched its last big-time negotiation with a superstar less than a year ago. Pickens was officially franchise tagged by the Cowboys on Friday and will earn just under $28 million on the tag if he is unable to secure a long-term deal. Jones said Pickens was “fired up” to learn he would be returning to the Cowboys for next season. We’ll see if he maintains that same enthusiasm if a long-term deal isn’t in place as training camp draws closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a074-d629-a1bc-b07d36ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos non-tendered RB Jaleel McLaughlin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07a-dbf6-abdd-ee7b96f50000</link>
      <description>It’ll make him a free agent. Entering his age-26 season, McLaughlin has averaged 4.8 yards per rush and caught 59-of-69 targets for 263 yards over three years in the league. McLaughlin is built like a third-down back and will likely resurface elsewhere to attempt to snag that role for a new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07a-dbf6-abdd-ee7b96f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans parted ways with QB coach Jerrod Johnson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07e-d89c-a1be-affffe360000</link>
      <description>Technically, the Texans let his contract expire. They’re reportedly elevating senior offensive assistant-pass game specialist Jerry Schuplinski — yet another John Carroll / Patriots legacy guy — to quarterbacks coach. It’s an uninspiring move considering Johnson has interviewed for several OC vacancies over the past few years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07e-d89c-a1be-affffe360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Anthony Richardson and the Vikings have “mutual interest” in a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a087-d042-afbc-fdd7a0780000</link>
      <description>It’s the first team we’ve seen linked to Richardson, though we’re not really sure what the Vikings would get out of adding a quarterback who has missed a lot of games and struggled to be accurate when he has been on the field to a room that already has a rookie-contract quarterback doing those things. We’ll see where this goes. It would not be surprising if Richardson surfaces as a backup option somewhere in 2026, as he seems locked out of the role in Indianapolis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a087-d042-afbc-fdd7a0780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes the Chiefs “loom as an interesting suitor” for Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker if he makes it to free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a08c-d89c-a1be-afdf89f20000</link>
      <description>Breer adds the Broncos and Texans as teams he’d “assume” would be interested in Walker coming off a Super Bowl MVP performance. With Breece Hall likely to be franchise or transition tagged if a deal isn’t worked out with the Jets, Walker appears set to be the best running back to hit the market. Seahawks GM John Schneider did not comment on the idea of franchise tagging Walker at his combine presser, while Adam Schefter called it “unlikely” earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a08c-d89c-a1be-afdf89f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Chad Graff reports one league source expects the Patriots to cut Stefon Diggs unless they’re able to dramatically lower his cap hit with a reworked contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c0-d89c-a1be-afdf849c0000</link>
      <description>It’s a tortured way to put it — we like when beat writers actually stand by their sources — but it’s been clear from Graff’s point of view the past few days that a Stefon Diggs release should at least be on the radar. Diggs has a $26.5 million cap hit and barely cleared the 1000-yard hurdle with a 85/1013/4 regular season. He’s entering his age-33 season and caught just 14 passes for 110 yards in four playoff games, he’s also facing felony strangulation and suffocation charges. It’s easy to see why the Patriots would look at the Diggs contract as perhaps not worthwhile, but harder to understand where they would expect to get great production at the position without Diggs. The wideout free agent market is barren, and unless they’re prepared to pay a first-rounder for A.J. Brown, there’s not an easily identifiable trade for them either.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c0-d89c-a1be-afdf849c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Chad Graff believes the Patriots will “be active” in trade discussions for Eagles WR A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c6-d89c-a1be-afdff8700000</link>
      <description>It’s one of the most sensible fits out there given that Mike Vrabel coached Brown in Tennessee. But Graff adds that it seems doubtful that the Patriots would give up their first-round pick for Brown, and if they aren’t willing to do that, it’s hard to believe Howie Roseman would sign off on a deal. It’s clear that Brown’s future will be one of the big offseason dominos to come post-Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c6-d89c-a1be-afdff8700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner reports the Bengals will have extension talks with CBs DJ Turner and Dax Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d4-dbf6-abdd-eed540c70000</link>
      <description>Turner had a 78.1 PFF coverage grade last year in a career-high 974 snaps and is entering the final year of his rookie deal, while Hill is entering his fifth-year option offseason having moved into the slot more often last year. Turner would appear to be the more important player to extend, but the Bengals are definitely still in “keep as many good pieces from last year’s defense as possible” mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d4-dbf6-abdd-eed540c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports he doesn’t expect George Pickens to report to the Cowboys facility “unless and until there is a long-term deal.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d8-d629-a1bc-b0dda1520000</link>
      <description>“Don’t expect him to sign the tag yet,” Rapoport continues. “I would also wonder if there is another team that wants to give a premium draft pick and sign Pickens to a long-term deal themselves.” Pickens clearly put himself in the WR1 stratosphere last year, but we’d be surprised if a team was willing to give up a first-round pick for Pickens in addition to a major extension. A second-round pick might be a reasonable ask here while still being an upgrade for Dallas on the third-round pick they dealt away to acquire Pickens last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d8-d629-a1bc-b0dda1520000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
