<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers designated LB Fred Warner (ankle/IR) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b902-d968-a19b-f9f38d410000</link>
      <description>His 21-day practice window will open. The 49ers have been clear that Warner will not play unless they get to the NFC Championship game, even that seems quick for their superstar linebacker who has been on the shelf since early October. Warner’s return will be fresh air for the 49ers if they can get to it — they opened as seven-point underdogs to the Seahawks in Seattle after the NFC West champs throttled San Francisco for the title in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b902-d968-a19b-f9f38d410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles fired OC Kevin Patullo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b90d-d35e-a1bf-fdcf4b9c0000</link>
      <description>In a stunning repeat of the 2023 season, the Eagles lost their offensive playcaller to head-coaching waters, replaced him in-house, and the house proved unable to live up to the talent on the roster. Certainly nobody should be struggling to make A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith prime parts of the offense, nor should an offensive coordinator not be able to find a way to make in-prime Saquon Barkley and this offensive line be pathologically unable to crack 100 yards in a game. And, well, Patullo did both those things. It’s possible he takes a smaller role on the Eagles staff. Philadelphia’s offensive coordinator position is right up there with Detroit’s as one of the best openings in the league. They will undoubtedly find an outside candidate interested in working with Jalen Hurts, Barkley, Brown, and Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b90d-d35e-a1bf-fdcf4b9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said WR Tyrell Shavers (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b913-d35e-a1bf-fdd3897c0000</link>
      <description>Shavers actually played 22 of the team’s snaps in the second half on the torn ACL, which is absurd. The 26-year-old heads to the offseason as unlikely to play early in the season due to how late this knee injury was suffered. He had a career-best 15/245/1 receiving line on 23 targets in the 2025 season, starting nine games and being sporadically useful when the team got annoyed with mercurial second-year receiver Keon Coleman. The Bills will need to rely on Coleman to give them something in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b913-d35e-a1bf-fdd3897c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen will be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</link>
      <description>McDermott didn’t have an actual term for what Allen was dealing with on Monday beyond him being “sore,” so we’re curious what the actual designation will be. We don’t think Allen is in any real danger of missing Saturday’s game against the Broncos, but it’s not surprising that he’d take it a bit easy after Joe Brady used him like a battering ram and he spent multiple occasions in the medical tent in Buffalo’s Wild Card win over the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said RB Ty Johnson (ankle) won’t practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited practice before hitting the questionable line and being ruled out Sunday against the Jaguars. He’s probably a true question mark at this point to be ready against the Broncos on Saturday, with practice participation being the guiding light here. If all he can do is get in another limited Thursday session ahead of a tag, Johnson probably will sit again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said TE Dalton Kincaid would be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b928-dc7a-af9b-ffbfedaa0000</link>
      <description>We’re not sure yet if he’ll add a new designation after being spotted in a walking boot after the win over the Jaguars, but Kincaid’s normal status has been “knee” over the past few weeks. Kincaid will likely play through this, but remain limited throughout the week in practice. That’s been the norm over the past month or so, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b928-dc7a-af9b-ffbfedaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed FB Carson Steele to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b92a-d968-a19b-f9fb79cf0000</link>
      <description>Steele hung on the Chiefs practice squad for most of last season and will now get a chance to stick in Philadelphia. With Will Shipley and Tank Bigsby under contract, it’s hard to see Steele making any sort of fantasy noise without injuries ahead of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b92a-d968-a19b-f9fb79cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed WR Chandler Brayboy, QB Carter Bradley, G Jerome Carvin, TE Patrick Herbert, RB Ja’Quinden Jackson, WR Tim Jones, T Ricky Lee, DB Keni-H Lovely, DB Jabbar Muhammad, DT Keivie Rose, DB Cam’Ron Silmon-Craig, DB Trevian Thomas, WR Austin Trammell, G Sal Wormley and T Kilian Zierer to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b950-d56e-afff-fff8a6a20000</link>
      <description>We at Rotoworld are dedicated to giving you all the Chandler Brayboy and Keni-H Lovely updates we can. Here’s what we know: They both signed reserve/futures contracts after spending all year on the Jaguars practice squad. That’s all we got. More to come later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b950-d56e-afff-fff8a6a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed QB DJ Uiagalelei, LS Peter Bowden, WR Dalevon Campbell, DL TeRah Edwards, WR Luke Grimm, WR JaQuae Jackson, RB Amar Johnson, LB Emany Johnson, C Josh Kaltenberger, TE Tanner McLachlan, OLB Garmon Randolph, OG Branson Taylor, CB Isas Waxter and TE Thomas Yassmin to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b955-d56e-afff-fffd4c760000</link>
      <description>Uiagalelei was elevated to back up Trey Lance in Week 18, but ultimately did not play at all in Los Angeles’ exhibition to tank into the No. 7 seed. He had a 67.0 PFF grade in 69 offensive preseason snaps this past offseason and could eventually become Los Angeles’ backup quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b955-d56e-afff-fffd4c760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans scheduled an interview with former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b959-d35e-a1bf-fddbb09f0000</link>
      <description>They probably want to ask him how it felt to be the only team to lose a game to Brian Callahan this year. Gannon also has an interview on Thursday with the Commanders regarding their defensive coordinator role. Gannon’s market is now “heating up,” if that’s what you want to call it. The deposed former Cardinals coach met with the Cowboys today to interview for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b959-d35e-a1bf-fddbb09f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
