<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said Travis Hunter will se a “likely uptick” in defensive snaps in Week 2 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b2-db7b-a5dd-b4b6c56a0000</link>
      <description>Hunter only played six snaps on defense in his NFL debut. Coen said he didn’t expect to use Hunter a ton on defense in Week 1 and it was always the plan to ramp up his defensive snaps as the season progressed. He also noted that the Bengals, Jacksonville’s Week 2 opponent, have a pair of elite wide receivers, further illustrating the team’s need for Hunter to play corner on Sunday. On offense, Hunter was targeted eight times and caught six of his looks, though he only managed 33 yards. Assuming an increase in defensive snaps doesn’t hamstring his role on offense, Hunter is a PPR WR3 for a potential shootout with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b2-db7b-a5dd-b4b6c56a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said he doesn’t believe CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) will practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b8-db7b-a5dd-b4bc382c0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez did not practice at all last week and was ruled out for Week 1 on Friday. It looks like he is headed for a similar fate in Week 2 as the Patriots look to get on track versus the Dolphins. The good news for New England is that the Dolphins looked pitiful in Week 1, failing to put a single point on the board until late in the fourth quarter when the game was already decided. On the other side of the coin, it’s now or never for Tua Tagovailoa and the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b8-db7b-a5dd-b4bc382c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34bc-d332-a1fd-b6be2f2d0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens haven’t officially released their first injury report of the week yet, but Likely was spotted working off to the side with trainers during the open portion of practice. That will go down as a DNP barring a surprise turn of events. Fullback Patrick Ricard was held out of practice entirely. Likely suffered a small fracture in his foot early in training camp and has been out ever since. The fact that Baltimore didn’t place him on injured reserve suggests it isn’t a long-term issue, but a DNP to open the week is a strong signal that Likely won’t suit up for Week 2. Mark Andrews managed a lone target in Week 1 versus the Bills. Even with Likely sidelined, Andrews appears to have little fantasy value left in the tank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34bc-d332-a1fd-b6be2f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said defensive coordinator Terrell Williams will be away from the team for the next few days for health-related reasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34c2-dbe3-a9bb-34d34ff50000</link>
      <description>Vrabel told reporters that inside linebackers coach Zak Kuhr will handle Williams’ duties while the latter is away from the team, though he didn’t name Kuhr the defensive play-caller. With cornerback Christian Gonzalez also missing Wednesday’s practice, New England’s defense looks likely to be understaffed both on the field and in the coaching ranks. Week 2 should give Tua Tagovailoa a chance to bounce back after a horrific opener versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34c2-dbe3-a9bb-34d34ff50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34cb-dbe3-a9bb-34dba84e0000</link>
      <description>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said Robinson “should be good” to play in Week 2 against the Cowboys. It could be tough going for the short-area weapon, with Cowboys slot CB DaRon Bland lining up opposite him. Robinson should be able to return high-floor FLEX value in PPR leagues, but he cannot be counted on for high-yardage outings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34cb-dbe3-a9bb-34dba84e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Giants “hope” LT Andrew Thomas (foot) returns to practice in “the next two days.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34ce-db7b-a5dd-b4ce33320000</link>
      <description>Thomas swayed between limited and non-participation last week. He kicks off Week 2 with another absence, which is purportedly “part of the plan.” The Giants are ostensibly playing things conservatively with their blindside pass protector, who continues to rehab his Lisfranc injury from last year. They can probably sneak past the Cowboys in Week 2, sans Thomas, without issue. The Chiefs’ vaunted pass rush is on tap in Week 3, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34ce-db7b-a5dd-b4ce33320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34df-db7b-a5dd-b4df293a0000</link>
      <description>Ward joins CB Jaylon Jones (hamstring) on the sideline to begin the week. Jones has not yet suited up this season after injuring his hamstring in late July. The Colts are tasked with covering Broncos WR Courtland Sutton this week, and Jones appears to have low odds of playing. If Ward can return, his presence would go a long way toward containing the X-receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34df-db7b-a5dd-b4df293a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>94 WIP’s Eliot Shorr-Park reports Dallas Goedert suffered a knee sprain that has his availability for Week 2 against the Chiefs “up in the air.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34e1-d332-a1fd-b6f7074a0000</link>
      <description>The good news is that it “is not believed to be a long-term injury” and may not even sideline him for Week 2. However, Goedert has played the entire season just once since entering the NFL in 2018 and it was his rookie campaign. He missed a total of seven games in 2024 with knee and hamstring issues. Goedert got off to a hot start this year with a team-high seven catches in Philly’s Week 1 win over the Cowboys. Even if he is active for Week 2, the veteran tight end will likely take a backseat to Philly’s elite wide receiver duo when they square off against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34e1-d332-a1fd-b6f7074a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (elbow) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34e6-db7b-a5dd-b4e62d140000</link>
      <description>Goodson is still sporting a brace on his injured left elbow. Backfield mate, RB DJ Giddens, has likely already passed Goodson on the depth chart after getting 12 rushing attempts in relief of Jonathan Taylor last week. Goodson does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues, even if he is active in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34e6-db7b-a5dd-b4e62d140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals S Joey Blount suffered a neck injury in Week 1 and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34f6-dbe3-a9bb-34f7d6e40000</link>
      <description>Blount will be placed on injured reserve. He suffered the injury after colliding with teammate Cody Simon on a kickoff return. Blount hasn’t played much on defense for Arizona but is a core special teamer, logging a combined 468 special teams snaps for the team over the past two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34f6-dbe3-a9bb-34f7d6e40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
