<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 02:31:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (chest/shoulder) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2975-d1bc-a3fb-ad754d130000</link>
      <description>Watson was injured in Week 15 against the Broncos and is now listed with both chest and shoulder injuries to open the week. His injury is not believed to be serious, but on a short week ahead of a Saturday game, it may be difficult for Watson to practice enough to play in Week 16. The Packers’ report is merely an estimate with a walkthrough practice, but Watson and Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) did not practice. The Packers’ deep passing game may be hampered if Watson and Wicks cannot play Saturday against the Bears, leaving rookie Matthew Golden some opportunities on the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2975-d1bc-a3fb-ad754d130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers OL Zach Tom (back/knee) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2980-d005-a9bf-f9b41cd10000</link>
      <description>Tom suffered a knee injury in Week 15 against the Broncos, but seems to have avoided a major absence. Still, the Packers’ right tackle begins the week with a DNP designation. Practicing later in the week will give him a better chance to play Saturday against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2980-d005-a9bf-f9b41cd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez (groin) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-298f-d1bc-a3fb-adafa9070000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez missed the Commanders’ Week 15 game against the Giants after going DNP-limited-limited in practice with the groin injury last week. Starting out the week as a full participant bodes well for his return. Rodriguez likely cuts back into Jacory Croskey-Merritt’s workload in his return, demoting both to RB3 fantasy plays at best in Week 16 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-298f-d1bc-a3fb-adafa9070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LT Laremy Tunsil (oblique) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2992-d1bc-a3fb-adb6475e0000</link>
      <description>Tunsil suffered an oblique injury in Week 15 and his status for Week 16 is in flux. Commanders head coach Dan Quinn on Monday that Tunsil will play “if he can”, but the left tackle starts out the week not practicing. Practice reports later in the week will tell if Tunsil is good to go for Saturday against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2992-d1bc-a3fb-adb6475e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (stinger) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2995-d1bc-a3fb-adb5f9e10000</link>
      <description>Barkley popped up with a new listing on the injury report, getting a DNP designation due to a stinger. It is unclear yet how serious the injury is, as stingers indicate some kind of head/shoulder nerve pain. He starts out the week with a DNP and practice reports later in the week will tell how serious the issue is. Should Barkley miss Week 16 against the Commanders, Tank Bigsby would be next man up. Bigsby was limited on Tuesday with an illness, but is still tracking to play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2995-d1bc-a3fb-adb5f9e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulders) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-299e-d8cf-affb-bdbee14d0000</link>
      <description>Carter remains sidelined after undergoing surgery on both shoulders two weeks ago. His timetable was week-to-week, but he is not back practicing yet. The Commanders’ running game will have an easier time attacking the middle of the Eagles’ defense if Carter cannot return for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-299e-d8cf-affb-bdbee14d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29a0-d005-a9bf-f9b4b1e80000</link>
      <description>In addition to Johnson, LG Landon Dickerson (calf) also was listed as DNP. Dickerson was at least able to play in Week 15, meaning the designation could just be out of precaution for Tuesday’s walkthrough ahead of a Saturday game. As for Johnson, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reportedlast week he was going to practice this week, but he remains out to start Week 16. Johnson has a few more days to practice before the Eagles play the Commanders on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29a0-d005-a9bf-f9b4b1e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Daniel Oyefusi reports Browns LB Devin Bush was found not guilty of assault and harassment charges stemming from a May incident.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29ca-d8cf-affb-bdeabb5b0000</link>
      <description>Bush was arrested in May on charges of simple assault and harassment. The 27-year-old linebacker has been available for the Browns this season with his trial set for December, snagging two interceptions and making 93 combined tackles in 14 games so far. Oyefusi reports that court documents show Bush was found not guilty of the simple assault and harassment chargers on Tuesday. Bush is now clear to play the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29ca-d8cf-affb-bdeabb5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame RB Jeremiyah Love has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29cf-d005-a9bf-f9ffaf8b0000</link>
      <description>Love is one of the nations’ top running back prospects, finishing his junior year at Notre Dame with 199 carries for 1,372 rushing yards and 18 touchdowns, adding 27 receptions for 280 yards and three touchdowns. He finished as a finalist for the Heisman Trophy award and won the Doak Walker award for the top running back in college football. Teams in the first round of the draft will already be circling Love’s name at the top of their running back big boards; he is certainly a candidate to go in the top 10 picks, similar to Ashton Jeanty in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29cf-d005-a9bf-f9ffaf8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</link>
      <description>As expected, Adams was listed with a DNP for the Rams’ Tuesday walkthrough. Sean McVay did not rule Adams out for Thursday’s game against the Seahawks and said he could be a game-time decision. Adams re-aggravated his hamstring injury in Week 15 and getting healthy on a short week will be difficult. Colby Parkinson emerges as a red zone target for the Rams if Adams is out for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
