<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b4-d332-a1fd-97b6c0df0000</link>
      <description>Kirk was set to play in both two- and three-wide receiver sets, as the Texans’ No. 2 wide receiver. The WR pecking order is murky behind Kirk. Day 3 rookies, WR Jayden Higgins and WR Jaylin Noel, won the Nos. 3 and 4 WR roles in camp, but late-August reports suggest Higgins could split time with WR Xavier Hutchinson. None of the backups offer a reliable floor, though Higgins is likely the best bet to return moderate FLEX value. New OC Nick Caley, a former Rams passing game coordinator, is expected to use three WRs frequently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b4-d332-a1fd-97b6c0df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (groin) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b8-de13-afdd-57fbfd390000</link>
      <description>The news puts Benford, the Bills’ No. 1 CB, on track to play in Week 1 against the Ravens. Fill-in No. 2 CB Tre’Davious White (groin) remains sidelined. The Bills’ first-round rookie CB Maxwell Hairston (knee) is eligible to return from injured reserve after four games. Stud slot CB Taron Johnson could kick outside in base formations, but the Ravens could go big-play hunting by keeping three WRs on the field while targeting the Bills’ chosen perimeter backup coverage defender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b8-de13-afdd-57fbfd390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Keon Coleman (groin) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15c5-d332-a1fd-97f7878e0000</link>
      <description>Coleman was a surprise addition to yesterday’s injury report as a limited participant. We do not yet know his participation level for today’s practice, but the fact that he is able to continue practicing in any capacity is a good sign for his Week 1 availability. He is a boom/bust WR4/5 for the Bills’ Sunday Night Football bout with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15c5-d332-a1fd-97f7878e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Elijah Moore (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5c4350000</link>
      <description>Although Moore is just 25 years old, his erratic participation and performances have seemingly been ever-present for fantasy managers in football’s modern era. We do not know why he was sidelined today, but the official injury report should clarify things. He dealt with an ambiguous leg issue in July. Moore is not worth rostering at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5c4350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15de-de13-afdd-57df5dab0000</link>
      <description>Likely appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 1 against the Bills. He underwent surgery to correct a foot fracture on August 1st and has been sidelined ever since. Mark Andrews should command a healthy target share. Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) has been sidelined since August 14th and likewise appears to be unlikely to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15de-de13-afdd-57df5dab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e1-de13-afdd-57ebcc600000</link>
      <description>The Panthers declared Ekwonu “day to day” on August 27th, after having his appendix removed. If he can return to practice tomorrow, he should be good to go for Week 1 against the Jaguars. Backup OT Yosh Nijman would start in Ekwonu’s stead, if Bryce Young’s blindside protector cannot suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e1-de13-afdd-57ebcc600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Hollywood Brown (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e8-db7b-a5dd-b5ec3d960000</link>
      <description>Brown should operate as the Chiefs’ No. 3 pass catcher in what could be a fantasy-friendly passing environment. He can only be started as a boom/bust FLEX option, given Xavier Worthy and Travis Kelce’s potential target shares. Chiefs OT Jawaan Taylor (knee), LB Drue Tranquill (back) and Kristian Fulton (knee) are likewise good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e8-db7b-a5dd-b5ec3d960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amari Cooper announced his retirement after 10 seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ec-de13-afdd-57efd32b0000</link>
      <description>Cooper retires as a member of the team that drafted him fourth overall in the 2015 NFL Draft. He entered the NFL as a decorated prospect and went on to five Pro Bowl nods and a PFWA All-Rookie Team selection to his resumé. Over the course of his career, Cooper caught 711-of-1,115 targets for 10,034 yards and 64 touchdowns in regular season play. The Raiders traded Cooper to the Cowboys during the 2018 season, and he had a successful stint with the Browns after signing with the club in 2022. He was ultimately traded to the Bills in-season last year, though his play was, unfortunately, hampered by a wrist injury. Cooper’s prime years with the Raiders and Cowboys define his career, though his renaissance with the Joe Flacco-led Browns will also be warmly remembered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ec-de13-afdd-57efd32b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cam Heyward (business) was not in uniform and “did not appear” to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ff-d332-a1fd-97ffcfb20000</link>
      <description>Heyward had held-in for a small portion of camp, but it sounds like it’s not completely over yet. We’d still bet on Heyward being there for Week 1’s game against the Jets, but the Steelers would be in significantly more trouble against New York’s run-focused attack without Heyward, so it’s something worth monitoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ff-d332-a1fd-97ffcfb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Eisen said Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh told him Omarion Hampton will start in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1614-db7b-a5dd-b614f9b70000</link>
      <description>He did lead with “all he would allow,” so we’re not exactly predicting this to not be a timeshare or anything. But it makes plenty of sense that the Chargers would go with the healthy young back as the main portion of their game plan as compared to Najee Harris coming off a lot of missed time in camp. Harris should probably mix in and take up to 30-40 percent of the snaps, perhaps more if the coaches like what they’re seeing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1614-db7b-a5dd-b614f9b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
