<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 14:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) was added to the injury report as a limited participant on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c2a-d45b-affe-7dbe70c60000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed Weeks 3-4 with a groin injury. A recurrence seems likely. The Cardinals’ secondary has lost multiple starters and/or contributors to injury this season. If Johnson cannot play in Week 9, as appears likely, the unit will have a tough time containing Cowboys WRs CeeDee Lamb and George Pickens on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c2a-d45b-affe-7dbe70c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c2e-d45b-affe-7dbed9db0000</link>
      <description>Collins spoke to reporters after Thursday’s practice, saying he had successfully cleared the NFL’s concussion protocol. He practiced in full on Friday and remains symptom-free. Collins faces a talented Broncos defense that is without star CB Pat Surtain II (pectoral). He is best viewed as a high-end WR2 with WR1 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c2e-d45b-affe-7dbed9db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c31-d1e7-a1fa-7efb49670000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ Week 9 wide receiver deployment is consequential. Rookie slot WR Jaylin Noel has played very well over the last two weeks while splitting time with veteran slot WR Braxton Berrios (chest). Kirk’s return jeopardizes Noel’s access to the slot, though it is possible Kirk could take some reps on the perimeter. Berrios has been cleared to play and will be available as well. Noel is worth holding, but carries clear risk as a FLEX option with upside. Kirk is a seemingly stable, floor-oriented FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c31-d1e7-a1fa-7efb49670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c32-d713-ad9e-7c76ea9f0000</link>
      <description>Marks practiced in full on Friday after appearing on Thursday’s injury report as a limited participant due to the new calf injury. It would be great to learn more about whether this is a stain or perhaps a bruise that occurred during a tackle. Regardless, fantasy managers and the Texans alike will have Marks at their disposal on Sunday. Marks (21 carries and nine targets) out-touched veteran RB Nick Chubb (22 carries and five targets) 28-25 over the last two weeks. The rushing work in particular is very promising. The talented rookie was initially viewed as a receiving back, but he appears to be in contention for the lead-rushing role as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c32-d713-ad9e-7c76ea9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 9 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c3a-d673-a39e-bcbbc86f0000</link>
      <description>Schultz was sidelined on Wednesday and Thursday before practicing in full on Friday. Assuming his injuries respond positively to the abrupt workload increase, he seemingly has a shot to play this weekend. Schultz flopped last week when he had a chance to earn a healthy target share with Nos. 1 and 2 WRs Nico Collins (concussion) and Christian Kirk (hamstring) sidelined. He is just a TE2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c3a-d673-a39e-bcbbc86f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c44-d45b-affe-7dd6585c0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is clearly still bothered by this shoulder injury, but he should have a healthy target share with WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee) now on injured reserve. The Raiders’ swinging-door defense also helpfully increases Thomas’ odds of hauling in a few downfield passes. The volatile wide receiver is a WR1 in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c44-d45b-affe-7dd6585c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c3d-d713-ad9e-7c7d60330000</link>
      <description>Brown’s target-earning potential increased with WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee) landing on injured reserve this week. Brown has delivered two WR4 finishes and one WR2 finish this season. He has a chance to solidify his status as a weekly WR4 or better now, especially against the Raiders’ fantasy-friendly defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c3d-d713-ad9e-7c7d60330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbe0bf0000</link>
      <description>Now healthy, Meyers gets one last chance to strut his stuff for any team that might be interested in trading for him before the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline. The Raiders’ No. 1 wide receiver has finished as a half-PPR WR4 three times this season, with his season-best performance (WR16) occurring in Week 1. He can generously be treated as a WR3 with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbe0bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbdace0000</link>
      <description>Bowers last played in Week 4 and is now ready to retake the field following the Raiders’ Week 8 bye. Only time will tell if his PCL sprain and bone bruise have fully healed, but fantasy managers do not want to be late to the punch on this one. Bowers belongs in season-long lineups as an elite TE1 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbdace0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RB Tyler Allgeier (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3d24-d1e7-a1fa-7fee707f0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier briefly caused a scare when he reappeared on the Falcons’ injury report on Thursday as a limited participant. He was upgraded to full on Friday and carries no game-day designation. Allgeier can be started as an RB3/FLEX option, if need be, though he is fairly touchdown-dependent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3d24-d1e7-a1fa-7fee707f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
