<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Zay Flowers (neck) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337b-dc7a-af9b-ffff82090000</link>
      <description>While Flowers’ full participation is encouraging, being added to the injury report with a neck injury mid-week is certainly unideal. Flowers is the Ravens’ only reliable wide receiver. It is worth checking back tomorrow to see if he maintains full practice participation. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337b-dc7a-af9b-ffff82090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337b-d087-addf-b3fb692a0000</link>
      <description>Bateman should be available for QB Lamar Jackson this weekend, though the field-stretching wide receiver has earned more than four targets just once this season. No. 1 WR Zay Flowers was added to the injury report with a neck injury today, which could free up a few targets for Bateman, if Flowers cannot play on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337b-d087-addf-b3fb692a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-338e-d087-addf-b3fe7bd60000</link>
      <description>Fellow Patriots LB Harold Landry (knee) was also sidelined. Fortunately, Patriots LB Christian Elliss (illness) resumed practicing in a limited capacity. The Ravens’ linebackers are tasked with stopping the Ravens’ rushing attack this weekend. The secondary is also dealing with injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-338e-d087-addf-b3fe7bd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-338e-d087-addf-b3fece360000</link>
      <description>Patriots CB Marcus Jones (knee) was also sidelined, and the linebacker corps has three players who are either hurt or ill. The Patriots face the Ravens’ up-and-down offense in Week 16. Although it is far from one of the NFL’s best offenses at this time, it would be nice to get either Davis or Jones on the field this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-338e-d087-addf-b3fece360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (groin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3399-d35e-a1bf-77db3e810000</link>
      <description>Johnston has a chance to suit up this week, but he remains in the questionable camp after logging another limited practice session. The Chargers could use their capable post-catch producer against the Cowboys this weekend, in what should be a fantasy-friendly game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3399-d35e-a1bf-77db3e810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-339f-d087-addf-b3ffaa640000</link>
      <description>Harris’ 49 receiving yards in Week 15 were a career-high. Although he will likely be reduced to a part-time role if WR Quentin Johnston (groin) returns this week, Harris’ development is promising. He would be too risky for WR4/FLEX consideration in that scenario but could warrant consideration in DFS lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-339f-d087-addf-b3ffaa640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RT Trey Pipkins (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a3-d087-addf-b3f35ebe0000</link>
      <description>Pipkins is on track to face the Cowboys this week, although it would be nice to see him practice fully on Friday. The Chargers’ banged-up offensive line is tasked with fending off the Cowboys’ pass-rush unit this week. It should be a high-scoring game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a3-d087-addf-b3f35ebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (neck) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf2d3e0000</link>
      <description>Williams is still on track to play this week against the Chargers, but it would be great to see him upgrade to full participation tomorrow. Williams suffered the neck injury early in his team’s Week 15 and managed to play through it, though he did give up snaps to RB Malik Davis. Davis should be stashed at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf2d3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Quinnen Williams (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a7-dc7a-af9b-ffbfeff20000</link>
      <description>Williams’ return is great to see, though he is not guaranteed to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol in time to play this week. Williams has had a significantly positive impact on the Cowboys’ defense since they acquired him. Chargers QB Justin Herbert would enjoy far more comfortable pockets if Williams is unable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a7-dc7a-af9b-ffbfeff20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ab-d087-addf-b3fbbbd50000</link>
      <description>Chubb is now on track to play. Texans starting RB Woody Marks (ankle), unfortunately, remains sidelined. Chubb would likely handle interior rushing duties if Marks cannot play, but RB Jawhar Jordan would change the pace and play on passing downs. In this scenario, Chubb may be able to punch in a touchdown against the lowly Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ab-d087-addf-b3fbbbd50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
