<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (elbow) has not yet been cleared for contact.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbaf-d82c-a79a-fbbff6860000</link>
      <description>Quinn said Daniels was “ripping” throws today and that the team will take it to “later in the week” before deciding if Daniels will play in Week 14. The Commanders coach mentioned it as “functional contact” the ability to stiff arm and make football moves. It sounds like Marcus Mariota has a real chance at getting a Week 14 start if the Commanders have not yet made a decision on Daniels playing on Monday. Mariota would be a worthwhile superflex start against the Vikings, while Daniels would obviously make the QB1 line if he were ready to go. We’ll probably get another update on this Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbaf-d82c-a79a-fbbff6860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Kyren Williams (ankle) was “pretty good” today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbb6-d82c-a79a-fbb6e6720000</link>
      <description>Williams briefly left Week 13’s game with an ankle injury, but returned and later rushed for a touchdown. It wouldn’t be surprising if he popped up on the injury report this week, but given that he already played on it yesterday, we’re expecting him to be ready to go for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbb6-d82c-a79a-fbb6e6720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports “One offensive player said he didn’t expect designed runs” for Jaxson Dart in Week 13 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbac-d90e-a9da-dfaff9600000</link>
      <description>Dart has taken a number of hard hits this year and landed himself in concussion protocol after going down in Week 10 against the Bears. The rookie signal-caller has totaled 57 carries this season, with 36 of those attempts coming on designed runs. Dart’s rushing upside has been an integral part of his fantasy value, as the rookie has finished in the top-12 in four of his last five starts while finding the end zone six times over that span. Any cutback in designed runs could put a dent in his weekly fantasy ceiling, but the Giants would be wise to find ways to cut back Dart’s rush attempts until he can better protect himself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbac-d90e-a9da-dfaff9600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Tyler Bass (hip/groin) will not return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbbc-d90e-a9da-dfbf38270000</link>
      <description>Bass was placed on injured reserve before the start of the season and has not played a game. McDermott said Bass recently underwent surgery, which would sideline him for the remainder of the year, leaving kicking duties to Matt Prater for the rest of the way. Bass signed a four-year extension with the Bills in 2023 and should be back as the Bills’ kicker in 2026 if all goes well with his recovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbbc-d90e-a9da-dfbf38270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd0-d6c4-abfb-dfd3b1830000</link>
      <description>Given that he hasn’t played since October 12, it’s a big step. He apparently practiced with a bulky brace, so it’s possible that the Lions decide it isn’t worth the risk with just a few days ahead of Thursday’s game. But they also need every win they can get and this will be an enormous game for wild card implications against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd0-d6c4-abfb-dfd3b1830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Kalif Raymond (ankle) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd2-db57-afda-dff249be0000</link>
      <description>Isaac TeSlaa took his place against the Packers on Thanksgiving, scoring a touchdown and catching a second ball on a 92.1 percent snap share. TeSlaa is probably too raw to trust given the low target counts for most fantasy leagues, but he could be a DFS slate play for sure on Thursday if Raymond can’t get back to practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd2-db57-afda-dff249be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions listed TE Brock Wright (neck) as DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd1-d6c4-abfb-dfd3484e0000</link>
      <description>Wright missed Week 12’s game against the Packers with a neck injury and is on the wrong side of being active for Thursday night’s game against the Cowboys. It’s only an estimated practice report, so we’ll see if things change between now and Wednesday, but if Wright is unable to go, the Lions would be down their third-string tight end as they look to keep their postseason hopes alive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd1-d6c4-abfb-dfd3484e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Trey Lance will get first-team practice reps in goal-line scenarios this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe5-db57-afda-dff7d44c0000</link>
      <description>Justin Herbert’s hand injury, which he is getting surgery for today, hampered him enough that the Chargers didn’t have him take any snaps under center. It’s possible that Lance handles some goal-line work for the Chargers this week even if Herbert starts the game, cutting into Herbert’s fantasy ceiling. We’d be a little surprised if such a scenario comes to pass, but the fact that the Chargers are openly admitting they’re doing due diligence on it says plenty on its own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe5-db57-afda-dff7d44c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR George Pickens (calf/knee) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe9-d82c-a79a-fbfdb24b0000</link>
      <description>Pickens played under this designation on Thanksgiving, showing no ill effects with a 13-target, 88-yard day. He should be a confident start in Week 14 against a Lions secondary that made Jordan Love come alive. We’d be extremely surprised if he didn’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe9-d82c-a79a-fbfdb24b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said the team will not open Kyler Murray’s (foot) 21-day return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</link>
      <description>Kedon Slovis will get at least one more game as Jacoby Brissett’s backup. Murray hasn’t played since Week 5 and was eventually benched for Jacoby Brissett, who outperformed Murray during his multi-week absence. Murray is under contract through the 2028 season, but there’s a good chance his time with the team will come to an end this offseason. The same can be said of Jonathan Gannon, but that’s a conversation for another day. The Cardinals don’t have anything to play for at this point, and any decisions to part with Murray could factor into whether the team decides to activate him at all over the final five weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
