<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:02:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 3-of-6 targets for 33 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2071-d1bc-a3fb-a575d3ba0000</link>
      <description>Pickens was hammered by the media throughout the week after his effort level was called into question in the team’s Week 14 loss to the Lions, with those same tendencies rearing their head against the Vikings. He was seen giving up on the route at least once and was hardly a contributor to the run game, routinely running at half speed off the line on called rush attempts. He even walked off the line on one occasion. Pickens’ talent has never been in question but putting mental lapses like this on film is surely going to influence offseason contract discussions, even with his eruption on the field through the middle parts of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2071-d1bc-a3fb-a575d3ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2076-d1bc-a3fb-a57603d20000</link>
      <description>Ferguson played through a calf ailment that had him enter the weekend listed as questionable, ultimately unable to return usable counting stats on a night quarterback Dak Prescott failed to throw for a score for the third time this season. He has not failed to return a solid fantasy score in all five games since the team’s Week 10 bye, with his performance in the first week of fantasy playoffs hurting the most. His next chance to return TE1 production comes in a difficult matchup against the Chargers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2076-d1bc-a3fb-a57603d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Aubrey made 4-of-6 field goal attempts and two extra points in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-207a-d8cf-affb-bc7a381d0000</link>
      <description>The normally elite kicker missed from 51 yards in the first half and from 59 yards after the break in a loss that all but ended the team’s chances at a postseason berth, now requiring three wins and three losses from the Eagles to do so. The two misses also matched his season total through 13 games after the veteran kicker connected on 27 of his first 29 attempts this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-207a-d8cf-affb-bc7a381d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said Woody Marks (ankle) could have returned to Houston’s Week 15 game over the Cardinals, but he wanted to “make sure Woody is good as we continue to go into the week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-21e4-d77b-adfb-ebe7cfab0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like with a 17-0 lead, Ryans prioritized Marks’ health — this is the third week in a row where he has been pulled mid-game with a nagging lower body injury. Sensible. Not fun for fantasy managers, but sensible. Marks enters Week 16 on the questionable line, with a big game possible against a Raiders defense that allowed 31 points to the Bad Vibes Eagles in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-21e4-d77b-adfb-ebe7cfab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Ravens fear LB Teddye Buchanan suffered a torn ACL in Week 15’s win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-222c-d1bc-a3fb-a72ca2d10000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Buchanan’s knee buckled under him while covering a punt early in Sunday’s win. The rookie linebacker is scheduled to undergo more tests on Monday to confirm things, but it sounds like Buchanan is trending toward missing the remainder of the season. Buchanan is second on the team with 93 tackles this season and has also registered five TFLs to go with one forced fumble and one pass breakup. His absence would be a big loss for the Ravens who are fighting to stay in the playoff hunt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-222c-d1bc-a3fb-a72ca2d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Williams caught 6-of-7 targets for 53 yards in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</link>
      <description>It was a career day for Williams, who ranked second among Jets receivers in routes (30) and third in snaps (41). Williams has played primarily on special teams this season and currently leads the league in punt return yards (396) and has two punt return touchdowns. He seemed to show good chemistry with Brady Cook, who he has presumably spent a lot of time with in practice, but his strong performance in Week 15 could warrant a stronger look over the final three weeks of the season. Williams has played 30-plus snaps and run 20-plus routes in back-to-back weeks. He’s worth a stash in deeper leagues ahead of next week’s game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (ankle) left Chicago’s Week 15 game against the Browns and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-225a-d8cf-affb-be7af1cc0000</link>
      <description>He was officially questionable to return after leaving in the third quarter. Bears coach Ben Johnson said after the game that they’d look at it tomorrow. It’s possible that the Bears will lose their ascending receiver ahead of Week 16’s date against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-225a-d8cf-affb-be7af1cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Christian Watson’s injury is not believed to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2248-d77b-adfb-eacb982c0000</link>
      <description>Watson appeared to have suffered a shoulder injury but was later listed with a chest injury. The Packers’ top deep threat was taken to the hospital for further evaluation, but was able to fly home with the team after the game. Whether or not he’s able to play in Week 16 against the may not be known until later in the week, but it sounds like this will be a short-term absence for Watson at the worst. With the Packers playing on Saturday, we should have our first injury report on Tuesday, which will give us a better sense of where Watson’s availability could stand for next week. If he’s unable to go, Romeo Doubs and Matthew Golden would be the favorites to see expanded roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2248-d77b-adfb-eacb982c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan “I would expect [Ricky Pearsall] to be alright” after Week 15’s win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-228e-d77b-adfb-ea8f28550000</link>
      <description>Pearsall battled through an ankle injury early in Sunday’s win and later went down with a knee injury. Shanahan said he believes Pearsall’s knee injury resulted from “irritating his PCL from the past,” and noted that such injuries tend to linger. Pearsall said after the game that he will have some imaging done, so we’ll likely know within the next 24 hours if there’s anything to be concerned about heading into Week 16. We’re well into the part of the season when every player is dealing with some injury or another. Hopefully, Pearsall will be available for Week 16’s game against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-228e-d77b-adfb-ea8f28550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets fired DC Steve Wilks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22a3-d005-a9bf-fab7d25b0000</link>
      <description>A 48-20 loss to the Jaguars was the final straw for Wilks, whose defense entered the day ranked in the bottom five in EPA per play entering the day and had allowed six 30-plus point performances on the year. Life got harder following this year’s trade deadline, when the Jets dealt stars Sauce Gardner and Quinnen Williams away for future draft picks, but Sunday’s loss to the Jaguars set a new low for the season. Wilks hasn’t spent more than one season with a team since his first stint with the Panthers, which lasted from 2012 to 2017. The long-time defensive coordinator who helped lead a top-five 49ers defense in 2023 could find a new home next offseason, but this latest stop left much to be desired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22a3-d005-a9bf-fab7d25b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
