<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Ja’Marr Chase (illness) is active for Week 6 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ba-db72-a199-fbfb3bf10000</link>
      <description>Chase was seen warming up earlier today and evidently made it through the session without issue. He remains firmly in the elite WR1 tier, having finished as the overall WR1 last week despite catching passes from fill-in starter QB Jake Browning. The Bengals traded for former Browns QB Joe Flacco this week, who, with any luck, will help stabilize the Bengals’ offense overall. The Bengals declared CB Marco Wilson, OG Dylan Fairchild, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DT Jordan Jefferson and EDGE Shemar Stewart inactive for Week 6 against the Packers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ba-db72-a199-fbfb3bf10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports Garrett Wilson suffered a knee injury in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ca-d94a-a79d-d9cfb94f0000</link>
      <description>Wilson was said to be dealing with a hip injury, but Hughes is now calling it a knee issue. ESPN’s Rich Cimini later added that Wilson will undergo an MRI on his knee, but it’s not believed to be an ACL injury. That is at least some good news, though an MRI suggests it could still be a serious injury. The Jets’ offense was already mostly dysfunctional with Wilson out there. It would fall into a state of complete disrepair if Wilson misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ca-d94a-a79d-d9cfb94f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared TE Brock Bowers, Guard Caleb Rogers, DT JJ Pegues, RB Zamir White, and DT Tonka Hemingway inactive for Week 6 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9cd-db72-a199-fbcf2f6d0000</link>
      <description>Bowers will miss his second straight game with a knee injury he suffered in Week 2. Michael Mayer, having recently cleared the NFL’s concussion protocol, will play this week and could be a legit fantasy option if he takes over as the Raiders’ No. 1 tight end. White remains a healthy scratch, leaving Raheem Mostert as the Raiders’ RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9cd-db72-a199-fbcf2f6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared K Brandon McManus, DL Devonte Wyatt, OT Anthony Belton and CB Kamal Hadden inactive for Week 6 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ba-d94a-a79d-d9bf38640000</link>
      <description>The Packers signed K Lucas Havrisik on Saturday, with McManus nursing a quad injury. Havrisik will kick in McManus’ stead. Green Bay received great news regarding the offensive line’s health. LT Rasheed Walker (quad), LG Aaron Banks (groin/knee), RT Zach Tom (oblique/back) and backup OG/C Jacob Monk are all active this week. The talented unit should keep QB Jordan Love upright against the Bengals. Starting CB Nate Hobbs (concussion) is not on the inactives list, indicating he successfully passed the NFL’s concussion protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ba-d94a-a79d-d9bf38640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared CB Zyon McCollum, RB Bucky Irving, WR Mike Evans, WR Chris Godwin Jr., RB Josh Williams and CB Benjamin Morrison inactive for Week 6’s game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d6-d94a-a79d-d9df55ae0000</link>
      <description>All players on this list were ruled out on Friday. Irving, Evans, and Godwin should all have a chance next week. Tampa Bay is down two corners against Jauan Jennings and the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d6-d94a-a79d-d9df55ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared RB Jordan James, QB Brock Purdy, WR Ricky Pearsall, WR Jordan Watkins, DL Yetur Gross-Matos and LB Nick Martin inactive for San Francisco’s Week 6 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d9-d94a-a79d-d9dd95540000</link>
      <description>James, who had been dealing with a wrist injury but is now in the clear, winds up as a healthy scratch along with Martin. The other four players were ruled out on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d9-d94a-a79d-d9dd95540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Rush was benched in the fourth quarter of Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9e0-db72-a199-fbeb50230000</link>
      <description>With the Ravens trailing 17-3 and Rush sitting on 11-of-19 passing for 72 scoreless yards and a pick, the Ravens turned to Tyler Huntley, who arguably should have been starting to begin with. Although Rush was one of the league’s more competent backups in Dallas, there has never been any doubt he’s a pure No. 2. With the Ravens on bye for Week 7, today was almost certainly Rush’s final start before Lamar Jackson’s (hamstring) likely Week 8 return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9e0-db72-a199-fbeb50230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Conklin (concussion) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 6 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d0-d94a-a79d-d9dd87740000</link>
      <description>Conklin exited in the third quarter to be evaluated for a concussion and did not return to the field. The veteran tackle has struggled to get on the field this season, with this concussion marking the latest setback. Conklin, a right tackle, was replaced by KT Leveston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9d0-d94a-a79d-d9dd87740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) went to the locker room in the fourth quarter of the Browns’ Week 6 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9eb-db72-a199-fbebdc0f0000</link>
      <description>Njoku briefly left the game in the second and third quarters only to return after missing a few plays. Now, the veteran tight end has headed to the locker room with trainers, which could signal the end of his day given the 23-6 deficit the Browns are facing in the final frame. If it is the end of the day for Njoku, he’ll exit with a line of 3-28-0 on six targets. He nearly found himself on the receiving end of score late in the second quarter but saw the pass broken up. Njoku’s status will likely be one to monitor ahead of the Browns’ Week 7 game against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9eb-db72-a199-fbebdc0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens EDGE Tavius Robinson suffered a foot injury in Baltimore’s Week 6 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9f5-dd4c-afb9-fff516e10000</link>
      <description>Meanwhile, fellow EDGE Brent Urban is in the concussion protocol with his second head injury in as many seasons. Initially listed as questionable in the first half, Robinson was ruled out after the break. It’s more injuries a hollowed-out defense can’t afford, though the Ravens at least have their Week 7 bye to try to heal up. Robinson entered this afternoon with two sacks on roughly 260 snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9f5-dd4c-afb9-fff516e10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
