<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) was ruled out in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9273-deb6-a7fd-d3ffc34f0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are now down six defensive starters with Humphrey sidelined for the rest of this game, and perhaps longer after suffering what appeared to be a serious calf injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9273-deb6-a7fd-d3ffc34f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Bond caught 3-of-6 targets for 58 yards in the Browns’ Week 4 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9274-deb6-a7fd-d3ff558c0000</link>
      <description>Bond led the Browns in receiving yards on the back of a 35-yard chunk play. His three grabs and six targets were both tied for second on the team. Bond has 10 targets over the past two weeks. That’s twice as many as Cedric Tillman. Neither player is a viable fantasy option for Week 5, but Bond is worth adding in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9274-deb6-a7fd-d3ff558c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 3-of-4 targets for 44 yards in the Giants’ Week 4 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9278-d6e9-af9d-9af89af70000</link>
      <description>Slayton actually led the Giants in receiving on an afternoon where Malik Nabers was lost to a second quarter ACL tear. That brutal development means an inevitable uptick in usage for Slayton, though this is going to be a hyper-conservative offense with dual-threat rookie QB Jaxson Dart just now finding his NFL sea leges. Slayton, who could come into WR4 value, is worth an add in 12-team leagues with bye weeks beginning, but you don’t need us to tell you to temper expectations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9278-d6e9-af9d-9af89af70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is questionable to return in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-927e-d6e9-af9d-9afe21e80000</link>
      <description>Jackson suffered the injury on an innocuous tackle in the third quarter of a game that Chiefs had dominated from the start. Jackson has received no medical attention on the bench and appears unlikely to re-enter the game with KC nursing a comfortable lead. Jackson had 147 passing yards, one touchdown, and an interception along with 48 rushing yards before the hamstring injury. Cooper Rush took over under center for Baltimore. An extended absence of Jackson could mean the end of the Ravens’ season after a 1-3 start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-927e-d6e9-af9d-9afe21e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 3-of-5 targets for 17 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 4 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9281-d95b-addb-fac7250d0000</link>
      <description>The second touchdown of Johnson’s career was his first of the season. It was a three-yard score on a third quarter shovel pass. Up to nine catches through four games, Johnson’s targets floor and yardage ceiling should both inch upward with Malik Nabers on the shelf with a season-ending ACL tear but not enough that we would feel comfortable labeling him a top-20 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9281-d95b-addb-fac7250d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared CB Kamal Hadden, OL Zach Tom, OL Aaron Banks, OL Anthony Belton, and DL Warren Brinson inactive for Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9286-d6e9-af9d-9a965ddc0000</link>
      <description>Safety Javon Bullard is active after progressing through the league’s concussion protocol, with the biggest absence for the Packers being Zach Tom. Green Bay heads into a matchup with the Lamb-less Cowboys looking to improve to 3-1 after a gut-wrenching loss to the Browns a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9286-d6e9-af9d-9a965ddc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 2-of-2 targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 4 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9288-deb6-a7fd-d3dfb8610000</link>
      <description>Henry’s touchdown was his third in two games. He took a short dump-off then rumbled down the sideline for a 31-yard score. Fantasy managers won’t love the two targets, but Drake Maye attempted only 17 passes in a convincing victory. The Pats’ passing game will undoubtedly be needed for more volume in Week 5 against the Bills. Henry will be a solid TE2 for that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9288-deb6-a7fd-d3dfb8610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught both of his targets for 29 yards in the Eagles’ Week 4 win against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-928a-dca3-a9fb-bf9bc2150000</link>
      <description>Smith has 18 receptions through four games in the massively run-heavy Eagles offense after Sunday’s slow outing against the Bucs. A.J. Brown dominated targets (9) but didn’t do much with the opportunity, gaining just seven yards on two grabs. Smith was coming off a hopeful Week 3 outing against the Rams in which he caught eight balls for 60 yards. Smith, the clear No. 2 wideout for the Eagles, will be a WR3/4 option in Week 5 against an elite Broncos defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-928a-dca3-a9fb-bf9bc2150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared WR CeeDee Lamb, LB Damone Clark, RB Jaydon Blue, G Tyler Booker, OT Ajani Cornelius and DT Jay Toia inactive for Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9288-deb6-a7fd-d3dfd1e90000</link>
      <description>Lamb will miss the first game in what is expected to be a 3-4 week absence with an ankle injury in the team’s Week 4 meeting with the Packers, placing additional emphasis on Jake Ferguson and George Pickens in a difficult matchup with the 2-1 Packers. Defensive End Jadeveon Clowney is active and will make his team debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9288-deb6-a7fd-d3dfd1e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
