<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints elevated K Charlie Smyth from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f54f-d8cf-affb-fd6fc8050000</link>
      <description>Smyth nailed a 56-yard field goal in his NFL debut in Week 13, and the product of Ireland will once again handle kicking duties for the Saints in Week 14 against the Buccaneers. His strong leg and New Orleans’ inability to complete drives makes him worthy of consideration for those who get added points for lengthier field goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f54f-d8cf-affb-fd6fc8050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed S Mike Edwards from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f555-d8cf-affb-fd7f6af60000</link>
      <description>Edwards, 29, made his first appearance of the season against the Cowboys on Thanksgiving, and the former starter will be a depth option for Kansas City in their Week 14 tilt against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f555-d8cf-affb-fd7f6af60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hassan Haskins (hamstring) is questionable for Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f568-d8cf-affb-fd6ac8a20000</link>
      <description>Haskins is currently on injured reserve with his hamstring issue, and hasn’t been able to play since Week 7. The former fourth-round pick would be a backup — presumably for Omarion Hampton (ankle) — option if he can go Monday night against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f568-d8cf-affb-fd6ac8a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers activated Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) off injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f58f-da9b-a9bf-ff8fb6b20000</link>
      <description>Rob Demovsky of ESPN reports that the expectation is that Reed will play in Week 14 against the Bears, but the Packers are listening the third-year wideout as questionable for that contest. Reed last played in Week 2. If he can actually suit up, he’ll knock Dontayvion Wicks out of the top 70, and perhaps render Romeo Doubs and even Christian Watson a bit more volatile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f58f-da9b-a9bf-ff8fb6b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders activated WR Noah Brown (groin) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f595-da9b-a9bf-ff9d5fcd0000</link>
      <description>Facing the Vikings, Brown will be active for the first time since Week 2. He figures to immediately slot back in as the No. 3 wideout for an offense that has been dealing with receiver injury carnage all season. Good news for Washington, especially with Jayden Daniels also returning, but it’s unlikely to make a ripple in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f595-da9b-a9bf-ff9d5fcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed WR Greg Dortch (chest) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f592-da9b-a9bf-ff9fd9a30000</link>
      <description>Dortch could return for the Week 18 finale, but it’s likely that the season is over for the 27-year-old. Assuming his campaign is done, he finishes 2025 with 29 receptions for 2026 yards and three touchdowns. Trent Sherfield has been promoted from the practice squad to take Dortch’s place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f592-da9b-a9bf-ff9fd9a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Chandler (knee) won’t play in Week 14 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59d-da9b-a9bf-ff9db42b0000</link>
      <description>Chandler will not come off injured reserve, so the Vikings will once again go with a Jordan Mason-Aaron Jones backfield for the tilt against the Commanders. Chandler likely wouldn’t have a big role/won’t have one whenever he is activated, anyways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59d-da9b-a9bf-ff9db42b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Brady Cook from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59f-da9b-a9bf-ff9fbbe20000</link>
      <description>Cook will be the backup signal-caller for the Week 14 contest against the Dolphins, as Justin Fields (knee) has been ruled out for that contest versus Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59f-da9b-a9bf-ff9fbbe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks activated S Julian Love (hamstring) off injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5a0-d77b-adfa-ffa3df6b0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks are also activating Jarran Reed (wrist/thumb) as Seattle is getting two of their core defensive players back for the final five contests of the year. Love should be the starting free safety against Atlanta, while Reed should see plenty of snaps/could start up the middle, as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5a0-d77b-adfa-ffa3df6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB John Wolford off their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5bb-da9b-a9bf-ffbf4e260000</link>
      <description>Wolford’s signing likely means that he’ll be the backup quarterback for JJ McCarthy for Week 14 against the Commanders, with Max Brosmer the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5bb-da9b-a9bf-ffbf4e260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
