<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pec) is out for Week 3 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5819-dfa0-a9bb-db9f0b2f0000</link>
      <description>Buffalo’s defense will be shorthanded against the Dolphins on Thursday night. DT Ed Oliver will also be sidelined with an ankle injury he suffered in Week 2. The Bills’ defensive injuries could make things slightly less bleak for the Dolphins offense in Week 3, especially De’Von Achane, who leads the Miami backfield with 29 touches over two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5819-dfa0-a9bb-db9f0b2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chargers LB Khalil Mack (elbow) “is expected to be back in a few weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-581d-d654-a19b-d87db3070000</link>
      <description>Mack appeared to suffer a serious arm injury during Monday night’s win over the Raiders, and after evaluation, he should be able to avoid surgery and return to the LA lineup in October. It’s great news for a Chargers defense that has allowed the third lowest success rate to opposing offenses through two weeks, generating consistent pressure on enemy quarterbacks. Mack has one sack and two QB hits over the season’s first two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-581d-d654-a19b-d87db3070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5846-dfde-a1bd-5ecf331f0000</link>
      <description>“We’ll see how it goes,” Morris said of Terrell’s practice participation this week ahead of Atlanta’s Week 3 game against the Panthers. “Obviously those hamstrings are tricky.” Terrell sustained the hamstring injury on Sunday against the Vikings. Terrell’s absence could be a boon for Bryce Young, Tetairoa McMillan, and the rest of the Panthers wideouts. the Falcons have allowed an average of just ten receiver catches per week through Week 2, one of the league’s lowest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5846-dfde-a1bd-5ecf331f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (concussion) is out for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-587a-d93f-ad9d-5aff701a0000</link>
      <description>Fields was ruled out Wednesday, which could mean he’ll be iffy for Week 4. The Jets will turn to 36-year-old journeyman QB Tyrod Taylor against a tough Bucs defense. Taylor last week completed seven of 11 attempts for 56 yards and a touchdown against Buffalo after Fields left the game with a brain injury. He’ll be a downgrade for Garrett Wilson, who profiles as a WR3 in 12-team leagues this week. Look for the Jets to be even more run heavy than usual against Tampa. Taylor’s rushing production could make him viable in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-587a-d93f-ad9d-5aff701a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said QB Jayden Daniels (knee) won’t practice until Friday at the earliest.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5890-d93f-ad9d-5ad7c20b0000</link>
      <description>Quinn added Daniels had a good rehab session on Wednesday but would not practice. There’s almost no chance Daniels will suit up for Week 3 against the Raiders after sustaining a knee sprain last week in a loss to the Packers. That means Marcus Mariota will get the starting nod against Vegas. Mariota will be a marked downgrade for Terry McLaurin, Zach Ertz, and Deebo Samuel. Last year in a Week 7 start against Carolina, Mariota threw just 23 passes while rushing 11 times for 34 yards. The Commanders were 7 percent below their expected pass rate that day. Mariota will be usable in superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5890-d93f-ad9d-5ad7c20b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58a4-dfde-a1bd-5ead896f0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez has yet to practice or play this season while dealing with a lingering hamstring issue. We would expect his workload in Wednesday’s practice to be rather light, but it’s a step in the right direction for the young corner. The Patriots just gave up 27 points to a Dolphins offense that looked lifeless in their previous appearance. Getting Gonzalez back won’t turn things around overnight, but it will certainly stem the bleeding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58a4-dfde-a1bd-5ead896f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor declined to rule out Joe Burrow (toe) for the year on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ab-d1b3-a5dd-59fbe1b20000</link>
      <description>Taylor did not have a timeline for Burrow’s impending surgery, though it should happen soon. The fact that a 2025 return is still on the table is notable, though it does not mean Burrow will actually play again this season. Burrow is expected to be sidelined for a minimum of three months, meaning the earliest he could get back on the field would be the middle of December. Burrow stands almost no chance of playing at the end of the year if the Bengals aren’t in the playoff hunt late in the season. Jake Browning is penciled in as the starter for now. Browning went 4-3 as the team’s starter in 2023 and should be able to get the ball into the hands of Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins often enough to keep both from bottoming out as fantasy assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ab-d1b3-a5dd-59fbe1b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed EDGE Preston Smith, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b3-d6a5-adff-fef7d6a00000</link>
      <description>Smith got his start in the pros as a second-round pick with the Commanders in 2015. He then spent six years in Green Bay, though the Packers traded him to Pittsburgh in his final year with the team. Smith totaled two sacks in eight games as a rotational EDGE for the Steelers. He will give the Commanders some extra depth at the position after they lost Deatrich Wise to a season-ending leg injury last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b3-d6a5-adff-fef7d6a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b9-d1b3-a5dd-59f983600000</link>
      <description>Worthy got in a pair of limited sessions last week after being listed as a DNP on Wednesday. Getting on the field for the first practice of the week this time around is a step in the right direction and suggests Worthy could be ready to return to action on Sunday. He is reportedly dealing with a fully torn labrum after taking a brutal hit from Travis Kelce in Week 1. Getting Worthy back after just one game would be a massive win for a Chiefs team still in search of its first win of 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b9-d1b3-a5dd-59f983600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said WR Jalen Royals (knee) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c1-d1b3-a5dd-59f1133e0000</link>
      <description>It will be Royals’ first practice of the season after missing the opening two weeks while dealing with knee tendinitis. Reid was cagey when talkign about Royals, saying, “He’s coming pretty good, we’ll see how he does here. He’s been out for a while.” Even if he is healthy for Week 3, it wouldn’t be surprising for the rookie to get another week off to ensure he doesn’t suffer any setbacks. For now, Royals is only on the radar in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c1-d1b3-a5dd-59f1133e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
