<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10b6-d332-a1fd-96b61dc40000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu underwent the procedure just over a week ago. Head coach Dave Canales called him “day to day” on Monday, though he appears to be on the wrong side of questionable to start the week. Yosh Nijman looks like Bryce Young’s starting left tackle for Carolina’s Week 1 matchup with the Jaguars. Fellow backup Brady Christensen is also an option for the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10b6-d332-a1fd-96b61dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10c6-db7b-a5dd-b0c671420000</link>
      <description>Reed missed most of training camp with a foot injury. He was in a walking boot at one point and was unable to run routes without feeling pain as of last week. He told reporters a week ago that his availability for Week 1 “still feels uncertain.” It’s a frustrating start to the season for a player looking to take the next step. Reed fell from 64 catches as a rookie to 55 in 2024. Despite the downtick in volume, Reed leveraged his elite play-making ability to up his yardage total to 857 through the air and another 163 on the ground. Even if he is ready to go by Sunday, fantasy managers shouldn’t count on a full workload for the third-year wideout. He will settle into the WR4/5 range if active, though that’s far from a guarantee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10c6-db7b-a5dd-b0c671420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (elbow) practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10cc-db7b-a5dd-b0cc65360000</link>
      <description>Goodson was vying for the RB2 job with rookie DJ Giddens this summer. Goodson suffered an elbow injury in Indy’s second preseason game, paving the way for Giddens to win the camp battle. While it’s a good sign that Goodson was able to practice today, Giddens should be treated as the clear backup to Jonathan Taylor for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10cc-db7b-a5dd-b0cc65360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10d8-db7b-a5dd-b0dc7cbe0000</link>
      <description>Guyton suffered a knee injury at the start of training camp that was initially feared to be a torn ACL. He escaped the ordeal with a bone fracture that took just a month to recover from. Guyton was a full participant in all three practices this week and is good to go versus Philly. Cowboys corner Trevon Diggs was also cleared from the injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10d8-db7b-a5dd-b0dc7cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10df-de13-afdd-56df690f0000</link>
      <description>Diggs went down with a knee injury late last year and initially looked unlikely to be ready for Week 1. Things progressed well for the standout corner and he managed three full practices this week before being cleared for action. Sans Micah Parsons, the Cowboys are going to need all the help they can get as they prepare to take on the reigning Super Bowl champion Eagles in the first game of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10df-de13-afdd-56df690f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b67-dbe3-a9bb-3b7715b70000</link>
      <description>Thomas spent much of the offseason rehabbing his season-ending Lisfranc injury suffered in October 2024. He underwent surgery to correct the issue and was placed on the active/physically unable to perform list in July. Having been activated in mid-August, Thomas has been ramping up with a Week 1 return date in mind. Today’s limited participation has him on track to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b67-dbe3-a9bb-3b7715b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers TE Tommy Tremble (back) is not on the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-110b-de13-afdd-57cb450e0000</link>
      <description>Tremble underwent back surgery in May and opened training camp on the PUP list. He returned to practice and was activated from PUP last week. J’Tavion Sanders should slot in as the Panthers’ starting tight end heading into his second season, but Tremble will pitch in for blocking reps and some work in 12-personnel looks. Tremble’s return to the lineup will keep Sanders off the tight end streaming radar for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-110b-de13-afdd-57cb450e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Noah Brown (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-111b-d332-a1fd-973f8a050000</link>
      <description>Brown was carted away from practice back in June, and the team opted not to divulge the exact nature of the injury. Now we know it’s a knee issue. Brown should not be rostered in 12-team leagues, injured and stuck in the No. 3 wide receiver role behind Terry McLaurin and Deebo Samuel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-111b-d332-a1fd-973f8a050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1122-de13-afdd-57eb060a0000</link>
      <description>Pittsburgh’s first-round pick this year suffered a knee injury during the team’s final preseason game. He avoided injured reserve to start the season but was initially expected to miss about a month. Later reports have been more optimistic on his timeline, though he is still a long shot to suit up for Pittsburgh’s opener versus the Jets. He should be ruled out for Week 1 later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1122-de13-afdd-57eb060a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said RB Najee Harris (eye) is expected to play in Friday’s game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1126-dbe3-a9bb-31772cb00000</link>
      <description>Harris missed the entirety of training camp while recovering from an eye injury suffered during a fireworks incident over the weekend of July 4th. He managed to avoid the NFI list to start the year and is at least going to be active for Week 1. Still, missing that much time during the offseason likely has Harris at less than his peak conditioning. He also gave first-round rookie Omarion Hampton two months to run with the starting offense. Harris will open the year as a backup running back and an RB5 for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1126-dbe3-a9bb-31772cb00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
