<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots designated WR Mack Hollins (abdomen) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e776-dc7a-af9b-efff51330000</link>
      <description>Hollins resumed practicing today, which gives him a chance to suit up for the Patriots’ AFC Championship Game against the Broncos. Hollins is a reliable blocker and a streaky producer, operating as a speedy field-stretcher for the Patriots. His return could reduce WR Kayshon Boutte’s snap share, though Boutte has caught 7-of-9 targets for 141 yards and one touchdown in two postseason games. He has a chance to retain the starting role even if Hollins returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e776-dc7a-af9b-efff51330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired Jesse Minter as their new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7cd-d56e-afff-e7ed33860000</link>
      <description>Minter, 42, served as the Chargers’ defensive coordinator under head coach Jim Harbaugh over the last two seasons. He also held the same role with Harbaugh’s Michigan squad from 2022-2023. He had a one-year stint at Vanderbilt, serving as defensive coordinator and safeties coach. He worked for former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh before that, signing on as a defensive assistant in Baltimore from 2017-2018. He was promoted to assistant defensive backs coach in 2019 and promoted again to defensive backs coach in 2020. Bills OC Joe Brady and former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury are reportedly “two names to keep an eye on” for the Ravens’ offensive coordinator role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7cd-d56e-afff-e7ed33860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills completed an interview with Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7d7-d56e-afff-e7ff02410000</link>
      <description>Anarumo spent the 2025 serving as the Colts’ defensive coordinator after being fired by the Bengals in 2024. He held the same position with them for six years. Anarumo also received interview requests from the Giants and Titans during this interview cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7d7-d56e-afff-e7ff02410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</link>
      <description>Davis still has a chance to clear the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol, but he will probably need to upgrade to full participation tomorrow. Davis leads the team with 12 pass breakups this season. It would be great to have him on the field for New England’s AFC Championship Game against the Broncos, though Denver may opt for a run-heavy approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (shoulder) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</link>
      <description>Henderson is practicing fully this week, so his availability for the Patriots’ AFC Championship Game against the Broncos’ top-tier defense is not in jeopardy. He will continue sharing the backfield workload with veteran RB Rhamondre Stevenson, who is playing very well at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</link>
      <description>Landry still has a chance to play, though it would be nice to see him resume practicing tomorrow. The veteran pass rusher ranks third on the team in quarterback pressures (50), second in sacks (nine) and 10th in tackles (28). Patriots LB Marte Mapu (hip) was also absent on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7ce-d968-a19b-ffff1c710000</link>
      <description>Great news. The Broncos’ third-round rookie is on track to play in the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots as long as he remains setback-free. Bryant caught three passes for 32 yards on the Broncos’ opening drive last week. He should handle a featured role in the offense once again this week, though head coach Sean Payton may opt for a run-heavy approach with backup QB Jarrett Stidham under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7ce-d968-a19b-ffff1c710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e817-d968-a19b-f8f7f2f30000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is in the questionable camp at this time. The 27-year-old rusher is attempting to return from a Lisfranc injury suffered during an illegal hip-drop tackle in Week 10 against the Raiders. Ideally, he upgrades to full participation tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e817-d968-a19b-f8f7f2f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Troy Franklin (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e81d-dc7a-af9b-efbf6ed30000</link>
      <description>Franklin has a chance to play this week, but hamstring injuries can be finicky. The young wide receiver was forced from last week’s Divisional Round win over the Bills after suffering the injury in-game. He earned zero targets before departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e81d-dc7a-af9b-efbf6ed30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed and interview with Steelers assistant general manager Andy Weidl for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e824-d35e-a1bf-ede6b1230000</link>
      <description>Weidl spent the last four seasons in his current role. He previously served as the Eagles’ vice president of player personnel and has worked in the NFL for 27 years. This is Weidl’s first interview in the current hiring cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e824-d35e-a1bf-ede6b1230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
