<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens (calf/knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c1-db57-afda-f7f310470000</link>
      <description>Pickens was limited during Monday’s practice but never appeared to be at risk of missing tomorrow’s game. He played through the pair of issues on a short week in Week 13 and went for 88 yards versus the Chiefs. In a shootout spot with the Lions, Pickens and CeeDee Lamb are both in the WR1 ranks for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c1-db57-afda-f7f310470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (ankle) will not play in Week 14 against the Lions</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c5-d90e-a9da-ffcf3a920000</link>
      <description>Guyton went down with a high-ankle sprain in Week 12 and missed the following game on Thanksgiving. Nathan Thomas will continue to start at left tackle this week. Though he will be a clear weak point for the Cowboys, that shouldn’t stop their offensive machine from rolling versus Detroit. Trevon Diggs was not activated from injured reserve and is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c5-d90e-a9da-ffcf3a920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers QB Justin Herbert (hand) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5cf-db57-afda-f7ffc9380000</link>
      <description>It should be noted, Wednesday’s session will not be logged on an official injury report. The Chargers’ official practice week is delayed by one day due to the team’s Monday Night Football game against the Eagles. Herbert’s absence today is unfortunate, but not necessarily indicative of his Week 14 availability. The team has yet to make that call. Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said Herbert could end up participating in a walk-through today, which is a plus. He also told reporters that he is optimistic Herbert will be able to play, though coaches almost universally lean toward optimism when talking about injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5cf-db57-afda-f7ffc9380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Omarion Hampton (ankle) is “on track and looking good” for Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5e3-d90e-a9da-ffef34ea0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh did not go as far as to say that Hampton will play this week, but it certainly sounds like he is on the right side of questionable. Fantasy managers, of course, will need to stay locked into this situation heading into the final week of the fantasy football regular season. Hampton would return for an RB2 ranking versus an Eagles defense that was just carved up by the Bears on the ground. If he is held out another week, Kimani Vidal would force his way to the top of the RB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5e3-d90e-a9da-ffef34ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring/knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5d6-d6c4-abfb-f7d7bc520000</link>
      <description>A hamstring strain kept Kincaid sidelined in Weeks 11-13. He resumed practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday last week. While he opened Week 14 practices with a limited designation as well, the team now lists him with both hamstring and knee injuries on the official report. Kincaid was plagued by a PCL sprain in his knee last season. Hopefully, this is a non-issue and he can retake the field on game day this weekend. Unfortunately, he may have suffered the knee injury during today’s practice, postponing his return. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5d6-d6c4-abfb-f7d7bc520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs (hip/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5f6-d90e-a9da-fffff0f60000</link>
      <description>Downs was on the injury report with a hip issue earlier in the year. The knee injury, however, is new. Downs had already taken a backseat to several Indy pass-catchers before suffering the knee injury. Even if he plays this week, it’s hard to see his role growing while he’s banged up. Downs is tumbling into the WR5 ranks with the fantasy playoffs on the horizon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5f6-d90e-a9da-fffff0f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 14 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5f8-d316-abff-f7fb59340000</link>
      <description>St. Brown did not practice at all this week, putting him on the wrong side of questionable heading into his team’s Thursday night game against the Cowboys. St. Brown is the type of player who does not need to practice in order to play, but he is clearly limited by the issue. He is worth starting, if active, though expectations must be lowered to some degree.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5f8-d316-abff-f7fb59340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions ruled out TE Brock Wright (neck) for Week 14 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c6-d90e-a9da-ffcf4f180000</link>
      <description>Fellow Lions TE Shane Zylstra (knee) is also out. With No. 1 TE Sam LaPorta (back) on injured reserve, TE Ross Dwelley will get the start. Dwelley warrants consideration in DFS tournaments, given the game’s expectedly high-scoring environment but he is just a touchdown-dependent TE2 in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c6-d90e-a9da-ffcf4f180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones (fibula) is practicing in full for Week 14 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5fc-d6c4-abfb-f7ff55110000</link>
      <description>Jones is playing through a fractured fibula and might be on the injury report for the remainder of the year. The good news is that he managed the issue well in Week 13, taking one sack without turning the ball over. A full practice today means that the injury won’t prevent him from playing in Week 14. With the Colts likely leaning on their ground game to protect Jones going forward, fantasy managers should treat him as a high-end QB2 as opposed to the locked-in QB1 they thought they had earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5fc-d6c4-abfb-f7ff55110000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
