<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs released DE Mike Danna.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</link>
      <description>Danna was selected by the Chiefs in the fifth-round of the 2020 NFL Draft. The veteran pass rusher totaled 21.5 sacks, 25 TFLs, and one interception in 87 games with the Chiefs and was a part of two Super Bowl-winning teams. The release of Danna, who will be 28 at the start of next season, saves the Chiefs $8.940 million against the cap. He should have plenty of suitors on the market as a pass-rushing specialist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released RB Antonio Gibson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</link>
      <description>Gibson suffered a torn ACL in Week 5 of last season and had one year remaining on the three-year deal he signed in 2024. The Patriots will save $3.140 million against the cap with the release of Gibson, who rushed for 25-106-1 in limited action last season. During his two years with the Patriots, Gibson rushed 145 times for 644 yards and two touchdowns while adding another 25-212-0 through the air. The soon-to-be 28-year-old back who had totaled 984 touches in his career should land elsewhere this upcoming season, but he’ll likely have to battle for playing time wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports “Packers backup QB Malik Willis and Alabama’s Ty Simpson are among the external QBs on the Browns’ radar.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c77-d990-a1de-ec7f40de0000</link>
      <description>With two Pro Bowl quarterbacks already on the roster in Shedeur Sanders and Deshaun Watson, it’s hard to imagine the Browns wanting to add even more to an already loaded QB room. That said, Willis, who is expected to be a highly coveted free agent this offseason, and Simpson could both be considered as options to add to the offense in Todd Monken’s first year at the helm. Watson remains a true question mark entering 2026. While he is under contract with the Browns through next season, the early return on his record-setting deal has been disappointing. Watson is returning from a torn Achilles he suffered in 2024 and has thrown for just 3,365-19-12 in the 19 games he’s played in for them over three years. When it comes to Sanders, the rookie QB is coming off a brutal first season that featured more lows than highs, and as a fifth-round pick, he shouldn’t be viewed as a lock to be handed any starting job. The Browns will have plenty of time to discuss all options at the NFL Scouting Combine this week, but Willis and Simpson will be two names to watch as free agency and draft talk continues to ramp up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c77-d990-a1de-ec7f40de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders re-signed OG Andrew Wylie to a two-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c88-d990-a1de-ecce70390000</link>
      <description>One of the few holdovers from the Ron Rivera era, Wylie appeared in 16 games for the Commanders last season while also making five starts. The veteran lineman has ample experience at both tackle and guard and makes for a solid depth piece along the offensive line. Wylie was slated to hit free agency this offseason but will now be under contract for the Commanders through 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c88-d990-a1de-ecce70390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Bozeman retired from the NFL after eight seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c8d-d629-a1bc-bc9d35ad0000</link>
      <description>Bozeman started his career as a sixth-round pick with the Ravens back in 2018 and also spent time with the Panthers and Chargers. The eight-year vet started 110 of the 129 games he appeared in during his career, and started all 156 games at center for the Chargers last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c8d-d629-a1bc-bc9d35ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos met with Mike Zimmer last week regarding a “senior coaching position.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</link>
      <description>The former Falcons, Bengals, and Cowboys defensive coordinator and Vikings head coach was not asked to return to the Cowboys following the 2024 season and spent the 2025 season away from coaching. The Broncos are now reportedly interested in his services in a “senior coaching position” capacity, although the extent of the position remain a mystery. The team retained defensive coordinator Vance Joseph through the 2026 hiring cycle. Stay tuned in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired former Titans GM Jon Robinson as their next Senior Personnel Executive.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</link>
      <description>Robinson will work hand-in-hand with general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan as the Dolphins careen towards a self inflicted rebuild, with the former likely playing a massive role in the direction of the franchise in the coming NFL Draft. The first order of business for the incoming front office will be finding their next quarterback after it was made evident that Tua Tagovailoa will no longer be the face of franchise moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lions will play a regular season game in Munich, Germany in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8fd1-d89c-a1be-afdf25c70000</link>
      <description>This will be the sixth regular season NFL game played in Germany as part of the league’s international series. It will feature Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown, a German-American and the centerpiece of the Detroit offense. Last year St. Brown was fifth in receiving yards and fourth in wideout receptions. The Lions will be looking to bounce back from a relatively disappointing 2025 campaign after losing OC Ben Johnson to the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8fd1-d89c-a1be-afdf25c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles general manager Howie Roseman did not dismiss the possibility of trading A.J. Brown this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-902a-d57c-a1dd-942abbd40000</link>
      <description>Roseman, who offered an “emphatic no” to teams looking to acquire Brown at the trade deadline in 2025, was more circumspect when asked this week if the Eagles would listen to trade offers for the superstar wideout, who appeared miserable in a lifeless Philadelphia offense last season. “We’re always listening,” Roseman said. “I don’t think you can go into any conversation with anyone and just shoot things down without hearing what they have to say — because you never know. ... You never know on any player. If someone’s going to give you something you didn’t anticipate and you won’t even have the conversation, I don’t think you’re necessarily doing your job, really servicing the team that you’re with.” Brown, 28, who is signed through the 2029 season, could end up elsewhere this offseason if a receiver-needy team is willing to part with major draft capital to acquire him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-902a-d57c-a1dd-942abbd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons general manager Ian Cunningham said the team will release QB Kirk Cousins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</link>
      <description>The move will be made on the first day of the 2026 NFL calendar year, according to Cunningham. This was all but confirmed last month when Cousins and the Falcons agreed to a contract modification that guaranteed he’d be gone ahead of the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
