<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (shoulder) will not return in Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-911f-d6e9-af9d-9b9f976d0000</link>
      <description>Austin went down in the second half with a shoulder injury and was initially listed as questionable to return. He was later spotted exiting the stadium in an ambulance with his shoulder in a sling. The Steelers get their bye next week, but Austin’s injury is likely much more serious than a one-week absence. Roman Wilson and Ben Skowronek will see an uptick in work until Austin returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-911f-d6e9-af9d-9b9f976d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz completed 30-of-46 passes for 350 yards, two touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Vikings’ 24-21, Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9100-d6e9-af9d-9b90216c0000</link>
      <description>Wentz struggled mightily through three quarters. The Vikings entered the game with a banged-up offensive line and then lost two more starters before the fourth quarter, putting Wentz under constant pressure. With a comfortable lead, the Steelers showed Wentz some soft coverage late in the game and he made them pay with a pair of touchdown passes in the final frame. Mike Tomlin also made a bewildering fourth-down decision to give Wentz the ball back with a minute on the clock. The journeyman passer completed a handful of short passes to Zavier Scott but otherwise seemed primarily focused on turning the ball over. He had two passes nearly intercepted and the Vikings failed to even threaten a long field goal try to tie the game. Despite the poor showing, Wentz should draw the start again next week versus the Browns while J.J. McCarthy nurses his ankle injury. He will remain a volume-based QB2 for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9100-d6e9-af9d-9b90216c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed 19 times for 99 yards and two touchdowns in the Steelers’ Week 4 win over the Vikings, adding six catches for 35 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-912b-deb6-a7fd-d3ff52df0000</link>
      <description>Jaylen Warren was a surprise inactive for Pittsburgh, much to the dismay of slumbering fantasy managers. Gainwell drew the start and didn’t disappoint, gashing the Vikings for 5.2 yards a carry with a healthy role through the air as well. He led the Steelers in targets and only ceded six carries to rookie running back Kaleb Johnson. The Steelers get their bye next week as they travel back from Dublin, Ireland, so it may have been a one-and-done start for Gainwell. Still, his performance could have earned him more touches even if Warren is back in action for Week 6. Gainwell should be rostered through his bye week in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-912b-deb6-a7fd-d3ff52df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught all five of his targets for 126 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 4 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9145-deb6-a7fd-d3dfc74d0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf target volume remained modest, but his big-play potential continued to save him from Pittsburgh’s low-wattage passing attack. Metcalf turned a shallow crossing route into an 80-yard touchdown in the second quarter. He simply turned on the jets and blew by nearly every member of the Vikings’ secondary en route to his third touchdown of the season. Metcalf will be asked to do even more going forward with Calvin Austin likely out because of a shoulder injury that put him in an ambulance today. Metcalf will remain a boom/bust WR2 when the Steelers return from their upcoming bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9145-deb6-a7fd-d3dfc74d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 10-of-11 targets for 126 yards in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9153-d6e9-af9d-9bd3b57c0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson was on fire in the first half, but the Vikings’ offensive lineman dropped like flies in this game. Carson Wentz, in turn, resorted to check-downs and sacks for much of the second half. Even when he got things going in a frantic fourth-quarter comeback bid, Jefferson was rarely involved. He caught two passes for 29 yards in the entire second half. Jefferson also had a likely long touchdown cut short when he slipped on the Croke Park field during a long catch-and-run in the first half. The Vikings are going from Ireland to England in Week 5 to face the Browns. Per usual, Jefferson will be a high-end WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9153-d6e9-af9d-9bd3b57c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt was forced from Los Angeles’ Week 4 game against the Giants with a right ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-915f-dca3-a9fb-bddf679d0000</link>
      <description>A poor development, to put it mildly, for a team already missing Rashawn Slater. Austin Deculus is now in the game on Justin Herbert’s blindside. Rolled up in the first quarter, Alt was in a heap of pain before being carted to the locker room. Alt has never missed extended time with injury during his short professional career, but he is almost certainly done for the day and “week to week” in a best-case scenario. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-915f-dca3-a9fb-bddf679d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 4-of-8 targets for 114 yards in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-915b-deb6-a7fd-d3dfd51f0000</link>
      <description>It was Addison’s first game back from his three-week suspension and it didn’t take long for him to get in a groove. After a relatively quiet three quarters, Addison hit the big one late in the fourth. He got behind the Steelers’ defense completely uncovered and fielded a moon-ball from Carson Wentz for an 81-yard gain. Addison had to stop and wait for the ball to reach him and then turned on the jets, only for Steelers linebacker Payton Wilson to track him down inside the five-yard line. Minnesota scored a few plays later. Addison is back to his high-variance WR3 ways heading into Week 5 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-915b-deb6-a7fd-d3dfd51f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 18-of-22 passes for 200 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ 24-21, Week 4 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-916a-dca3-a9fb-bdfb39a10000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was dialed in versus Minnesota, averaging 9.1 yards per attempt while completing 82 percent of his passes. The bulk of his fantasy output came on an 80-yard touchdown throw to DK Metcalf. Rodgers hit Metcalf on a mid-range crossing route and Metcalf sprinted past the entire Minnesota secondary for Rodgers’ 91st career completion of 50 or more yards. He now holds the record alone in that totally real stat. Rodgers still has some juice as a real-life passer, but his fantasy outlook is severely capped as an immobile, low-volume option. He will be stuck at the back of the QB2 ranks when the Steelers return to face the Browns after their Week 5 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-916a-dca3-a9fb-bdfb39a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 2-of-3 targets for six yards in the Steelers’ Week 4 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9175-d6e9-af9d-9bf57e880000</link>
      <description>Smith’s production has steadily declined over the first month of the season. He caught five passes in Week 1 and that number has fallen in every subsequent game. Darnell Washington led the team’s tight ends with three catches. With a bye week on tap for the Steelers, fantasy managers don’t need to hang on to Smith any longer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9175-d6e9-af9d-9bf57e880000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
