<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) will not play in Week 11 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8364-d713-ad9e-ef74df2b0000</link>
      <description>Godwin’s first practice of the week was considered a walk-through, which should have served as a clear indicator that he would be a long shot to play in Week 11. The veteran receiver hasn’t played since Week 5 after dealing with pain in the leg that ended his 2024 season, but could have a chance to suit up in Week 12 against the Rams with another week of practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8364-d713-ad9e-ef74df2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears designated CB Jaylon Johnson (core) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-836e-d1e7-a1fa-dbee03a20000</link>
      <description>The Bears will have 21 days to activate Johnson from injured reserve, but this is a very encouraging sign for a defense in need of help in the secondary. Johnson hasn’t played since the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Lions, but would be on track to return no later than December 7th when the Bears visit the Packers in Week 14. One of the top corners in the league, Johnson totaled 53 tackles, eight pass breakups, and two intereceptions for the Bears last season and has been named to the Pro Bowl in back-to-back years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-836e-d1e7-a1fa-dbee03a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-837a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaf1aa0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle was upgraded from a limited participant to a full participant in Friday’s practice and was removed from the injury report as a result. The Panthers’ RB1 gets a juicy matchup against a Falcons run defense that ranks in the bottom five in total rushing yards allowed and yards per carry this season. Dowdle is firmly in the RB1 ranks for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-837a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaf1aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interim HC Mike Kafka said Jaxson Dart is “on track” with where he should be in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8381-d673-a39e-a791d1120000</link>
      <description>Dart has already been ruled out for Week 11’s game against the Packers, but the rookie was on the practice field Friday and should have a chance to be cleared early next week. Jameis Winston will draw the start in Dart’s absence this week, but this is great news for Dart before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8381-d673-a39e-a791d1120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 11 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-838d-d1e7-a1fa-dbefd8b80000</link>
      <description>He worked limited sessions all week and is likely on the optimistic side of questionable. This was a new listing on Wednesday, implying that it was something that came up during Week 10’s game that he was able to play through to the tune of 10 targets. Johnston will be a WR3 against a Jaguars defense that allowed 29 offensive points to Davis Mills somehow last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-838d-d1e7-a1fa-dbefd8b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (ankle) is not on Los Angeles’ final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8390-d45b-affe-d79654820000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a plugged in WR2 against the Jaguars after being limited in the early sessions of this week. McConkey hasn’t been listed with this ankle injury before, but apparently it isn’t all that serious.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8390-d45b-affe-d79654820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden II (quad) is not on Los Angeles’ final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8391-d713-ad9e-efd5e6ae0000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a dialed-in TE1 against the Jaguars in Week 11. Gadsden left Week 10’s game with the injury and had an MRI, but was practicing in full by Thursday. It looks like the Chargers have avoided anything serious happening to their 22-year-old breakout tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8391-d713-ad9e-efd5e6ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets coach Aaron Glenn said “I’m evaluating everything” when asked if he was considering a quarterback change.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-839a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaab120000</link>
      <description>It should be noted that when coaches go to the “evaluating” line this year, the incumbent quarterback tends to wind up on the bench. Frankly, the Jets have stuck with Justin Fields longer than we expected this year despite his struggles in the passing offense. Tyrod Taylor would be the name to watch here — though he’s old enough that he can’t realistically be expected to start without getting dinged up at this point. Fields-reliant managers will want to stay tuned for the next 30 updates about the situation in which Glenn continues to talk without saying anything.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-839a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaab120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Lamar Jackson (knee) will start in Week 11 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8397-d1e7-a1fa-dbff326b0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh didn’t beat around the bush on Friday when asked about Jackson’s availability, acknowledging that his QB1 will be good to go in Week 11’s matchup against the Browns. Lamar was on the practice field each of the final two days to close out the week after being a DNP on Wednesday. Jackson will be in his typical QB1 slot for fantasy managers against the lowly Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8397-d1e7-a1fa-dbff326b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he thinks Garrett Wilson (knee) will return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83a1-d1e7-a1fa-dbeb178e0000</link>
      <description>Glenn also said that it’s up to the doctors whether or not Wilson, who was placed on IR earlier this week, will return. The star receiver is required to miss at least three more games before a return can even be considered, but it wouldn’t be surprising if the team opted to play it cautious with him in what is already a lost season. The earliest Wilson can return is Week 15 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83a1-d1e7-a1fa-dbeb178e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
