<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said he expects OL Austin Jackson (toe) to miss Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-344d-d93a-abbb-7d5f3e400000</link>
      <description>Miami will likely be without Jackson and RG James Daniels, who was placed on injured reserve this week with a pectoral injury. It’s a major blow to the Dolphins offense, which struggled mightily in their Week 1 blowout loss to Daniel Jones and the Colts. Tua Tagovailoa in Week 1 was pressured on just 22 percent of his drop backs, the third lowest rate in the league. The team’s quick-passing offense should prevent Tagovailoa from facing much pressure this week against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-344d-d93a-abbb-7d5f3e400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers (back) was limited during Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3485-db7b-a5dd-b4851e920000</link>
      <description>As long as Nabers practices in full by week’s end, he should be OK for the Giants’ Week 2 game against the Cowboys. Nabers went for five grabs and 71 scoreless yards in Week 1 against the Commanders, leading the team in targets and air yards. Against a Dallas offense that should put up plenty of points this week, Nabers could benefit from a pass-heavy game script. He should be locked into all fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3485-db7b-a5dd-b4851e920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart will remain the QB2 in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3488-d332-a1fd-b6be92280000</link>
      <description>Daboll was once again effusive with praise for the rookie quarterback, complimenting his work ethic and understand of the team’s offense. “We’ll continue to work with him,” Daboll said. The Giants are almost assuredly prepping Dart to get under center as the team’s starter in the coming weeks following Russell Wilson’s disastrous outing in Week 1 against Washington. Only two QBs were more inaccurate than Wilson last week. Dart should be rostered in all superflex formats. He could have a shot at playing time this week against the Cowboys if things go south for Russ in a hurry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3488-d332-a1fd-b6be92280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said he expected Drake London (shoulder) to play in Week 2 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3496-d332-a1fd-b6b6385f0000</link>
      <description>London left the Falcons’ Week 1 loss to the Bucs in the fourth quarter and did not return after being listed as questionable. The contest was nearly over when London went down. It’s possible he could have made his way onto the field had Atlanta forced overtime. Morris mentioned how tough London is and said he also expects him to practice on Wednesday. London earned a massive 36 percent target share in Week 1, good for 15 looks in total. Likely facing negative game script versus the Vikings on the road, he should get peppered with opportunities once again, keeping him in the WR1 ranks despite the minor injury scare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3496-d332-a1fd-b6b6385f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said Darnell Mooney (shoulder) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-349a-d332-a1fd-b6be46b70000</link>
      <description>Mooney also practiced in a limited capacity three times last week but did not suit up. He was listed as questionable and was spotted working out during warmups. The team ultimately held him out when they declared their inactives. Mooney appears to be nearing a return, but it’s too soon to say he is guaranteed to play in Week 2. Atlanta desperately needs a second receiver to earn targets opposite Drake London. Mooney is a capable No. 2 receiver and will have no issues earning looks once healthy, putting him in the WR3/4 ranks when he next takes the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-349a-d332-a1fd-b6be46b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will not undergo surgery at this time and is not a candidate for injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34a7-d93a-abbb-7dff214a0000</link>
      <description>Reid noted that Worthy won’t practice on Wednesday, but it’s still as good of an update as you could hope for after seeing the hit he took from Travis Kelce in the Chiefs’ 2025 opener. Kelce and Worthy collided on a crossing route, sending the 165-pound receiver to the turf and ending his night on the first drive. Reid called him day-to-day after the game. It would be a surprise to see Worthy play in Week 2 against the Eagles, but the good news is that this isn’t a long-term issue. The Chiefs would have put Worthy on injured reserve if they were certain he would miss at least four games. For now, Hollywood Brown will be tasked with operating as Kansas City’s No. 1 receiver. Brown saw 16 targets last week, turning them into 10 catches for 99 yards. The target volume alone makes Brown a WR2 for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34a7-d93a-abbb-7dff214a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said it would be “a stretch” for WR Jalen Royals (knee) to play in Week 2 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34ad-d332-a1fd-b6bfa2330000</link>
      <description>The fourth-round rookie is dealing with knee tendinitis that held him out of Kansas City’s Week 1 opener. He didn’t practice at all last week and isn’t expected to do so today. It sounds like Royals may need a few more weeks to get past the knee issue, leaving the Chiefs with Tyquan Thornton and JuJu Smith-Schuster as the second and third receivers until one of Xavier Worthy or Rashee Rice returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34ad-d332-a1fd-b6bfa2330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said Travis Hunter will se a “likely uptick” in defensive snaps in Week 2 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b2-db7b-a5dd-b4b6c56a0000</link>
      <description>Hunter only played six snaps on defense in his NFL debut. Coen said he didn’t expect to use Hunter a ton on defense in Week 1 and it was always the plan to ramp up his defensive snaps as the season progressed. He also noted that the Bengals, Jacksonville’s Week 2 opponent, have a pair of elite wide receivers, further illustrating the team’s need for Hunter to play corner on Sunday. On offense, Hunter was targeted eight times and caught six of his looks, though he only managed 33 yards. Assuming an increase in defensive snaps doesn’t hamstring his role on offense, Hunter is a PPR WR3 for a potential shootout with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b2-db7b-a5dd-b4b6c56a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said he doesn’t believe CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) will practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b8-db7b-a5dd-b4bc382c0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez did not practice at all last week and was ruled out for Week 1 on Friday. It looks like he is headed for a similar fate in Week 2 as the Patriots look to get on track versus the Dolphins. The good news for New England is that the Dolphins looked pitiful in Week 1, failing to put a single point on the board until late in the fourth quarter when the game was already decided. On the other side of the coin, it’s now or never for Tua Tagovailoa and the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34b8-db7b-a5dd-b4bc382c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34bc-d332-a1fd-b6be2f2d0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens haven’t officially released their first injury report of the week yet, but Likely was spotted working off to the side with trainers during the open portion of practice. That will go down as a DNP barring a surprise turn of events. Fullback Patrick Ricard was held out of practice entirely. Likely suffered a small fracture in his foot early in training camp and has been out ever since. The fact that Baltimore didn’t place him on injured reserve suggests it isn’t a long-term issue, but a DNP to open the week is a strong signal that Likely won’t suit up for Week 2. Mark Andrews managed a lone target in Week 1 versus the Bills. Even with Likely sidelined, Andrews appears to have little fantasy value left in the tank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34bc-d332-a1fd-b6be2f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
