<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared RB Bhayshul Tuten, DE Danny Striggow, OL Chuma Edoga, TE Hunter Long, DT Maason Smith inactive for Week 16 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427b-d35e-a1bf-47fb24a90000</link>
      <description>Tuten is expected to miss the rest of the season after undergoing finger surgery this week. Travis Etienne should see an increase in snaps and touches with Tuten sidelined. LeQuint Allen Jr. would presumably function as the team’s RB2 behind Etienne, and could find himself in the lead back role if Etienne were to miss time in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427b-d35e-a1bf-47fb24a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) left Week 16’s game against the Giants and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427c-d087-addf-f3fc2d7b0000</link>
      <description>Kelly previously spent time on injured reserve this year because of a concussion. He has a lengthy history of head injuries. We suspect the team will shut him down for the year after his latest concussion. Michael Jurgens is in at center for Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427c-d087-addf-f3fc2d7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Zamir White, QB Aidan O’Connell, CB Darnay Holmes, TE Ian Thomas and DT Brodric Martin inactive for Las Vegas’ Week 16 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4279-d087-addf-f3f96b560000</link>
      <description>Jordan Meredith (ankle) was questionable but is active for the Raiders. They had nobody else with a status this week, so these are all healthy scratches. White has not been active since October 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4279-d087-addf-f3f96b560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared C Graham Glasgow, OL Kayode Awosika, OL Trystan Colon, OL Tyler Lacy, WR Dominic Lovett, S Jalen Mills and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Week 16 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427e-d087-addf-f3fe53b70000</link>
      <description>The good news for Jared Goff and Lions fans is that fellow offensive linemen Taylor Decker and Christian Mahogany are active. Decker was listed as questionable with a shoulder issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427e-d087-addf-f3fe53b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared RB Woody Marks (ankle) inactive for Houston’s Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d087-addf-f3f06e880000</link>
      <description>Jawhar Jordan and Nick Chubb will split what would appear to be fantasy-valuable carries against the Raiders. Derek Stingley (oblique) is playing off a questionable tag. Also inactive for the Texans are LB Azeez Al-Shaair (ankle/knee), WR Braxton Berrios, QB Graham Mertz, CB Ameer Speed and T Jarrett Kingston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d087-addf-f3f06e880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared EDGE Nick Herbig, WR Roman Wilson, QB Will Howard, CB James Pierre, OG Isaac Seumalo, OLB T.J. Watt, and DL Logan Lee inactive for Week 16 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d35e-a1bf-47c238c10000</link>
      <description>Watt remains out because of a partially collapsed lung. Herbig was listed as doubtful because of a hamstring issue. The Lions should have an easy time picking apart the Steelers today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d35e-a1bf-47c238c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared LB Justin Strnad, QB Sam Ehlinger, RB Cody Schrader, CB Reese Taylor, OT Geron Christian, DL Jordan Jackson, and DL Sai’vion Jones inactive for Week 16 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d35e-a1bf-47c297a50000</link>
      <description>The Broncos come into this game with a few concerning defensive injuries, including Strnad. It could make things a little easier for the Jaguars offense in a critical AFC showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4280-d35e-a1bf-47c297a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) left Los Angeles’ Week 16 game against the Cowboys and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-429b-da28-afbb-c6ffd30c0000</link>
      <description>He was down on the field for an extended period of time, walked off with the trainers, and was declared questionable after a few minutes. Hassan Haskins took over as Omarion Hampton’s change-up back. Vidal had five carries for 11 yards before leaving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-429b-da28-afbb-c6ffd30c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said QB Marcus Mariota (quad/hand) is considered day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4274-d35e-a1bf-47f614560000</link>
      <description>Mariota reportedly “had stitches on his right hand and is also dealing with a quad injury,” following the Commanders’ Saturday game against the Eagles. Quinn adds that the team “would not consider playing” QB Jayden Daniels (elbow) if Mariota cannot play in Week 17 against the Cowboys. Mariota is backed up by QB Josh Johnson, who would presumably start in his stead if he is unable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4274-d35e-a1bf-47f614560000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
