<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 22 times for 67 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens, adding 32 yards on five receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a3-d1b3-a5dd-75f37e860000</link>
      <description>Gibbs handled 22 carries and six targets to the 13 opportunities of David Montgomery, but it was the latter back that stole the show while amassing 151 yards and two scores on the ground. Even so, the 28 opportunities were the most in a game in which Montgomery also was on the field during Gibbs’ three-year NFL career - a solid sign for what is to come for the talented back. Gibbs could find the sledding difficult again in Week 4 against a Cleveland defense leading the league in yards allowed per carry through three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a3-d1b3-a5dd-75f37e860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 7-of-8 targets for 77 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a7-dfde-a1bd-7eaf2a2e0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown remained an integral part of the offense on a night quarterback Jared Goff attempted just 28 passes. He also contributed to a touchdown run by Jahmyr Gibbs on a fourth down trick play to start the fourth quarter, during which he took a handoff from Jared Goff before pitching the football to Gibbs on the perimeter. He would also come up big late in the game when he caught a 20-yard dime from Goff on fourth-and-two while up by seven points. St. Brown can continue to be counted on as a weekly WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a7-dfde-a1bd-7eaf2a2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 2-of-3 targets for 43 yards in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ab-dfde-a1bd-7eaf63430000</link>
      <description>Williams notched both of his receptions on the first drive of the game before disappearing from the game plan as Jahmyr Gibbs and David Montgomery dominated the work. He now has just 12 targets through three games, laying fantasy duds in all but his Week 2, 2-108-1 receiving line on four targets. Fantasy managers should remain patient with the talented fifth-year receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ab-dfde-a1bd-7eaf63430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught all four targets for 33 yards in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ae-dfde-a1bd-7eafeb980000</link>
      <description>LaPorta did most of his damage on third downs to move the chains, beating both man and zone coverage in key situations for the Lions. Quarterback Jared Goff attempted only 28 passes on a night Jahmyr Gibbs and David Montgomery stole the show, meaning fantasy managers will want to stay patient with the young tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ae-dfde-a1bd-7eafeb980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson completed 21-of-27 passes for 288 yards and three touchdowns in the Ravens’ 38-30, Week 3 loss to the Lions, adding 35 yards on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b1-d93f-ad9d-7ef720760000</link>
      <description>The two-time MVP was sacked seven times while the Ravens managed only 54 offensive plays. The low play volume was largely caused by two long touchdown drives by the Lions, one for 96 yards and one for 98 yards, which combined to take 14:29 off the clock. Jackson got tight end Mark Andrews back on the fantasy radar with two touchdown passes to the veteran tight end, although the frustrating loss drops the Ravens to 1-2 ahead of a meeting with the Chiefs in Week 4. This is one that can’t be attributed to the perennial MVP candidate’s play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b1-d93f-ad9d-7ef720760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 12 times for 50 yards, one touchdown, and one fumble in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b6-d1b3-a5dd-75f794290000</link>
      <description>Henry lost a fumble deep in his own territory half way through the fourth quarter with the team down by four points, gifting the Lions a comfortable lead that they would not relinquish. His night started off hot as he would score from 28 yards out on the team’s first possession, but he managed just 22 yards on his other 11 carries against a stout Detroit defensive front. Things don’t get easier for the King when the Ravens travel to Kansas City to face the Chiefs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b6-d1b3-a5dd-75f794290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught all six targets for 91 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ba-dfde-a1bd-7ebf587e0000</link>
      <description>Andrews ranked second in targets and caught two of the three passing touchdowns from Lamar Jackson, resurrecting his fantasy season in the process. The Ravens managed only 54 offensive plays on a night the Lions dominated the time of possession battle, which helps to explain the modest 27 pass attempts from Jackson. The veteran tight end gets another difficult matchup against Steve Spagnuolo’s Chiefs defense in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ba-dfde-a1bd-7ebf587e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 5-of-7 targets for 61 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74bc-d6a5-adff-f6fdc5b40000</link>
      <description>Bateman knotted the game at 14 at the end of the second quarter from three yards out, adding the bulk of his yardage in the fourth quarter as the Ravens played from behind. His seven targets marked a season high, keeping him firmly in touchdown-or-bust territory for fantasy managers as bye weeks creep closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74bc-d6a5-adff-f6fdc5b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 2-of-3 targets for13 yards in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74c6-d93f-ad9d-7ec731e20000</link>
      <description>Flowers was never able to get anything going against an aggressive Lions defense, managing catches of just seven and six yards. The Ravens weren’t able to attack down the field in the face of mounting pressure from the Detroit defensive front, evidenced by the seven sacks taken by quarterback Lamar Jackson. The three targets were a far cry from the 10 targets per game he averaged in the first two games of the season, sending fantasy managers a sharp reminder of his boom or bust nature in this offense. He gets another difficult matchup against the Chiefs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74c6-d93f-ad9d-7ec731e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) will miss 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f47-dfde-a1bd-7fcfcad30000</link>
      <description>Tracy went down with an apparently serious shoulder injury during Sunday night’s loss to Kansas City and did not return to the game. Now he could miss up to a month as he recovers from a dislocated shoulder. Cam Skattebo, who had 16 touches for 121 yards and a touchdown against the Chiefs, will function as the Giants’ lead back. Devin Singletary will likely take on RB2 duties, and could be thrust into the RB1 role should Skattebo get dinged up while Tracy is sidelined. Skattebo’s pass game involvement will make him a weekly top-15 fantasy play, starting this week against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f47-dfde-a1bd-7fcfcad30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
