<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ba-d45b-affe-77beffb00000</link>
      <description>McConkey appeared on Wednesday’s injury report with a calf issue, yet managed to practice in a limited capacity. Although limited sessions early in the week are positive, new soft tissue listings are concerning. At this point, McConkey should be considered truly questionable to play in Week 9 against a Titans defense that notably just traded away starting slot CB Roger McCreary. His practice participation on Friday is critical.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ba-d45b-affe-77beffb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36d3-d1e7-a1fa-7efbcee90000</link>
      <description>Stevenson is now on the wrong side of questionable for the Patriots’ Week 9 game against the Falcons. Theoretically, rookie RB TreVeyon Henderson would be in line to start if Stevenson cannot play, though RB Terrell Jennings would likely rotate in. Hopefully, the coaching staff will provide clarity on Friday. ESPN’s Mike Reiss recently reported that the Patriots are likely to target a running back via the trade market before the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline. Stevenson’s health could be a factor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36d3-d1e7-a1fa-7efbcee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ede91db0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots’ No. 1 pass catcher should be good to go for his team’s Week 9 game against the Falcons. His results have been a bit volatile this season, but Diggs can be started as a low-end WR2 in this one, particularly with the Falcons’ defense dealing with multiple injuries. He has finished as the WR24 and WR35 in half-PPR scoring over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ede91db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36f5-d673-a39e-b6f5c9fe0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers are unlikely to let Pearsall play without practicing in consecutive sessions, so even if he returns to practice tomorrow, he could only be considered questionable at best. Fantasy managers should expect him to miss yet another game, this time against the Giants. The 49ers face the Rams in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36f5-d673-a39e-b6f5c9fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Pat Freiermuth (quad) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3701-d673-a39e-b79179610000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth suffered a bruised quad on a low hit in Week 8. His return to practice on Thursday indicates he will be on the field for the Steeles’ Week 9 game against the Colts, though he can only be started as a low-end TE2, running routes in his team’s three-player tight end rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3701-d673-a39e-b79179610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-370d-d713-ad9e-7f5da0500000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ No. 3 wide receiver should be considered doubtful to play in Week 9 against the Texans at this point. Mims has been sidelined through each of the first two practices this week, unfortunately. Mims’ expected absence gives No. 2 WR Troy Franklin a chance to solidify his status as a consistent contributor in head coach Sean Payton’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-370d-d713-ad9e-7f5da0500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (calf) was added to the injury report as a limited participant on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3710-d45b-affe-779642be0000</link>
      <description>Brutal. Mid-week additions to the injury report are never a good sign. Marks is coming off consecutive RB2 finishes while out-touching Nick Chubb 28-25 during that span. Marks has not yet been ruled out, but the events suggest he suffered the injury in practice today, putting him in the questionable camp at best. The Texans face the Broncos this week, so although Chubb will likely handle a sizable workload if Marks is sidelined, it could be tough sledding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3710-d45b-affe-779642be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3710-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa97c70000</link>
      <description>Kirk is now on track to return for Week 9 against the Broncos, while backup slot receiver Braxton Berrios (chest) remains limited. Kirk’s expected return jeopardizes rookie slot WR Jaylin Noel’s access to the starting slot role. Noel has played very well in recent weeks, but Texans coaches could choose to keep the veteran installed as the starter. Friday’s injury report is worth monitoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3710-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa97c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tony Pollard (neck) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3718-d45b-affe-779efe950000</link>
      <description>Pollard should be active for the Titans’ Week 9 game against the Chargers, though No. 2 RB Tyjae Spears could end up out-touching him anyway. Spears has played more efficiently than Pollard as of late, and the 28-year-old veteran is still technically nursing some sort of neck issue. Pollard is just a shaky RB3 here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3718-d45b-affe-779efe950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
