<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts EDGE Samson Ebukam has been ruled out in Week 7 against the Chargers after suffering a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe36-df81-ab9b-fef7413c0000</link>
      <description>Ebukam got hurt in the second half. He attempted to walk it off, momentarily, but was visibly limping. He sat down on the field and awaited assistance from the Colts’ training staff. He was ruled out shortly thereafter. Colts fellow EDGE Tyquan Lewis (groin) is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe36-df81-ab9b-fef7413c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 3-of-3 targets for 17 yards in the Patriots’ Week 7 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe9e-df81-ab9b-fedf149f0000</link>
      <description>As suspected, Douglas’ 71-yard Week 6 outburst is looking like an outlier, as today was the sixth time in seven games be finished below 20 yards receiving. Failing to even enter the WR5 mix, Douglas will be mostly out of sight, out of mind for Week 8 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe9e-df81-ab9b-fedf149f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 4-of-5 targets for 36 yards in the Titans’ Week 7 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea2-da18-a39b-feb390110000</link>
      <description>Helm essentially matched his career-best line from two weeks ago, kicking his season-best yardage total up to 36 from 34. The Titans have followed through on their word of getting Helm more involved, but Chig Okonkwo is still seeing targets, while this is a terrible overall offensive environment. That has Helm struggling for TE2 value heading into Week 8 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea2-da18-a39b-feb390110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Jayden Daniels (hamstring) left Washington’s Week 7 game against the Cowboys and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe8c-df81-ab9b-fecf5c060000</link>
      <description>Daniels grabbed awkwardly at his hamstring after a fourth-down sack in the third quarter, immediately leaving with a posse of trainers to the blue medical tent. He gave a thumbs up to his mother in the crowd (per FOX’s Erin Andrews) and jogged to the locker room. Marcus Mariota took over at quarterback for the Commanders. More updates to come, but this looked very concerning on the field and slightly better once Daniels was in the tent. He had completed 12-of-22 passes for 156 yards and a touchdown, adding a rushing touchdown on the ground along with 35 yards, before leaving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe8c-df81-ab9b-fecf5c060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo was held without a catch on two targets in Tennessee’s Week 7 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea5-d99b-a1dd-fead8ee60000</link>
      <description>This was Okonkwo’s first catch-less game of the year, while his two targets were a new season low. This, as Gunnar Helm had a modest career day with 4/36. The down effort coming in Mike McCoy’s first game as interim head coach is another not-great sign for the veteran seam stretcher. Okonkwo will probably find himself outside the top 24 for Week 8 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea5-d99b-a1dd-fead8ee60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 2-of-5 targets for 29 yards in the Titans’ Week 7 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea8-d651-a9df-ffbde35e0000</link>
      <description>This is Ayomanor’s standard statline of late. The difference today was, it came with Calvin Ridley (hamstring) on the shelf and fellow rookie Chimere Dike getting more involved. Ayomanor still has some long-term upside, but he doesn’t seem particularly close to becoming an every-week WR4 as Cam Ward continues to struggle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fea8-d651-a9df-ffbde35e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Jefferson caught 4-of-4 targets for 41 yards in the Titans’ Week 7 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feab-d651-a9df-ffbfb2490000</link>
      <description>Veteran journeyman Jefferson now has back-to-back 4/40 efforts, but we doubt that is his floor, while it could ultimately prove to not even be his ceiling. This rebuilding, coach-swapping team is trying to figure out what it has in a host of young players, and Jefferson is mostly out there as a routes shock absorber who can provide a big target when needed. He’s fine to leave on the wire in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feab-d651-a9df-ffbfb2490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney is active for Week 7 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feac-df81-ab9b-feef63e80000</link>
      <description>Mooney makes his return to the game day lineup after missing Week 6 with a hamstring injury, with the team’s Week 5 bye week providing enough time to only miss one contest. Expect the veteran to slot back into a featured role in the offense. Inactive for the Falcons are EDGE Jalon Walker, CB Billy Bowman Jr, WR Ray Ray McCloud, OL Jack Nelson, and DL LaCale London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feac-df81-ab9b-feef63e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 5-of-8 targets for 30 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 7 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feae-d651-a9df-ffbfad700000</link>
      <description>The catches, targets and yards were all new season highs for second-year pro Washington, who you could argue was a “rare bright spot” amidst a three-INT Tua Tagovailoa implosion. 30 yards, of course, is nothing to call home about, while any modest Washington floor would be accompanied by very little ceiling right now. He’s a last-gasp WR5 with limited spiked week potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feae-d651-a9df-ffbfad700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared QB Brock Purdy, WR Ricky Pearsall, DL Yetur Gross-Matos, WR Jordan Watkins, OL Drew Moss, CB Upton Stout, and RB Jordan James inactive for Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feaf-da18-a39b-febf110a0000</link>
      <description>Purdy will miss his third consecutive game and fifth game of the season while Pearsall will miss his third straight as well. Mac Jones will start under center for a team fighting through multiple key injuries this season. The 49ers do get back tight end George Kittle after the veteran was activated from injured reserve Friday. Expect Kendrick Bourne to continue to be relied on with Pearsall out and Jauan Jennings gutting out multiple injuries of his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feaf-da18-a39b-febf110a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
