<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c0-d95b-addb-eec69e540000</link>
      <description>For the second straight week, a Commanders beat reporterdeclaredan injured player had returned to practice after seeing them trot out to a side field for individual work with the training staff. In this case, it was Samuel. Unfortunately, this does not constitute a return to practice. The Commanders’ No. 2 wide receiver remains sidelined. Nos. 1 and 3 WRs, Terry McLaurin (quad) and Noah Brown (groin/knee), have been ruled out, leaving slot receiver Jaylin Lane and No. 4 WR Luke McCaffrey with a path to potential FLEX-relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c0-d95b-addb-eec69e540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c1-d95b-addb-eec789230000</link>
      <description>Collins is on track to play in Week 5 against the Ravens’ injury-depleted defense, as expected. The opportunity provides Collins with a clear runway to a WR1 performance. The Ravens could be without their two most productive pass rushers and one or more starting defensive backs. Keep Collins locked into lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c1-d95b-addb-eec789230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6e3-d6e9-af9d-aef31aa10000</link>
      <description>Ridley is now on the wrong side of questionable for Week 5 against the Cardinals. The 30-year-old wide receiver is having a disappointing season, and may only return to matchup-based FLEX status when he becomes available again. Titans rookie WR Elic Ayomanor is taking over as the team’s No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6e3-d6e9-af9d-aef31aa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c7-d95b-addb-eec73f240000</link>
      <description>The Titans desperately need Spears’ speed on the field, but they have been smartly conservative with his rehab program thus far. He will probably need to graduate to full practice participation before they activate him on game day. Unfortunately, while Spears could provide Cam Ward with a helpful receiving presence out of the backfield, he only profiles as a PPR FLEX option for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c7-d95b-addb-eec73f240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (ankle/hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6f1-dca3-a9fb-bff9ca150000</link>
      <description>Mims continues to intermittently deliver big plays, operating in a part-time role for the Broncos. Through four games, he has weekly finishes in the WR1 and WR4 tiers, plus two more outside the position’s top 80. Big plays could be harder to come by against the Eagles, but Broncos head coach Sean Payton will undoubtedly give him a few opportunities to generate some.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6f1-dca3-a9fb-bff9ca150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6f8-dca3-a9fb-bff92ad50000</link>
      <description>Dissly is seemingly on track to return for the Chargers’ Week 5 game against the Commanders, but his continued limitations suggest he still has a little way to go before he is at full strength. In the meantime, rookie TE Oronde Gadsden II took over as the Chargers’ positional leader in Week 4, though he caught just 2-of-3 targets for 16 yards. Dissly’s return could muddy the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6f8-dca3-a9fb-bff92ad50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes (groin) is practicing in full for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ea-dca3-a9fb-bffbb4850000</link>
      <description>This is a new injury for Mahomes, who was listed on the injury report with a right wrist injury in recent weeks. The superstar quarterback totaled 13 carries for 123 yards and two touchdowns in Weeks 1-2. Over the last two weeks, he has rushed nine times for just seven yards. While Mahomes will assuredly be on the field for the Chiefs’ Week 5 game against the Jaguars, a return to his early-season rushing productivity appears to be unlikely. He is a mid-tier QB1, operating as a pocket passer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ea-dca3-a9fb-bffbb4850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR JuJu Smith-Schuster (knee) is practicing in full for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6fb-deb6-a7fd-f7ffcf6c0000</link>
      <description>Smith-Schuster is barely on the FLEX radar, now thoroughly past his prime. He has totaled five targets in 3-of-4 games thus far, though, so losing him to an injury could hurt Patrick Mahomes’ scoring ability a tad. Fortunately, that will not be an issue here. Smith-Schuster should be good to go for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6fb-deb6-a7fd-f7ffcf6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a718-dca3-a9fb-bf995d210000</link>
      <description>Brown should be on track to return this week. He practiced in a limited capacity on Thursday and Friday in Week 4 but was ultimately ruled inactive. The Jaguars play the Chiefs on Monday night, so Thursday marks the first practice of the week. Brown will be a WR5/FLEX option in what should be a pass-heavy game script, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a718-dca3-a9fb-bf995d210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared QB Brock Purdy, WR Jauan Jennings, WR Ricky Pearsall, RB Jordan James, WR Jordan Watkins, DL Robert Beal and LB Nick Martin inactive for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a71b-d95b-addb-ef5f7be90000</link>
      <description>Losing Purdy, Jennings (ankle, ribs) and Pearsall (knee) for a Thursday night divisional showdown is brutal. The 49ers, Rams and Seahawks sit in a three-way tie for first place in the NFC West with 3-1 records. Fantasy managers should expect Christian McCaffrey to handle a significant workload in this one. Kendrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson will serve as the Nos. 1 and 2 wide receivers, respectively. 49ers TE Jake Tonges has comparatively earned targets moderately efficiently in his role as a fill-in starter. Mac Jones is a viable starter in two-quarterback leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a71b-d95b-addb-ef5f7be90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
