<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a7f-d005-a9bf-da7fa0380000</link>
      <description>Njoku went down with the knee issue early in the Browns’ Week 14 loss to the Titans and did not return. His lone catch of the day resulted in a touchdown. Njoku was already being phased out of the offense before suffering the injury. Harold Fannin is now locked in for a high-volume role, putting him firmly within the TE1 ranks for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a7f-d005-a9bf-da7fa0380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedric Tillman (concussion/rib) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a85-d77b-adfb-ca87dace0000</link>
      <description>Tillman caught one pass for 23 yards versus Tennessee on Sunday. His role was already on the decline before suffering the concussion and rib injuries. He is now a safe bet to miss Week 15 entirely. Isaiah Bond will see an uptick in routes in his absence, though there isn’t much fantasy value to be had in Cleveland outside of Jerry Jeudy and Harold Fannin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a85-d77b-adfb-ca87dace0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson (calf/hand) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a87-da9b-a9bf-de8ffdb60000</link>
      <description>Sampson played through the calf issue on Sunday and didn’t appear to be bothered by it. He only ran the ball twice but added 64 yards through the air on five catches. The rookie did, however, lose a fumble in the fourth quarter. The hand issue is a new addition to the injury report. If he plays through it, Sampson will be a low-end RB4 for PPR leagues versus the Chicago in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a87-da9b-a9bf-de8ffdb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a93-d005-a9bf-dab7a2630000</link>
      <description>Golden has been dealing with the wrist injury since Week 11, returning in Week 14 to the tune of four routes. The rookie is still limited due to the injury and is now lost in the shuffle of a deep wide receiver room that saw Bo Melton score a touchdown last week and Jayden Reed return. Golden is still trending to play Week 15 against the Broncos, but is not on the fantasy radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a93-d005-a9bf-dab7a2630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a96-d8cf-affb-bebe43a80001</link>
      <description>Reed returned from foot and shoulder injuries to play in Week 14, getting four targets on the day. He saw a sizeable role, running over 60 percent of available routes; the Packers will limit his practice workload to start the week. Also limited were fellow wide receivers Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) and Savion Williams (foot). Wicks played through the ankle injury in Week 14 while Williams did not practice all of last week. Reed is still trending to play and is the best receiver out of the three, while Wicks is worth a speculative deep league dart throw and Williams is not fantasy relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a96-d8cf-affb-bebe43a80001</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE T.J. Hockenson (shin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a9b-da9b-a9bf-de9f698a0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson pops up on the injury report with a new shin issue. He did not practice Wednesday, putting his status for Week 15 in doubt. The veteran has not had much fantasy utility this season, and even saw fellow tight end Josh Oliver score twice in Week 14, despite scoring once himself. Fantasy managers should stay tuned throughout the rest of the week for Hockenson’s status; he is a TE2 if he can play against the Cowboys, otherwise Oliver will get a boost for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a9b-da9b-a9bf-de9f698a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aa5-d8cf-affb-beaf61f10000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw has had a pattern of not practice, practicing limited, and eventually playing due to his knee injury. This week, he starts out not practicing and should not be in jeopardy of missing Week 15 unless he cannot practice at all this week. The franchise left tackle is a key blocker for J.J. McCarthy and the Vikings offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aa5-d8cf-affb-beaf61f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jordan Addison (Achilles) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aa9-d77b-adfb-caabebe10000</link>
      <description>Addison gets a new listing with an Achilles issue on Wednesday. He practiced in a limited fashion, though the fact that this seems to be a new issue brings some concern for his Week 15 status. It is unclear how severe the Achilles injury is yet, but fantasy managers should keep an eye on Addison’s practice status throughout the rest of the week. If he cannot go against the Cowboys, Jalen Nailor will see a bump in usage for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aa9-d77b-adfb-caabebe10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aae-d8cf-affb-beae2fe70000</link>
      <description>Jones practiced last week with the shoulder issue and was cleared from the injury report prior to running for 76 yards against the Commanders in Week 14. The 31-year-old will likely continue to nurse the injury throughout the final games of the season, meaning this limited listing has little cause for concern. Expect Jones to play in Week 15 against the Cowboys, barring setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aae-d8cf-affb-beae2fe70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab0-da9b-a9bf-debd5d140000</link>
      <description>McConkey seems to have picked up a foot injury from Monday’s Week 14 game against the Eagles and gets a limited listing to start out Week 15. The Chargers held a walkthrough, so this is just an estimation, but McConkey should get at least a limited practice with pads before the end of the week in order to play against the Chiefs. The Chargers passing game has been rough since LT Joe Alt was ruled out for the season, making McConkey a borderline WR2 for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab0-da9b-a9bf-debd5d140000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
