<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Derwin James Jr. is believed to have suffered a low-ankle sprain in Week 8’s win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16fb-d5d8-a3ff-fffbf2ca0000</link>
      <description>According to Pelissero, James will undergo an MRI to confirm, but the hope is the veteran safety has avoided the worst here. James was injured in the first half of Sunday’s win and ruled out in the second-half, but if this injury doesn’t prove to be anything major, it’s possible James will be good to go when the Chargers face the Titans in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16fb-d5d8-a3ff-fffbf2ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haason Reddick (ankle/knee) will not play in Week 8 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1711-dab4-a3fb-9f711bde0000</link>
      <description>Reddick, along with OG Luke Haggard (shoulder), have been ruled out for Sunday’s game. Reddick has totaled 1.5 sacks in seven games for the Buccaneers this season while also breaking up one pass. It’s the first missed game of the season for Reddick, who was unable to practice this week and now sets his sights to Week 10 with the Buccaneers having a Week 9 bye on tap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1711-dab4-a3fb-9f711bde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers listed Bryce Young (ankle) as doubtful for Week 8 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-171c-dab4-a3fb-9f7cccc80000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Young failed to take the practice field during the first two days of the week. Before that, it was reported by NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero that Young’s injury was the kind that “is generally a 2-4 week injury,” setting an early precedent that the Panthers’ QB1 would miss at least one game, and perhaps multiple. The doubtful designation foreshadows Young being ruled out sooner or later, paving the way for Andy Dalton to start vs. the Bills. Dalton could be on the fantasy radar for superflex or 2QB leagues with six teams on bye this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-171c-dab4-a3fb-9f7cccc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced the Giants have been fined $200k for violating the league’s concussion protocol in Week 6’s game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1720-deb1-a39b-372ed1f10000</link>
      <description>In addition to the team being fined, head coach Brian Daboll was also fined $100k for his involvement, while rookie RB Cam Skattebo was fine $15k for his involvement. In a joint statement released by the NFL and NFLPA, the league reinforced the fact that “no other individuals are permitted in the tent or locker room during an evaluation,” which was something both Daboll and Skattebo both violated during Jaxson Dart’s concussion evaluation. The Giants were at risk of losing a draft pick if found to be in violation, however, it appears the league will bypass removing draft picks in exchange for the fines levied against the teams and those directly involved with the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1720-deb1-a39b-372ed1f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers QB Andy Dalton is expected to start in Week 8 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1728-deb1-a39b-372e2e400000</link>
      <description>Bryce Young (ankle, doubtful) hasn’t officially been ruled out for Sunday’s game, but we can see the writing on the wall here. Young is dealing with a high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 7’s win over the Jets, and could be at risk of missing more than just one game. With Young set to be ruled out at some point before kickoff, the Panthers will pivot to Andy Dalton, who has thrown for 118 yards and one touchdown on 13 pass attempts. Dalton will have some appeal in 2QB/superflex leagues but shouldn’t be trusted in 1QB formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1728-deb1-a39b-372e2e400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said Josh Downs (concussion) has cleared protocol and will play in Week 8’s game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-172d-dab4-a3fb-9f7d2dc70000</link>
      <description>Downs only went off for 2/34 against the Titans in Week 3, but remains a viable FLEX play with six teams on bye. He’ll cut into Alec Pierce’s streamer appeal too, as Downs is a target commander.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-172d-dab4-a3fb-9f7d2dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 8 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1737-dab4-a3fb-9f77803c0000</link>
      <description>Njoku got in limited practice days all week and would seem to be eligible to play. It’s possible the Browns keep him down if they feel like there’s any doubt, because the last thing they want to do before the trade deadline is get Njoku’s knee messed up when they could trade him for potential assets. But if Njoku plays, the Patriots project as a pass funnel and Dillon Gabriel throws to tight ends often — it’s definitely a potential TE1 situation for the veteran tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1737-dab4-a3fb-9f77803c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Jaylen Waddle (hamstrings/rest) is expected to play against the Falcons in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1744-dab4-a3fb-9f74a1130000</link>
      <description>Waddle popped up on the injury report, and McDaniel said that he is expected to play through “tweaked” hamstrings. We’d expect a questionable tag later today. Based on that report, Waddle is probably a re-injury risk and you can break near-ties in the rankings against Waddle. But given how little the Dolphins have, unless your wideout room is just stacked, you’re probably going to wind up starting Waddle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1744-dab4-a3fb-9f74a1130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) will not play in Tennessee’s Week 8 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1755-d245-adfb-975f39ab0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week. We’d bet more on a Week 10 return than a Week 9 return for Simmons given how this has gone thus far, and we probably can’t rule out an IR placement on Saturday. Without their best defensive player the Titans will be in (searching for word that is worse than deep trouble) deeper trouble than usual against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1755-d245-adfb-975f39ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) will not play in Week 8 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-172c-d245-adfb-977fe8af0000</link>
      <description>Ridley will miss a second-straight game with the hamstring injury he suffered in Week 6. As a result, we can once again expect Van Jefferson, Elic Ayomanor, and Chimere Dike serve as the team’s top three receivers against a Colts defense that ranks eighth in points allowed and 16th in yards per attempt allowed this season. Ayomanor tied for the team lead in targets last week with five, but hasn’t topped 30 receiving yards since Week 4. Both he and Jefferson profile as WR4/WR5 dart throws in deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-172c-d245-adfb-977fe8af0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
