<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles placed Ben VanSumeren (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b90-de13-afdd-5fdbb5430000</link>
      <description>The first injury of the season chronologically, blocking fullback VanSumeren looks likely to miss the rest of the season. He’ll miss at least the next four weeks, and the Eagles may look to find another fullback off the street or on someone else’s practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b90-de13-afdd-5fdbb5430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b95-dbe3-a9bb-3bd743390000</link>
      <description>He got in a third straight limited session on Friday. Most sourced reports expect Parsons to play, but it’s possible he’ll have a limited role in Week 1 as he acclimates to his new team and deals with the back injury. Green Bay would certainly like him available for passing downs in a must-win against the defending division champions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b95-dbe3-a9bb-3bd743390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Jordan Love (left thumb) is off Green Bay’s final injury report for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b97-de13-afdd-5fdfd0880000</link>
      <description>He’ll start against the Lions. Love had surgery on the thumb in the middle of training camp and has practiced in full all three days. Love is a borderline QB1 against the Lions to open the fantasy football season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b97-de13-afdd-5fdfd0880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9a-db7b-a5dd-bb9ea9c20000</link>
      <description>He got in a second straight limited session and seems to be on the optimistic side of questionable. Reed is a risky fantasy play, but with Dontayvion Wicks also questionable and Christian Watson opening up on the PUP list, he could get enough targets to make some hay in a WR3 role. As it has all offseason, this looks more like an open road for Matthew Golden to go nuclear than anything else.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9a-db7b-a5dd-bb9ea9c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b96-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7a4970000</link>
      <description>Horton’s training camp performance impressed Seahawks coaches to the point that they released veteran WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling. While MVS’ drops are legendary, he also boasts 60 combined regular season starts, playing for the Packers and Chiefs. Horton’s downfield role and position on the depth chart lend themselves to volatile results, if he is even able to make good on the promise he showed this summer. He does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues currently, but for those wishing to stash a dart throw wide receiver, Horton fits the bill. Horton should have unencumbered access to the No. 3 wide receiver role this week, with Jake Bobo (concussion) and Dareke Young (hamstring) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b96-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7a4970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontyavion Wicks (calf) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9d-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf1b900000</link>
      <description>Ditto Savion Williams, as both got in three limited sessions and are likely on the optimistic side of questionable. Malik Heath could get involved if one of these two receivers gets ruled out ahead of the action on Sunday. As it is, Wicks profiles as a FLEX dart throw and Williams probably shouldn’t be started without either Wicks or Jayden Reed being ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9d-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf1b900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks rule out WR Jake Bobo (concussion) for Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</link>
      <description>Both Bobo and LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) kicked the week off with promising limited practice participation statuses, but they were ultimately unable to get cleared for action. With Bobo out, rookie speedster WR Tory Horton (ankle) should operate as the clear-cut No. 3 wide receiver. Backup WR Dareke Young (hamstring) is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) is questionable to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1baf-dbe3-a9bb-3bff30100000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero implicitly confirms the concern that McCaffrey did indeed suffer a new injury, saying the 49ers’ “opener against Seattle is on Sunday, just three days after the injury” occurred, removing the possibility that this was a precautionary measure due to some sort of muscle irritation. Pelissero previously reported that “alarm bells” are not going off within the 49ers’ facility, but the new injury-related phrasing is hardly comforting. For now, fantasy managers must prepare to be without McCaffrey, while hoping for the best. No. 2 RB Brian Robinson will be a top-18 option if McCaffrey is sidelined for Week 1. No. 3 RB Isaac Guerendo is worth adding in 12-team leagues, where available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1baf-dbe3-a9bb-3bff30100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bc3-de13-afdd-5fcb841c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings will likely operate as the No. 1 wide receiver and No. 2 pass catcher behind George Kittle when the 49ers take on the Seahawks this weekend. With Christian McCaffrey questionable to play due to his calf injury, the 49ers could shift toward a more balanced offensive approach, which would benefit 49ers pass catchers in the stat sheet. Jennings is a WR4 with upside for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bc3-de13-afdd-5fcb841c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Jordan James (finger) is doubtful to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bcf-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf032d0000</link>
      <description>James and WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) were seemingly headed in the right direction, but head coach Kyle Shanahan is often reticent to trust rookies, so maybe the team is just playing it safe with two players who are unlikely to take the field anyway. With Christian McCaffrey (calf) questionable, it’s possible the team chooses to keep James active if McCaffrey is unable to go. James could be stashed on deep-league benches, if need be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bcf-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf032d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
