<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 18 times for 83 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 17 win over the Buccaneers, adding three receptions for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e1-d968-a19b-7ef175b70000</link>
      <description>Achane turned 21 touches into 112 yards, still making up the lion’s share of the Dolphins offense. The spike weeks have not come for Achane with the Dolphins getting limited scoring opportunities amidst the struggles at quarterback and transition to Quinn Ewers. Still, Achane’s heavy usage as a runner and pass-catcher has kept him in the RB1 range. His first carry did not come until the second quarter, but the Dolphins ultimately ran the ball 30 times, 18 going to Achane. He finishes the fantasy season as an RB1 heading into Week 18 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e1-d968-a19b-7ef175b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquez Valdes-Scantling caught 3-of-9 passes for 21 yards in the Steelers’ Week 17 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66ea-d56e-afff-e6ea0d520000</link>
      <description>Four of Valdes-Scantling’s targets came on the Steelers’ final two drives of the game. Aaron Rodgers went to MVS on three-straight tries in the end zone in hopes of securing a game-tying touchdown, but the veteran receiver was unable to make the most of his opportunities. MVS will get another chance to step up for the Steelers with DK Metcalf set to serve his second game of a two-game suspension next week, but he remains a feast-or-famine player even in an expanded role. There’s not much to get excited about here ahead of Week 18’s game against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66ea-d56e-afff-e6ea0d520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 8-of-11 targets for 119 yards and a touchdown in the Saints’ Week 17 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e6-dc7a-af9b-efffbdc60000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Olave dominated targets for the Saints, seeing 41 percent of Tyler Shough’s attempts with loads of air yards to juice the numbers. The Titans were unable to keep up with Olave and he repeatedly gashed them for chunk plays. His touchdown came from 19 yards out and he hit on a 60-yard connection down the sideline later in the game. Olave’s fantasy playoff run is quietly one of the best in recent memory, with 24 grabs for 352 yards and four touchdowns over his past three games. He will claim a spot in the WR1 ranks for his Week 18 date with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e6-dc7a-af9b-efffbdc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Wright rushed five times for 56 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 17 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66ea-d56e-afff-e6eac14e0000</link>
      <description>Wright saw just five of the Dolphins’ 30 total carries, but ripped off a few lengthy runs. His longest was a 32-yard carry he took down to the five-yard line in the second quarter. Wright seemingly has the RB2 role back in his pocket for the Dolphins, running behind De’Von Achane for the last few games. He will be a valuable handcuff to be rostered after Week 18 against the Pats and heading into next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66ea-d56e-afff-e6eac14e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught none of his six targets in Indianapolis’ Week 17 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e9-dc7a-af9b-efff3d550000</link>
      <description>It’s the first bagel on more than six targets since Calvin Ridley’s 0-for-8 against the Colts in Week 6 of the 2024 season. Pierce did manage to draw a near-end zone defensive pass interference call to get the Colts into goal-to-go, so you can hold that in some solace while you stare at the zero in your box score. Pierce, an impending free agent, seems like someone who could possibly rest in Week 18 against the Texans in a meaningless game for the Colts. Shane Steichen wasn’t forthcoming on answers on resting players in the post game scrum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66e9-dc7a-af9b-efff3d550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 2-of-5 targets for 34 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 17 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f3-dc7a-af9b-efffdd280000</link>
      <description>Downs managed an 18-yard third-down catch on the sideline that was challenged but upheld to put the Colts in field-goal range. Otherwise, well, the Jaguars sat on everything underneath and challenged Rivers to make deeper throws, and he mostly couldn’t. Downs seems like a better bet to play than the other Colts’ wideouts in Week 18 — assuming the Colts want him to — since he’s under contract in 2026 and still on his rookie deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f3-dc7a-af9b-efffdd280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 5-of-7 targets for 54 yards in the Browns’ Week 17 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f1-d968-a19b-7ef180ed0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy and Sheduer Sanders were in sync early, as Sanders connected with Jeudy for gains of 10, 13, and 15 yards on the Browns’ first three drives of the game. Jeudy saw four of his seven targets come on those first two drives, but saw little work the rest of the way as the Steelers put the clamps on the Browns’ passing game. Sunday’s outing marked just the second time this season that Jeudy has gone for 50-plus yards with Sanders under center. He’ll look to close out the season with another strong outing in Week 18 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f1-d968-a19b-7ef180ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 5-of-5 targets for 43 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 17 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f5-d968-a19b-7ef5ff1b0000</link>
      <description>It was his first time over 40 yards since Week 12. Warren managed a bunch of short-area contested catches, but wasn’t targeted in the red zone. It’s been a disappointing second half of the season for Warren, who has 171 yards in six games since returning to American soil after the win in Germany. He’ll be a TE2 play against the Texans in Week 18 if the Colts want to keep playing him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f5-d968-a19b-7ef5ff1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheim Sanders rushed eight times for 21 yards in the Browns’ Week 17 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f6-d56e-afff-e6fe986c0000</link>
      <description>Sanders drew the start in Sunday’s win over the Steelers, and handled six of his eight carries on the Browns’ first three possessions. His longest gain of the day came on a six-yard plunge on the first play of the game, and he also added a 10-yard reception in the fourth quarter. If Sanders finds himself in another split with Dylan Sampson next week, both backs will be hard to trust in Week 18 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f6-d56e-afff-e6fe986c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo Alie-Cox caught 3-of-3 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in Indianapolis’ Week 17 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f9-d35e-a1bf-67fb6fe00000</link>
      <description>It was his first touchdown of the season. FOX did not have a graphic of the 32-year-old veteran. He’ll be a free agent this offseason. Fantasy managers need not chase the hot hand here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66f9-d35e-a1bf-67fb6fe00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
