<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Minkah Fitzpatrick (calf) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2899-d1bc-a3fb-adbd2e180000</link>
      <description>It’s possible Fitzpatrick is able to get back for one of the final two games, but we’d be stunned if he played in Week 16. The veteran safety has enjoyed a bounceback year for the Dolphins with a 81.8 PFF defensive grade — his finest since 2022 — and has one year left on his deal at a $18.8 million cap hit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2899-d1bc-a3fb-adbd2e180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed WR Andre Baccellia (neck) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28ab-d77b-adfb-eaab68fc0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss the remainder of the regular season. Baccellia suffered a scary neck injury and was stretchered off against the Texans in Week 15. The soon-to-be 29-year-old will be an exclusive rights free agent this offseason. He has had nine catches for 53 yards in three seasons on the active roster since coming into the NFL as a UDFA in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28ab-d77b-adfb-eaab68fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee/IR) said “I got healthy. I’m back healthy,” despite the fact that the Cowboys did not activate him from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28ae-d005-a9bf-f8bef6580000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Todd Archer chronicles what has been a weird season of deactivations and inactive list placements for Diggs, who has refused to discuss his mid-season concussion that was caused by an accident other than to say “Accidents happen all the time.” The Cowboys will need to activate Diggs by next Saturday or he’ll be lost for the rest of the season. From the outside, it sure looks like the team is making sure Diggs doesn’t have activate any of his 2026 salary that is guaranteed for injury. And with Dallas’ season all but over, it wouldn’t seem like there’s a reason to put Diggs out there if they’re worried about his 2026 salary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28ae-d005-a9bf-f8bef6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur, asked about a return for MarShawn Lloyd this week, said “I’m not going to say no, but I think you can use deductive reasoning on that one.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28cf-d77b-adfb-eacf27d30000</link>
      <description>Lloyd has to be activated this week or lost to injured reserve for the rest of the season. The second-year third-round pick did not play a single NFL snap for the Packers this year as he never was able to get all of his various injuries healed at the same time. LaFleur added “It’s very, very, very unfortunate, because this guy has worked his ass off.” Lloyd isn’t a must-drop in dynasty leagues, but with Emanuel Wilson showing well against the Vikings in Josh Jacobs’ one absence this year, there’d certainly appear to be no reason for Lloyd to be handed the backup role when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28cf-d77b-adfb-eacf27d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed RB Deejay Dallas.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28d3-d8cf-affb-bcfbcf660000</link>
      <description>He’ll fill in for Bhayshul Tuten (finger) over the final three games of the season. We’re all looking forward to the legendary Week 18 Deejay Dallas game, should the Jaguars sew up their playoff position to the point where they can rest starters. Well, everyone but LeQuint Allen is, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28d3-d8cf-affb-bcfbcf660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed RB Zonovan Knight (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2909-d005-a9bf-f93d555e0000</link>
      <description>The ankle injury suffered against the Texans in Week 15 will send the running back to season-ending IR. Knight had control of the lead role in the Cardinals backfield for the majority of the season after season-ending injuries to James Conner and Trey Benson left Arizona reliant on depth. The 24-year-old acquitted himself well with a 82/269/4 line on the ground, adding one receiving score on a 22/160 line through the air. He’ll be a restricted free agent this offseason. Knight showed enough to stick on a roster somewhere, even if he isn’t necessarily someone dynasty managers should build around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2909-d005-a9bf-f93d555e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed RB Jawhar Jordan to their active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-291b-d005-a9bf-f93fbcef0000</link>
      <description>It’s possible he had outside interest. It’s also possible that the Texans got worse news than expected on the health of Woody Marks (ankle) or Nick Chubb (ribs) — if Marks doesn’t make it to Sunday healthy, Jordan would be a halfway interesting RB3 play against what certainly appears to be a dead-on-arrival Raiders squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-291b-d005-a9bf-f93fbcef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans placed S Kevin Winston Jr. (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-291e-d8cf-affb-bd3e2c150000</link>
      <description>He’s joined there by fellow safeties Mike Brown (ankle) and Xavier Woods (hamstring) as the Titans signed Erick Hallett and Sanoussi Kane off the Lions and Ravens practice squads. It is certainly End Of Season Hours in Tennessee. 2025 third-round pick Winston finishes his rookie season with a 89.4 PFF run defense grade, but just a 43.4 PFF coverage grade. It was a land of contrasts. He’ll probably be the favorite to start next to Amani Hooker next season if he’s healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-291e-d8cf-affb-bd3e2c150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Josh Jacobs (knee) wouldn’t have practiced Tuesday if the Packers held a practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2924-d1bc-a3fb-ad241d420000</link>
      <description>Jacobs, who played last week on a pitch count, aggravated his knee injury against the Broncos in Week 15’s loss. “He’s battling through,” LaFleur told reporters. “This guy is as tough as they come. So I’ll never count him out of the fight, I’ll tell you that.” We’d expect another week of Jacobs playing through the injury on Saturday in a huge game against the Bears for the top of the NFC North. Emanuel Wilson would certainly be a playable fantasy football starter in Week 16 if it came to that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2924-d1bc-a3fb-ad241d420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants waived K Younghoe Koo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2928-d005-a9bf-f93ce7f50000</link>
      <description>▬▬▬.◙.▬▬▬═▂▄▄▓▄▄▂◢◤ █▀▀████▄▄▄◢◤█▄ █ █▄ ███▀▀▀▀▀▀╬◥█████◤══╩══╩═╬═╬ He was 4-of-6 on field goals and 11-of-12╬═╬ on extra points.╬═╬ Ben Sauls is the current viable╬═╬ replacement on the Giants practice squad.╬═╬ Koo’s stumbled non-kick against the╬═╬ Patriots will live on in our hearts.╬═╬☻/╬═╬/▌╬═╬/ \</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2928-d005-a9bf-f93ce7f50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
