<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35d-d56e-afff-e7fda49d0000</link>
      <description>Minter interviewed with the Ravens yesterday and the Raiders earlier today. Three down. Five to go. The Chargers’ defensive coordinator is a sought-after candidate in this hiring cycle. He has coached under head coach Jim Harbaugh with the Chargers (2024-2025) and Michigan (2022-2023) over the last four years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35d-d56e-afff-e7fda49d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports the Ravens are targeting Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36a-d968-a19b-dbfbbae10000</link>
      <description>Todd Monken was quickly labeled as a likely Harbaugh offensive coordinator in New York, but we had to wait about 12 hours to get a good leak about the defensive coordinator. Weaver makes plenty of sense as a former Harbaugh defensive line/assistant head coach in the early 2020s before taking his current job as Dolphins defensive coordinator. Weaver has interviewed for several head-coaching positions this cycle, so it’s possible he gets a shot as a head man, but it seems like he’d be in good hands if those didn’t shake out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36a-d968-a19b-dbfbbae10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested an interview with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36f-d35e-a1bf-c7efb7aa0000</link>
      <description>He’ll interview Sunday, per Ian Rapoport. Saleh has drawn requests from Miami, Baltimore, and Arizona this offseason. The 49ers DC has done an admirable job holding down the fort this year while missing stars Fred Warner and Nick Bosa for most of the season. For the Titans, he is one of19different interviews they’ve conducted so far. They’ll move past the initial round after this one and try to nail down a list of finalists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36f-d35e-a1bf-c7efb7aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase will interview for the Raiders, Steelers, Ravens and Browns’ head-coaching vacancies on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c337-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe9df0000</link>
      <description>This is quite the impressive lineup for the 35-year-old offensive coach. Scheelhaase coached in the college ranks from 2015-2023 before signing on as an offensive assistant and passing game specialist with the Rams in 2024. He was promoted to his current role last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c337-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe9df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c387-d968-a19b-dbf7faed0000</link>
      <description>He also, per Mike Reiss, shed the non-contact jersey on Thursday. It can be tricky to make definitive statements about concussion protocol, but Gonzalez certainly seems like he has a real chance to play against the Texans on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c387-d968-a19b-dbf7faed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c389-d968-a19b-dbf95bf60000</link>
      <description>He was listed with this knee injury ahead of last week’s game as well and it looks like it won’t be a problem for Henry to play against the Texans on Sunday. It would be surprising if he weren’t cleared off the injury report on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c389-d968-a19b-dbf95bf60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) is questionable for Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38b-d56e-afff-e7eb0ebd0000</link>
      <description>Uh oh. Darnold was not listed on the injury report at all before today’s practice. This certainly has the potential to tip things. Mike MacDonald is not slated to speak to reporters again until Friday. We’d tentatively assume Darnold will still play, but it can be unpredictable what happens when you get an in-practice injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38b-d56e-afff-e7eb0ebd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfef7d0000</link>
      <description>Two sessions would seemingly give him a real chance to suit up, though it’s unclear if the Texans would make him the No. 2 back ahead of Nick Chubb after Chubb’s output against the Steelers last Monday night. Jordan is probably trending towards a questionable tag on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfef7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) is questionable for San Francisco’s Divisional Round game against the Seahawks</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c393-dc7a-af9b-cfbff41d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall has been practicing in a limited capacity this week. He was entirely unable to practice last week, so the increased participation is a positive sign. Pearsall aggravated the PCL sprain in his knee at the end of a 30-yard play against the Bears in Week 18. He told reporters that he “landed straight on [his] knee,” and he “just can’t take tackles like that right now.” Instead, he must “adjust a little bit within [his] game.” Getting out of bounds would have been the “wiser move.” Pearsall is seemingly on track to play, but he may be stuck running vertical routes along the sideline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c393-dc7a-af9b-cfbff41d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) said he is “confident” that he will play in Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a2-d968-a19b-dbf323010000</link>
      <description>Darnold adds that there is “close to zero” percent chance that he misses his team’s playoff game against the division-rival 49ers. This is encouraging. He told reporters that he “felt something during routes on air and didn’t want to push it.” Smart move. The Seahawks are one game away from a trip to the NFC Championship Game. We expect him to play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a2-d968-a19b-dbf323010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
