<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Bills hosted EDGE Matthew Judon for a workout today and “they intend to sign him to their practice squad.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3867-da28-afbb-fc7f57260000</link>
      <description>The former Dolphins pass rusher now has a chance to make a playoff run. The 33-year-old can serve as a rotational pass rusher. He has 11 tackles and 10 quarterback pressures to his name this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3867-da28-afbb-fc7f57260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane (ribs) is not on Miami’s final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-386e-da28-afbb-fc7f0fa20000</link>
      <description>Neither is Ollie Gordon (ankle) — Achane figures to be a top-end RB1 in what looks a smash spot against an abysmal Bengals defense ... assuming the Bengals can’t just turn first-time starter Quinn Ewers into a total pumpkin. Still, even if with that threat, it’s not like Tua Tagovailoa was playing well this year. Achane can be started with confidence against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-386e-da28-afbb-fc7f0fa20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins K Jason Sanders (hip) is questionable for Miami’s Week 16 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3870-da28-afbb-fc7d6bef0000</link>
      <description>If you’re thinking “haven’t thought of him for a minute,” well, Sanders has missed the entire season to this point with the hip ailment. Dolphins ST coordinator Craig Aukerman was asked Thursday about whether Sanders or Riley Patterson would kick this weekend and said he didn’t want to speculate. Dolphins long-time beat Barry Jackson noted that Aukerman was asked if he views it as “A). Sanders is Dolphins kicker moving forward period or B). This is a decision above my pay grade that must be made by whoever is in charge in next 8 months,” and Aukerman politely declined to answer. So, yeah. We don’t know who will kick for the Dolphins yet against the Bengals. Someone, probably.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3870-da28-afbb-fc7d6bef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) is questionable for Arizona’s Week 16 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3878-dc7a-af9b-fffff3710000</link>
      <description>He said his heel is “good enough to go” in a locker room availability on Friday, which is great news. Harrison did not get in a full session at any point this week though, so we still have a little bit of a question mark on if he’ll play against the Falcons. He’d be a WR2/WR3 if active. Michael Wilson is a WR3 if Harrison plays, but a high-end WR2 if not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3878-dc7a-af9b-fffff3710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons placed WR KhaDarel Hodge (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-387d-da28-afbb-fc7d1dfa0000</link>
      <description>That’ll end his season as the Falcons aren’t going to the playoffs. Hodge went for 3/31 on eight targets against the Dolphins in Week 8 and was held to two catchless targets on the rest of the season. It was a land of contrasts. The soon-to-be 31-year-old veteran is signed to a reasonable $3.36 million cap figure in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-387d-da28-afbb-fc7d1dfa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (illness) is not on Dallas’ final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3884-d35e-a1bf-7dc62b4c0000</link>
      <description>Not a surprise after he made it back to the field today. Lamb is in line for a WR1 workload against the Chargers in Week 16. Lamb missed the first two days of practice this week, though he was taking mental reps and otherwise involved on Thursday. Managers can plug him right into the lineup and worry about their other spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3884-d35e-a1bf-7dc62b4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (neck) is not on Dallas’ final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3886-d087-addf-b9f605ce0000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old back should be good to go as he chases more fantasy glory in the final three games of the season. Williams is a high-end RB2 against the Chargers in Week 16’s matchup. Jake Ferguson (calf) also was cleared off the final injury report after three full sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3886-d087-addf-b9f605ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Quinnen Williams (concussion) is questionable for Dallas’ Week 16 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3887-dc7a-af9b-ffbf82770000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full today, but the questionable tag implies he has not fully exited concussion protocol yet. He’ll have a chance to do so on Saturday. Williams, by far the best player in Dallas’ front seven, would create some upgrades for the Chargers running game if he were to be ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3887-dc7a-af9b-ffbf82770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys T Tyler Guyton (ankle) will not play in Dallas’ Week 16 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3888-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc5a10000</link>
      <description>He hasn’t practiced or played since Week 12’s high-ankle sprain, so this will be his fourth-straight missed game. The Cowboys don’t necessarily have to shut him down, but they probably won’t bother trying to play him in Week 17 or 18 if there’s any question about his health now that they’re all but eliminated from the playoff picture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3888-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc5a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Geno Smith (shoulder/back) will start against the Texans in Week 16.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-388a-d35e-a1bf-7dca4def0000</link>
      <description>Sugar, we’re going down swinging. Smith will be a backend QB2/QB3 in superflex leagues against the Texans defense. He was practicing in full ahead of Friday, and we’re going to assume he had no setbacks based on this statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-388a-d35e-a1bf-7dca4def0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
