<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 21:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrod Taylor (knee) was limited in practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d92-dab4-a3fb-9ff2a6b70000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t seem like the knee issue is serious enough to prevent Taylor from starting, if that’s the direction head coach Aaron Glenn goes in. The injury is at least mildly concerning. Taylor has dealt with a plethora of injuries in the back half of his career and is banged up after playing just 33 snaps in Week 7. The issue could be large enough for Glenn to side with Fields for another week. Superflex fantasy managers will want to keep tabs on this situation throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d92-dab4-a3fb-9ff2a6b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d94-deb1-a39b-2d9ec3b20000</link>
      <description>Mooney suffered no reported setbacks in the Falcons’ Week 7 loss to the 49ers, so Mooney’s limited listing is likely just maintenance. He is firmly on track to suit up in Week 8 against the Dolphins’ fantasy-friendly defense. Mooney promisingly led the team in receiving (68) yards. He is on the FLEX radar this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d94-deb1-a39b-2d9ec3b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d96-d245-adfb-9ddf96e60000</link>
      <description>Hall got banged up during the team’s Week 7 loss to the Panthers, but head coach Aaron Glenn said after the game that he would be fine for Week 8. A limited practice confirms that. Hall has been the subject of unending trade rumors and the Jets might want to continue feeding him as a way of showing him off to interested parties ahead of the trade deadline. As long as he is healthy, expect plenty of touches and low-end RB1 numbers for Hall heading into Week 8 versus the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d96-d245-adfb-9ddf96e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RB Tyler Allgeier (hip/knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d9d-deb1-a39b-2d9f62b60000</link>
      <description>Allgeier evidently got a little banged up in Week 7 against the 49ers, perhaps explaining his four-carry workload. Allgeier had logged double-digit carries in 4-of-5 games before that. His limited session to begin the week bodes positively for his availability on Sunday, though. He remains a high-upside bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d9d-deb1-a39b-2d9f62b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da0-deb1-a39b-2daef8850000</link>
      <description>This is great news. Chargers RT Trey Pipkins III (knee) and backup LT Austin Deculus (ankle) are listed as questionable as well. All three offensive tackles practiced in a limited capacity each day this week. The Chargers’ offensive line is tasked with fending off the Vikings’ blitz-heavy defensive scheme on Thursday night. Getting one or both of the team’s starting offensive tackles back would go a long way toward keeping QB Justin Herbert upright.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da0-deb1-a39b-2daef8850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa (left thumb) is practicing in full for Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d9e-deb1-a39b-2d9ef09b0000</link>
      <description>As a lefty, the thumb injury is more notable for Tua than almost any other quarterback. A full practice means he isn’t at risk of missing Week 8, but it’s always a slight concern when a quarterback makes a surprise appearance on the injury report for any reason. With Tagovailoa looking more likely to be benched every week, he will be a risky fantasy start versus the Falcons, regardless of the thumb issue. Facing an Atlanta defense giving up the fewest passing yards per game in the league, Tua is buried in the QB2 ranks for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d9e-deb1-a39b-2d9ef09b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers ruled out RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) for Week 8 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da0-d5d8-a3ff-fde1b4e50000</link>
      <description>The Chargers will likely promote one or more practice squad running backs to the active roster tomorrow. The available players include RBs Nyheim Hines, Amar Johnson and Jaret Patterson. All three profile as pass catchers and/or speedy change-of-pace players, so starting RB Kimani Vidal can be expected to continue handling a three-down workload. He is an RB2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da0-d5d8-a3ff-fde1b4e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs (chest) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dac-deb1-a39b-2dae6b270000</link>
      <description>Diggs popped up on the injury report with the chest issue last week. He was listed as questionable for Sunday’s game despite practicing in full on Friday. To no one’s surprise, Diggs was active versus the Titans. He went for 69 yards on seven grabs. Barring a setback, Diggs should be active and on the WR2/3 borderline for Week 8 versus the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dac-deb1-a39b-2dae6b270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Jerry Jeudy (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da9-d5d8-a3ff-fde9b73a0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy has not been a reliable contributor this year, so his potential absence in Week 8 is unlikely to meaningfully alter fantasy lineups. It would, however, free up targets for the Browns’ remaining pass catchers. David Njoku (knee) practiced in a limited capacity, so he has a chance to suit up. Regardless, Harold Fannin Jr. should have access to a decent workload on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0da9-d5d8-a3ff-fde9b73a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0db2-d245-adfb-9dff82b90000</link>
      <description>Njoku promisingly returned to practice after sitting out all three sessions last week. Browns WR Jerry Jeudy (knee) was sidelined on Wednesday after being limited by the issue last week. Njoku is on track to play, which could mean he and rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr. operate as the passing game’s top two weapons in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0db2-d245-adfb-9dff82b90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
