<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chris Godwin (ankle) is expected to practice in a limited capacity on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3940-d903-afbd-fdec78750000</link>
      <description>Godwin is recovering from a second surgery he underwent in the spring to repair some hardware he had put in his ankle. It was reported earlier that Godwin and the Bucs are targeting a Week 5 return, but Rapoport reports “Week 6 is also possible” as a return date. The Buccaneers made the decision to keep Godwin off injured reserve to start the season, and now appear ready to ramp him up for a return next month. If all goes well, Godwin is likely looking at multiple weeks of practice before he takes to the field. He avoided injured reserve to start the year, but there’s little reason to expect an early return, keeping the fantasy stocks for Mike Evans and rookie Emeka Egbuka high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3940-d903-afbd-fdec78750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers beat writer Rick Stroud reports Tristan Wirfs (knee) is expected to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3962-d903-afbd-fdee89160000</link>
      <description>Wirfs and Chris Godwin (ankle) are both making their practice debuts on Thursday as the team plans to ramp them up for a return. Wirfs underwent knee surgery in July but avoided a stay on short-term IR to open the season, indicating he could have a shot at returning before Week 5 if all goes well. Second-year lineman Graham Barton drew the Week 1 start against the Falcons in Wirfs’ absence and allowed three pressures and three hurries, on 38 pass-blocking snaps, per PFF. Wirfs will likely practice in a limited capacity on Thursday and seems unlikely to play in Week 2 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3962-d903-afbd-fdee89160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns OC Tommy Rees said the team will “take it day to day to see how (Quinshon Judkins) continues to progress in practice.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-397a-d8e3-affd-7bfab2e00000</link>
      <description>Judkins is finally set to practice with the Browns for the first time since his July arrest. The rookie second-rounder could have a chance to suit up in Week 2 against the Ravens, but it doesn’t sound like the team is rushing to put him on the field after missing all of training camp. Even if he is active, expectations for Judkins should be low out of the gate, as the team will likely have him on a snap/touch count as he continues to get up to speed. Rookie Dylan Sampson will be the only fantasy viable running back for the Browns in Week 2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-397a-d8e3-affd-7bfab2e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on KNBR Thursday, 49ers GM John Lynch said Brock Purdy (foot) will not play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-398c-d903-afbd-fdec1c930000</link>
      <description>In addition to ruling Purdy out for Week 2’s contest against the Saints, Lynch also declined to put a timeline on his QB1’s recovery. Hours after NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported Purdy would be looking at a 2-5 week absence, Lynch said the information the team has received from doctors has them viewing it as “a week-to-week thing.” With Purdy already confirmed as out for Week 2, the 49ers will shift to Mac Jones as their starter and lean on him throughout the duration of Purdy’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-398c-d903-afbd-fdec1c930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones is slated to start in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39a9-d903-afbd-fdedb2400000</link>
      <description>The team did not officially confirm Jones as the Week 2 starter, but speaking on KNBR radio early Thursday morning, General Manager John Lynch confirmed Brock Purdy (foot) would not play in Week 2, leaving Jones as the next man up. Jones signed a two-year, $7 million contract with the 49ers this offseason and was the rumored target of head coach Kyle Shanahan during the 2021 NFL Draft when the Niners used the No. 3 overall pick to select Trey Lance. Viewed as an ideal fit in Shanahan’s system, Jones completed 17-of-23 passes for 209 yards and two interceptions this preseason, and will have his work cut out for him with George Kittle (hamstring) on injured reserve and Jauan Jennings (shoulder) at risk of also missing Week 2. Jones shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a low-end QB2/high-end QB3 in his Niners debut and can be avoided altogether outside of 2QB and superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39a9-d903-afbd-fdedb2400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the league is reviewing Lamar Jackson’s “interaction with a Bills fan Sunday night.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39b3-d8e3-affd-7bb3d4da0000</link>
      <description>Jackson was seen shoving a fan during Sunday night’s loss to the Bills after said fan reached from the stands onto the field to shove DeAndre Hopkins. The fan was subsequently ejected from the game andlater banned from all NFL gamesfor the foreseeable future by the league. The league’s decision to ban the fan would suggest Jackson will face little if any repercussions for his role in the event. The Ravens said they have also addressed the matter with Jackson while adding they “have implemented additional security protocols” to better protect their players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39b3-d8e3-affd-7bb3d4da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said Malik Nabers (back) will “be good” to play in Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39c7-da68-ad9d-fddff37b0000</link>
      <description>Nabers’ participation level has not yet been disclosed, but fantasy managers should not be alarmed if he remains limited today. The elite WR1 is already on a veteran wide receiver’s practice program. While we would certainly feel better about him regularly practicing in full, there is no reason to think that limited practice sessions will result in limited in-game usage. Count on him to perform as usual on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39c7-da68-ad9d-fddff37b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39cd-d5f6-abfd-b9ddf5e50000</link>
      <description>Giants head coach Brian Daboll has already said he expects Robinson to face the Cowboys this week. The real story here is that Dallas lost star slot CB DaRon Bland to a multi-week foot injury during yesterday’s practice. Bland missed seven games after injuring his left foot last year. The new injury is reportedly a right foot issue. Robinson’s ceiling is always in question due to his low target depth but his odds of returning PPR FLEX value just went up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39cd-d5f6-abfd-b9ddf5e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that “the NFL says it will not discipline Ravens QB Lamar Jackson for his interaction with a fan in Buffalo on Sunday night.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39cd-d5f6-abfd-b9ddee850000</link>
      <description>The NFL ruled that “the matter has been addressed by the club and there is no further action from the league.” During the Ravens’ Sunday Night Football game against the Bills, a fan shoved DeAndre Hopkins’ head as he walked past the stands. Jackson then engaged in a brief shoving match with the fan, who was later banned from attending NFL games indefinitely. The matter has been resolved. Jackson is an elite QB1 against the Browns this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39cd-d5f6-abfd-b9ddee850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39d3-d5f6-abfd-b9df64950000</link>
      <description>Thomas will reportedly participate in “some team drills” as he works through his rehab program following a 2024 Lisfranc injury. Thomas did not practice yesterday. At best, he can be considered questionable to play in Week 2 against the Cowboys. The Giants listed him as doubtful following Friday’s practice last week. For good or ill, we should have a decent idea of his availability by the end of the day tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39d3-d5f6-abfd-b9df64950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
