<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jacob Cowing missed Wednesday’s practice with a hamstring strain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9a3-d332-a1fd-dfb76b770000</link>
      <description>Cowing strained his hamstring in practice last month. Just as he was set to return, he now suffers a setback, having strained his hamstring again in Tuesday’s practice. The 49ers wideout group continues to take hits, with Demarcus Robinson facing suspension and Jordan Watkins (ankle), Brandon Aiyuk (knee), and Jauan Jennings (calf) all out for now. Ricky Pearsall seems to be the only wide receiver slated for targets, but the 49ers may shop around for a veteran to add to the mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9a3-d332-a1fd-dfb76b770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired DT Harrison Phillips and a 2027 seventh-round pick from the Vikings in exchange for 2026 and 2027 sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ad-dbe3-a9bb-f9ffc9950000</link>
      <description>The Jets added their second defensive lineman of the day, acquiring Phillips from the Vikings after getting Jowon Briggs from the Browns. Phillips is a seven-year veteran who has split time with the Bills and Vikings. He started all 51 games for Minnesota over the last three seasons and tallied two sacks, 56 combined tackles, and a forced fumble last season. The Jets beef up their defensive line heading into year one under defensive-minded head coach Aaron Glenn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ad-dbe3-a9bb-f9ffc9950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints acquired WR Devaughn Vele from the Broncos in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick and 2027 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9bb-dbe3-a9bb-f9fba5cd0000</link>
      <description>Vele heads to the Saints after a productive rookie season with the Broncos in 2025. He was a 26-year-old rookie, posting 41 receptions for 475 yards and three touchdowns while primarily working out of the slot. An offseason knee procedure limited Vele in camp, while the emergence of second-year receiver Troy Franklin and rookie Pat Bryant made him more expendable. The Saints add Vele’s 6-foot-5 frame to a receiver room in need of reinforcement behind Chris Olave and Rashid Shaheed. Vele has some value as a late-round dart throw in fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9bb-dbe3-a9bb-f9fba5cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer believes EDGE Micah Parsons will play Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9c3-de13-afdc-cfcb72740000</link>
      <description>Schottenheimer said, “I feel good that Micah will be out there against the Philadelphia Eagles.” Parsons and the Cowboys are still at a contract impasse, with little to no progress being made on a new deal. The 26-year-old has also reportedly been dealing with back tightness while he holds out. Schottenheimer’s vote of confidence doesn’t have much substance behind it in terms of Parsons’ progression back to practice, but things can change quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9c3-de13-afdc-cfcb72740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said, “the more opportunities [RB Jarquez Hunter] gets, the better it’s going to be.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9cd-d332-a1fd-dfffc7310000</link>
      <description>The Rams drafted the 22-year-old Hunter in the fourth-round of April’s draft. He brings pass-catching upside to the Rams backfield and has received praise from the Rams’ coaching staff throughout camp. This spells bad news for Blake Corum, who did not carve out a sizeable role last season. Kyren Williams is still slated to take the vast majority of backfield touches, but Hunter can mix in on passing downs and earn handcuff value for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9cd-d332-a1fd-dfffc7310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers acquired WR Skyy Moore from the Chiefs in exchange for swapping 2027 sixth and seventh-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ed-d332-a1fd-dfffe8830000</link>
      <description>Moore was a second-round pick in the 2022 NFL Draft, but could never really stick with the Chiefs’ receiving corps. He caught 43 passes for 494 yards and a touchdown over his first two seasons, while failing to catch any of his three targets last season. Moore adds value as a returner, recently returning a punt for a touchdown in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 2 game. The 49ers’ receiver group has been decimated by injuries and the recent suspension to Demarcus Robinson. They now add Moore, who is a shot in the dark at some production from the receiver spot. He is unlikely to hold fantasy relevance heading into the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ed-d332-a1fd-dfffe8830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports Vikings WRs Jordan Addison and Tai Felton will have “no issues going forward” after suffering arm injuries in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ca47-de13-afdc-cecfd94f0000</link>
      <description>Seifert earlier reported that Addison and Felton had left with “what looked like hand/arm injuries.” Neither resumed practicing for Wednesday, but seem to be fine moving forward, according to Seifert. The Vikings avoid a major injury with Addison, but he is still set to miss the first three games of the season. Felton is the team’s third-round rookie and in line to compete with Jalen Nailor for the WR3 role this season. Both are still on track for Week 1, but with Nailor (hand) currently week-to-week, the Vikings may still look to acquire a veteran receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ca47-de13-afdc-cecfd94f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed C Nick Harris.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccc7-de13-afdc-cecfc4ca0000</link>
      <description>Harris fractured his fibula in 2024, ending his season after just two starts, and also lost his entire 2023 season to injury. The 2020 fifth-round pick looks to be healthy enough to actually sign. Harris has 612 total snaps in four seasons and is a decent depth add for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccc7-de13-afdc-cecfc4ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Buccaneers are activating Chris Godwin off the active/PUP list, but that he is unlikely to play until October.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccca-dbe3-a9bb-fcdb39170000</link>
      <description>The tone of Schefter’s report is that the Buccaneers will carry Godwin on the active roster at the start of the year rather than sending him to IR or the in-season PUP list, so that he can practice with the team. With Godwin and Jalen McMillan both out for at least the first month — longer for McMillan — Emeka Egbuka and Cade Otton will have bigger roles in the offense early. Egubka is going to be one of the highest ADP risers in the last two weeks before the season we’ve ever charted. This is not terrible news for Godwin, and it’s certainly been trending towards him missing time at the start of the season for a while, but his fantasy stock will take a hit in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccca-dbe3-a9bb-fcdb39170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s DJ Bien-Aime reports Jayden Higgins is “rotating” with Xavier Hutchinson on the outside when the Texans play three wideouts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cccf-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf73460000</link>
      <description>It sounds like we won’t be able to instantly put Higgins in fantasy lineups for Week 1. Higgins had been the starter on the depth chart for at least some of training camp, but Hutchinson has put together an impressive enough preseason and camp to force a timeshare early. We’d still favor the odds of Higgins pushing Hutchinson out at some point this year, but he’ll be hard to trust early if he’s splitting snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cccf-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf73460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
