<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:11:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Eagles LG Landon Dickerson will have “a minor procedure on his knee” and hopes to be ready for the start of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac9-d45c-a7fc-9adb8fd00000</link>
      <description>Dickerson suffered a meniscus injury on Sunday and has been undergoing tests and seeking multiple opinions to figure out the best course of action. Now, according to Garafolo, Dickerson will be considered week-to-week after a minor surgery to correct the issue and is eyeing a Week 1 return if all goes according to plan. It’s about the best news the three-time Pro Bowler could have hoped for after the initial diagnosis sounded far worse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac9-d45c-a7fc-9adb8fd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is “on track to be back around Week 6.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ad7-d90d-a5bd-badf0ad60000</link>
      <description>That “around” is doing a lot of lifting, but this is the first gesture towards a real timetable we’ve had about Aiyuk’s potential return. He’ll almost certainly open the season on the PUP list with this estimate. Aiyuk’s ADP has fluctuated outside of the top 40 among wideouts at this point and he’s probably best-regarded as a dart throw at the moment. The fifth-year receiver will be at the top of the 49ers receiver pecking order when he’s healthy — we just don’t know when he will be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ad7-d90d-a5bd-badf0ad60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jordan Watkins is expected to miss about a month with a high ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9add-df63-a199-dbffb9010000</link>
      <description>The hits keep on coming for the Niners, who are expected to be without Brandon Aiyuk (knee) for at least the first month of the season, and are at risk of being without Jauan Jennings (calf) as well. Jacob Cowing is also battling a hamstring injury, although Kyle Shanahan said he could return to practice on Tuesday. Still, it goes without saying that the Niners’ receiver room is banged up, and Watkins had a chance to see some work early in the season with the injuries piling up. It was reported earlier this month that Watkins was ‘in the mix’ for WR3/WR4 duties. A month-long absence means Watkins could be at risk of missing the first month of the season, but we’ll likely get more clarity on that as Week 1 draws closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9add-df63-a199-dbffb9010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Marquez Callaway.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</link>
      <description>Cut after the draft by the Buccaneers and by the 49ers in training camp, Callaway continues his quest to be rostered for the 2025 season. He has five targets and no catches since 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Cameron Heyward said “It’s hard for me, after the year that I had, to really justify playing at the number I’m playing at.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aea-d90d-a5bd-bafb2e4c0000</link>
      <description>It’s possible Heyward is just letting his thoughts be known while he seeks a reworked deal, but it’d be foolish to think these comments may not foreshadow a potential holdout or hold-in at some point before the season starts. Heyward, 36, is currently the 22nd-highest paid defensive tackle in the league and is coming off his fourth First-Team All-Pro season since 2017. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported last week that Heyward and the Steelers “have not made any progress” in talks for a new deal, which has likely led to the star lineman growing increasingly disgruntled as the season approaches. Heyward signed a three-year extension just last offseason, which may further complicate things. It’s safe to assume this won’t be the last we hear from Heyward on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aea-d90d-a5bd-bafb2e4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns listed Shedeur Sanders as their QB4 on their second unofficial depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b05-d90d-a5bd-bb5f9fef0000</link>
      <description>We take these depth charts with a grain of salt, but for anybody who thought the team would reward Sanders for his preseason performance with a higher spot on the depth chart, that would appear not to be the case. Sanders was solid in his first taste of pro football, throwing for 138 yards and two scores in nearly three full quarters of play. For now, Joe Flacco, Kenny Pickett, and Dillon Gabriel all remain ahead of Sanders on the depth chart. He should see plenty of action in the Browns’ next preseason game, which will come on Saturday against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b05-d90d-a5bd-bb5f9fef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns DE Myles Garrett was cited for doing 100 mph in a 60 mph zone early Saturday morning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b3e-df63-a199-db3f13d90000</link>
      <description>Browns beat reporter Mary Kay Cabot broke the news first, stating that the star defensive end was cited going 100 mph in a 60 mph zone just after 2 am Saturday morning after the team returned from Charlotte. Cabot also noted that Garrett had “vowed to slow down” after flipping his Porsche and that the team was aware of his citation. This is unlikely to draw any league discipline but demonstrates an alarming pattern of reckless driving out of Garrett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b3e-df63-a199-db3f13d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Brevin Jordan (leg) injured Monday at practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b42-d90d-a5bd-bb5bc1cb0000</link>
      <description>From the words of Texans beat reporter Aaron Wilson, “He appears to be in serious pain. Lot of noise coming from the field team huddled around him. Practice halted as Brevin Jordan is hurting very badly. Inconsolable.” We’ll need official word from the team before any conclusions can be drawn, but it certainly looks like an unfortunate injury for a tight end that was attempting to come back from a lost season in 2024 due to a torn ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b42-d90d-a5bd-bb5bc1cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hosted RB Boston Scott for a visit over the weekend.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b68-d05a-adda-bbea7f740000</link>
      <description>Scott is reportedly healthy and looking for the right opportunity to contribute, saying he’s in “terrific” shape. He last played in 2023, his sixth season with the Eagles, and could make sense for a team like the Ravens as a contingent third-down option and special teams contributor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b68-d05a-adda-bbea7f740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Saints OG Will Clapp suffered “a serious foot injury that is believed to be season-ending.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ba5-d05a-adda-bba77d8f0000</link>
      <description>Reports surfaced earlier Monday that Clapp sustained the injury but it wasn’t until Schultz’s report that we had any clue into the severity. Schultz adds that the foot injury is likely to require surgery and would keep Clapp out for the duration of the 2025 regular season, a tough blow to the veteran after he was brought in to operate as a sixth offensive lineman for the Saints. The team is awaiting final confirmation pending follow-on testing but it appears as if Clapp’s season is over before it began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ba5-d05a-adda-bba77d8f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
