<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Foster Moreau (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a192-dca3-a9fb-bd9bf44d0000</link>
      <description>Moreau and Taysom Hill (knee) both returned to practice today, while Weeks 1-4 starting TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) was sidelined. It is too early to tell if Moreau will be active for the Saints’ Week 5 game against the Giants, though Moreau really does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a192-dca3-a9fb-bd9bf44d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a195-deb6-a7fd-f3df212f0000</link>
      <description>Ridley barely logged a 50 percent snap share in Week 4 after routinely playing nearly every snap for the team over the first three weeks of the season. Titans coach Brian Callahan told reporters on Monday that Ridley was playing through something, and we now know precisely what. Even if he returns to practice later this week and suits up on Sunday, fantasy managers can’t trust Ridley as anything more than a WR4. He has 141 scoreless yards on 10 receptions this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a195-deb6-a7fd-f3df212f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE ﻿﻿Tyler Higbee﻿﻿ (hip) is doubtful for Week 5 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a195-dca3-a9fb-bd9df5350000</link>
      <description>The Rams are also likely to be without RT Rob Havenstein﻿﻿ (ankle). Havenstein’s absence could be more consequential than Higbee’s. The 32-year-old tight end has just six receptions and 62 yards on 10 targets this season. He does not need to be rostered in 12-team re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a195-dca3-a9fb-bd9df5350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars EDGE Travon Walker’s wrist injury “won’t be season-ending, but it could jeopardize his status” for Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a180-dca3-a9fb-bd99f3b30000</link>
      <description>Walker reportedly met with a specialist this week regarding the wrist injury he suffered in Week 4. The fact that ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler clarified that the injury is not season-ending suggests Walker could be out beyond Week 5. It’s a tough break for the Jaguars’ defense. Walker has 14 quarterback pressures and two sacks on the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a180-dca3-a9fb-bd99f3b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a199-d95b-addb-e9df06fb0000</link>
      <description>Collins played through the knee injury with no issues last week. We fully expect him to do so again in Week 5 against the Ravens. Collins has had a quiet start to the 2025 season for his lofty standards. He is averaging 4.5 catches for 65 yards per game, down from 5.7 for 84 in 2024. Collins gets a good matchup versus a struggling Baltimore defense this week, giving him one more shot at a WR1 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a199-d95b-addb-e9df06fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens LT Ronnie Stanley (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b0-deb6-a7fd-f3ff217f0000</link>
      <description>Stanley attempted to play through the ankle issue in Week 4 but left after just 16 snaps. Joe Noteboom took his spot in the lineup. With Lamar Jackson likely out for Week 5, the Ravens might be better off resting Stanley for a week or two so he is good to go when Baltimore’s superstar quarterback is back under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b0-deb6-a7fd-f3ff217f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devontez Walker (oblique) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b3-d6e9-af9d-abb3bc6b0000</link>
      <description>Walker spiked for two touchdowns in Week 2 but hasn’t been heard from since. His absence could free up a few more routes for DeAndre Hopkins, but we don’t expect fantasy managers to be crate-digging in the receiver room with Cooper Rush as the starter for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b3-d6e9-af9d-abb3bc6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Nate Wiggins (elbow) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b6-dca3-a9fb-bdbf658b0000</link>
      <description>The injuries are piling up on both sides of the ball for Baltimore. Cornerback Marlon Humphrey is expected to be out for multiple weeks with a calf injury. Fellow corner Chidobe Awuzie and linebacker Roquan Smith were also absent from practice because of hamstring injuries. The Texans got on track last week with a 26-0 win over the Titans. They have a shot at riding that momentum to another win versus a Ravens team without multiple starting defenders and likely Lamar Jackson on the other side of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1b6-dca3-a9fb-bdbf658b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1bb-deb6-a7fd-f3ffebd30000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear if this is the same knee issue that held him out of Week 2’s game against the Chiefs or a new injury entirely. We’re not sure which outcome is better. Either way, Goedert is now at risk of missing his second game of the season. Backup tight end Grant Calcaterra caught one pass in his absence two weeks ago and is not on the fantasy radar whether or not Goedert is healthy. The Eagles’ star receivers could see a slight uptick in targets if Goedert can’t suit up for Week 5 versus Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1bb-deb6-a7fd-f3ffebd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (hip/ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1c1-d6e9-af9d-abd1db030000</link>
      <description>Mims remains stuck in a part-time role despite being the recipient of plenty of offseason hype from the Broncos. He made the most of his limited opportunities in Week 4 with 69 yards and a touchdown through the air plus 16 yards and another score on the ground. A limited practice suggests he will be good to go for Week 5, but don’t expect his role to change anytime soon. Mims will be a boom/bust WR5 for his upcoming matchup with the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1c1-d6e9-af9d-abd1db030000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
