<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 23:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a02-d673-a39e-fe9353700000</link>
      <description>Mitchell has been encroaching on RB Justice Hill’s role in recent weeks and Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters on Monday that he wants to get Mitchell even more involved. While Mitchell’s limited session is less than ideal, Hill was unable to practice at all while dealing with a toe injury. Mitchell is a high-upside stash option. He should be rostered in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a02-d673-a39e-fe9353700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a08-d1e7-a1fa-7aeaf6990000</link>
      <description>Players almost always play through the “illness” injury designation, especially when it pops up this early in the week. Still, fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on this situation just to be sure. Barring a surprise, London will be a WR1 like he always is for the Falcons Week 11 date with the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a08-d1e7-a1fa-7aeaf6990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RG Chris Lindstrom (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a0b-d45b-affe-7f9fc78d0000</link>
      <description>Lindstrom played through the foot issue last week and only missed one snap in the overtime loss to Indianapolis. The DNP today is hopefully just a maintenance day. If the foot issue got worse in Week 10, Jovaughn Gwyn would seemingly be in line to start in his place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a0b-d45b-affe-7f9fc78d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (hip) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a09-d673-a39e-fe991ab80000</link>
      <description>Likely is on track to play, but his status is worth following for fantasy managers who roster TE Mark Andrews. The latter player could see a decent target share increase if Likely were to sit out in Week 11 against the Browns. Andrews has largely been relying on touchdowns to score his fantasy points in recent weeks. An uptick in targets between the 20s would be helpful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a09-d673-a39e-fe991ab80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a13-d713-ad9e-7e575fed0000</link>
      <description>This was expected. Just yesterday, the Denver Gazette’s Chris Tomasson reported that the Broncos are considering placing Dobbins on injured reserve. Until they make an official call, though, we are on practice watch. Broncos rookie RB RJ Harvey is an RB2 this week, while RB Tyler Badie warrants PPR FLEX consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a13-d713-ad9e-7e575fed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Davante Adams (oblique) will be ready to play in Week 11 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a12-d1e7-a1fa-7afa785c0000</link>
      <description>Adams did not practice Wednesday. The veteran wideout left Week 10 late in the game while holding his back in pain. McVay later told reporters that he could have returned if needed. Adams is up to nine receiving touchdowns this year after scoring another last week. Even as the clear WR2 in LA’s offense, he is pushing for a WR1 ranking heading into a must-win game versus the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a12-d1e7-a1fa-7afa785c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder/toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a1b-d1e7-a1fa-7afbfdd70000</link>
      <description>Jones was held out of last Wednesday’s practice entirely and still suited up. He should have no issues playing in Week 11. In Week 10, Jones led the Vikings with nine carries, which he turned into 47 scoreless yards. Jordan Mason only saw four attempts. As the lead back of the team, Jones could work his way into the RB2 ranks for a Week 11 date with the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a1b-d1e7-a1fa-7afbfdd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a26-d45b-affe-7fb61fdb0000</link>
      <description>Schultz has been dealing with the shoulder issue for a few weeks and it hasn’t cost him any playing time yet. He should be able to return to practice later this week, though fantasy managers may want to keep an eye on the situation. Schultz caught 7-of-11 targets in Week 10 against the Jags. He will push for a low-end TE1 ranking if there aren’t any surprises with the shoulder issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a26-d45b-affe-7fb61fdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a2f-d1e7-a1fa-7aef31320000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez played ahead of rookie Jacory Croskey-Merritt in the first half of the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions. He then hurt his shoulder in the third quarter and JCM took over. Rodriguez did not return after playing just one snap in the second half. A limited practice suggests he should be good to go for Week 11 versus Miami. In a game that could be close, Rodriguez will have some RB3 potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a2f-d1e7-a1fa-7aef31320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a33-d45b-affe-7fb72e240000</link>
      <description>Gordon was active last week but only saw one carry. Jaylen Wright operated as the backup to De’Von Achane, seeing five rush attempts. With the backup role now undecided, neither Gordon nor Wright should be cracking any fantasy lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a33-d45b-affe-7fb72e240000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
