<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 3-of-7 targets for 71 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d294-a19b-f4f4ea660000</link>
      <description>Justin Hebert struggled to get the ball to Johnston for much of this game, but a 60-yard dime from Herbert to the 24-year-old wideout saved the fantasy day. That’s three touchdowns already for the 2023 first-round pick, and while there are some other mouths to feed in this offense, it’s been clear over the first two contests that the Chargers have made getting the football to Johnston a priority. He remains volatile, but there’s a ton of upside even in a touch matchup against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d294-a19b-f4f4ea660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 5-of-5 targets for 48 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-da67-a99f-dcf730940000</link>
      <description>McConkey was efficient, but the second-year wideout was third in targets against the Las Vegas defense, as it appeared the Raiders wanted Keenan Allen and Quentin Johnston to beat them, instead. They did. The 23-year-old had one 19-yard connection with Justin Herbert, but the rest was dink-and-dunk stuff. It could be worse, but it’s not exactly what fantasy managers signed up for. Expect McConkey to be more involved against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-da67-a99f-dcf730940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) caught 5-of-8 passes for 38 yards in the Raiders’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-dc44-a9d9-57e6d6330000</link>
      <description>Some if Bowers’ disappointing game can be blamed on the knee injury. Some of it can be blamed on Geno Smith playing an atrocious football game. Ultimately, it adds up to Bowers doing very little, and his one deep target was overthrown by Smith in the end zone. Bowers is obviously a TE1 as long as he’s healthy enough to play, but fantasy managers are going to need to see Smith play a lot better for him to reach his ceiling in Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-dc44-a9d9-57e6d6330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 6-of-12 targets for 68 yards in the Raiders’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c7-d86f-abdd-55ff03470000</link>
      <description>Meyers was the top target for Geno Smith, but Smith struggled to get him the ball as seen in a 50-percent rate of completion rate on those attempts. That does make back-to-back games that the 28-year-old wideout has received double-digit targets, and there was just enough success to call it a decent fantasy game for the clear top wideout in the Las Vegas passing attack. Meyers will likely see a similar amount of action — and hopefully more receptions — against the Commanders in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c7-d86f-abdd-55ff03470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 3-of-8 passes for 12 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c8-d294-a19b-f4f8b1310000</link>
      <description>Geno Smith was wholly ineffective Monday night, and Tucker was one of a few Las Vegas receivers who didn’t have much success on a night where the Raiders didn’t complete a single pass thrown over 10 yards. It’s worth noting that Tucker doubled the targets of Dont’e Thornton (one catch, 20 yards on four passes thrown his way), and he’s pretty clearly the WR2 on the Raiders’ for now. He’s nowhere close to that range from a fantasy perspective for Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c8-d294-a19b-f4f8b1310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said it would be “hard” to start QB Justin Fields (concussion) if he doesn’t practice on Wednesday or Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5269-da67-a99f-defda9e70000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Fields, who suffered a head injury in the second half of the Jets’ Week 2 loss to the Bills, won’t suit up if he can’t get on the practice field by Thursday. Fields, who had never had a documented brain injury before Week 2, is in the league’s concussion protocol. Tyrod Taylor would be under center for the Jets in Week 3 against the Bucs if Fields can’t go. “We have to get more information so we can be more pinpointed on that, but we do have to look at it that way,” Glenn said. “If Justin can’t play, then Tyrod would be the guy, and we’d build a plan that’s suitable for him.” Glenn said he has “no concerns” about Taylor, 36, who completed seven of 11 attempts for 56 yards and a touchdown against Buffalo. Taylor would be a decent option in superflex formats if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5269-da67-a99f-defda9e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed QB Mike White, formerly of the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-528f-d654-a19b-d2ef96100000</link>
      <description>The Bengals are scrambling for practice squad quarterbacks after losing Joe Burrow (toe) for most of the rest of the regular season. Jake Browning will take over at QB with Burrow sidelined, and White — who completed 12-of-24 passes for 166 yards and two touchdowns for Buffalo in the preseason — could eventually make his way onto the game day roster. The Bengals also signed QB Sean Clifford, formerly of the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-528f-d654-a19b-d2ef96100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed QB Sean Clifford, formerly of the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52d9-d051-a3df-7ef9d61c0000</link>
      <description>Clifford will join newly signed Mike White on the Cincy practice squad as Jake Browning takes over at quarterback for the remainder of the season following Joe Burrow’s season-ending toe injury. Brett Rypien is expected to be the team’s backup to Clifford. Either White or Clifford will serve as QB3. Clifford completed 9-of-17 attempts for 44 scoreless yards in three preseason outings for Green Bay last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52d9-d051-a3df-7ef9d61c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reports there’s “no guarantee” LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) plays in Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52f6-d606-a5db-5ef61b250000</link>
      <description>The Vikings offensive line has struggled mightily through two games with Darrisaw out and C Ryan Kelly dealing with a head injury. J.J. McCarthy, who’s out for multiple weeks with an ankle sprain, has been pressured on 40 percent of his drop backs through Week 2, the eighth highest rate in the NFL. No Darrisaw for Minnesota would be a potential problem for QB Carson Wentz as he takes over the Vikings offense in McCarthy’s absence. Pro Football Focus grades the Bengals’ pass rush as the 13th best in the league through two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52f6-d606-a5db-5ef61b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) is “questionable at best” for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-533b-d654-a19b-d37b4ea90000</link>
      <description>Porter missed last week’s loss to the Seahawks while recovering from a hamstring injury and could sit out this week against the Patriots. The Steelers’ secondary has struggled to start the season, allowing the NFL’s sixth highest adjusted yards per attempt and the seventh highest accuracy rate. Porter’s absence could be a boon for Drake Maye in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-533b-d654-a19b-d37b4ea90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
