<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that the Bills are expected to re-sign DT Jordan Phillips later this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</link>
      <description>Phillips worked out with the Bills today, and evidently, it went well. The 32-year-old previously played for the Bills in 2019 and from 2022-2023. He spent the 2024 season with the Cowboys. He can be expected to serve as a rotational player on the Bills’ interior defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Tomasson of the Denver Gazette reports that the Broncos waived WR Joaquin Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</link>
      <description>Davis caught one pass for 14 yards after being added as an undrafted free agent by the Broncos. The 6-foot-4 wideout is likely to hang around on the practice squad. Denver also waived linebacker Andrew Farmer according to Tomasson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Patriots are “shopping” S Kyle Dugger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de1f-de13-afdc-dedf3fb00000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s report backs up what Jordan Schultz reported on August 20th. The Patriots’ new coaching staff is hoping to move on from Dugger. Earlier today, ESPN’s Mike Reissreportedthat it has been a “challenging year” for Dugger, who underwent offseason ankle surgery and has played “deep into preseason games” this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de1f-de13-afdc-dedf3fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions released CB Dicaprio Bootle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de17-d332-a1fd-de37c7200000</link>
      <description>Bootle, 27, was signed in the middle of July, and didn’t stick around past the summer. The speedy corner will now be free to sign with another team, but is likely just roster-fodder at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de17-d332-a1fd-de37c7200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived CB Micah Abraham.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de44-dbe3-a9bb-fe57c8830000</link>
      <description>Abraham suited up for two Broncos preseason games this year, allowing one catch for nine yards on two targets. He recorded zero tackles. The 2024 sixth-round pick will now look to make a final roster elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de44-dbe3-a9bb-fe57c8830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars traded T Fred Johnson to the Eagles in exchange for for a 2026 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de5b-d332-a1fd-de7ff04b0000</link>
      <description>Johnson returns to the Eagles after signing with the Jaguars in March. The 28-year-old will likely be a backup bookend for Philadelphia; a role that he served for the majority of the 2024 season with the club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de5b-d332-a1fd-de7ff04b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released RB Jarveon Howard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de66-db7b-a5dd-fe6607700000</link>
      <description>Howard’s release comes with the designation of “failure to disclose condition,” which isn’t a common one. The 25-year-old could be a candidate for a practice squad, but it seems likely it won’t be with Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de66-db7b-a5dd-fe6607700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles traded T Darian Kinnard to the Packers in exchange for a 2027 sixth-round draft selection.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de99-dbe3-a9bb-fedb6e7d0000</link>
      <description>It’s the third trade of the day for the Eagles, and the second involving a tackle. After re-acquiring Fred Johnson from the Jaguars, Kinnard become expendable, and instead he’ll serve in a similar capacity for Green Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de99-dbe3-a9bb-fedb6e7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton thinks Marvin Mims is the Broncos’ No. 2 wide receiver.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-deb0-de13-afdc-defb241d0000</link>
      <description>That’s good news. Stuck in a part-time offensive role through two NFL seasons, Mims has teased excellent per-play efficiency, particularly as a post-catch producer. Sutton aptly notes that Mims “can make plays anywhere,” and his special teams returner showings have bagged him second- and first-team All-Pro honors. If Mims has indeed secured the No. 2 wide receiver role and will be allowed to remain on the field in two-wide receiver sets, we could see a breakout season from him in 2025. His PPR WR55, 13th-round ADP makes him a low-risk, high-reward draft pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-deb0-de13-afdc-defb241d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The San Francisco Standard’s Tim Kawakami reports, Jauan Jennings’ “lingering calf injury and long contractual stalemate with the 49ers could combine to send him to the injured reserve list this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dece-de13-afdc-decf483b0000</link>
      <description>Kawakami outlines multiple scenarios that could take place between now and Week 1, with frustration growing on both the 49ers’ and Jennings’ sides. Jennings is reportedly set to make $1.5 million guaranteed, and up to $3.5 million in performance incentives this year. Kawakami suggests the idea of a designated-to-return/injured reserve spots “could be a tacit threat to the Jennings camp.” Should they opt to make the move, it could also serve as “a nervous compromise and delay tactic for this increasingly tense situation.” This scenario is bad for all involved, though, as it limits their ability to bring back other players who are also injured. It’s entirely “possible nothing dramatic happens this week,” Jennings shows up for Week 1 with a healthy calf and all of this fades into the background. Still, the tense situation in San Francisco is worth noting. Regardless, for fantasy leagues with an injured reserve spot, Jennings looks like a sharp pick at his PPR WR46 ADP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dece-de13-afdc-decf483b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
