<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 20:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Buscaglia believes Keon Coleman will lead the Bills wideouts in snaps, targets, and yards in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b52-db7b-a5dd-bb568acb0000</link>
      <description>“Even if a traditional breakout into him becoming a true No. 1 NFL receiver doesn’t occur, the table is set for Coleman to lead the Bills in almost everything,” Buscaglia writes while predicting Coleman to get “85 to 90 percent” of the snaps on offense. Coleman, who is available on many waiver wires, may be a worthy preemptive scoop ahead of Sunday if you have space on your roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b52-db7b-a5dd-bb568acb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Denzel Ward (shoulder) is off Cleveland’s final Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b5a-db7b-a5dd-bb5e6dc70000</link>
      <description>He’ll play against the Bengals after notching a full practice upgrade on Friday. Ward had two limited sessions earlier in the week and has been dealing with this shoulder injury since the middle of August. We hope Mr. Ward enjoys his afternoon chasing Tee Higgins and Ja’Marr Chase around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b5a-db7b-a5dd-bb5e6dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (hamstring) remained limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b64-db7b-a5dd-bb6436c10000</link>
      <description>It looks like he remains on track to play on Monday, and the Bears badly need that to be the case with Roschon Johnson missing back-to-back practices. Chicago doesn’t have another back on its active roster behind D’Andre Swift and would likely need to elevate Brittain Brown from the practice squad and sign another back to elevate if both Johnson and Monangai missed Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b64-db7b-a5dd-bb6436c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roschon Johnson (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b66-dbe3-a9bb-3b77962a0000</link>
      <description>Two is a trend as the Bears prepare for Monday Night Football against the Vikings. Johnson has been sidelined by this injury for most of training camp and it wouldn’t be completely surprising if an IR stint came for him over the weekend if he can’t practice on Saturday. He looks very doubtful for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b66-dbe3-a9bb-3b77962a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b43-db7b-a5dd-bb47748c0000</link>
      <description>Being limited in consecutive practices generally puts veterans on track to play, so overall, this is a good sign. Given the duration of Johnson’s groin rehab, dating back to July, and his new calf issue, we would really like to see Johnson graduate to full participation on Saturday. The Bears face the Vikings in Week 1’s Monday Night Football game. Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hamstring) did not practice but DB Josh Blackwell (Groin) was upgraded to limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b43-db7b-a5dd-bb47748c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey (calf) was seen “working on a side field as the 49ers begin their Friday practice.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b6b-db7b-a5dd-bb6f02380000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey was seen wearing pads during warmups, which briefly gave us hope that he would return to full participation today. He was limited in Thursday’s session and we expect him to receive the same designation today. His Week 1 status is entirely up in the air. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan is set to address the media at 1:45 pm on the West Coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b6b-db7b-a5dd-bb6f02380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane (calf) is not on Miami’s final injury report for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b68-db7b-a5dd-bb6c8f970000</link>
      <description>As expected, he’ll start and play against the Colts in Week 1, shouldering the majority of the load for Miami in the backfield. Achane got in a full practice on Friday for the first time all week. He’ll be on the RB1 line in fantasy leagues. Ollie Gordon will back up Achane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b68-db7b-a5dd-bb6c8f970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Tyreek Hill (oblique/calf) is off Miami’s final Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b6d-d332-a1fd-9f7f23770000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday and will be good to go against the Colts. He profiles as a high-end WR2 for the occasion. Hill had only gotten in limited sessions on Wednesday and Thursday but never appeared to be in any real danger of missing the tilt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b6d-d332-a1fd-9f7f23770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) has been ruled out for Miami’s Week 1 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b70-dbe3-a9bb-3b7307600000</link>
      <description>Waller wasn’t able to stay healthy before he retired and it doesn’t appear the year off helped much. Julian Hill will draw the start at tight end for the Dolphins in Week 1, which likely means they’ll use a lot of Alec Ingold at fullback and run 20-personnel more often. We’ll see how quickly Waller is able to shake this off, but we have our doubts he’ll be available any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b70-dbe3-a9bb-3b7307600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins G James Daniels (ankle) is questionable for Miami’s Week 1 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b74-de13-afdd-5fff20a70000</link>
      <description>He was a DNP on Friday after a surprise ankle injury in Thursday’s practice. That would certainly lead us to believe he’s on the doubtful side of questionable. Daniel Brunskill and Kion Smith are potential fill-ins for Daniels should he miss Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b74-de13-afdd-5fff20a70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
