<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 13:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles hired Mike Pellegrino as their new defensive backs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5906-d355-a5bd-df56a27a0000</link>
      <description>The former college lacrosse player entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as a coaching assistant with the Patriots in 2015. He was promoted to cornerbacks coach in 2019 and held that role through 2024. He served as the Bills’ nickels coach in 2025. Pellegrino, 32, takes over a talented, young Eagles secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5906-d355-a5bd-df56a27a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Seahawks are hiring Daniel Stern “possibly as their pass-game strategist.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5918-d042-afbc-7dda013a0000</link>
      <description>Stern most recently served as the Ravens’ director of football strategy and assistant quarterbacks coach. His new role will likely be formalized once the Seahawks’ new offensive coordinator is hired. This is a fun one. Stern gained notoriety as a 25-year-old football analyst with the Ravens back in 2019, then in his fourth season with the Ravens, assisting former head coach John Harbaugh execute their plan to go for it on a play that resulted in a 4th-and-2 touchdown run by Lamar Jackson—against the Seahawks. Stern has advanced up the Ravens’ ranks since then. He was reportedly close to following former Ravens OC and new Browns head coach Todd Monken to Cleveland, but will instead reunite with Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5918-d042-afbc-7dda013a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys hired Kyle Fuller as their new assistant offensive line coach and quality control coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5906-d042-afbc-7dd6a0940000</link>
      <description>The former NFL offensive lineman entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as offensive quality control coach with the Raiders last season. He previously worked as a graduate assistant at North Carolina and Appalachian State.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5906-d042-afbc-7dd6a0940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports that the Cardinals are set to hire Zac Etheridge as their new cornerbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5961-d355-a5bd-df75fc040000</link>
      <description>Etheridge has coached in the college ranks since 2012 and spent last season serving as the University of Miami’s defensive backs coach and defensive pass game coordinator. He served as Houston’s defensive backs coach in 2024. Before that, he spent the 2021-2023 seasons working as Auburn’s secondary coach and was also named associate head coach in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5961-d355-a5bd-df75fc040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders will interview Seahawks S coach Jeff Howard for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-596f-d89c-a1be-ffff06df0000</link>
      <description>Howard has coached in the NFL since 2013 and has been in his current role with the Seahawks for the past two seasons, He worked as the Chargers’ linebackers coach for one year before that. He spent 2020-2022 with the Browns as their defensive backs coach and pass game coordinator after a seven-year stint as a defensive assistant with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-596f-d89c-a1be-ffff06df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said he “wouldn’t be surprised” if Commanders general manager Adam Peters is “active” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-595a-d355-a5bd-df5eb74f0000</link>
      <description>Per Over The Cap, the Commanders currently have the fifth-most salary cap space with more than $75.4 million available in 2026. Rapoport notes that general manager Adam Peters has been an active trader in recent seasons. Regarding free agency, Rapoport adds that “with a good, young quarterback, the time to spend is now.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-595a-d355-a5bd-df5eb74f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers hired Sean Spence to their defensive staff.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5972-d355-a5bd-df767d6a0000</link>
      <description>Spence is expected to serve as the Chargers’ new inside linebackers coach, though the role has not yet been finalized. The former NFL linebacker (2012-2017) began his coaching career as a special teams analyst at Western Michigan in 2023. He coached linebackers for them in 2024 and edges in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5972-d355-a5bd-df767d6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Jaguars “plan to play” Travis Hunter as a full-time cornerback and part-time wide receiver in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5998-d355-a5bd-dfdcf3cf0000</link>
      <description>Per Wolfe, the Jaguars believe Hunter can be an “elite” cornerback, while still being “an impact player” on offense. For fantasy purposes, this is unfortunate. Hunter may be stuck rotating in as a contributor in three-wide receiver sets, which would make him frustratingly unreliable, though head coach Liam Coen will likely try to scheme up ways to get the ball in his hands. On the plus side, Wolfe said Hunter will be “full-go” by Week 1. The Jaguars are reportedly expected to let one of their free agent cornerbacks, Montaric Brown or Greg Newsome, walk in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5998-d355-a5bd-dfdcf3cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Colts could “be aggressive” in their pursuit of Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson via a tag-and-trade scenario or free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-59de-d355-a5bd-dfdeccbb0000</link>
      <description>Bengals DC Lou Anarumo and DL coach Marion Hobby both coached Hendrickson, in the exact same roles, when all three were employed by the Bengals for four-plus seasons. Hendrickson’s relationship with the Bengals has soured, though the front office has thus far been unwilling to let the talented pass rusher leave town. This will be worth watching. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-59de-d355-a5bd-dfdeccbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe said “don’t be surprised” if the Browns do not draft a quarterback in the first round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-592e-d629-a1bc-f93fa00e0000</link>
      <description>The Browns have two first-round picks this year. Wolfe reports that the Browns believe they are “close to set” on defense and are expected to “go heavy on offense” in the 2026 NFL Draft. New head coach Todd Monken’s scheme is said to have more “flexibility” than former head coach Kevin Stefanski’s scheme did, and the Browns apparently believe Monken’s scheme could allow Shedeur Sanders to “use his play-making ability” more effectively. The Browns also “believe” Deshaun Watson will compete with Sanders for the starting role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-592e-d629-a1bc-f93fa00e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
