<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings open Blake Cashman’s practice window.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deed-d94a-a79d-dfedd5b10000</link>
      <description>Cashman has been on injured reserve since suffered a hamstring injury in Week 1 against the Bears. Now the seventh-year linebacker will have his 21-day return window opened, allowing him a chance to ramp up before making his return to the field. Cashman totaled 69 tackles and 4.5 sacks with the Vikings last season and tallied three tackles in his limited action this season. He’s not a lock to return in Week 7, but the decision to designate him for return means the Vikings can activate him at any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deed-d94a-a79d-dfedd5b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Lisa Salters reports Deebo Samuel (heel) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df02-def2-abdb-df63e6740000</link>
      <description>Deebo entered the weekend as a game-time decision. While the team will still probably take a good look at him during warmups, but the early report seems like good news regarding his availability. Samuel played through the same heel injury last week and managed to log only one practice this week, so hopefully he isn’t too limited on Monday night. With Terry McLaurin (quad) still sidelined, the Commanders can ill-afford to be without Samuel, who has caught 14 passes for 168 yards and two touchdowns over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df02-def2-abdb-df63e6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray (foot) is “the starting quarterback” when he’s healthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-dd4c-afb9-ffd9d5e20000</link>
      <description>Of course, it’s kind of telling that the question was even asked. Jacoby Brissett’s 320-yard game against a solid Colts defense — mostly without Marvin Harrison Jr. — certainly showcased the Cardinals offense in a different light than what we’ve seen from Murray up to this point. Murray is averaging just 6.0 yards per attempt in five starts, while Brissett hit 7.1 in turning Zay Jones and Michael Wilson into more involved players. Gannon complimented Brissett’s “poise and command” while Wilson tellingly complimented Brissett by noting: “His ability to stay in the pocket, deliver strikes, his vision of the game, throws a catchable ball.” We don’t quite see a change as imminent, but Brissett putting a strong foot forward on Sunday at least opens up the possibility of an in-season benching for Murray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-dd4c-afb9-ffd9d5e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Cairo Santos (thigh) questionable for Week 6 against the Commanders, the Bears have elevated K Jake Moody from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-db72-a199-ff5bc4c00000</link>
      <description>The decision to elevate Moody suggests Santos will be inactive for Monday night’s game against the Commanders, although fantasy managers will want to check inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to confirm. Moody converted 1-of-3 field goal attempts this season and was cut by the 49ers after Week 1. A career 74.2 percent kicker, fantasy managers counting on Santos can pivot to Moody in a pinch if Santos is ultimately ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-db72-a199-ff5bc4c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said EDGE Lukas Van Ness (foot) “avoided serious injury.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df46-d94a-a79d-df4f50a40000</link>
      <description>So in other words, more of a short-term loss than a long-term loss and we can probably expect Van Ness to miss Week 7. LaFleur would only say how much time Van Ness misses “remains to be seen.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df46-d94a-a79d-df4f50a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports Garrett Wilson “appears to have avoided a serious knee injury” in Week 6’s loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df45-d94a-a79d-df4d12690000</link>
      <description>This news comes after Wilson underwent an MRI to reveal the extent of the damage. As Cimini points out, The winless Jets have two games before their Week 9 bye, which could factor into how soon he returns to the field. The Jets already have a painfully thin receiving room that is now expected to feature Allen Lazard and Josh Reynolds as its top options. After watching Justin Fields fail to top 100 passing yards for a second time this season, there’s little reason to take a shot on either while Wilson is out,</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df45-d94a-a79d-df4d12690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed QB Anthony Richardson (eye) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df49-d94a-a79d-df4d1f3d0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games, though he was already missing all the games anyway while watching Daniel Jones, so that’s nothing too new. Richardson, per ESPN’s Stephen Holder “was hospitalized after a pole that he had affixed an elastic stretch band to snapped during his pregame routine, resulting in the pole forcefully impacting his face.” Through three years, Richardson’s best comp is the French waiter inThe Simpsonsthat somehow falls into a dumptruck filled with rat traps. We’d be unsurprised if Richardson was left on IR after the Colts find a replacement backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df49-d94a-a79d-df4d1f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanner Hudson (concussion) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df4d-dd4c-afb9-ffcd303b0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimated DNP, but we almost never see someone clear protocol ahead of a Thursday night game. With Mike Gesicki also likely out, it looks like Noah Fant may have some stream appeal as a TE2 as the Bengals are forced to rely heavily on him and Drew Sample in their well-stocked tight end platoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df4d-dd4c-afb9-ffcd303b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals listed Trey Hendrickson (back) as a DNP on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df50-db72-a199-ff5be02a0000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson is reportedly day-to-day after suffering a back injury in Sunday’s loss to the Packers. The star pass rusher drawing a DNP on the team’s estimated report isn’t all that surprising, but giving the timeline for his injury, we’ll assume he still has a chance to suit up against the Steelers until we hear otherwise. Hendrickson has totaled four sacks and 10 tackles in the six games he has appeared in this season and would be a major loss for the league’s 30th ranked defense if he is unable to go on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df50-db72-a199-ff5be02a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals listed DE Shemar Stewart (ankle) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df54-dd4c-afb9-ffd524320000</link>
      <description>Stewart hasn’t played since Week 2, but a full practice designation on Monday is a good indication he’ll be suiting up on Thursday night against the Steelers. The rookie first-rounder has totaled just two tackles in the two games he’s appeared in this season, and could see a fairly significant role if Trey Hendrickson (back) is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df54-dd4c-afb9-ffd524320000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
