<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:02:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 5-of-5 targets for 60 yards in Seattle’s Divisional Round win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf60-d35e-a1bf-cfe22d7d0000</link>
      <description>Kupp was able to take advantage of the extra attention Jaxon Smith-Njigba drew today to lead the team in receiving yards. It was the first time he’d cleared 50 yards since Week 10. Kupp will likely remain a touchdown-or-bust bet in DFS in the NFC Championship game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf60-d35e-a1bf-cfe22d7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rasheed Shaheed rushed two times for 27 yards in Seattle’s Divisional Round win over the 49ers, failing to catch either of his two targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf62-dc7a-af9b-cfff3f8f0000</link>
      <description>He opened the game with a kick return touchdown, narrowly getting past 49ers K Eddy Pineiro’s studs up, poor form tackle attempt. We were hoping to see Shaheed a little more involved in the offense after a bye week to work on some things, but it looks like he’s just going to be a premium can of juice that the Seahawks save for when they really need a big play. He’ll again play a big role in the NFC Championship game, just not a big role for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf62-dc7a-af9b-cfff3f8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Barner rushed one time for two yards in Seattle’s Divisional Round win over the 49ers</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf64-d35e-a1bf-cfe67c2e0000</link>
      <description>He wasn’t targeted as the Seahawks attempted just 17 passes. Barner converted a third-down on a tight end tush push. Seattle’s best option at tight end will continue to remain dependent on touchdowns to be a fantasy option, and that very much includes next week’s NFC Championship match.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf64-d35e-a1bf-cfe67c2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 2-of-5 targets for 23 yards in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf69-d968-a19b-dff968090000</link>
      <description>Jennings didn’t crack 100 yards in a game all season, but he did become a reliable red zone threat as he scored a career-high nine touchdowns on his 90 targets. Jennings will be a free agent in 2026 and would be a great fit for a team that needs a bully over the middle. He likely profiles as a WR3 in 2026, assuming he finds a reasonable landing spot where he can continue to command 90-110 targets a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf69-d968-a19b-dff968090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall caught failed to catch either of his two targets in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6a-d56e-afff-efea753b0000</link>
      <description>Unsurprising given that he entered this week looking like he was one big hit from being sidelined again as he continues to battle through the knee injury that defined his season. After a breakout first three weeks where he crossed 100 yards twice, Pearsall spent the rest of the season dealing with a PCL injury and never seemed fully healthy again. We wouldn’t be surprised if he pops up with an offseason surgery. Nevertheless, his age-26 season in 2026 looks to be in a great spot if he can rehab this and get to Week 1 healthy. Brandon Aiyuk looks likely to be released. George Kittle will be rehabbing his torn Achilles early in the season. Jauan Jennings is not a guarantee to be back. Pearsall looks like a WR2 candidate as one of the trustable targets in a Kyle Shanahan offense. “Get to Week 1 healthy,” of course, is not a minor ask for Pearsall based on his first two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6a-d56e-afff-efea753b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 5-of-6 targets for 59 yards in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6c-d968-a19b-dffdedb60000</link>
      <description>He left the game just after halftime with an injured ankle, playing only 29 of 60 snaps. Filling in admirably for George Kittle when he went on IR early in the season (and again when he missed Week 17), Tonges caught five touchdowns and averaged 4.5 catches for 44.5 yards before Kittle returned in Week 7. He’ll be a restricted free agent in 2026, and the 49ers would likely love to have him back to fill in while Kittle rehabs his torn Achilles. Tonges’ situation would leave him as a low-end fill-in TE1 while Kittle is hurt assuming no one tries the rarely-seen “steal away a restricted free agent” gambit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6c-d968-a19b-dffdedb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught his only target for one yard in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6f-d56e-afff-efef5ee50000</link>
      <description>Robinson came on as a depth piece late in the year (after a brief DUI suspension) as he played over Kendrick Bourne and shined in the NFC Wild Card game to the tune of a 6/111/1 receiving line against the Eagles. He’s under contract with the 49ers for 2026 but should only be a depth piece unless several rehab assignments go long – which, given that it’s the 49ers, perhaps we shouldn’t pretend that won’t be the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf6f-d56e-afff-efef5ee50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne failed to catch either of his two targets in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf70-d35e-a1bf-cff216320000</link>
      <description>Bourne went for 142 yards in Week 4, 142 yards in Week 5, and 180 yards from Weeks 7-18. It was a fun ride. Bourne enters free agency as a respectable outside depth receiver, but he hasn’t cracked 600 yards since 2021 and will need extreme circumstances to be fantasy-relevant going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf70-d35e-a1bf-cff216320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Juszczyk caught his only target for 11 yards in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf72-d968-a19b-dff340500000</link>
      <description>Juicecheck had his most prolific regular season in terms of catches and touches since 2021, recording a 24-213-2 receiving line in the regular season and a 4/49 performance in the Wild Card round against the Eagles. He’ll enter free agency again this offseason and figures to be a low-priority target for the 49ers entering his age-35 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf72-d968-a19b-dff340500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddy Pineiro made both of his field-goal attempts in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf73-d35e-a1bf-cff31d410000</link>
      <description>Pineiro missed just one of his 29 attempts on the season — 32 if you count the postseason — after the 49ers finally moved on from Jake Moody following Week 1. He now has hit 139-of-155 regular season attempts in six years in the league. It’s very funny that he was freely available to anyone before Week 2 and had a season this good. A 2026 free agent, the 49ers will probably prioritize re-signing him after this performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf73-d35e-a1bf-cff31d410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
