<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 03:30:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brandin Cooks caught 2-of-6 targets for 20 yards in the Bills’ Divisional Round loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cee8-dc7a-af9b-cfffba340000</link>
      <description>Cooks made two spectacular almost catches. On one of them, he caught the ball while twisting on the sideline, and his knee came down in bounds, but his wrist landed a fraction of a second earlier and landed out of bounds. The other play was far more controversial. It seemed like Cooks had hauled in a 44-yard pass to set the Bills up for a game-winning field goal in overtime, but the ball was stripped away by a Broncos defender. The Bills believed Cooks was down by contact before the ball was stripped loose, but the call was not reviewed, and the Broncos would then drive for a game-winning field goal of their own. The 32-year-old came on down the stretch for the Bills, showing that he still has enough deep speed to make big plays. He finished the season with 24 catches on 36 targets for 279 yards and no touchdowns in 15 games with the Bills and Saints. Some team will sign him in free agency and give him a role as a deep threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cee8-dc7a-af9b-cfffba340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims Jr. caught all eight of his targets for 93 yards and a touchdown in Denver’s AFC Divisional Round win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ceed-d968-a19b-defd60340000</link>
      <description>Mims had topped 30 yards receiving only twice during the regular season, but he showed up big when the Broncos needed him most. Both Pat Bryant (concussion) and Troy Franklin (hamstring) left this game early, and Mims stepped up to fill their shoes. His biggest catch was a go-ahead score late in the fourth quarter. After the Bills had to bring in fourth-string cornerback Dane Jackson, Mims burned him on a corner route and hauled in a tough over-the-shoulder catch in the end zone. It’s unclear if either of Franklin or Bryant will be cleared to play next week, so Mims may be relied on heavily again, but with Bo Nix out for the remainder of the season, it’s hard to get excited about this Broncos passing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ceed-d968-a19b-defd60340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said Jarrett Stidham will start the AFC Championship game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ceec-d968-a19b-defdecb00000</link>
      <description>Stidham has not thrown an NFL pass since 2023, but after the jaw-dropping reveal that Bo Nix (ankle) will miss the remainder of the playoffs after breaking a bone deep in overtime, Payton announced that Stidham will start the AFC title game. Sam Ehlinger is the only other quarterback on the roster. Stidham has a 1-3 career record as a starter with a 59.4 percent completion rate, eight touchdowns, and eight interceptions. Whoever wins the Patriots/Texans game on Sunday will almost undoubtedly be favored next Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ceec-d968-a19b-defdecb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (knee) left Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cefd-d56e-afff-eefdf7230000</link>
      <description>He was tackled awkwardly on a third-and-1 carry, spent some time in the medical tent after walking off gingerly with trainers, and was later spotted walking to the locker room. Charbonnet had five carries for 20 yards before leaving. Kenneth Walker seems likely to carry the bulk of the load with Charbonnet out, though George Holani could get extra work here seeing as how as of this typing it’s 24-6 Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cefd-d56e-afff-eefdf7230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired Kevin Stefanski as their new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf01-d968-a19b-dff1fca30000</link>
      <description>Stefanski gets a five-year contract from the Falcons. This has seemed to be a fait accompli since John Harbaugh agreed to a deal with the Giants. Stefanski was reportedly the favorite in Atlanta on Friday per SNY’s Connor Hughes, and after Stefanski got the second interview docket finalized, the Falcons just decided to go ahead and make that irrelevant. Atlanta gets the best available offensive mind on the market, and Bijan Robinson should only continue to flourish under Stefanski’s guidance. His biggest task will be, as it was in Cleveland, getting the most out of what looks to be a substandard quarterback room. Michael Penix (knee) is under contract, but perhaps not a certainty to be ready for the season. The Falcons could cut Kirk Cousins to free up salary space, but don’t necessarily have to if Stefanski would turn to him as a starter. Atlanta’s quarterback decision will set up some offseason dominoes. But for now, they have to be thrilled to land a two-time AP Coach of the Year — even if he is coming off two rough seasons in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf01-d968-a19b-dff1fca30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 4-of-9 targets for 53 yards in the Broncos’ AFC Divisional Round win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf0d-d56e-afff-efed68830000</link>
      <description>Sutton was matched up against the Bills’ top cornerback, Christian Benford, for much of the day and was held in check for most of it. He did make a few key catches near the end of the fourth quarter and could shoulder a heavy burden next week with both Pat Bryant (concussion) and Troy Franklin (hamstring) banged up. However, with Jarett Stidham at quarterback, it’s hard to get overly excited about Sutton next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf0d-d56e-afff-efed68830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil’Jordan Humphrey caught 2-of-5 targets for 31 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ AFC Divisional Round win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf14-d56e-afff-effc5ee00000</link>
      <description>Humphrey was thrust into a larger role after Pat Bryant suffered a concussion on the first drive. However, things didn’t start great for Humphrey as he dropped a sure-fire touchdown pass from Bo Nix on that same drive. Later, right before halftime, Humphrey was able to get behind fourth-string safety Darnell Savage for a touchdown. The 27-year-old may be relied on again next week if Bryant can’t return to the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf14-d56e-afff-effc5ee00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 1-of-3 targets for seven yards in the Broncos’ Divisional Round win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf17-d35e-a1bf-cfd76e710000</link>
      <description>You’d be forgiven if you didn’t notice that Engram played in this game. The Bills are generally pretty strong against tight ends, but the Broncos didn’t seem too interested in getting Engram involved in this one. There’s a chance that changes next week with backup quarterback Jarrett Stidham under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf17-d35e-a1bf-cfd76e710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 1-of-3 targets for 10 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ AFC Divisional Round loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf19-d968-a19b-dff9be0b0000</link>
      <description>The touchdown catch was a nice play where Coleman caught a quick slant, planted his foot, avoided a defender, and then dove to stretch the ball across the end zone. The 22-year-old had a brutal drop in the end zone earlier in the game on a ball that hit him right in the hands. It wouldn’t have been a touchdown anyway due to a holding penalty, but the drop is indicative of the struggles Coleman has had in his second season. The former second-round pick caught 38 of 59 targets during the regular season for 404 yards and four touchdowns. He only played in 13 games and was a healthy inactive in a few, as Coleman dealt with some off-field disciplinary issues. It wouldn’t be out of the question for the Bills to see if another team wanted to take a gamble on Coleman, but his value may be too low for a trade right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf19-d968-a19b-dff9be0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mecole Hardman caught 1-of-2 targets for four yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ AFC Divisional Round loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf1f-d968-a19b-dfffde170000</link>
      <description>Hardman was elevated from the practice squad with both Gabe Davis and Tyrell Shavers suffering season-ending ACL injuries. His touchdown was the first score of the game for the Bills, but he also dropped a catch that would have kept Buffalo’s drive alive at the end of the fourth quarter. Hardman had no catches on just one target during the regular season as he bounced around a few practice squads. He’ll probably need to settle for a practice squad spot in 2026 as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf1f-d968-a19b-dfffde170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
