<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet rushed 12 times for 39 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals, adding two receptions for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8425-d6e9-af9d-8eb5b3060000</link>
      <description>Returning from a one-game absence with an apparently minor foot issue, Charbonnet converted a one-yard score in the second quarter after getting stuffed on an earlier goal-line tote. He appeared to have another touchdown in the fourth frame, a sever-yarder, but it was called back by a bogus Jaxon Smith-Njigba holding penalty. Frustrating for Charbonnet managers, but a complete nightmare for Kenneth Walker III impresarios. KWIII didn’t come particularly close to the end zone this evening, rotating work with Charbonnet on early downs and mostly ceding passing-game reps to his less efficient 1B back. Charbonnet is less efficient but has greater coaching staff trust in higher-leverage situations. That is for now at least. Maybe something changes in the 10 days Seattle has to prepare for Tampa. We wouldn’t count on it, keeping Charbonnet locked in as a high-floor FLEX despite his paltry yards per carry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8425-d6e9-af9d-8eb5b3060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 4-of-5 targets for 79 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals, adding three carries for 11 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-842b-d95b-addb-ec6f2a740000</link>
      <description>Smith-Njigba was lucky to escape with the line he did, as he somehow drew zero first half targets. He obviously went to work after the break, where he contributed several critical grabs, including a 22-yarder with 0:23 remaining to help get the Seahawks in range for the game-winning field goal. JSN was looking dangerous on the boundary this evening as he continues to become a more all-around wideout after buttering his early-career bread over the middle of the field. A bonafide WR1 despite Seattle’s limited passing-game volume, JSN will probably have to go to work in what could end up a Week 5 shootout with the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-842b-d95b-addb-ec6f2a740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 7-of-11 targets for 52 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8430-dca3-a9fb-bdb9f1aa0000</link>
      <description>McBride is stuck on just one touchdown through four contests after his 2024 scoring woes, but he has caught at least five passes for 43 yards all four times out. That’s an elite floor for the position, and we know ceiling efforts will be coming. Even if they’re not, McBride is long since proven as one of the most reliable PPR options in all of fantasy football. The Titans will be a soft Week 5 matchup for a Cardinals team that will be operating on 10 days rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8430-dca3-a9fb-bdb9f1aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado rushed two times for eight yards in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks, adding two receptions for 13 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8433-d6e9-af9d-8eb3acad0000</link>
      <description>With Trey Benson needed for bigger things in James Conner’s season-long absence, Demercado immediately re-emerged as the primary passing-down/two-minute drill back. That included in the game’s dying moments where Demercado leaked out for a seven-yard score, tying the proceedings up at 20-20. Demercado got out-touched 13-4 by Benson, but was on the field enough to prove a nuisance. The Cardinals now have 10 days to reassess ahead of a soft Titans matchup, but we would expect Demercado to remain involved. Just not enough to carve out genuine PPR value of his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8433-d6e9-af9d-8eb3acad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 3-of-6 targets for 15 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8439-d6e9-af9d-8eb9015c0000</link>
      <description>Wilson finally caught more than one pass for the first time in four games, but it is never exactly good when your season high for yardage is 15. Wilson did make a highlight-reel grab on a fourth quarter 4th-and-4, extending the drive with a one-handed catch. Cool, but Wilson is miles from re-draft relevance in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8439-d6e9-af9d-8eb9015c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dortch caught 4-of-5 targets for 35 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843b-d95b-addb-ec7f17eb0000</link>
      <description>Dortch entered the game with just four catches for 12 yards on four targets through three games. Arizona evidently wanted to put his YAC-based skill-set to use against the Seahawks. They succeeded, but there is little reason to expect this to remain a theme going forward. The 27-year-old remains best forgotten in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843b-d95b-addb-ec7f17eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo caught 2-of-4 targets for 44 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843c-dca3-a9fb-bdbdf68a0000</link>
      <description>Both the targets and yards were new season highs for the rookie second-rounder, who also drew an end zone DPI and commanded another painted area target. Good stuff, though Arroyo is going to remain a zero-floor player as he fights for looks in this run-based offense. He has yet to demonstrate enough ceiling to be worth a TE2 look in 12-team re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843c-dca3-a9fb-bdbdf68a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 4-of-5 targets for 26 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843f-d6e9-af9d-8ebf46990000</link>
      <description>The four catches were Kupp’s second most in four games as a ‘Hawk, though he’s now been held below 32 yards in 3-of-4 contests. We have little doubt Kupp is doing the “little things” well for Seattle on the real-life gridiron, but it is abundantly clear he is not going to see enough targets to be a legitimate WR3 in fantasy, while even WR4 could prove to be a stretch. That theory will be put to the test for what could be a higher-octane game in Week 5 against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843f-d6e9-af9d-8ebf46990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8441-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa32b0000</link>
      <description>Horton’s unconverted look was a deep target he probably should have caught at the goal line. The fifth-round rookie has now caught a pass in 3-of-4 contests, but he has just 10 total targets. Horton is a deep-shot role player who is unlikely to come into WR5 fantasy value this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8441-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa32b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 3-of-3 targets for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8444-d6e9-af9d-8ed40df60000</link>
      <description>The second-year pro now has a touchdown in 2-of-4 2025 appearances. Tonight’s was a 16-yard grab where he soundly beat Akeem Davis-Gaither 1-on-1. Good stuff, though rookie Elijah Arroyo was also more involved this evening. Barner is going to make some important real-life catches, but he seems unlikely to produce consistently enough to warrant a TE2 look in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8444-d6e9-af9d-8ed40df60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
