<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 5-of-9 targets for 48 yards in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-dc44-a9d9-3fe7682f0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin’s nine targets were the most of any Washington receiver, but those hoping for more deep chances after his 2-27 line against the Giants came away disappointed. There’s a good chance some of this mediocre production has to do with his training camp absence, but it doesn’t make it any less disappointing. He should still be considered in the WR2 range for Week 3 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-dc44-a9d9-3fe7682f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 7-of-8 targets for 44 yards with a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d294-a19b-fff18d380000</link>
      <description>Samuel didn’t have a rushing attempt, but did add a 50-yard kick return to open the second half. The wideout was mostly targeted in the short-to-intermediate range, with a long catch of 12 yards. The touchdown saves the fantasy day, but most of this was rather uninspiring. He profiles as a lower-end WR2 for the Week 3 contest against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d294-a19b-fff18d380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed has been diagnosed with a broken collarbone and is out indefinitely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-36c5-db7b-a5dd-b6c511740000</link>
      <description>Coach Matt LaFleur confirmed the third-year pro will miss “a lot of time.” LaFleur did say Reed should return at some point this season. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the “hope” is Reed misses “only” 6-8 weeks. The Packers have been up to their typical receiver rotation tricks through the first two weeks of 2025, but this might force LaFleur to start putting more on first-round rookie Matthew Golden’s plate. It could help that the Pack now have 10 days to prepare for Week 3 against the Browns. Still, that could prove to be wishcasting with a club that just doesn’t treat receiver the way most other teams do. Considering the aforementioned rotation and Reed’s famously streaky production, you could be hard pressed to stash him for the better part of two months even if you have an open I.R. spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-36c5-db7b-a5dd-b6c511740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Commanders believe Austin Ekeler tore his Achilles during Thursday’s Week 2 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3c31-d86f-abdd-7dbdbc030000</link>
      <description>Ekeler will undergo imaging Friday to confirm whether there’s structural damage. The 30-year-old looked visibly upset after walking off following the injury, and it would be a surprise if his 2025 campaign isn’t over. Jacorey Croskey-Merritt will almost assuredly be the starting running back going forward, with Jeremy McNichols operating as his backup. This could also lead to more touches in the backfield from Deebo Samuel, as well, and it’s possible the Commanders will look at the trade market for a potential replacement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3c31-d86f-abdd-7dbdbc030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derek Carr said, “I wouldn’t say never,” when asked about coming out of retirement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3dfc-da67-a99f-fdfd76490000</link>
      <description>Speaking on the Dan Patrick Show, Carr made his return sound like a real possibility. He told Patrick, “I wouldn’t say never because I’ve learned that when I say never, it usually happens.” HW also said he is still training just because he loves it. Carr chose not to undergo surgery on his shoulder in the offseason and called it quits on a lengthy career. Teams typically hold the rights to a player after they retire, so the Saints would also need to find a trade partner for Carr, assuming they don’t want him back. Of course, he still needs to be medically cleared before playing football again. We aren’t holding our breath for a Carr comeback, but the odds appear to be meaningfully higher than zero.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3dfc-da67-a99f-fdfd76490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said he thinks CB Sauce Gardner (groin) will “be okay” for Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e05-dc44-a9d9-3f67d21b0000</link>
      <description>Gardner was added to the injury report with a groin issue on Thursday and was limited in practice. A mid-week addition to the injury report is never a good sign, but it looks like the light workload in practice may have been a precaution. We will get more info on Gardner’s availability for Week 1 when the Jets drop their final injury report later today. Barring a setback, the Jets should have their top corner available for a must-win game versus Buffalo on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e05-dc44-a9d9-3f67d21b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said DT Ed Oliver (ankle) will not play in Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e91-da67-a99f-fef54d410000</link>
      <description>Per McDermott, Oliver had his foot stepped on in practice this week. He was held out of Thursday’s practice and was spotted in a boot, indicating this could sideline him for more than one game. Oliver was a force in Week 1, totaling one sack, three TFLs, and a forced fumble. His absence will make life far easier for Justin Fields and the Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e91-da67-a99f-fef54d410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Darius Slayton said he thinks Darius Slayton (groin) will be okay for Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e99-d86f-abdd-7fbde3d00000</link>
      <description>Daboll didn’t commit to any injury status for the veteran wideout when talking to the media, though it sounds like a questionable tag could be in Slayton’s future. Slayton was a mid-week addition to the injury report after being left off it entirely on Wednesday. That’s never a good sign, but New York’s final injury report of the week will be more telling. Jalin Hyatt would likely be in line for more routes if Slayton can’t suit up this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e99-d86f-abdd-7fbde3d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) will not play in Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e9f-da67-a99f-feff84170000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation after Waller missed Week 1 and failed to practice during the opening session this week. It’s unclear when Waller will play in 2025, but it doesn’t look like that will happen anytime soon. Fantasy managers can safely cut ties with the veteran tight end, even in deep formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e9f-da67-a99f-feff84170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RT Austin Jackson (toe) will not play in Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea1-da67-a99f-fef58ee70000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have now lost two starting offensive linemen in one week of action. Right guard James Daniels went on injured reserve earlier this week with a pec injury. Expect Mike McDaniel to dial up another quick-hitting passing attack to keep Tua Tagovailoa out of harm’s way in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea1-da67-a99f-fef58ee70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
