<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Luke McCaffrey caught his lone target for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-def2-abdb-fdf1a3f80000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey took advantage of a busted coverage to walk into the end zone and give the Commanders a 24-16 lead. The second-year wideout has an impressive 41.5 yards per reception over the last two weeks, but it’s hard to be too excited about that when you’ve touched the ball twice. He’ll be off the radar for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-def2-abdb-fdf1a3f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 6-of-6 targets for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f513fd0000</link>
      <description>A very nice bounceback from Ertz after he failed to bring in a single catch against the Chargers in Week 5. The veteran tight end worked his way into the back of the end zone to give Washington a 17-16 lead on a connection with Jayden Daniels. Ertz doesn’t have elite upside — nor anything close — but despite his bagel in Week 5, he remains a TE2 for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f513fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 4-of-5 targets for 19 yards in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f519e00000</link>
      <description>There were a lot of factors going against Samuel for this one — bad weather, a heel issue, a defense focused on him with no Terry McLaurin — but regardless, it was a dud for the 29-year-old wideout. He had a long gain of nine on the day, and he was targeted exclusively underneath the Chicago secondary. Samuel has been excellent to begin his tenure with Washington, but this wasn’t an example of it — again, for a variety of reasons. He’ll get a chance to rebound against the Cowboys in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f519e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Moore caught 3-of-5 targets for 46 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-def2-abdb-fdf521400000</link>
      <description>Yes, that Chris Moore. With Terry McLaurin out and Deebo Samuel clearly hampered by a hamstring issue, Moore ended up second in targets behind Zach Ertz during the Monday Night Football contest, and led the team in yardage. It’s a fun story for a player who has hung around for an awfully long time, but even with the trip to the end zone, he can’t be trusted in fantasy for Week 7 against the Cowboys. Or any other week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-def2-abdb-fdf521400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden caught 4-of-4 passes for 51 yards in the Bears’ Week 7 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c7-db72-a199-facf91b00000</link>
      <description>Burden ended up leading the Bears in catches and yardage, which is a vast improvement over the negative-four yards he put up against the Raiders. The shifty 21-year-old rookie did most of his damage on a 37-yard connection to set up a score. There is considerable upside in Burden’s profile, but there just aren’t enough touches to suggest he’s worth a fantasy roster spot right now in redraft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c7-db72-a199-facf91b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 3-of-5 passes for 42 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c8-dd4c-afb9-e7c907ca0000</link>
      <description>Another quiet yardage day for Moore, and no trips to the end zone. The 28-year-old has now gone under 50 yards in four-straight games, and he hasn’t made up for it with touchdowns as seen in just one in 2025. Moore could find room against the Saints’ weak secondary in Week 7, but he is more FLEX play than someone who has to be in lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c8-dd4c-afb9-e7c907ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 2-of-5 targets for 32 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</link>
      <description>Odunze nearly had his fantasy day saved with an 11-yard touchdown, but that was negated by a penalty. It was a quiet day for the second-year wideout in a contest where the Bears relied heavily on D’Andre Swift in the run game. Expect Odunze to bounce back with more touches — and a potential trip to the end zone — against the Saints in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said the team’s running backs might be focusing too much on ball security.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e29b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdd1e0000</link>
      <description>That focus on not fumbling, Vrabel said, is limiting some rushing plays in the Patriots offense. His comments come after a rash of fumbles and miscues from New England running backs during the first month of the regular season. Against a middling Saints defense in Week 6, Rhamondre Stevenson and TreVeyon Henderson combined for 45 yards on 22 carries in another pass-first game plan. It’s hard to say when — or if — the team’s backs will pay a proper amount of focus on not fumbling and costing the team points and themselves playing time. For now, Stevenson appears to be the nominal lead runner for the Patriots, who this week take on a Titans defense allowing 4.6 yards per rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e29b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdd1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said he’s helping J.J. McCarthy (ankle) on “building that foundation back up.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e2ed-db72-a199-faefa11f0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell has reportedly spent the bye week working with McCarthy on improving his mechanics, especially his footwork, an area of concern over the season’s first two games before McCarthy apparently sustained a serious ankle injury that has kept him sidelined for more than a month. Concerns about McCarthy’s unrefined mechanics stretch back to the offseason, when the second-year QB would miss easy throws and held the ball long enough for the pass rush to get home in practices. O’Connell and the Vikings might have no choice but to turn back to McCarthy in Week 7 against the Eagles with Carson Wentz “managing a serious left shoulder injury,” according to The Athletic’s Alec Lewis. McCarthy would be a significant downgrade for all of Minnesota’s pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e2ed-db72-a199-faefa11f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (unknown) was hospitalized Monday evening following the Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e393-dd4c-afb9-e7d3de970000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on an update from the team after Moore finished the game against the Commanders but was mysteriously hospitalized Monday evening in the Washington area. Moore was notably seen blocking 15 yards downfield on the team’s final drive of the game, leading to the game-winning field goal. He did not travel home with the team while spending the night in a D.C. area hospital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e393-dd4c-afb9-e7d3de970000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
