<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “league sources believe Rashid Shaheed can be had for the right price.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2084-d5d8-a3ff-f9e557330000</link>
      <description>Schefter notes that the Saints are attempting to sign Chris Olave to a contract extension. He has one year left on his rookie deal and the Saints aren’t likely to let him see free agency. Shaheed, on the other hand, is 27 years old and an impending free agent, making him a prime candidate for a rebuilding Saints to move at the trade deadline. Schefter mentioned the Steelers, Broncos, and Bills as teams aggressively pursuing wide receivers via trade. Schefter also mentioned Brandin Cooks as a trade candidate, though it’s hard to imagine much of a market for his services at this point in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2084-d5d8-a3ff-f9e557330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports D’Andre Swift (groin) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2089-deb1-a39b-218ff9140000</link>
      <description>Swift was listed as questionable after a week of limited practices. He did the same thing last week and had no issues suiting up come game time. Swift wound up running for 124 yards and a touchdown on 19 carries. Facing a Ravens team without Lamar Jackson, the Bears are now favored, creating the potential for positive game script for both Swift and Kyle Monangai. Swift remains a staple of the RB2 ranks for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2089-deb1-a39b-218ff9140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Jaguars are “listening on calls” for Brian Thomas Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-208e-d5d8-a3ff-f9ef4b850000</link>
      <description>Russini herself notes that a trade for the second-year wideout is “highly unlikely.” Still, it’s notable that the Jags are even picking up the phone. Coming off 1,282 receiving yards as a rookie, expectations were sky high for BTJ entering his second season. The results, however, have been underwhelming. He is on pace for 886 receiving yards on just 66 receptions. Thomas Jr. has also been playing through multiple injuries, seemingly leading him to avoid contact at the catch point, resulting in several uncharacterstic drops. While things haven’t gone his way this year, we don’t expet the Jaguars to abandon ship anytime soon. Barring an offer they can’t refuse, the Jags will be keeping BTJ through the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-208e-d5d8-a3ff-f9ef4b850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports “the hope is that” A.J. Brown (hamstring) will play in Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20af-d245-adfb-b5ff5cd50000</link>
      <description>Brown is out for Week 8 after missing all three practices. The Eagles get their bye next week, giving Brown an extra week of rest before he attempts to return for a showdown with Green Bay that will have massive playoff implications. Garafolo also shut down any notions of a trade for Brown. Despite the rumor mill operating at max capacity in regards to Brown, the Eagles aren’t trading their superstar wideout in the midst of another season with Super Bowl aspirations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20af-d245-adfb-b5ff5cd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa (illness) was added to the injury report but will play in Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20be-deb1-a39b-21be50e10000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are just doing their due diligence with injury reporting by making note of the illness. Or they are giving themselves an alibi for when they pull Tagovailoa for Quinn Ewers at halftime. Who’s to say? In all seriousness, this shouldn’t affect Tua as the Dolphins prepare to take on Atlanta, eying just their second win of the season. Tua has had his moments this year with four multi-score games, but the lows have been lower than ever. Tagovailoa leads the league with 10 interceptions. The illness won’t prevent him from finishing Week 8, but his play might.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20be-deb1-a39b-21be50e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports J.J. McCarthy (ankle) is expected to start in Week 9 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20cc-d5d8-a3ff-f9edd03f0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport did add one final, “assuming health-wise he is all good,” caveat. Seven weeks removed from his high-ankle sprain, we fully expect McCarthy will be good to go for Week 9. Carson Wentz was given every opportunity to keep the starting job. Things began on a high note with wins over the Bengals and Browns in his first three starts. His play, however, quickly spiraled out of control, culminating in a close loss to the Eagles two weeks ago and a blowout at the hands of the Chargers on Thursday. Wentz tallied seven sacks and three interceptions in the pair of losses. His left shoulder injury also reached a breaking point at the end of Thursday’s game and he was pulled for rookie Max Brosmer in garbage time. McCarthy struggled to start the year before getting hurt, but Kevin O’Connell has been working closely with him to get the young quarterback ready for his return to action. A Week 9 date with Detroit will be a true test of McCarthy’s quarterback whisperer reputation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20cc-d5d8-a3ff-f9edd03f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the NFL is reviewing the Ravens’ reporting of Lamar Jackson’s practice status.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20d3-d5d8-a3ff-f9f3c0af0000</link>
      <description>Jackson was listed as a limited participant on Wednesday and Thursday. He was upgraded to a full session on Friday. It was reported over the weekend that he took scout team reps on Friday before being listed as questionable. This is usually a sign that a player won’t be suiting up. The Ravens then retroactively changed his Friday stats from full to limited and ruled him out entirely. Whether it was an honest mistake or a bit of gamesmanship from John Harbaugh is unclear. Either way, we expect the team and potentially Harbaugh himself to receive a hefty fine for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20d3-d5d8-a3ff-f9f3c0af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Raiders would trade Jakobi Meyers “only if they felt they were getting strong value in return.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20db-d245-adfb-b5dfe8730000</link>
      <description>Nothing of the sort has materialized. Meyers requested a trade in the offseason when he and the Raiders failed to reach an agreement on a contract extension. The team’s season hasn’t gone as planned and they now sit at 2-5 as the trade deadline approaches. Meyers confirmed that he still wants to be traded when asked about it following the team’s Week 7 blowout loss to the Chiefs. It doesn’t make much sense for the Raiders to hold onto Meyers in the back half of a lost season, only for him to leave in free agency in a few months. Still, teams rarely make the most obvious of trades, so we aren’t holding our breath for Meyers to be moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20db-d245-adfb-b5dfe8730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cowboys are “looking for some defensive help in advance of the trade deadline.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20e2-dab4-a3fb-bbf2b1ef0000</link>
      <description>If only the Cowboys had a superstar EDGE defender to bolster their basement-dweller defense. Jerry Jones is looking for the guy who did this. The Cowboys currently rank 30th in both points allowed and EPA per play allowed. They are beatable on the ground and through the air, forcing them to enter every game with a shootout mentality. Dallas has scraped together a 3-3-1 record, but they won’t be true Super Bowl contenders until their defense turns things around. As Rapoport notes, the impending return of DeMarvion Overshown and Shavon Revel could dissuade the Cowboys from buying at the deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-20e2-dab4-a3fb-bbf2b1ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Matthew Golden (hip) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2104-d5d8-a3ff-f96596600000</link>
      <description>Christian Watson is also expected to play. Golden was a surprise addition to the injury report on Friday, being listed as limited because of the hip issue. The team then hit him with a questionable designation. With Watson back, Golden could face increased competition for deep targets in an already low-volume passing attack. He is stuck in the WR4 ranks for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2104-d5d8-a3ff-f96596600000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
