<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7646-d968-a19b-7ef7f23a0000</link>
      <description>A DNP because of an illness early in the week is usually nothing, though there is slightly more risk of JCM missing Sunday’s game this time around. The Commanders have nothing to play for in Week 18 and are already down to their third-string quarterback. If JCM is still under the weather on Sunday, he could get the week off. He will likely split reps with Chris Rodriguez if he suits up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7646-d968-a19b-7ef7f23a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7648-d56e-afff-f6e879bc0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons regularly limited Pitts’ practice reps as he works through a knee issue, though it has not impacted his availability on game day. The Falcons’ star tight end should be good to go as a high-end TE1 against the Saints this week. Both teams have been eliminated from playoff contention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7648-d56e-afff-f6e879bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez (illness) is not on the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-764a-dc7a-af9b-ffffd0e60000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez was a late addition to the injury report last week because of an illness. The team ultimately ruled him out ahead of kickoff, allowing Jacory Croskey-Merritt to handle the bulk of the carries. He ran for 102 yards and two touchdowns on 11 carries. JCM is now on the injury report because of an illness, putting his availability for Week 18 at risk. Rodriguez would operate as the lead back if JCM doesn’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-764a-dc7a-af9b-ffffd0e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-764f-d56e-afff-f6effa7c0000</link>
      <description>This would normally be a non-story, but the Rams have almost nothing to play for in Week 18. They are locked into either the No. 5 or No. 6 seed for the playoffs. Even a minor ankle issue for Williams could be enough to get him a week of rest. Backup Blake Corum is also dealing with an ankle injury, meaning we could see a lot of third-string running back Ronnie Rivers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-764f-d56e-afff-f6effa7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7652-d56e-afff-f6fa49650000</link>
      <description>Corum left Week 17 with an ankle issue just before halftime and did not return. The Rams are stuck with a road game for the Wild Card Round no matter what happens on Sunday, meaning they can rest their starters without losing much. Sean McVay has said his starters will play, though we doubt any of the Rams’ injured players will push through their issues this week with nothing on the line. With Corum out, Ronnie Rivers could see a lot of work if the backups take over at some point in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7652-d56e-afff-f6fa49650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder/knee) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7648-dc7a-af9b-ffff7f4d0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield is dealing with an injury in his throwing shoulder. The Buccaneers’ quarterback regularly plays through injuries, though. We expect him to be on the field when his team takes on the Panthers in Week 18, though he can only be viewed as a borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7648-dc7a-af9b-ffff7f4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7655-d35e-a1bf-77d7d38d0000</link>
      <description>Adams hasn’t played since re-aggravating his hamstring injury in Week 15. With little to play for this week, he won’t be active versus the Cardinals on Sunday. Xavier Smith led the Rams with 67 yards on four catches last week. Even if Matthew Stafford and Puka Nacua start in Week 18, we suspect they could leave the game early, teeing Smith up for another high-volume day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7655-d35e-a1bf-77d7d38d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (toe) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7659-d968-a19b-7ef9ac1c0000</link>
      <description>Wirfs has a chance to face the Panthers on Saturday. The winner takes the NFC South’s crown and punches a ticket to the postseason. Wirfs’ return to practice is very encouraging. His presence makes a difference for QB Baker Mayfield, who is currently dealing with injuries in both his knee and throwing shoulder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7659-d968-a19b-7ef9ac1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers CB Jamel Dean (shoulder) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7659-dc7a-af9b-ffff9cef0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers’ No. 1 cornerback is now on the wrong side of questionable for his team’s Week 18 game against the Panthers. The Buccaneers (7-9) and Panthers (8-8) are playing for the NFC South title and a postseason appearance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7659-dc7a-af9b-ffff9cef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
