<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals, Dolphins, Falcons and Giants each requested an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8b4-d35e-a1bf-fdf691af0000</link>
      <description>Everybody’s doing it. Not enough people are talking about the dangers of peer pressure forcing you to interview Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy at home. Here are the signs you need to look out for if your teens come home wanting to interview Jesse Minter. There are now eight teams with head-coaching vacancies and all eight have requested an interview with the 42 year-old defensive coordinator who held Drake Maye’s offense to 16 points in the AFC Wild Card round. We’re not sure if Minter will get a head-coaching job this cycle, but he’s definitely going to lead all coaches in words used in interviews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8b4-d35e-a1bf-fdf691af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin resigned.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8c1-dc7a-af9b-ffff1ba60000</link>
      <description>Tomlin told his players that he plans to step away from coaching. We’re not completely sure that he’ll be content with a booth gig, and at the very least other NFL teams will spend the next 36-48 hours trying to change his mind on that. Tomlin was 193-114-2 in his 19 years as Steelers head coach, winning a Super Bowl in 2008 and going to another in 2010. The end of his career became a morass of tough defensive teams that didn’t have a quarterback as Ben Roethlisberger declined, and yet Tomlin persisted in dragging the team to the playoffs in five of the last six seasons anyway. The Steelers head coaching vacancy figures to be an extremely attractive one for other head coaches, but Tomlin has set a standard that will be hard to match. The Steelers retain Tomlin’s rights and, should he come back to coach for another team, could get trade compensation for him ala the Saints with Sean Payton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8c1-dc7a-af9b-ffff1ba60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens owner Steve Bisciotti said “I want [Lamar Jackson] to be my quarterback.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8e1-d968-a19b-f8f1d2200000</link>
      <description>There was a brief groundswell towards the end of the season about the Ravens possibly moving on from Jackson by the sourced men, but it doesn’t appear like the Ravens are heading in that direction if you listen to their owner. Bisciotti told the media that he “made it very clear” to Jackson that he wants to get an extension done before free agency. Ravens GM Eric DeCosta has also mentioned in this press conference the idea of extending Lamar and that cap space being used to sign some “big ticket” players. It sounds like Jackson — hopefully a healthier version of him — will be back in the black and purple next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8e1-d968-a19b-f8f1d2200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) will be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8fc-dc7a-af9b-ffff71b40000</link>
      <description>It will be a walkthrough, and coaches do not have a perfect record of what they say winding up being the injury report truth. Still, it’s a good sign for Pearsall’s availability against the Seahawks in the Divisional Round to have any momentum towards the limited line after three straight DNPs and a wishful thinking questionable tag. Pearsall has not played since Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8fc-dc7a-af9b-ffff71b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Raiders DC Patrick Graham for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8fe-d968-a19b-f8ffa2af0000</link>
      <description>It’s Graham’s first head-coaching interview request of the cycle — he did have a DC request with the Commanders. The Raiders brought him back despite massive turnover on the offensive side of the ball and at head coach last year, so it’s possible if they hired an offense-first head coach that they’d seek to bring Graham back again in 2026. Graham did have two head-coaching interviews with the Jaguars in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b8fe-d968-a19b-f8ffa2af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers designated LB Fred Warner (ankle/IR) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b902-d968-a19b-f9f38d410000</link>
      <description>His 21-day practice window will open. The 49ers have been clear that Warner will not play unless they get to the NFC Championship game, even that seems quick for their superstar linebacker who has been on the shelf since early October. Warner’s return will be fresh air for the 49ers if they can get to it — they opened as seven-point underdogs to the Seahawks in Seattle after the NFC West champs throttled San Francisco for the title in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b902-d968-a19b-f9f38d410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles fired OC Kevin Patullo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b90d-d35e-a1bf-fdcf4b9c0000</link>
      <description>In a stunning repeat of the 2023 season, the Eagles lost their offensive playcaller to head-coaching waters, replaced him in-house, and the house proved unable to live up to the talent on the roster. Certainly nobody should be struggling to make A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith prime parts of the offense, nor should an offensive coordinator not be able to find a way to make in-prime Saquon Barkley and this offensive line be pathologically unable to crack 100 yards in a game. And, well, Patullo did both those things. It’s possible he takes a smaller role on the Eagles staff. Philadelphia’s offensive coordinator position is right up there with Detroit’s as one of the best openings in the league. They will undoubtedly find an outside candidate interested in working with Jalen Hurts, Barkley, Brown, and Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b90d-d35e-a1bf-fdcf4b9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said WR Tyrell Shavers (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b913-d35e-a1bf-fdd3897c0000</link>
      <description>Shavers actually played 22 of the team’s snaps in the second half on the torn ACL, which is absurd. The 26-year-old heads to the offseason as unlikely to play early in the season due to how late this knee injury was suffered. He had a career-best 15/245/1 receiving line on 23 targets in the 2025 season, starting nine games and being sporadically useful when the team got annoyed with mercurial second-year receiver Keon Coleman. The Bills will need to rely on Coleman to give them something in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b913-d35e-a1bf-fdd3897c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen will be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</link>
      <description>McDermott didn’t have an actual term for what Allen was dealing with on Monday beyond him being “sore,” so we’re curious what the actual designation will be. We don’t think Allen is in any real danger of missing Saturday’s game against the Broncos, but it’s not surprising that he’d take it a bit easy after Joe Brady used him like a battering ram and he spent multiple occasions in the medical tent in Buffalo’s Wild Card win over the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said RB Ty Johnson (ankle) won’t practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited practice before hitting the questionable line and being ruled out Sunday against the Jaguars. He’s probably a true question mark at this point to be ready against the Broncos on Saturday, with practice participation being the guiding light here. If all he can do is get in another limited Thursday session ahead of a tag, Johnson probably will sit again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
