<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 21:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Ruckert caught his only target for a five-yard touchdown in a Week 2 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fa-da67-a99f-cdff33d60000</link>
      <description>The touchdown came on the final offensive drive of the game when the Jets were down 30-3, so we wouldn’t overreact too much to this. That being said, Ruckert out-targeted Marson Taylor in Week 1 and only had one fewer target than Taylor in Week 2, so we’re not so sure Taylor is going to be useful in fantasy leagues this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fa-da67-a99f-cdff33d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 5-of-10 targets for 89 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 2 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fb-da67-a99f-cdffbdf80000</link>
      <description>Already playing through a Week 1 shoulder issue, Jennings picked up some sort of left foot or ankle injury in New Orleans. He ultimately stayed in the game to post an excellent fantasy line. He also out-targeted Ricky Pearsall 10-6. Despite his contract squabbling and subsequent injury woes, Jennings has nevertheless held the trust of coach Kyle Shanahan. He’ll be a back-end WR3 for Week 3 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fb-da67-a99f-cdffbdf80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku caught 4-of-5 targets for 40 yards in the Browns’ Week 2 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fc-d294-a19b-edfc1ef30000</link>
      <description>Njoku saw 23 of his yards coming on a deep pass down the middle late in the second quarter to convert a third and 13 and move the Browns into field goal range before the half. Two of his four receptions came on that drive, as the veteran tight end was largely held in check by a defense that didn’t give up much through the air or on the ground on Sunday. The use of Harold Fannin continues to be a thorn in the side of Njoku’s fantasy managers, and will likely continue to limit his upside. Njoku won’t be on the TE1 radar in Week 3 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fc-d294-a19b-edfc1ef30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed 11 times for 54 yards in the Patriots’ Week 2 loss to the Dolphins, adding five receptions for 88 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49f5-dc44-a9d9-4ff727580000</link>
      <description>Stevenson was once again the lead back for the Patriots, getting the first three touches of the game. He had 39 offensive snaps, eclipsing TreVeyon Henderson’s 19 and Antonio Gibson’s 10. The Patriots used him as the go-to back in all situations as Stevenson also led all backs in passing-down snaps. His most explosive play was a 58-yard catch-and-run on a wheel route in the second half. Stevenson totaled 142 yards from scrimmage on just 16 touches against the shaky Dolphins defense. It’s unlikely we see this kind of efficiency again from Stevenson, though he has the clear lead role in the Pats backfield. Expect him to regress back down to the RB3 range in Week 3 against a tough Steelers defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49f5-dc44-a9d9-4ff727580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Williams completed 19-of-30 passes for 207 yards, two touchdowns and an interception in the Bears’ 52-21, Week 2 loss to the Lions, adding five carries for 27 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ff-dc44-a9d9-4fffb3b70000</link>
      <description>For the second week in a row, Williams’ best drive was probably the Bears’ scripted opening series. The Bears can at least score on their opening possession — unlike 2024, where they never found the end zone — but things haven’t been a whole lot better afterward. That being said, the defense was a bigger issue than the offense today, while Williams was not as visibly inaccurate as he was in the opener. He found second-year first-rounder Rome Odunze for 7/128/2. New coach Ben Johnson has a few things working. Just not enough to get Williams in the QB1 mix for Week 3 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ff-dc44-a9d9-4fffb3b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Browning completed 21-of-32 passes for 241 yards, two touchdowns, and three interceptions in the Bengals’ 31-27, Week 2 win over the Jaguars, adding one carry for a one-yard touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49f9-da67-a99f-cdfd70d10000</link>
      <description>Browning took over for Joe Burrow late in the second quarter when the latter suffered a toe injury on a sack. Burrow went in for an MRI and was spotted on a scooter during halftime. He did not return. Browning struggled at times, tossing two interceptions that were his fault and a third where his receiver stopped on the route, leading to an easy pick for the Jaguars’ secondary. Just like he did when the Bengals called on him in 2023, Browning was given plenty of screens, getting the ball into his best players’ hands without asking much of the backup passer. He then stepped up in the fourth quarter, leading the Bengals on a 92-yard scoring drive, which he capped with a one-yard rushing score. The Jags couldn’t make anything of the final 18 seconds and Browning came away with the win. With Burrow’s status for Week 3 unknown at this time, Browning will be a must-add in Superflex and 2QB formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49f9-da67-a99f-cdfd70d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught 5-of-5 targets for 48 yards in the Browns’ Week 2 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ff-dc44-a9d9-4fff7fd90000</link>
      <description>The targets dropped a bit in this one, but Fannin’s five targets on the day tied David Njoku while his 48 receiving yards were second only to Jerry Jeudy’s 51. Fannin played on 46 offensive snaps per the early PFF data, with 23 of those coming from the slot. He remains a viable fantasy option after breaking out in Week 1, but will face a tough test in Week 3 against the Packers. He profiles as a fringe TE1/TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ff-dc44-a9d9-4fff7fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson completed 30-of-41 passes for 450 yards, three touchdowns and an interception in the Giants’ 40-37, Week 2 overtime loss against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fa-dc44-a9d9-4ffe600a0000</link>
      <description>The moonball was working as the Cowboys defense looked woefully overmatched, barely challenging some of the touchdown throws. Wilson was 7-of-11 for 264 yards and all three of his touchdowns on throws that went over 20 yards past the line of scrimmage. But in what appeared to be a miscommunication to end the game, Wilson threw a sitting duck pick to Donovan Wilson — the second ball the Cowboys successfully defensed all day — when Malik Nabers turned to the corner route instead of back over the middle on New York’s second possession of overtime. Jaxson Dart worked in sparingly and only on runs, with three snaps. Wilson’s inability to win the game won’t keep the heat entirely off of him going forward — almost nothing could after Dart’s preseason — but this will at least end calls for his benching for the moment. The main takeaway from this game in fantasy should be that we need to target the Dallas secondary. The Giants will draw the Chiefs in Week 3 and Russ figures to go back to more modest numbers in that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49fa-dc44-a9d9-4ffe600a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
