<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 03:10:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared QB Brock Purdy, WR Jauan Jennings, WR Ricky Pearsall, RB Jordan James, WR Jordan Watkins, DL Robert Beal and LB Nick Martin inactive for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a71b-d95b-addb-ef5f7be90000</link>
      <description>Losing Purdy, Jennings (ankle, ribs) and Pearsall (knee) for a Thursday night divisional showdown is brutal. The 49ers, Rams and Seahawks sit in a three-way tie for first place in the NFC West with 3-1 records. Fantasy managers should expect Christian McCaffrey to handle a significant workload in this one. Kendrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson will serve as the Nos. 1 and 2 wide receivers, respectively. 49ers TE Jake Tonges has comparatively earned targets moderately efficiently in his role as a fill-in starter. Mac Jones is a viable starter in two-quarterback leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a71b-d95b-addb-ef5f7be90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared TE Tyler Higbee, OL Rob Havenstein, QB Stetson Bennett IV, OL Beaux Limmer and DE Desjuan Johnson inactive for Week 5 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a724-d95b-addb-ef660b720000</link>
      <description>Higbee is sidelined by a hip injury, which further condenses the target pecking order in Puka Nacua and Davante Adams’ favor. Havenstein﻿﻿'s absence is likely a larger issue for Matthew Stafford as he navigates pressures from the 49ers’ pass rush, though. Havenstein﻿﻿ is sidelined by an ankle injury, and Higbee has earned just 10 targets this season. Regardless, Stafford remains on the QB1/2 borderline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a724-d95b-addb-ef660b720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a740-d6e9-af9d-afd027c50000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon’s situation is tough to read. Hopefully, he returns to practice as a full participant on Friday. He was able to play through the knee injury in Week 4. Seahawks S Julian Love (hamstring) and DE Demarcus Lawrence (quad) both remained sidelined. All three should be considered highly questionable to play in Week 5 against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a740-d6e9-af9d-afd027c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a745-deb6-a7fd-f7df1e180000</link>
      <description>It is time to make backup plans. Bowers practiced in full last week. He worryingly kicked off Week 5 with a limited session and was unable to practice at all today. No setbacks have been reported. One wonders if he indeed suffered one, though technically this could be precautionary. Raiders backup TE Michael Mayer (concussion) remains limited. Both players are on the wrong side of questionable for Week 5 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a745-deb6-a7fd-f7df1e180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a717-deb6-a7fd-f7df5c6c0000</link>
      <description>This is, unfortunately, a new injury for the Raiders’ stalwart pass rusher and he appears to have suffered it in practice. He should be considered questionable to play in Week 5 against the Colts. It would be impossible for the Raiders to replace his productivity if he is ruled out. Crosby ranks and/or ties for first on the team in quarterback pressures (16), sacks (two) and tackles (eight).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a717-deb6-a7fd-f7df5c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that “there is a real chance” TE George Kittle (hamstring) returns for the 49ers’ game against the Buccaneers in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a74c-dca3-a9fb-bfdd0bfb0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that Kittle “has had no setbacks” in his recovery from the hamstring strain he suffered early in September. This would be a hugely positive development for a 49ers squad jockeying for first place in the NFC West despite experiencing myriad star-play injuries. Kittle would immediately vault back into the elite TE1 tier if active next week, likely catching passes from capable fill-in starter Mac Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a74c-dca3-a9fb-bfdd0bfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that 49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is considered “week-to-week” after suffering a setback in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a754-d6e9-af9d-afd4d20f0000</link>
      <description>Last week, Purdy reportedly “got hit the same way” that he did when he initially suffered the injury. He reported soreness the next day and underwent an MRI to confirm that a re-injury had occurred. On the plus side, it is not considered a “major, major” re-injury, and the 49ers likely would have placed Purdy on injured reserve before Thursday Night Football kicks off if they expected him to miss more than three games, though Rapoport adds that Purdy’s Week 6 availability is already in question. Mac Jones should be added by quarterback-needy squads in all formats, though he will likely remain in the QB2 rankings tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a754-d6e9-af9d-afd4d20f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) “could be back” for the 49ers’ Week 6 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a75d-d95b-addb-ef5f2dc70000</link>
      <description>49ers TE George Kittle (hamstring) and WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) could also return, which is good news for a team that is expected to be without Brock Purdy in the short term after the starting quarterback aggravated his turf toe injury in Week 4. Pearsall’s 327 receiving yards rank fourth among NFL wide receivers, though he has not yet scored a touchdown, which could afford savvy fantasy managers a one-week buy-low opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a75d-d95b-addb-ef5f2dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) “could be back” for the 49ers’ Week 6 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a760-deb6-a7fd-f7ff51840000</link>
      <description>The 49ers are expected to be without Brock Purdy (toe) for one or more games after the starting quarterback suffered a re-injury in Week 4. Potentially getting Jennings, TE George Kittle (hamstring) and WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) would significantly stabilize the 49ers’ turbulent situation. Continue stashing Jennings on benches. He should return to his typical WR4/FLEX status soon enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a760-deb6-a7fd-f7ff51840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that 49ers WR Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is “still weeks away” from returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a768-d6e9-af9d-aff8eba30000</link>
      <description>Aiyuk’s recovery from ACL and MCL tears suffered in Week 7, 2024, continues. The remaining 49ers pass catchers are only in moderately better health, with TE George Kittle (hamstring), WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) and WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) currently rehabbing injuries of their own. Hopefully, Aiyuk can return before too long. Until then, he remains stashed on injured reserve roster spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a768-d6e9-af9d-aff8eba30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
