<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks DB Devon Witherspoon (knee) was listed as a full participant for Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3295-d321-a5bf-b2d7dbb10000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon has missed the last three games of the season with his knee issue, but the defender appears to be on track to return to the secondary for Sunday Night Football against the Commanders in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3295-d321-a5bf-b2d7dbb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31fe-d48c-ad9f-fdff99df0000</link>
      <description>The good news for Houston fans is that Nico Collins and Christian Kirk were both back on the practice field on Wednesday. Schultz could play this week if he returns to practice eventually, though fantasy managers may want to work on contingency plans for him. Harrison Bryant would likely draw the start in Schultz’s place if he misses Week 9 against Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31fe-d48c-ad9f-fdff99df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers (knee) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-352d-d71c-afdf-bd6d75fe0000</link>
      <description>It looks like both Meyers and Brock Bowers will be back for the team’s Week 9 matchup with the Jaguars. Meyers publicly reiterated his desire to be traded before missing Week 7’s game against the Chiefs with the knee injury. He will get one final chance to showcase his value to other teams on Sunday before the Tuesday deadline. Meyers will sit on the WR2/3 border for his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-352d-d71c-afdf-bd6d75fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed RG Brady Christensen (Achilles) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3563-d1e7-a1fa-7feb2afa0000</link>
      <description>Christensen suffered a season-ending Achilles injury in Week 8. He underwent surgery earlier this week. Christensen will hit free agency at the age of 29 after this season. The Panthers signed Mike White to their 53-man roster in a corresponding move. White could serve as Bryce Young’s backup this week with Andy Dalton banged up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3563-d1e7-a1fa-7feb2afa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals designated EDGE BJ Ojulari (knee) to return from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3603-d45b-affe-779739200000</link>
      <description>Ojulari suffered a torn ACL early in training camp last year. He began the 2025 season on the PUP list and is now eligible to return. By opening his practice window, the Cardinals have three weeks to officially activate him from PUP. Defensive tackle Walter Nolen has also been designated to return, meaning the Cardinals could be getting multiple upgrades on defense over the next few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3603-d45b-affe-779739200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (concussion) is “back for another practice and is expected to clear protocol if all goes well today.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-321e-d4ed-a9de-779e31ca0000</link>
      <description>Collins practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday. Given this morning’s report, Collins was likely in phase three of the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol. Should he respond positively to phase four activities today, he could pass through phase five, the clearance phase, quickly. Setbacks remain possible, but as of Thursday, Collins appears to be on track for a return in Week 9 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-321e-d4ed-a9de-779e31ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f4-d4ed-a9de-77fed0930000</link>
      <description>Schultz has now missed Week 9’s first two practices, though head coach DeMeco Ryans said “he expects him to return later this week,” per NBC Houston’s Aaron Wilson. Ostensibly, that means tomorrow. Schultz is firmly in the questionable camp, though, and would seemingly play at less than 100.0 percent if active on Sunday. He would be tough to trust if he cannot practice in full tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f4-d4ed-a9de-77fed0930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon told reporters he is “preparing” QB Kyler Murray (foot) to start in Week 9 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3632-d713-ad9e-7e76478c0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals face the Cowboys on Monday night. Murray remained limited through Week 7 practices and the team was on bye in Week 8. We expect Murray to practice in full today, given Gannon’s comments. Expect an update if that is not the case. The Cowboys’ defense has functioned as a matchup to target for fantasy quarterbacks this season, though concerns over Murray’s poor play are warranted. The Cardinals’ quarterback has finished as the QB16 in 4-of-5 games. Assuming he practices in full this week, he can be treated as a volatile starter in single-quarterback leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3632-d713-ad9e-7e76478c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-363f-d1e7-a1fa-7effb01a0000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson and LB Logan Wilson (calf) were both sidelined on Thursday. Hendrickson continues to be the subject of trade rumors, though the Bengals have reportedly rebuffed inquiries thus far. Conversely, Wilson asked to be traded after losing his job as a defensive starter and was instead tasked with special teams duties, during which hereportedlyinjured his calf. The Bengals face the Bears in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-363f-d1e7-a1fa-7effb01a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
