<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is not practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030c-d651-a9df-6b1d28420000</link>
      <description>Teams often have practices on Monday after bye weeks, and the NFL does not require them to submit an injury report. Thus, it does not make too much sense to read heavily into this regarding Jackson’s Week 8 availability. He may simply be saving it for Wednesday. But it’s an inauspicious sign that he’s still sidelined in a practice where Roquan Smith, Ronnie Stanley, and Chidobe Awuzie all got into. Jackson’s hamstring will be the number one question about Week 8’s slate, so look for several more updates on it this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030c-d651-a9df-6b1d28420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels’ hamstring injury is not considered long-term, but his uncertain about his Week 8 availability.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030b-da18-a39a-db1b95180000</link>
      <description>Quinn has seldom been clear about the health of his QB1. He beat around the bush for two weeks while Daniels worked through a groin injury, and will likely play the status of his QB1 close to the vest for most of this week. The proof will be in the practice report, which won’t be released until Thursday since the Commanders play on Monday night, but fantasy managers counting on Daniels in Week 8 would be wise to stash backup Marcus Mariota on their bench in case he is ruled out late Sunday or on game day. If he is unable to play in Week 8, it would mark the third game Daniels has missed this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030b-da18-a39a-db1b95180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said EDGE Dorance Armstrong’s knee injury is season-ending.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-031e-da18-a39a-db1fde580000</link>
      <description>Armstrong signed a three-year, $33 million contract two offseasons ago and the Commanders are not tied to him in 2026, where they’ll be able to save $3.3 million by releasing him or more by using the post-June 1 designation. It’s a devastating injury for the Commanders as Armstrong was by far the best player on the defense this year, with a 77.6 PFF defensive grade in 239 snaps. Entering his age-29 season in 2026, Armstrong is probably playing well enough to stay, but the Commanders will likely look to upgrade the room around him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-031e-da18-a39a-db1fde580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions activated DL Alim McNeill (PUP/knee) for Week 7 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-033a-d651-a9df-6b3fa5610000</link>
      <description>This will be the first taste of action for McNeill this season. The fifth-year lineman is returning from a torn ACL he suffered in Week 15 of last season, but had his 21-day return window opened late last month. In 14 games for the Lions last season, McNeill totaled 25 tackles, 3.5 sacks, and seven TFLs while also forcing one fumble. He should be able to step in and immediately bolster a run defense that entered the week graded as the fourth-highest by PFF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-033a-d651-a9df-6b3fa5610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said LB Divine Deablo (forearm) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0343-da18-a39a-db53c6b10000</link>
      <description>He fractured the forearm against the 49ers in Week 7 and will “miss some time.” JD Bertrand replaced Deablo and played acceptably on the inside against the 49ers in what was a down game for the unit in run defense. He’ll replace Deablo going forward as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0343-da18-a39a-db53c6b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Michael Penix is day-to-day with a bone bruise in his foot.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0342-d651-a9df-6b5727770000</link>
      <description>Penix was visibly slowed by an injury that he picked up in Sunday’s loss to the Niners, now we know the culprit. This reported bone bruise, which he played through in Week 7, doesn’t sound like anything too serious at the moment, but fantasy managers considering starting Penix in Week 8 against the Dolphins will want to monitor his practice status throughout the week. If he is unable to go, Kirk Cousins would draw his first start of the season in what could be a very favorable defensive matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0342-d651-a9df-6b5727770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0346-da18-a39a-db57db6a0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimation, as always on Monday, but this is the first we’re hearing of an injury for Haskins. Nyheim Hines would figure to be Kimani Vidal’s backup on Thursday night against the Vikings if Haskins is sidelined. Fantasy managers can probably feel free to drop Haskins with six teams on bye if they need to make a move for another position, given both his standing on the depth chart after these last two weeks and the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0346-da18-a39a-db57db6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OT Joe Alt (ankle) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0349-d99b-a1df-3b4d47a20000</link>
      <description>He was limited twice last week in practice before being called doubtful and scratched on Sunday. The Chargers also had Austin Deculus (ankle) and Trey Pipkins (knee) limited on Monday, leaving Foster Sarell and Bobby Hart as their current healthy alternatives on the roster. Hart started last week, and Deculus was relieved by Sarell with both Alt and Pipkins inactive. It would be nice if Alt could be ready for Week 8, but it doesn’t feel like something we can count on at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0349-d99b-a1df-3b4d47a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots claimed LB Caleb Murphy off waivers from the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-035a-d651-a9df-6b5fe8770000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old former Titans UDFA had been a rotational pass rusher for the Chargers this year, seeing 88 pass rush snaps of his 129 total snaps in six weeks with the team. He’ll likely be tried in the same role in New England, now reunited with former head coach Mike Vrabel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-035a-d651-a9df-6b5fe8770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills designated CB Maxwell Hairston (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0364-d651-a9df-6b751e570000</link>
      <description>His 21-day practice window will open, so the Bills will have three weeks to see him in practice before they have to activate him. Hairston sprained his knee early in training camp and, whenever he makes his Bills debut, it will be the first time we have any film of him on an NFL field. We’d bet on the Bills taking a conservative approach with the rookie first-rounder during his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0364-d651-a9df-6b751e570000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
