<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 21 times for 120 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 11 win over the Commanders, adding five receptions for 45 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dcc-d713-ad9e-eddc5c0c0000</link>
      <description>Achane was once again the engine of Miami’s offense. He carried the ball more than 20 times for the second week in a row. This is the first time Miami has given him 20 carries in back-to-back games in his entire career. Achane also led the Dolphins in receptions and came up just seven yards shy of Jaylen Waddle for a team-high in yards. Achane got shaken up on his final touch of the fourth quarter but came back for three game-sealing carries in overtime. A Week 12 bye should help him recover ahead of a great matchup versus the Saints. He will remain a high-end RB1 in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dcc-d713-ad9e-eddc5c0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota completed 20-of-30 passes for 213 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Commanders’ 16-13, Week 11 overtime loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dd4-d1e7-a1fa-dffea7df0000</link>
      <description>Mariota added 49 yards on four carries, highlighted by a 44-yard dash in the fourth quarter. The run set up a goal line showdown with the Miami defense to take the lead. Mariota threw a potential touchdown to Zach Ertz, but the veteran tight end stumbled out of his break and was unable to bring down the pass. The Commanders had another chance to win at the end of the fourth quarter, only for a Matt Gay miss from 56 yards out to doom onlookers to overtime. Mariota immediately tossed an easy interception to Dolphins corner Jack Jones over the middle of the field on his first attempt of overtime. The Commanders will look to bounce back in a nightmare matchup versus the Broncos after their Week 12 bye. Mariota will be stuck in the middle of the QB2 ranks for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dd4-d1e7-a1fa-dffea7df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylin Lane caught his only target for 13 yards before exiting the Commanders’ Week 11 loss to the Dolphins with a hip injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8da6-d673-a39e-adb75e990000</link>
      <description>Lane was listed as questionable to return after taking a hard hit on his only catch of the day. His absence nearly proved fatal late in the game when backup punt returner Mike Sainristil muffed a punt in the fourth quarter. Miami recovered it and made its way to the one-yard line on the ensuing drive. Washington mounted a goal line stand and the game made its way to overtime. Lane hasn’t done much on offense as a rookie but has been an elite punt returner. Losing him would be a notable blow to Miami’s special teams unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8da6-d673-a39e-adb75e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamel Dean is questionable to return to Week 11 against the Bills with a hip injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de6-d673-a39e-adf74c5f0000</link>
      <description>Dean played one series to start the game and then limped to the locker room. Benjamin Morrison will take over for him, but this would be a big loss because Dean has been the Bucs’ best cornerback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de6-d673-a39e-adf74c5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (ankle) left Tennessee’s Week 11 game against the Texans and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8deb-d673-a39e-adfb61980000</link>
      <description>On Tennessee’s first play from scrimmage, Ridley caught the ball and immediately went down in a heap holding his ankle. He was later carted off the field, though he didn’t appear to be in much pain and was conversing with trainers. The Titans provided an update on his status before the drive was over. Ridley’s lone catch went for 13 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8deb-d673-a39e-adfb61980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 7-of-8 targets for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 11 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de4-d713-ad9e-edf498e20000</link>
      <description>Samuel also added three yards on his lone carry. Deebo has struggled to generate explosive plays this year, but that wasn’t the case versus Miami. He gashed the Dolphins in the second quarter, turning a short catch into a 20-yard score by cutting across the field after securing the grab. Samuel also broke off a 28-yard catch later in the game, eventually setting up a potential game-winning field goal from Matt Gay. Gay missed the kick and the Commanders lost in overtime. With Terry McLaurin uncertain to return after the team’s Week 12 bye, Samuel will likely stay in the WR2 ranks for Week 13 versus the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de4-d713-ad9e-edf498e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love was forced from Green Bay’s Week 11 game against the Giants with a non-throwing shoulder injury and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8df8-d713-ad9e-edfcc6a10000</link>
      <description>Love absorbed a huge hit late in the first quarter and was pulled off the field by the referee. Rather than a head issue, however, it’s his left arm. Love was then spotted jogging to the locker room. In his absence, Malik Willis engineered a touchdown drive. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8df8-d713-ad9e-edfcc6a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young left for the locker room in the first quarter of the Panthers’ Week 11 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8df8-d1e7-a1fa-dffa095c0000</link>
      <description>Young was drilled by an unblocked Atlanta defender for a sack. He stayed on the field, writhing in pain for a few moments before trainers helped him to his feet. Young managed to walk into the locker room under his own power. Billy Bowman Jr. stepped on Young’s ankle while taking him down, which could be the source of the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8df8-d1e7-a1fa-dffa095c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young (ankle) has returned to the Panthers’ Week 11 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dfe-d1e7-a1fa-dffef4730000</link>
      <description>Young took a hard hit from Falcons safety Billy Bowman Jr. in the first quarter. Bowman stepped on his ankle while making the tackle and Young was slow to get up. He left for the locker room and was listed as questionable to return. Young previously dealt with an ankle injury and missed one game because of it. He will attempt to play through the issue for the remainder of this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dfe-d1e7-a1fa-dffef4730000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
