<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:04:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db8-d6e9-af9d-ffb8ec5e0000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon went down with the knee issue in Week 1 and has been out ever since. It’s a good sign to see him back after two weeks, given that the Seahawks had a short turnaround to Thursday Night Football for Week 4. Fellow defensive back Julian Love is also good to go for Seattle’s NFC West showdown with Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db8-d6e9-af9d-ffb8ec5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) was a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddb-d6e9-af9d-ffdbff760000</link>
      <description>Wirfs is trending towards returning in Week 4 as he recovers from a training camp knee injury. The Bucs could use the boost to a battered offensive line heading into a showdown against the Eagles’ stout defensive front. Expect Wirfs to give Baker Mayfield a little more time in the pocket on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddb-d6e9-af9d-ffdbff760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (biceps) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddf-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2f90000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was listed as a limited participant due to a right biceps injury on Wednesday. The veteran has taken hits behind a battered offensive line this season and took on a limited workload to begin the week, though there is no indication that his status for Week 4 against the Eagles is in jeopardy. He will get extra help with Tristan Wirfs (knee) and Chris Godwin (ankle) slated to return this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddf-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Will Shipley (oblique) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7de8-deb6-a7fd-7fff6ff60000</link>
      <description>Shipley was a full participant for the first time since injuring his oblique in the season opener. He had three carries for 26 yards against the Cowboys in Week 1 and profiles as Saquon Barkley’s primary backup. He is back on fantasy radars as a valuable handcuff as the Eagles play the Bucs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7de8-deb6-a7fd-7fff6ff60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ded-deb6-a7fd-7fff973a0000</link>
      <description>Likely has not yet played this season, but got in limited practices last week and starts out this week with a limited designation. The 25-year-old is trending to return to the field in Week 4 against the Chiefs, but a full practice later in the week will offer better confirmation. Mark Andrews finally had a breakout game with two touchdowns in Week 3, but Likely’s addition will decrease opportunities, landing both in the TE2 range</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ded-deb6-a7fd-7fff973a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LB Zack Baun (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7dfc-d6e9-af9d-fffcf0070000</link>
      <description>Baun missed Wednesday with a knee issue, his first instance of an injury in 2025. Also out on Wednesday were LB Jihaad Campbell (triceps) and Adoree’ Jackson (groin). The Eagles’ front seven has been driven by Baun and Campbell’s contributions and absences in Week 4 would leave the middle of the field open for the Buccaneers. If Jackson misses time, Kelee Ringo is next in line for opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7dfc-d6e9-af9d-fffcf0070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e04-d95b-addb-7e46a6910000</link>
      <description>Ricard has not practiced the entire season and continues to be held out of practice with a calf issue. The Ravens had not placed him on injured reserve, but the injury seems to be a lengthier issue than expected. Ricard is a key part of the Ravens’ blocking schemes, which have struggled at times without the 31-year-old. Also out was OT Ronnie Stanley (ankle). The Ravens are banged-up in the trenches heading into Week 4 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e04-d95b-addb-7e46a6910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e0b-deb6-a7fd-7fdf336c0000</link>
      <description>Dissly continues to miss time with a knee issue that kept him out for Week 3. Rookie Oronde Gadsden took over at tight end with Dissly sidelined while veteran Tyler Conklin did not catch any of his targets against the Broncos. Fantasy managers should expect another Gadsden boost should Dissly miss Week 4. WR Derius Davis (knee) also missed practice on Wednesday. He is primarily a returner, so there is little impact for fantasy managers if Davis misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e0b-deb6-a7fd-7fdf336c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OG Mekhi Becton (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e13-dca3-a9fb-7f9be92d0000</link>
      <description>In addition to Becton, center Bradley Bozeman (back) also did not practice Wednesday. The Chargers’ interior offensive line is banged up to start the week and will have a couple days to return to practice ahead of a Week 4 showdown against the Broncos. Should Bozeman and Becton miss time, Omarion Hampton will have a tough time finding running lanes against the Denver defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e13-dca3-a9fb-7f9be92d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) is doubtful for Week 4 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e1d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2eb0000</link>
      <description>Johnson did not practice all week after already missing Week 3. He is listed as doubtful to play Thursday against the Seahawks. Meanwhile, fellow CB Darren Hall (ankle) is listed as questionable. Also questionable are LB Akeem Davis-Gaither (elbow) and OL Kelvin Beachum (knee), Evan Brown (heel), Paris Johnson Jr. (knee), and Will Hernandez (knee). Missing Johnson and Brown especially would deplete the left side of the Cardinals’ offensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e1d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2eb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
