<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:18:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said, “somebody would have to come with something fairly strong for us to consider” trading QB Mac Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-921f-d57c-a1dd-961fbdf80000</link>
      <description>Jones started a few games for the 49ers in 2025, putting himself on the radar for quarterback-needy teams. However, Lynch said Jones has been “really good for us and we value that...I think we’re a better team with him on it.” The 49ers value Jones as a capable backup quarterback behind Brock Purdy, who has missed time due to injury over the last couple seasons. If a team values Jones as a starter and crafts a strong offer, Lynch and the 49ers would at least consider trading the 27-year-old.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-921f-d57c-a1dd-961fbdf80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When asked about using the franchise tag on EDGE Trey Hendrickson, Bengals executive Duke Tobin said, “I don’t throw anything on or off the table with Trey.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-923c-d042-afbc-fffe12de0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals and Hendrickson have been in contentious contract talks for a while with all options still on the table, according to director of player personnel and de facto general manager Duke Tobin. The franchise tag is still a possibility and theCincinnati Enquirer’sKelsey Conway reported last week the Bengals will get a feel for the 31-year-old’s market at this week’s NFL Combine. The tag would guarantee $30.2 million to Hendrickson in 2026, making it difficult to afford for the Bengals. However, the team still won’t publicly deny the franchise tag as an option, likely in an effort to generate value in possible trade scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-923c-d042-afbc-fffe12de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Penn State QB Drew Allar (ankle) will throw at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9255-d629-a1bc-b25d840d0000</link>
      <description>Allar is recovering from season-ending ankle surgery but will throw at the NFL Combine this week. The 21-year-old will get the chance to show off his arm strength, though his mobility may not be at full strength just yet. Allar started the past three seasons at Penn State, choosing to return instead of declaring for the draft last season. His ankle surgery came after an ankle injury sustained in October, prohibiting from showcasing his skillset to NFL teams later in the season. Allar is on the radar as a mid-round prospect for now, with the chance to improve his stock with a strong showing at the NFL Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9255-d629-a1bc-b25d840d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports Cowboys K Brandon Aubrey is seeking $10 million per season in a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-92e6-d57c-a1dd-96eedaa90000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys have already offered Aubrey the league’s highest-paid kicker contract. Watkins reports the 30-year-old “was offered a deal with an average salary of close to $7.5 million but is looking for nearly $10 million per season.” Despite exceeding Chiefs kicker Harrison Butker’s $6.4 million average annual salary with this contract offer, the Cowboys are still below Aubrey’s desired number. He has one first-team All-Pro and two second-team All-Pro selections over the last three years, a resume certainly worth demanding the highest kicker salary in the league. The Cowboys can still place a first- or second-round tender on Aubrey if an extension does not happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-92e6-d57c-a1dd-96eedaa90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders will play a 2026 regular season game in London.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</link>
      <description>Jayden Daniels, coming off an injury-plagued 2025 season in which he threw eight touchdowns and three interceptions over seven games, will lead Washington into London for one of the NFL’s many international games in 2026. The Commanders will look to get back to their 2024 offensive form after scoring points on just 37 percent of their offensive possessions in 2025, the tenth lowest rate in the league. Daniels last season had a drop back EPA on par with Tyler Shough and Kirk Cousins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jaguars will play two 2026 regular season games in London.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-952d-d042-afbc-fdff62b30000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars, with an avid UK fanbase, will once again play a couple games overseas in 2026. Jacksonville is 7-7 over 14 regular season games in London since the 2013 NFL season. Last year Trevor Lawrence and the Jaguars were blown out 35-7 by the Rams at Wembley stadium. Lawrence and head coach Liam Coen will look to bounce back from that loss in 2026 after a 2025 season in which they ranked 12th in EPA per play and 16th in offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-952d-d042-afbc-fdff62b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LG Tyler Smith underwent knee surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9532-dbf6-abdd-ff335d3c0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports Smith should be ready for offseason activities in April following the knee procedure. The Pro Bowl left guard gutted it out through the knee injury for much of the 2025 season. Pro Football Focus graded Smith 31st among guards in pass blocking last season. He ranked top-5 among guards in run blocking grade. The Cowboys last year made Smith, their 2022 first round pick, the NFL’s highest paid interior offensive lineman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9532-dbf6-abdd-ff335d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings executive vice president of football operations Rob Brzezinski said the team is “casting a wide net” in exploring quarterback options for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9546-d89c-a1be-bfdfdfa80000</link>
      <description>Neither Brzezinski nor head coach Kevin O’Connell committed to J.J. McCarthy as the team’s 2026 starter following McCarthy’s ugly 2025 campaign. McCarthy, coming off a knee injury that wiped out his 2024 rookie season, ranked 39th out of 40 qualifying QBs in accuracy and 37th in drop backs success rate over ten games. O’Connell reportedly had to simplify the Minnesota playbook because McCarthy could not grasp the offense. “What we do know is we need a level of baseline quarterback play for us to be effective,” Brzezinski said. “A lot of this has been J.J. in unfortunate [situations] with some of the injuries and things that he’s dealt with, but we’re going to explore every opportunity, and I don’t think there’s anything specifically we’re looking for.” The team’s firing of GM Kwesi Adofo-Mensah last month might mean McCarthy’s time with the Vikings is all but over. Look for the Vikings to talk with Kirk Cousins in the coming weeks as the Falcons are expected to part ways with the former Minnesota starter. They could also show interest in Kyler Murray and Aaron Rodgers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9546-d89c-a1be-bfdfdfa80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman reports Eagles OC Sean Mannion is “expected to install more zone-blocking concepts that originate from the Shanahan tree offensive philosophies.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-959c-d042-afbc-fddebcad0000</link>
      <description>Mannion is expected to lean on run game coordinator and tight ends coach Ryan Mahaffey in installing a zone-blocking scheme reminiscent of the one used by the Shanahans and their acolytes over the decades. Eagles head coach Nick Sirriani said he expects Saquon Barkley — coming off a down 2025 season — to be “exceptional” in the team’s new rushing scheme. “He’s been highly productive in many of the schemes,” Sirianni said of Barkley, who had 28 rushes of more than ten yards in 2025 after having 46 such runs in 2024. The Eagles in 2025 used zone rushing concepts on 45 percent of their carries, the 13th lowest rate in the NFL. They were efficient with zone rushes, logging a 50 percent success rate, the tenth highest in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-959c-d042-afbc-fddebcad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano said NFL teams are “monitoring” the trade market for Jaguars WR Brian Thomas, Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-95df-d89c-a1be-bfdf746c0000</link>
      <description>Thomas was drafted by a previous Jaguars regime and his play fell off dramatically — completed with major effort issues — in 2025. “There has been no indication that trading Thomas is something the Jaguars are planning, but there are teams monitoring the situation in case the hypertalented LSU product has fallen far enough down the Jacksonville depth chart that the front office would consider a move,” Graziano said. ESPN’s Ben Solak named the Patriots, Bills, Steelers, and Raiders as potential Thomas suitors this offseason. As a rookie in 2024, Thomas went for 1,282 yards and 10 touchdowns as an explosive threat, mostly with Mac Jones under center for the Jags. Thomas has shown vanishingly little chemistry with Trevor Lawrence, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-95df-d89c-a1be-bfdf746c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
