<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Ashton Jeanty will play in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6521-dc7a-af9b-efbfc8ab0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty isn’t dealing with any injuries right now. The Raiders are simply tanking so effectively that Schefter felt the need to mention he won’t be getting the day off. Vegas has already shut down Brock Bowers and Maxx Crosby. Both players had been playing through their respective injuries for weeks. The Raiders’ game versus the Giants today will determine the No. 1 overall pick, making Week 17 the perfect time for the team to put the pair of star players on ice. With no injuries of note this year, the Raiders couldn’t find a reason to do the same for Jeanty. Coming off a 188-yard, two-score explosion in Week 16, Jeanty is back in our RB1 good graces versus New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6521-dc7a-af9b-efbfc8ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports George Kittle “will test out his ankle pregame to see if he can go” in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6528-d56e-afff-e7e86d5b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added that Kittle is intent on testing out his ankle. He didn’t mention whether or not the 49ers wanted him to give it a go. Kittle didn’t practice once this week, which is typically a sign that a player won’t suit up. It sounds like Kittle is pushing to play, but we wouldn’t be surprised if the team forces him to take the week off. If Kittle is ultimately inactive, Jake Tonges would take over the starting job for Week 17. Tonges would have some TE2 appeal in a possible shootout with Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6528-d56e-afff-e7e86d5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (finger) will not play in Week 17 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6548-dc7a-af9b-efffd3ad0004</link>
      <description>Tuten was limited in practice throughout the week after recently undergoing surgery on his finger. The team downgraded him to out over the weekend. He has a shot at returning in Week 18 to get in some reps before the playoffs. Travis Etienne will see the bulk of the carries versus Indianapolis this week, putting him in the RB1 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6548-dc7a-af9b-efffd3ad0004</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Ricky Pearsall (ankle/knee) is “likely to play” in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-654c-d56e-afff-e7ec47ee0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall logged three limited practices this week before being listed as questionable. He has been dealing with the knee issue all year and the ankle injury on top of that certainly hasn’t helped. Pearsall’s return couldn’t have come at a better time with George Kittle expected to miss Week 17. With targets up for grabs in the 49ers offense, Pearsall will be a high-risk WR4 versus the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-654c-d56e-afff-e7ec47ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports George Kittle (ankle) is “highly unlikely” to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6552-d56e-afff-e7fa54ac0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports this morning that Kittle will test out his ankle in warmups. While that may still happen, all signs point to the superstar tight end getting Week 17 off. Jake Tonges will draw the start in his place. Tonges is a low-end TE2 for the final week of the fantasy football season. Jauan Jennings and Ricky Pearsall should also see an uptick in targets with Kittle sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6552-d56e-afff-e7fa54ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lamar Jackson (back) could be back for Week 18 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6559-dc7a-af9b-efff3db30000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s graphics team wrote that Jackson was “likely” to play in Week 18, but the man himself didn’t go that far. For now, we will consider him questionable for the Ravens’ upcoming date with the Steelers. Baltimore needs the Steelers to lose today to stay alive in the AFC playoff hunt. It’s hard to imagine Jackson missing a play-in game next week if that does happen. Things could change if the Ravens are eliminated by a Steelers win later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6559-dc7a-af9b-efff3db30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Travis Kelce will “take some time after the season” to consider retirement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-655f-d56e-afff-e7ff93a40000</link>
      <description>This is not a surprise, but it does help us set a timeline for when Kelce might make his decision. It doesn’t sound like we will know whether or not Kelce is done anytime soon. Rapoport noted that Kelce will not play for a team other than Kansas City if he chooses to keep the cleats on for another season. Kelce is an impending free agent, but he and the Chiefs should have no issues working out a one-year deal to give him a final ride if that’s what he wants. If not, a Week 18 date with the Raiders will be his last game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-655f-d56e-afff-e7ff93a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RT Anton Harrison (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6567-d968-a19b-7df766370000</link>
      <description>Harrison was added to the injury report on Sunday morning, likely after falling ill over the weekend. Players tend to play through illnesses, so this shouldn’t be an issue for the Jags. Cole Van Lanen will take his spot in the lineup if Harrison can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6567-d968-a19b-7df766370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-656c-d35e-a1bf-65eef8290000</link>
      <description>McMillan is an extremely late addition to the injury report. He presumably woke up this morning feeling sick and is now at risk of missing today’s game. While players tend to play through illnesses, an addition to the report this late means fantasy managers will need to watch the Panthers’ inactives when they drop 90 minutes before kickoff. Jalen Coker would be in line for more work if McMillan is inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-656c-d35e-a1bf-65eef8290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Packers “are expected to rest key players” in Week 18 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65a0-d35e-a1bf-65e2a29d0000</link>
      <description>The Packers secured a playoff spot by beating the Ravens yesterday. They are locked in as the No. 7 seed with no ability to move up in the order. Jordan Love missed Week 17 with a concussion and Josh Jacobs has been playing through knee issues for most of the season. Christian Watson recently suffered a chest injury and has been playing through it as well. The list goes on and on for the Packers, as it does for most teams at this point in the season. With nothing to play for in Week 18, expect those three players and several others to get the week off as Green Bay prepares for a Wild Card Round game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65a0-d35e-a1bf-65e2a29d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
