<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports Garrett Wilson “appears to have avoided a serious knee injury” in Week 6’s loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df45-d94a-a79d-df4d12690000</link>
      <description>This news comes after Wilson underwent an MRI to reveal the extent of the damage. As Cimini points out, The winless Jets have two games before their Week 9 bye, which could factor into how soon he returns to the field. The Jets already have a painfully thin receiving room that is now expected to feature Allen Lazard and Josh Reynolds as its top options. After watching Justin Fields fail to top 100 passing yards for a second time this season, there’s little reason to take a shot on either while Wilson is out,</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df45-d94a-a79d-df4d12690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed QB Anthony Richardson (eye) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df49-d94a-a79d-df4d1f3d0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games, though he was already missing all the games anyway while watching Daniel Jones, so that’s nothing too new. Richardson, per ESPN’s Stephen Holder “was hospitalized after a pole that he had affixed an elastic stretch band to snapped during his pregame routine, resulting in the pole forcefully impacting his face.” Through three years, Richardson’s best comp is the French waiter inThe Simpsonsthat somehow falls into a dumptruck filled with rat traps. We’d be unsurprised if Richardson was left on IR after the Colts find a replacement backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df49-d94a-a79d-df4d1f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanner Hudson (concussion) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df4d-dd4c-afb9-ffcd303b0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimated DNP, but we almost never see someone clear protocol ahead of a Thursday night game. With Mike Gesicki also likely out, it looks like Noah Fant may have some stream appeal as a TE2 as the Bengals are forced to rely heavily on him and Drew Sample in their well-stocked tight end platoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df4d-dd4c-afb9-ffcd303b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals listed Trey Hendrickson (back) as a DNP on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df50-db72-a199-ff5be02a0000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson is reportedly day-to-day after suffering a back injury in Sunday’s loss to the Packers. The star pass rusher drawing a DNP on the team’s estimated report isn’t all that surprising, but giving the timeline for his injury, we’ll assume he still has a chance to suit up against the Steelers until we hear otherwise. Hendrickson has totaled four sacks and 10 tackles in the six games he has appeared in this season and would be a major loss for the league’s 30th ranked defense if he is unable to go on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df50-db72-a199-ff5be02a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals listed DE Shemar Stewart (ankle) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df54-dd4c-afb9-ffd524320000</link>
      <description>Stewart hasn’t played since Week 2, but a full practice designation on Monday is a good indication he’ll be suiting up on Thursday night against the Steelers. The rookie first-rounder has totaled just two tackles in the two games he’s appeared in this season, and could see a fairly significant role if Trey Hendrickson (back) is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df54-dd4c-afb9-ffd524320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Brian Branch has been suspended for one game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df61-dd4c-afb9-ffe1c0460000</link>
      <description>It will be a one-game suspension without pay for Wilson, who can appeal the decision. NFL Vice President of Football Operations Jon Runyan wrote Branch’s actions on Sunday night, “Your’e aggressive, non-football act was entirely unwarranted, posed a serious risk of injury, and clearly violated the standards of conduct and sportsmanship expected of NFL players. Your conducted reflected poorly on the NFL and has no place in our game.” It’s a pretty justified response after Branch’s actions at the end of Sunday’s game against the Chiefs resulted in an on-field brawl. Assuming he doesn’t appeal the suspension Branch will likely be out for Week 7’s game against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df61-dd4c-afb9-ffe1c0460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Titans are expected to name Mike McCoy as their interim HC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df67-dd4c-afb9-ffe747720000</link>
      <description>McCoy, who joined the Titans this season as a senior offensive assistant, will make his Titans head coaching debut in Week 7 against the Patriots. The 53-year-old coach served as head coach of the Chargers from 2013-2016, racking up a 27-37 record in four seasons while going a combined 9-23 in his final two years. McCoy held offensive coordinator roles with the Broncos in 2017 and the Cardinals in 2018, where his teams finished 27th and 32nd in points scored, respectively. Regardless of how the next 12 weeks go for McCoy and company, we would expect the Titans to completely clean house as they look to bring on yet another new coach during the 2026 offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df67-dd4c-afb9-ffe747720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) is inactive for Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73a830000</link>
      <description>Despite being limited in practice throughout the week, the Bills will opt to play it safe with Kincaid. The third-year tight end would have been coming off one of the best performances of his career (6-108-0) in last week’s loss to the Patriots, but will instead sit this one out in hopes of getting a little extra rest before the Bills’ Week 7 bye. Fantasy managers in need of an emergency option can look for Dawson Knox, who should be available in most leagues. In addition to Kincaid, the Bills also declared WR Curtis Samuel, LB Jimmy Ciarlo, LB Matt Milano, and OT Chase Lundt inactive for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73a830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared WR Darnell Mooney, WR Ray-Ray McCloud, CB Clark Phillips, RB Nathan Carter, CB Billy Bowman, DL LaCale London, and OL Jack Nelson inactive for Week 6 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df8d-def2-abdb-dfede9000000</link>
      <description>Mooney was ruled out before the weekend but McCloud, who has played the third-most snaps of any receiver on the roster, is a surprise scratch. Third-year pro Casey Washington is expected to see an increase in snaps on Monday night and has seen nine targets on 63 routes run this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df8d-def2-abdb-dfede9000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray-Ray McCloud will not play in Week 6 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df93-dd4c-afb9-ffd303cd0000</link>
      <description>Any hopes that McCloud would see an increased role with Darnell Mooney (hamstring) can be cast aside. McCloud who ranks third this season in snaps among Falcons receivers, won’t be suiting up on Monday, giving way to backups Casey Washington and Jamal Agnew to see bigger roles. McCloud has caught six passes for 64 yards this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df93-dd4c-afb9-ffd303cd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
