<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-7 targets for 35 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Aaron Rodgers narrowly missed Metcalf for what would have been an easy touchdown on the team’s second possession, which was one of many overthrows by Rodgers on the evening. Another such overthrow resulted in a Los Angeles interception in the second quarter. Metcalf continues to be hamstrung by a low-volume pass offense, leaving his fantasy value lacking in any game he’s held out of the end zone. He gets a matchup boost in Week 11 when the Steelers take on the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught all three targets for 33 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</link>
      <description>The “Muth” chants from the well-traveled Pittsburgh fans weren’t enough to return any semblance of fantasy value for the veteran tight end on a night the offense managed only 221 yards of total offense on the road. Freiermuth remains a touchdown-dependent dart throw in fantasy circles ahead of a plus matchup against the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden is scheduled to undergo an MRI on his knee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6dec-d45b-affe-7dfe32820000</link>
      <description>A knee-to-knee collision knocked Gadsden out in the third quarter of the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers. Gadsden has totaled 35 receptions for 466 yards and two touchdowns this season and officially broke out in Week 7 against the Colts when he went for 7-164-1 on nine targets. His absence will make for a big hole in a Chargers offense that has been surprisingly pass heavy in their second year in Greg Roman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6dec-d45b-affe-7dfe32820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders DT Daron Payne has been suspended for one game after punching Amon-Ra St. Brown in Week 10’s loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e0e-d45b-affe-7f9ed8e30000</link>
      <description>Payne could appeal this, but the tape doesn’t exactly work in his favor. Payne took a blatant, cheap shot at St. Brown during the second quarter of Sunday’s game and was immediately ejected for his actions. Assuming this holds up, which it should, Payne will miss Week 11’s game against the Dolphins in Spain and will be eligible to return in Week 13 after the Commanders’ bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e0e-d45b-affe-7f9ed8e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rob Gronkowski retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</link>
      <description>Gronkowski will sign a one-day contract to retire as a Patriot on Wednesday, but he has technically been retired for four seasons. The future Hall of Famer last played in 2021 and returned to the game in 2020, joining Tom Brady and the Buccaneers after a year away. Gronk, a four-time Super Bowl champion and four-time All-Pro, will officially walk away as one of the best tight ends in league history. He currently ranks 10th amongst TEs in all-time receptions (621), sixth in receiving yards (9,286), and third in touchdowns (92).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he isn’t sure if Garrett Wilson (knee) will be able to play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</link>
      <description>Wilson re-aggravated the knee injury he suffered in Week 6 against the Broncos. It was Wilson’s first game back from the injury, and he failed to haul in any of the three targets that came in his direction. Although Justin Fields can certainly be blamed for some of that. Wilson will undergo additional imaging on his knee to determine where things stand right now, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he was again sidelined after this latest setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Azareye’h Thomas (concussion) will not play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is in the league’s concussion protocol after going down in Week 10’s win against the Browns. With the Jets slated to play on Thursday against the Patriots, the short turnaround was always going to make it tough for Thomas to clear protocol in time for Week 11. Thomas played on 24 defensive snaps in Sunday’s win and has seen an increased role in the Jets’ last three games after playing primarily as a backup through the first six weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 4-of-4 targets for 89 yards in the Giants’ Week 10 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e79-d1e7-a1fa-7efb203e0000</link>
      <description>It was a typical low-volume day for Slayton, but he made the most of his looks. The veteran receiver hauled in one of the more impressive catches you will see in Sunday’s loss when he created just enough separation from the defender to turn around and make an outstretched, one-handed grab to pick up 31 yards and move the ball into Bears territory. He would haul in a 38-yard reception on the following play. Slayton has now gone for 62 or more yards in back-to-back games and but is averaging just 5.5 targets per game in his last four outings. He won’t be anything more than a desperation dart throw in Week 11 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e79-d1e7-a1fa-7efb203e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn opened Monday’s presser saying, “Please don’t ask me anything about the QBs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e82-d1e7-a1fa-7eea9d9c0000</link>
      <description>It’s par for the course for Glenn, who reminded reporters that “I’m not going to tell you” even if they do ask. Justin Fields threw for a whopping 54 yards in Sunday’s win over the Browns, which was only made possible by two special teams touchdowns and a 42-yard touchdown reception by Breece Hall that came on a screen pass. Glenn has been in Fields’ corner since day one and was nearly backed into benching him before an injury to Tyrod Taylor forced Fields back into the starting lineup for Week 9. Fields will likely continue to start until the losses again pile up, which could happen as early as Thursday when they take on the 8-2 Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e82-d1e7-a1fa-7eea9d9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jackson Powers-Johnson’s ankle injury “could potentially end his season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</link>
      <description>Powers-Johnson will land on injured reserve, but it sounds like he’ll be evaluated later in the season to see if he can return. Powers-Johnson has started every game at right guard for the Raiders this season, earning a PFF grade of 63.8 while being one of the few bright spots of an underwhelming group. Backup Alex Cappa replaced Powers-Johnson in Week 10’s loss and will likely take over as the starter for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
