<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 4-of-5 targets for 67 yards in the Steelers’ Week 11 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec2-d673-a39e-aed330ce0000</link>
      <description>Washington turned in a highlight reel play in the second quarter when he turned a short reception into a 31-yard gain after breaking two tackles and laying out a third defender for good measure at the end of the play. Washington is a clear problem for opposing defenders whenever the ball is in his hands, and has seen five or more targets in four of his last six games. He’ll have some value as a dart throw TE2 in Week 12 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec2-d673-a39e-aed330ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard rushed four times for 21 yards in the Panthers’ Week 11 win over the Falcons, adding one catch for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec3-d45b-affe-dfd790fc0000</link>
      <description>Rico Dowdle ran 19 times and caught five passes on seven targets. Hubbard has seen five or fewer touches in three straight games. He is a distant backup to Dowdle amidst the latter’s late-career breakout. Fantasy managers don’t need to hold Hubbard into Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec3-d45b-affe-dfd790fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin caught his lone target for five yards in the Steelers’ Week 11 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec6-d1e7-a1fa-deeef1c90000</link>
      <description>There’s not much to say here. After leading the Steelers with 5-56-0 on six targets in his previous game, Austin returned from the team’s bye week only to fade into irrelevance in Week 11. We’ve come to expect this kind of inconsistent play from Austin, who won’t be on the fantasy radar in Week 12 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec6-d1e7-a1fa-deeef1c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 4-of-8 targets for 53 yards in the Packers’ Week 11 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ecb-d45b-affe-dfdf53040000</link>
      <description>That quiet box score doesn’t tell the story of just how rough Doubs’ day was, as he committed at least three drops, each of which came in critical situations in another “surprisingly close” game. Doubs was also briefly shaken up after a hard fall on his head but was thankfully never announced with an injury. Doubs remains the closest thing this team has to a “No. 1 receiver,” but his play far too often comes nowhere close to that level. His usage should make him a WR2 in fantasy, but he is struggling for WR3 stats. That seems unlikely to change for a tough Week 12 Vikings matchup, though the Vikes are prone to surrendering the kind of down-field grabs Doubs in theory excels at.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ecb-d45b-affe-dfdf53040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught his lone target for 19 yards in the Steelers’ Week 11 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec9-d713-ad9e-eedd2acc0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth went for 6-111-2 a few weeks ago against the Bengals, but things looked a bit different this time around, as the veteran tight end was unable to get anything going, and was held to just one target on the day. Freiermuth remains in a three-way split with Jonnu Smith and Darnell Washington for playing time, which makes all three Steelers tight ends hard to trust in Week 12 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec9-d713-ad9e-eedd2acc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker caught all four of his targets for 52 yards in the Panthers’ Week 11 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec9-d45b-affe-dfdfada60000</link>
      <description>Coker operated as the Panthers’ No. 3 receiver again this week. He averaged an impressive 13 yards per target but only accounted for nine percent of the team’s receiving opportunities. Coker is ultimately a better real-life player than a fantasy asset. He is buried in the WR6/7 ranks ahead of his Week 12 date with the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ec9-d45b-affe-dfdfada60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 19 times for 73 yards and two touchdowns in the Jaguars’ Week 11 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ecf-d713-ad9e-eedfcc850000</link>
      <description>Etienne was held without a catch on two targets. The struggling back’s best fantasy performance in nearly two months came even as he found himself in a much more even timeshare with Bhayshul Tuten, who posted a 15/74/1 line of his own before departing with a fourth quarter ankle injury. With the game shockingly out of reach, Tuten did not return, though we have little insight into his Week 12 status. Greater Tuten involvement has seemed overdue for some time now, but Etienne was one goal-line stop away from a three-score day. If Tuten can’t make it back for Week 12 against the Cardinals, Etienne will suddenly be looking like a strong RB2 again for a matchup that could be very fantasy friendly for the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ecf-d713-ad9e-eedfcc850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders caught all four of his targets for 22 yards in the Panthers’ Week 11 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ed4-d673-a39e-aed5e9150000</link>
      <description>Sanders led the team’s tight ends in targets and catches, but Tommy Tremble was the hero of the day with a 54-yard reception to set up a game-winning field goal. Rookie tight end Mitchell Evans also caught a pair of passes. With all three tight ends seeing some work every week, Sanders is barely in the TE2 mix ahead of Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ed4-d673-a39e-aed5e9150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 5-of-6 targets for 64 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 11 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ed7-d45b-affe-dfd730ab0000</link>
      <description>With this snaps predictably trending up in his second game for the Jags, Meyers comfortably led the team in every receiving category in a surprisingly non-competitive contest, one where the Jaguars’ ground success limited their aerial volume. 5/64 is a classic Meyers statline for those familiar with his time in Vegas, but coming on just 22 Trevor Lawrence attempts is a bullish indicator heading into Week 12 against the Cardinals. He can be fired up as a WR3 for that against Arizona’s shaky defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ed7-d45b-affe-dfd730ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 2-of-5 targets for 41 yards in the Chargers’ Week 11 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ede-d45b-affe-dfde3ea70000</link>
      <description>If you throw out his injury-shortened Week 10 against the Steelers, this was Gadsden’s first quiet box score since Oct. 5. Of course, he was second on the Chargers in both targets and receiving yards. It just didn’t mean much in a game where a beleaguered Justin Herbert was limited to 81 yards on 18 attempts. The good news is Gadsden’s quad injury already appeared to be a thing of the past. With the Bolts headed on bye for Week 12, Gadsden can be trusted as a TE1 for their Week 13 return against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ede-d45b-affe-dfde3ea70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
