<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said “the intention” is to get Brandon Aiyuk back on the field this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e03-d1e7-a1fa-7eebfc4a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers keep pushing back Aiyuk’s return date and now Lynch isn’t even putting a timeline on it. The team hasn’t designated him to return from the PUP list yet, meaning he might not even be that close to taking the field. Aiyuk is recovering from the multi-ligament knee injury he suffered in the middle of the 2024 season. The injury was more complicated than a standard ACL tear and it’s unclear when he will be ready to suit up. The question Lynch was answering was whether this could be a redshirt year for Aiyuk. He rebuffed the idea, but then ominously ended his statement with, “But we’ll see, no absolutes there.” It sounds like the 49ers have at least considered the possibility that Aiyuk doesn’t play this year. Needless to say, it doesn’t sound like Aiyuk will be returning anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e03-d1e7-a1fa-7eebfc4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Matthew Golden (shoulder) was “definitely close” to playing in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eeec6ad0000</link>
      <description>Golden was limited in practice last Wednesday before missing the final two sessions of the week. He got a questionable tag but was ruled out ahead of kickoff. Golden returned to practice yesterday for a limited session and LaFleur told reporters the team will see how things go in practice for him this week before making a final call on his availability. Golden has struggled to make much of an impact this year and a lingering injury won’t do him any favors. Fantasy managers shouldn’t feel the need to hold onto him, healthy or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eeec6ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez (shoulder) is practicing in full for Week 11 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e32-d45b-affe-7fb63d1a0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez missed most of the second half of Week 10 with the shoulder issue but managed a limited practice on Wednesday. A full practice today means he will be good to go for Week 11 versus a beatable Miami run defense. Rodriguez operated as the Commanders’ lead back in the first half of Week 10’s game. He should hold onto that role this week, putting him in the RB3 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e32-d45b-affe-7fb63d1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e36-d1e7-a1fa-7efef63d0000</link>
      <description>Gordon was also limited on Wednesday. He should be able to suit up this week, but Jaylen Wright ran as Miami’s RB2 in Week 10. Gordon’s ankle injury may have played a role in that, but the bad news is the ankle is still an issue. Neither Miami backup holds much fantasy value right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e36-d1e7-a1fa-7efef63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (hamstring) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e44-d45b-affe-7fd6e91c0000</link>
      <description>Washington was held out of Wednesday’s session, causing some concern that he could miss Week 11. Even a limited practice today puts him on track to suit up for Sunday’s game. Washington let the Jags with seven targets in Week 10. He scored once through the air and returned a punt to the house. Assuming he gets past the hamstring issue this week, Washington will slot in as a WR4 versus the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e44-d45b-affe-7fd6e91c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e60-d1e7-a1fa-7eea1b460000</link>
      <description>NBC Houston’s Aaron Wilson notes that Stroud is still experiencing concussion-related symptoms. Backup QB Davis Mills is getting ready to start for the second straight game in Week 11 against the Titans. The Texans could end up with a run-heavy game script here, so Mills may not be needed to engineer another improbably good showing, though the Titans’ defense certainly could provide him with opportunities to make plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e60-d1e7-a1fa-7eea1b460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (shoulder) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e6c-d713-ad9e-7e7c756b0000</link>
      <description>Two weeks ago, Schultz sat out during Wednesday and Thursday’s practices before practicing in full on Friday and suiting up on Sunday. The 29-year-old tight end is clearly banged up, but he knows the offense and can play on game day without participating much during the practice week. Schultz’s target share could take a hit if second-year tight end Cade Stover (foot) returns from injured reserve this week, though. Stover was limited on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e6c-d713-ad9e-7e7c756b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed WR Isaiah Hodgins, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e71-d45b-affe-7ff79cd30000</link>
      <description>This is GM Joe Schoen’s third time bringing Hodgins aboard one of his teams, having first been part of the Bills’ front office that drafted Hodgins in the 2020 NFL Draft’s sixth round. Schoen later plucked Hodgins off waivers in 2022, after Schoen had vacated the Bills’ assistant general manager role for the Giants’ general manager role earlier in the year. Hodgins has toiled away on the Steelers’ practice squad this season. He has never cracked 400 yards in a single season, but at times served as a capable intermediate-depth clasher. Given the state of the Giants’ wide receiver corps, Hodgins could work his way into a starting role at some point, though he cannot be started in 12-team leagues at this time. He is a name to know moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e71-d45b-affe-7ff79cd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (knee soreness) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e70-d673-a39e-fef1780a0000</link>
      <description>Jackson is back. Per ESPN’s Jamison Hensley, the Ravens’ quarterback “moved around well during media viewing and looks set to start Sunday at Browns.” Playing through knee soreness against the Browns’ top-tier defense is unideal, but Jackson remains in the high-end QB1 ranks thanks to his elite dual-threat talents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e70-d673-a39e-fef1780a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (knee) “once again is expected to assume a larger workload” with RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e8c-d45b-affe-7f9eb5980000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Mike Reiss notes that “the only other running back on the roster is former practice squad player Terrell Jennings” (knee), who is questionable to play this evening. The Patriots will likely elevate veteran RB D’Ernest Johnson “from the practice squad for the third straight week,” and also re-signed RB Jonathan Ward to the practice squad on Tuesday, making him an elevation option alongside rookie RB Rushawn Baker. Henderson should handle a borderline RB1/2-level workload, and possesses the explosive traits required to finish squarely in the RB1 pool this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e8c-d45b-affe-7f9eb5980000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
