<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:07:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sports’ John Gambadoro reports the Cardinals are “intrigued” by Bears QB Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cdd-d89c-a1be-efdf62cb0000</link>
      <description>This is not a usual source for NFL news, but the long-time Phoenix-based reporter has a strong track record in other sports. Bagent threw six interceptions and three touchdowns in a four-start trial in 2023, but is entering his age-26 season and has two years left on his contract after signing a two-year extension last offseason. In a quarterback landscape this barren for teams looking for solutions, it’s not a surprise that younger backups could be of interest around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cdd-d89c-a1be-efdf62cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Matthew Golden will “be a much bigger part of the game plan” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce5-d629-a1bc-fcfd90580000</link>
      <description>Of course, he also says that he’s “not putting him above Christian Watson or Jayden Reed just yet,” as there’s space to grow from what Golden did as a rookie and still not hit any fantasy-intriguing upside scenarios. He probably deserves to be approached cautiously in offseason best ball formats, though it was nice to see him pop off for 4/84/1 in the playoffs before the Packers collectively turtled on a lost fourth-quarter lead to the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce5-d629-a1bc-fcfd90580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Romeo Doubs “is as good as gone” from the Packers in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce8-d042-afbc-7dfa0c320000</link>
      <description>Doubs profiles as one of the better available receivers after we clear away George Pickens (expected to be tagged) and Alec Pierce (could be tagged), and enters his age-26 season as a likely No. 2 or No. 3 target somewhere. We’d be surprised if his fantasy role grew much, but perhaps he’ll find the exact right spot (Miami?) to be a strong No. 2 target and snag a WR3 ranking in 2026 drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce8-d042-afbc-7dfa0c320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes the Packers will move on from EDGE Rashan Gary.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cea-d89c-a1be-efff94cc0000</link>
      <description>“I would be surprised if Gary is on the team next season. I’ll put it like that,” Schneidman notes. Releasing Gary, who disappointed in much better circumstances (next to Micah Parsons) in 2025 to the tune of just 7.5 sacks, would free up $11 million in cap space for the Packers per Schneidman. The career Packer will enter his age-29 season in 2025 with 46.5 career sacks but hasn’t been quite the same caliber of player since a 2022 ACL tear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cea-d89c-a1be-efff94cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers re-signed LS J.J. Jansen to a one-year deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</link>
      <description>The long-time snapper of snaps longer than the average snap will enter his age-40 season with the Panthers in 2026. Jansen has played in every single game of Panthers football since signing with the club as a UDFA in 2009. He has recovered one fumble and made one Pro Bowl. He also has snapped many, many balls a moderate distance away from his person in an attempt to set up some good punts and kicks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Vic Tafur believes “it seems like the 49ers have big plans for second-year player Jordan James.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</link>
      <description>It’s an interesting assertion because James rarely played this year, starting the season with a wrist injury and eventually playing only three offensive snaps in three active regular season games. However, James did close out the Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks with six carries for 28 yards and it appears he could seize the No. 2 role behind Christian McCaffrey if Brian Robinson walks in free agency. Isaac Guerendo, per Tafur, “seems like an easy cut” if Robinson returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes Mac Jones “checks more boxes for what the Vikings are looking for” than the other potentially available quarterbacks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d01-d042-afbc-7dd3eeb60000</link>
      <description>Yes, we are again banging the drum that the 49ers may get an offer they can’t refuse for Jones, who has only $1 million in guaranteed salary in 2026 and could be a major upgrade for the Vikings over J.J. McCarthy. Lewis believes the 49ers will “drive a hard bargain” for Jones. As has been rumored for a bit, it would likely take a Day 2 pick for the 49ers to move on from Jones, and perhaps a second-rounder rather than a third-rounder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d01-d042-afbc-7dd3eeb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reports the Vikings “removed most of [their] over-the-middle passing concepts throughout the season” to keep J.J. McCarthy’s line of sight “simple.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d09-d89c-a1be-efdfab780000</link>
      <description>The depths of the McCarthy struggles last year were obvious, but the fact that the Vikings didn’t even trust him to do some fairly remedial work adds another layer to just how fractured this offense was. It’s almost impossible to imagine McCarthy winning a starting job against whoever the Vikings bring in this offseason. In fact, with Kwesi Adofo-Mensah fired, it’s probably not far-fetched to suggest that McCarthy could be available in a trade if another team still believes in him. If he stays in Minnesota, McCarthy is an easy fantasy football fade in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d09-d89c-a1be-efdfab780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes Jim Schwartz could come back as the Eagles defensive coordinator in 2027.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d1f-d990-a1de-6d5f649d0000</link>
      <description>Schwartz, who resigned from the Browns defensive coordinator job in early February after Todd Monken was named head coach, is set to take the year off with all defensive coordinator chairs filled. Vic Fangio appears to be very “year to year” with the Eagles at this point and contemplated stepping down this offseason. Schwartz’s deal with the Browns has a club option for 2027 that may require compensation in return, but Breer believes he will be the “belle of the defensive coaches’ ball” in 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d1f-d990-a1de-6d5f649d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Enquirer’s Kelsey Conway reports the Bengals will gather information from other teams about Trey Hendrickson’s market at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</link>
      <description>The Bengals have left open the option to trade Hendrickson through the franchise tag, but that seems like a really unrealistic scenario on paper. Hendrickson would, after being tagged back-to-back years, be guaranteed a $30.2 million salary in 2026. He could simply sign the tag and likely do better for himself than he would on the free market. This feels a lot like the Vikings trying to drum up a market for Sam Darnold in a tag-and-trade last year — if a team can’t afford to tag the player and simply keep him, it’s hard to believe that a trade will come to fruition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
