<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer is active for the Bills in Week 15 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ddd-d8cf-affb-bdffb9660000</link>
      <description>Palmer had missed the last few weeks with an ankle injury, but was able to get in a few limited practices this week and appears good to go. It wouldn’t be a surprise if he is not quite at 100%, but the Bills need his athleticism and downfield capability in their receiving corps. Surprisingly, Gabe Davis was made in inactive for this game, which might signal a more pass heavy approach for the Bills since Davis is arguably their best run blocking wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ddd-d8cf-affb-bdffb9660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared WR/KR Efton Chism III, OLB Bradyn Swinson, TE C.J. Dippre, OT Marcus Bryant, DT Eric Gregory, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 15 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1de2-d77b-adfb-dfe3f74e0000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here. The Patriots come into this game relatively healthy, except for defensive tackle Milton Williams being on the IR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1de2-d77b-adfb-dfe3f74e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was ruled out after re-aggravating his foot injury before Week 15’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dc0-d005-a9bf-ddf4da560000</link>
      <description>Odunze is officially active, but Rapoport’s report that he’s been ruled out after re-aggravating his foot injury pregame came just minutes before kickoff. It’s disastrous news for anyone that was counting on Odunze in the first round of the fantasy playoffs. Luther Burden should see a boost in value with Odunze sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dc0-d005-a9bf-ddf4da560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Zonovan Knight (ankle) left Arizona’s Week 15 game against the Texans and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e19-d8cf-affb-be3b24460000</link>
      <description>He was carted off the field after being tackled on his first carry. Knight left with minus-2 rushing yards. Though they initially called him questionable, FOX’s sideline reporter Jen Hale described Knight as being “in a tremendous amount of pain.” Knight may be staring at a season-ending injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e19-d8cf-affb-be3b24460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens LB Teddye Buchanan was carted from the field in Week 15’s game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dff-d1bc-a3fb-9dffd6510000</link>
      <description>Buchanan was running down field with the punt coverage team when he went down on a non-contact play. The rookie linebacker was grabbing at his right knee before heading to the sideline and was later carted to the locker room. A rookie fourth-round pick, Buchanan has started 12 of the 13 games he’s appeared in this season, totaling 91 tackles, a half sack, and a forced fumble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dff-d1bc-a3fb-9dffd6510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) left Houston’s Week 15 game against the Cardinals and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e42-d8cf-affb-be6a9e230000</link>
      <description>Marks had seven carries for 30 yards before leaving, adding a “fumble recovery” touchdown in the box score. Marks is on the sideline jogging and doesn’t seem like he is certainly done for the day, though he doesn’t have his helmet. Jawhar Jordan has been Houston’s main changeup back today with Dare Ogunbowale also mixing in behind Marks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e42-d8cf-affb-be6a9e230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Andre Baccellia (neck) left Arizona’s Week 15 game versus the Texans and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e4d-d005-a9bf-de7dcfa90000</link>
      <description>Baccellia took a kickoff and appeared to get lost in the pile after getting a helmet-to-helmet hit. We’re unsure exactly what the diagnosis is, but it looked serious and several players were praying as he was loaded up on the cart. He did show a little movement and gave a thumbs up while leaving. It would not be surprising if this injury sent Baccellia to season-ending injured reserve. He was taken to the hospital for further observation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e4d-d005-a9bf-de7dcfa90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Phillips is questionable to return to Week 15 against the Patriots with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e6c-d8cf-affb-be6e4d340000</link>
      <description>Phillips is getting extra playing time with Ed Oliver (biceps) on the IR. If Phillips is unable to return, rookies Deone Walker and T.J. Sanders will likely see more playing time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e6c-d8cf-affb-be6e4d340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (knee) is active for Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e2f-d77b-adfb-deaf3f220000</link>
      <description>It was rumored earlier in the day that Jacobs was expected to play, but it has now been confirmed. Jacobs was not listed among the team’s inactives released for Week 15, meaning he’ll be good to go against a stout Broncos defense. Backup Emanuel Wilson is also active after being listed as questionable, but can’t be trusted for fantasy this week. While Jacobs is active, the Packers did declare RB Pierre Strong, OL Donovan Jennings, DL Quinton Bohanna, WR Savion Williams, DL Nazir Stackhouse, and DL Barryn Sorrell inactive for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e2f-d77b-adfb-deaf3f220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LB Cody Simon (knee) left Arizona’s Week 15 game against the Texans and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e6e-d77b-adfb-deef24490000</link>
      <description>Simon left in the first quarter, was initially questionable, and then was later ruled out. Owen Pappoe took over at linebacker. This injury could possibly end Simon’s season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e6e-d77b-adfb-deef24490000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
