<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 01:29:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brenton Strange caught 5-of-5 targets for 93 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 12 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b35c-db57-afda-f77e9f130000</link>
      <description>Strange looked great in his first game back from injured reserve. He first touched the ball on the Jaguars’ second play from scrimmage, a play-action pass from the Jaguars’ own five-yard line, by getting open on a corner route and coming down with a 30-yard gain. Shortly after halftime, Strange once again got open on a corner route before hauling in a diving 24-yard completion. Strange is right back in the TE1 tier. He faces the Titans next weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b35c-db57-afda-f77e9f130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirk Cousins completed 16-of-23 passes for 199 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Falcons’ 24-10, Week 12 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b356-d82c-a79a-b3d6d04c0000</link>
      <description>Cousins is now the Falcons’ starter with Michael Penix Jr. (ACL) out for the season. Drake London was also out for this game as the Falcons got off to a rough start. Cousins was strip-sacked in the first quarter for a fumble the Falcons recovered, then threw a pick-six later in the first half. He threw his first touchdown at the start of the second quarter for nine yards and threw a deep shot to Darnell Mooney for a 49-yard score. With two touchdowns, Cousins tied Johnny Unitas for 17th-most touchdown passes in NFL history. The Falcons offense only needed to push the ball downfield sparingly and Cousins was able to take advantage of the Falcons defense’s stops to come away with the win. He will be a low-end fantasy QB2 for Week 13 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b356-d82c-a79a-b3d6d04c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-6 targets for 60 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b363-d82c-a79a-b3f72dda0000</link>
      <description>It was the most receiving yards Ferguson has mustered since Week 3. He’s faded deep into the background of the Dallas passing offense as George Pickens has emerged as a dominant pass-catching option for Dak Prescott. Ferguson ran a route on 36 of 41 Dallas drop backs and was third in targets among Cowboys pass catchers. Ferguson will only be viable in PPR formats next week against the Chiefs, who have been rather generous to opposing tight ends in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b363-d82c-a79a-b3f72dda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 23-of-36 attempts for 354 yards, two touchdowns, and an interception in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles, adding five rushes for nine yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b366-db57-afda-f776557d0000</link>
      <description>Showing no ill effects from the hip injury that cost him some playing time last week, Prescott rolled through an Eagles defense that has taken no prisoners of late, most recently embarrassing Dan Campbell’s Lions offense in Week 11. He had three completions of more than 40 yards — one to George Pickens, one to CeeDee Lamb, and one to KaVontae Turpin. Prescott ran one into the end zone in the fourth quarter, only his second rushing score of the season. As the head of a high-scoring Cowboys offense, Prescott should be in lineups every week no matter the matchup. He’ll take on the Chiefs in Thanksgiving Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b366-db57-afda-f776557d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 15 times for 86 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 12 win over the Cardinals, adding three receptions for 30 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b364-d413-ad9f-b7fd0b330000</link>
      <description>Etienne operated as the Jaguars’ clear-cut lead back despite being limited by a shoulder injury in practice all week. After TE Brenton Strange ripped off a 30-yard gain to get the Jaguars out of their own red zone on the team’s first drive, Etienne broke loose on an interior run to the right side, bringing the offense 45 yards downfield. The Jaguars then dialed up a screen pass for Etienne on the left side of the field. Etienne’s would-be coverage defender tripped over his own feet, eating turf, right after Etienne secured the catch and the Jaguars’ running back easily weaved through blocks set up by his teammates just in front of the goal line. He is an RB1 against the Titans next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b364-d413-ad9f-b7fd0b330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 14 times for 70 yards in the Falcons’ Week 12 win over the Saints, adding two catches for 37 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b363-d413-ad9f-b7ff3b7f0000</link>
      <description>It was a relatively quiet day for Robinson, though he still totaled 107 yards on 16 touches. The Falcons never really got close enough for goal-line carries to be impactful in this one and Robinson’s best plays were explosive runs. He had a 32-yard rush to get into the red zone in the first quarter and a 32-yard reception to get into Saints territory in the fourth quarter, both supporting scoring drives. Tyler Allgeier is still a threat to take short-yardage carries, but Robinson’s explosive burst keeps him in the RB1 ranks. He gets a good matchup against the Jets defense for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b363-d413-ad9f-b7ff3b7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed 12 times for 44 yards in the Falcons’ Week 12 win over the Saints, adding one catch for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b36b-d82c-a79a-b3ff75220000</link>
      <description>Allgeier saw ample usage with the Falcons leading most of the way against the Saints. He played just 22 snaps, but touched the ball 13 times for a total of 49 yards. Allgeier remains the short-yardage back for the Falcons, though there weren’t many short-yardage or goal-line situations for the offense on the day. He gets a good matchup against the Jets in Week 13 and should be in the fantasy RB4 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b36b-d82c-a79a-b3ff75220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed seven times for 17 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 12 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b374-d413-ad9f-b7fd6b520000</link>
      <description>Tuten took a backseat to starting RB Travis Etienne until the second half, and even then, Tuten was only mildly involved. The rookie running back looked good on a third-drive carry, maintaining balance while being hit at the line and picking up three extra yards. He looked similarly flashy and physical returning the opening kick in the second half 39 yards, but this stat line is not usable. Tuten is a volatile FLEX against the Titans in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b374-d413-ad9f-b7fd6b520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught all three of his targets for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 12 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b370-d90e-a9da-bf7fe0160000</link>
      <description>Mooney got another chance to operate as the Falcons’ WR1 with Drake London out in Week 12. With Kirk Cousins back at quarterback, he made a 16-yard reception on the sideline for first catch of the game. He only saw two targets the rest of the game, one being a 49-yard deep throw from Kirk Cousins for Mooney’s first touchdown of the season. Having Cousins at quarterback may mean more deep throws for Mooney, but it is still difficult to trust the 28-year-old on a weekly basis. Mooney is a boom-or-bust WR3 for Week 13 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b370-d90e-a9da-bf7fe0160000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
