<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Florida Times-Union’s Ryan O’Halloran believes WR Jakobi Meyers is “not just a rental” player for the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5469-d673-a39e-f4f9bd670000</link>
      <description>The team gave up a fourth and a sixth round pick for Meyers in their trade with the Raiders Tuesday, shoring up an injury-marred receiver room ahead of their Week 10 matchup against the Texans. “They feel like they’re going to keep Jakobi Meyers here after this season, probably not even let him hit the market,” O’Halloran said, adding Meyers becomes the team’s No. 1 receiver ahead of Parker Washington with both Travis Hunter and Brian Thomas dealing with injuries. O’Halloran expects Meyers to have a “package of plays” for the Jaguars’ Week 10 game. Washington could still function as the team’s top wideout until Meyers is up to speed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5469-d673-a39e-f4f9bd670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns QB Shedeur Sanders practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54b9-d1e7-a1fa-5efbdfa10000</link>
      <description>Sanders did not practice ahead of the Browns’ Week 8 loss to the Patriots and exits the team’s Week 9 bye in better health with a return to practice. Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski has made every effort to dodge questions about whether Sanders will get a shot to start this season. Stefanski said after the loss to New England that the starting QB situation was “not my focus.” Dillon Gabriel has been one of the league’s worst passers since landing the starting job. It would hardly be shocking if Sanders eventually got a start in another lost season for Cleveland. He can be rostered in deep superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54b9-d1e7-a1fa-5efbdfa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner remains in the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54d1-d673-a39e-f4d1bc2a0000</link>
      <description>Gardner, according to head coach Shane Steichen, will practice Wednesday despite being in the protocol. He hasn’t played since Week 7 and seems iffy to suit up in Week 10 against the Falcons after being traded to the Colts on Tuesday. Steichen said Gardner would likely suit up against Atlanta if he clears concussion protocol. While Gardner’s early-career play has fallen off a bit over the past couple years, he’ll be a marked upgrade for an injury-riddled Colts secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54d1-d673-a39e-f4d1bc2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a great development as the Bucs come out of their bye week. There was hope Irving would be back at practice ahead of Tampa’s Week 10 game against the Patriots after being sidelined more more than a month with foot and shoulder injuries. If Irving can’t get in a limited practice Thursday or Friday, he’ll likely miss Week 10, leaving Rachaad White as the team’s lead back. White, who has 67 touches over his four games as the Bucs’ starter, would be a top-20 fantasy option against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</link>
      <description>Godwin continues to sit with a lingering fibula injury, even coming out of Tampa’s Week 9 bye. He would appear to be a long shot to suit up for Week 10 against New England unless he can practice tomorrow or Friday. Godwin hasn’t played since early October. Returning from a major 2024 ankle injury, he has six catches on 14 targets this season. Sterling Shepard and Tez Johnson could continue as Tampa starters this week if Godwin remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54f9-d1e7-a1fa-5efb46f30000</link>
      <description>It’s something of a surprise after Cook appeared fully healthy in Week 9 against the Chiefs. Cook had 114 scoreless yards on 27 rushes against KC, and now has 417 rushing yards over his past three outings. Cook’s DNP could be cautionary ahead of the Bills’ Week 10 matchup with a weak Miami defense. Cook drafters should keep a close eye on his late-week practice status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54f9-d1e7-a1fa-5efb46f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joey Bosa (wrist) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54fc-d673-a39e-f4fd1d3e0000</link>
      <description>Bosa apparently picked up the wrist injury in Week 9 against Kansas City. He’ll need to log a practice tomorrow or Friday if he’s going to suit up in Week 10 against the Dolphins. The veteran has four sacks and four forced fumbles this season on a Buffalo defense that pressures the quarterback at the NFL’s third highest rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54fc-d673-a39e-f4fd1d3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent CB Asante Samuel Jr. is visiting with the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5504-d673-a39e-f595f2e90000</link>
      <description>Samuel was recently medically cleared after undergoing a spinal fusion procedure and will begin visiting potential suitors, starting with the Panthers. The former Chargers star missed most of the 2024 season with a serious neck injury. He has six interceptions and 148 tackles over 50 NFL games. It would be something of a surprise if Samuel sees game action in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5504-d673-a39e-f595f2e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said the team is “sorting through the medical opinions” on Jayden Daniels (elbow).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5518-d713-ad9e-7d5c60a60000</link>
      <description>Quinn said the team would announce a plan on how to proceed with the serious elbow injury Daniels sustained in Week 9 after looking strongly into various medical opinions on how to address the injury. Quinn said Monday there is no timetable for Daniels’ return to game action, though there remains some hope Daniels can avoid surgery and return later this year. He did not suffer a fracture in his elbow. For now, Marcus Mariota will start for Washington. He’ll be a superflex option in Week 10 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5518-d713-ad9e-7d5c60a60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
