<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:33:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Max Brosmer completed 9-of-16 passes for 51 yards in the Vikings’ 23-10, Week 17 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-580b-d968-a19b-58fba1460000</link>
      <description>No thank you. Brosmer could start the finale against the Packers if JJ McCarthy isn’t able to play. The FAAB bids on the Green Bay defense should be borderline incalculable if that happens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-580b-d968-a19b-58fba1460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 18-of-29 passes for 197 yards with a touchdown and two interceptions in the Lions’ 23-10, Week 17 loss to the Vikings while rushing for two yards and losing three fumbles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5813-d35e-a1bf-5dd3a2f30000</link>
      <description>Horrendous, down-bad play from Goff, and he was the best quarterback on the field. Max Brosmer was able to avoid the mistakes because the Vikings refused to allow them to happen, and Goff’s five turnovers were too much for Detroit to overcome. With the loss, Detroit is now eliminated from playoff contention. Goff will have a chance to compile some stats in a meaningless game against the Bears in Week 18. Fantasy managers who rostered Goff for this one are going to have to play catch up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5813-d35e-a1bf-5dd3a2f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 8-of-13 targets for 68 yards in the Lions’ Week 17 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d968-a19b-58f5d9d70000</link>
      <description>St. Brown left the contest late with an apparent injury, to add to the offensive insult for Detroit. The 26-year-old was able to make the most of an atrocious afternoon from Jared Goff/impressive showing again from Brian Flores and the Vikings’ defense. The Lions are eliminated from playoff contention, so don’t be surprised if Detroit is extra cautious with St. Brown in Week 18 against Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d968-a19b-58f5d9d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 17 times for 41 yards in the Lions’ Week 17 loss to the Vikings while adding two receptions for 23 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d56e-afff-fefdea130000</link>
      <description>The Lions tried to run the football with the Detroit offensive line unable to effectively protect Jared Goff, but didn’t find much room. Gibbs was also unable to get going as a receiver in what was an ugly result for the 23-year-old for many a fantasy manager in their championship game. Gibbs and the Lions will have one last meaningless game against the Bears in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d56e-afff-fefdea130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed 10 times for 25 yards in the Lions’ Week 17 loss to the Vikings while adding two receptions for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-dc7a-af9b-dfbff6740000</link>
      <description>Montgomery was questionable due to illness for Thursday’s game, but it seemed the Lions’ offensive line/Vikings’ front seven had more to do with the ineffectiveness. It’s an increase in production to his awful 14-yard effort against the Steelers, but that’s obviously faint praise. Montgomery is a RB3 at best for Week 18 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-dc7a-af9b-dfbff6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 2-of-3 targets for 37 yards in the Lions’ Week 17 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d968-a19b-58f5e1ba0000</link>
      <description>Williams finished third in targets and yardage behind both Amon-Ra St. Brown (8/68) and Isaac TeSlaa (3/49/1) in an abhorrent offensive showing for Detroit on Christmas Day. Give much of the credit to Minnesota, but also “credit” a horrific Jared Goff performance that reminded of his last few weeks as a Ram. Williams remains in the WR2 range for Week 18 in a meaningless game against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5815-d968-a19b-58f5e1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught 3-of-4 targets for 48 yards in the Lions’ Week 17 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5816-d35e-a1bf-5dd619850000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa made another impressive leaping effort for a touchdown in the first half in the red zone for the only touchdown of the game for Detroit. The rookie’s athleticism is obvious. His fit in the offense is a little more questionable. TeSlaa could get a chance to show out in a game without playoff ramifications against the Bears in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5816-d35e-a1bf-5dd619850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones rushed 18 times for 53 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 17 win over the Lions while adding three catches for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5817-d968-a19b-58f703470000</link>
      <description>Jones plunged in from a yard out to give the Vikings a 7-0 lead near the end of the first quarter. He was clearly the top option in the Minnesota offense, with Ty Chandler chiming in for 24 yards on his seven carries and Jordan Mason unavailable due to injury. Jones should be considered an RB2 for the finale against the Packers in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5817-d968-a19b-58f703470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin jefferson caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards in the Vikings’ Week 17 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5817-dc7a-af9b-dfbf0bba0000</link>
      <description>It could have been worse? Max Brosmer threw for all of 51 yards in a game that set offense back to before there even was a streaming service to watch a football game on, so getting even 30 yards becomes a little more impresssive. Imagine being issued caveats about a Justin Jefferson game coming into 2025. He’ll get one more chance to add to the disappointing numbers in Week 18 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5817-dc7a-af9b-dfbf0bba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison didn’t catch his only target but picked up a 65-yard rushing touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 17 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-581b-d56e-afff-fefbc2ae0000</link>
      <description>Addison was a complete non-factor, but then rushed around the Lions’ defense for a 65-yard score to save the fantasy day. The 23-year-old wideout will be a WR4 for the season finale against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-581b-d56e-afff-fefbc2ae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
