<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 16-of-31 passes for 270 yards, two touchdowns and an interception in the Patriots’ 28-23, Week 10 win over the Bucs, adding seven rushes for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a95-d713-ad9e-6ed533ec0000</link>
      <description>It was in some ways a disappointing statline, as Maye racked up 180 yards and both of his scores before halftime. He also tossed an end zone interception. He rolled to the side of the field where there were no wide receivers and paid the price. It was still ultimately another mighty impressive day for the young quarterback, who hit a streaking Kyle Williams for a 72-yard touchdown and found Stefon Diggs for an end zone jump ball on 4th-and-goal with no time remaining in the first half. Maye also lost a lot of potential yardage to long TreVeyon Henderson rushing touchdowns. Making big plays every week while performing with poise and toughness, Maye has confirmed he won’t be leaving the top five at quarterback. That includes for Thursday’s show-week date with the rebuilding Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a95-d713-ad9e-6ed533ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 20 times for 75 yards in the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a92-d673-a39e-ee93b25e0000</link>
      <description>Henry struggled for most of the day against a stout Vikings defense. The Big Dog saw six of his carries go for one or fewer yards, but came on strong later in the game on a touchdown drive that helped the Ravens put the game out of reach. This is the second straight week that Henry has failed to find the end zone. However, fantasy managers should find solace in knowing he faces the Browns in Week 11, where he profiles as a strong RB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a92-d673-a39e-ee93b25e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davis Mills completed 27-of-45 passes for 292 yards, two touchdowns, and an interception in the Texans’ 36-29, Week 10 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a94-d45b-affe-7f966f190000</link>
      <description>He added three carries for 30 yards and another touchdown — a scramble on third-and-goal with less than a minute left that gave the Texans their first lead of the game. The Texans were dead to rights in this game, down 29-10 with a minute left in the third quarter, then reeled off 20 straight points to take the lead and won the game on a walkoff pick-six by Sheldon Rankins. We’d like to tell you that this was a marked change of play — and Mills did make some nice throws — but largely the Jaguars got kicked around up front by the Texans and Mills was able to take sideline curls and middle-of-the-field throws with aplomb. We imagine he’ll remain on the low end of the QB2 superflex discussion in Week 11 on a short week against the Bills — assuming C.J. Stroud doesn’t clear concussion protocol by then — but this was much more ceiling than we imagined Mills to have today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a94-d45b-affe-7f966f190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Neal rushed four times for 22 yards in Week 10 against the Panthers, adding three catches for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a90-d45b-affe-7f963ae20000</link>
      <description>Alvin Kamara continued to dominate touches in the Saints’ backfield in Week 10 against the Panthers. Kamara had 22 carries to Neal’s four while each back had three catches. Neal looked good rushing for 22 yards on the four carries he had. The 22-year-old rookie running back remains a solid bench stash even through the Saints’ Week 11 bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a90-d45b-affe-7f963ae20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 4-of-6 targets for 75 yards in the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a98-d673-a39e-ee99ab2f0000</link>
      <description>It wasn’t a high-volume day for Flowers, but the Ravens’ WR1 still made the most of his limited opportunities. Flowers’ Longest play came on a 27-yard reception that helped set up a Tyler Loop field goal before halftime, which proved crucial in a game where the Ravens struggled to move the ball at times. Flowers will be back on the high-end WR2 radar in next week’s game against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a98-d673-a39e-ee99ab2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield completed 28-of-43 passes for 273 yards and three touchdowns in the Bucs’ 28-23, Week 10 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9a-d1e7-a1fa-7afa87080000</link>
      <description>Rather amazingly, the three-touchdown effort was Mayfield’s first since Week 1, though score No. 3 came in what amounted to garbage time. He found Tez Johnson twice and Emeka Egbuka once, with the first-round wideout capping the Bucs’ opening drive with a 21-yard strike from Mayfield. He leaked out and got lost on the right side of the red zone. Mayfield took only two sacks but absorbed quite a beating as the Bucs lost LG Ben Bredesen. Not as consistent as last season as the Bucs deal with a makeshift skill corps, Mayfield is still making big plays. He’s just not stacking them together the way he did in 2024. The Bills are an unideal Week 11 road matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9a-d1e7-a1fa-7afa87080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 7-of-8 targets for 75 yards in the Giants’ Week 10 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9b-d673-a39e-ee9bb93f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson, who missed practice time this week with a shoulder issue, had another solid outing as Jaxson Dart’s middle-of-the-field target. He now has at least three catches in three straight games. On Sunday against Chicago, Johnson ran a route on 36 of the Giants’ 45 drop backs and was second among New York pass catchers in targets (trailing Wan’Dale Robinson). TE Daniel Bellinger, meanwhile, ran 25 routes and had two targets. Johnson will be a viable streaming play in Week 11 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9b-d673-a39e-ee9bb93f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 3-of-5 targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9e-d45b-affe-7f9e273a0000</link>
      <description>Andrews has been little more than a touchdown-dependent play for fantasy managers this season and he didn’t do anything to beat those allegations in Sunday’s win over the Vikings. The veteran tight end found the end zone in the fourth quarter on a two-yard strike from Lamar Jackson, but had an otherwise unforgettable outing. Andrews has a 17-94-2 line over his last four games and shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a TE2 in next week’s game against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a9e-d45b-affe-7f9e273a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 13 times for 53 yards in the Bills’ Week 10 loss to the Dolphins, adding five catches for 24 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a8e-d713-ad9e-6edea84e0000</link>
      <description>In a sign of things to come, Cook got off on the wrong foot in this game with a lost fumble in the second quarter. The Bills would go on to turn the ball over three times in total en route to a blowout loss. Cook marginally saved the day for his fantasy backers with five receptions. With game script working against him, Cook never stood a chance at posting a big fantasy outing. He should get back on track in Week 11 against the Bucs. Cook will take a spot in the back half of the RB1 ranks next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a8e-d713-ad9e-6edea84e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
