<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:10:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived QB Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</link>
      <description>Buechele is a strong candidate to end up on the Bills’ practice squad. He’s the second quarterback Buffalo has dropped Tuesday, as they also waived Mike White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers waived WR Brenden Rice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-d332-a1fd-f7b650fa0000</link>
      <description>Rice appeared in three games for the Chargers last season, playing just three snaps on offense. Getting fanfare as Jerry Rice’s son coming out of USC in the seventh round last year, he earned a spot on the 53-man roster. However, he dealt with a shoulder injury and is now out after the Chargers added Keenan Allen and Tre Harris to the receiving group this offseason. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo mentions Rice is a candidate for the team’s practice squad if he clears waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-d332-a1fd-f7b650fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders acquired QB Kenny Pickett from the Browns in exchange for a 2026 fifth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b4-de13-afdc-e7ff6ca20000</link>
      <description>The Raiders add Pickett to the quarterback room, needing a backup quarterback after Aidan O’Connell fractured his wrist in the preseason. Browns GM Andrew Berry had expressed his intent to keep four quarterbacks on the roster, it was always going to be tough to justify the roster spots. Instead, opportunity came knocking from the Raiders and the Browns get a fifth-rounder for their troubles. Pickett had been dealing with a hamstring injury in the preseason, but the Raiders seem to believe he will be ready for Week 1. Meanwhile, this all but guarantees the Browns will be keeping Joe Flacco as the starting quarterback with rookies Dillon Gabriel and Shedeur Sanders as backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b4-de13-afdc-e7ff6ca20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings traded CB Mekhi Blackmon to the Colts for a 2026 sixth-round selection.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b6-dbe3-a9bb-f3f7d6890000</link>
      <description>Blackmon will give the Colts some needed depth in the secondary. The 26-year-old missed all of 2024 with a torn ACL, but showed promise in his rookie campaign the previous year after being selected with the 102nd pick out of USC. Assuming good health, Blackmon should contribute in packages and also on special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b6-dbe3-a9bb-f3f7d6890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3c3-dbe3-a9bb-f3d3e2400000</link>
      <description>Head coach Mike Macdonald announced Bobo is in concussion protocol after suffering a head injury in preseason Week 3. The Seahawks’ receiving depth behind Jaxon Smith-Njigba and Cooper Kupp is banged up heading into Week 1, with Tory Horton (ankle) aiming for a return to full practice next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3c3-dbe3-a9bb-f3d3e2400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the team will “have plays for Jalen [Milroe] in game plans.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3d9-db7b-a5dd-e3ddd5ed0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald said, “we’re going to have plays for Jalen in game plans and he’s going to rep those with the 1s.” It seems the Seahawks have a plan to use Milroe offensively despite Sam Darnold still being the starter. We can expect to see the 22-year-old rookie have a package of plays, likely in the run game, for the Seahawks to utilize his rushing skillset. For fantasy purposes, this won’t make Milroe fantasy-relevant, but might take high-value rushing touches away from Kenneth Walker in the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3d9-db7b-a5dd-e3ddd5ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Vikings and Panthers continue to discuss a trade involving Adam Thielen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e433-dbe3-a9bb-f473799b0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings need help in the wideout room, and Thielen would like to return to Minnesota, as Schefter notes. The two sides have just not been able to agree to compensation yet, and while numerous reports have mentioned the potential hurdles, this also feels like something that can be solved before the start of the season. If Thielen does remain with Carolina, he’ll likely open the campaign as the Panthers’ third wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e433-dbe3-a9bb-f473799b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released QB Tommy DeVito.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e64c-dbe3-a9bb-f65fef8c0000</link>
      <description>While DeVito was competing for the backup quarterback job in camp, he had little chance of making the Giants roster after New York brought in Russell Wilson, Jameis Winston and Jaxon Dart this offseason. The 27-year-old started six games with the Giants in 2023, throwing for eight touchdowns and three interceptions. DeVito is unlikely to be claimed by another team on waivers, meaning he’s destined for a practice squad. While carrying a fourth quarterback on the practice squad may be a little excessive, Wilson and Winston aren’t exactly spring chickens either and DeVito’s best path forward for his career may be to remain in the Giants organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e64c-dbe3-a9bb-f65fef8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports CB Rasul Douglas is signing a one-year deal with the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e658-d332-a1fd-f67e68700000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins had been in contact with Douglas over the offseason. The signing comes just in time for the season and it addresses a crucial need as it was already readily apparent the Dolphins needed help in the secondary. Douglas started 30 games mostly for the Bills over the last two seasons. The 30-year-old cornerback isn’t what he was earlier in his career, but with less than two weeks before the start of the regular season and the Dolphins desperate for secondary help he’s a good fit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e658-d332-a1fd-f67e68700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Browns have acquired G KT Leveston from the Rams in exchange for a 2028 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e66d-de13-afdc-e6ef1db90000</link>
      <description>Leveston was drafted in the seventh-round of the 2024 NFL Draft by the Rams out of Kansas State. While the Rams seem content to get whatever they can for Leveston, this could be a worthwhile gamble for a Browns team looking for offensive line depth. If not, well, the investment they’ve made in Leveston is minimal as the 2028 NFL Draft is still years away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e66d-de13-afdc-e6ef1db90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
