<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Chad Graff believes the Patriots will “be active” in trade discussions for Eagles WR A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c6-d89c-a1be-afdff8700000</link>
      <description>It’s one of the most sensible fits out there given that Mike Vrabel coached Brown in Tennessee. But Graff adds that it seems doubtful that the Patriots would give up their first-round pick for Brown, and if they aren’t willing to do that, it’s hard to believe Howie Roseman would sign off on a deal. It’s clear that Brown’s future will be one of the big offseason dominos to come post-Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0c6-d89c-a1be-afdff8700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner reports the Bengals will have extension talks with CBs DJ Turner and Dax Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d4-dbf6-abdd-eed540c70000</link>
      <description>Turner had a 78.1 PFF coverage grade last year in a career-high 974 snaps and is entering the final year of his rookie deal, while Hill is entering his fifth-year option offseason having moved into the slot more often last year. Turner would appear to be the more important player to extend, but the Bengals are definitely still in “keep as many good pieces from last year’s defense as possible” mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d4-dbf6-abdd-eed540c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports he doesn’t expect George Pickens to report to the Cowboys facility “unless and until there is a long-term deal.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d8-d629-a1bc-b0dda1520000</link>
      <description>“Don’t expect him to sign the tag yet,” Rapoport continues. “I would also wonder if there is another team that wants to give a premium draft pick and sign Pickens to a long-term deal themselves.” Pickens clearly put himself in the WR1 stratosphere last year, but we’d be surprised if a team was willing to give up a first-round pick for Pickens in addition to a major extension. A second-round pick might be a reasonable ask here while still being an upgrade for Dallas on the third-round pick they dealt away to acquire Pickens last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0d8-d629-a1bc-b0dda1520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said “it’s hard to put a timetable” for Zach Charbonnet (knee) to return to play next year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0e9-d89c-a1be-afffcbf90000</link>
      <description>“If you’re betting on anybody, you’re going to bet on Zach, so we’ll go from there. But he’s not going to do anything in the spring or anything like that,” Macdonald finished. A torn ACL suffered in the playoffs will almost certainly eat into Charbonnet’s regular season. The Seahawks could bring Kenneth Walker back, but if they don’t, Charbonnet may eventually be the lead back in 2026 — it’d just be a matter of when his recovery concluded and how comfortable the team felt giving him the role at that point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0e9-d89c-a1be-afffcbf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said he doesn’t expect WR Tory Horton (shin) to “do anything in the spring.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0ee-d042-afbc-fdfe1e480000</link>
      <description>He got “fixed up” in Macdonald’s lingo — we assume that means surgery — and is likely questionable for the start of training camp given how much time he missed with this shin injury in the 2025 season. If healthy, Horton could challenge for a real role next year depending on if the Seahawks bring Rashid Shaheed back or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0ee-d042-afbc-fdfe1e480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans GM Mike Borgonzi said the team’s goal is to “get something done” with OL Peter Skoronski.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0f0-d629-a1bc-b0fd46a30000</link>
      <description>Skoronski is entering his fifth-year option offseason off the best year of his career. The 24-year-old put up a 79.0 PFF grade — compared to 60.4 and 61.6 in his first two seasons — and turned into one of the main linchpins of the line. Given how much cap space they have and how few truly great players are in this free agent class, it wouldn’t be surprising to see the Titans try to get out in front of keeping Skoronski.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0f0-d629-a1bc-b0fd46a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys extended a second-round tender to restricted free agent G T.J. Bass.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0fe-dbf6-abdd-eeff4b2b0000</link>
      <description>He will make about $5.8 million in 2026. Bass started five games last year and finished with a career-best 67.6 PFF blocking grade. He’s valuable depth for the Cowboys and they’ll be able to match any offer he receives in free agency or allow him to walk for a second-round pick — very few restricted free agents are actually signed, so we expect he’ll be back in Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a0fe-dbf6-abdd-eeff4b2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune’s Brad Biggs believes DT Logan Hall will “have a robust market in free agency.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a107-d042-afbc-fdd775fd0000</link>
      <description>Hall managed a career-best 66.8 PFF defensive grade in 2025 — not saying much, but he was much improved from his rookie form — and managed 26 hurries. Biggs notes that he’s scheme-versatile and said something “approaching $10 million per season wouldn’t be a surprise” based on his conversations with several agents. We did not blurb Hall at all in the final year of his rookie deal, but it appears he may be a surprise contract in free agency ahead of his age-26 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a107-d042-afbc-fdd775fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune’s Brad Biggs believes the Bears would probably need “a second-round pick (or two picks equaling that value)” to make it “worthwhile” to trade Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a10d-d89c-a1be-afdf6f950000</link>
      <description>“I’m not sure a team would offer a Round 2 pick for Bagent. It’s worth noting the Bears have had meetings with agents representing some No. 2-type quarterbacks, so they’re putting contingency plans in place,” Biggs continues while specifically pointing out that the Jets are a team that could look to go the budget route at quarterback. Of all the things that happened during the NFL Combine, the hard-launching of the Tyson Bagent Trade Complex was definitely one of them. The desperation is real for those without a solidified quarterback position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a10d-d89c-a1be-afdf6f950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane believes a decision by the Eagles on keeping or trading A.J. Brown will be made “in the next 10 days” ahead of the start of the legal tampering period.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a117-d042-afbc-fdd7a1e60000</link>
      <description>McLane has talked to several sources about this at the combine and doesn’t make a real guess on if Brown will be traded — the article is full of Mike Vrabel quotes, if you want a sense of a lean — but also mentions the Ravens and Bills as teams that could use a Brown to get over the championship hump. He notes that if Howie Roseman doesn’t get the compensation he wants, he’ll simply keep Brown. Brown’s 2026 team will determine a lot about the next few weeks in the NFL, but it sounds like it will simply unfold based on how willing the market will be to give Roseman the kind of premium draft assets he’d desire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a117-d042-afbc-fdd7a1e60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
