<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said he thinks CB Sauce Gardner (groin) will “be okay” for Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e05-dc44-a9d9-3f67d21b0000</link>
      <description>Gardner was added to the injury report with a groin issue on Thursday and was limited in practice. A mid-week addition to the injury report is never a good sign, but it looks like the light workload in practice may have been a precaution. We will get more info on Gardner’s availability for Week 1 when the Jets drop their final injury report later today. Barring a setback, the Jets should have their top corner available for a must-win game versus Buffalo on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e05-dc44-a9d9-3f67d21b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said DT Ed Oliver (ankle) will not play in Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e91-da67-a99f-fef54d410000</link>
      <description>Per McDermott, Oliver had his foot stepped on in practice this week. ESPN’s Adam Schefter also chimed in, reporting that this is expected to be a multi-week injury for Oliver, who was spotted in a boot on Thursday. Oliver was a force in Week 1, totaling one sack, three TFLs, and a forced fumble. His absence will make life far easier for Justin Fields and the Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e91-da67-a99f-fef54d410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Darius Slayton said he thinks Darius Slayton (groin) will be okay for Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e99-d86f-abdd-7fbde3d00000</link>
      <description>Daboll didn’t commit to any injury status for the veteran wideout when talking to the media, though it sounds like a questionable tag could be in Slayton’s future. Slayton was a mid-week addition to the injury report after being left off it entirely on Wednesday. That’s never a good sign, but New York’s final injury report of the week will be more telling. Jalin Hyatt would likely be in line for more routes if Slayton can’t suit up this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e99-d86f-abdd-7fbde3d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) will not play in Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e9f-da67-a99f-feff84170000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation after Waller missed Week 1 and failed to practice during the opening session this week. It’s unclear when Waller will play in 2025, but it doesn’t look like that will happen anytime soon. Fantasy managers can safely cut ties with the veteran tight end, even in deep formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3e9f-da67-a99f-feff84170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RT Austin Jackson (toe) will not play in Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea1-da67-a99f-fef58ee70000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have now lost two starting offensive linemen in one week of action. Right guard James Daniels went on injured reserve earlier this week with a pec injury. Expect Mike McDaniel to dial up another quick-hitting passing attack to keep Tua Tagovailoa out of harm’s way in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea1-da67-a99f-fef58ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) should be available for Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea3-dc44-a9d9-3fe7c2c90000</link>
      <description>Waddle got banged up in Week 1 and briefly left the Dolphins’ blowout loss to the Colts to have his shoulder checked out. He eventually returned and was later a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice. Per usual, Waddle will labor through an injury on Sunday. The good news is that he will be out there. He will top out at a WR3 ranking given how dysfunctional the Dolphins looked in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea3-dc44-a9d9-3fe7c2c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said RB Jaylen Wright (leg) is not expected to play in Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea7-d86f-abdd-7fbfd7160000</link>
      <description>McDaniel did note that Wright isn’t guaranteed to miss Week 2, though we still expect that to be the outcome. It does, however, sound like Wright could be nearing a return. Backup runner Ollie Gordon only saw three touches in Week 1. The No. 2 role has no value in the Miami offense right now, no matter who it is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ea7-d86f-abdd-7fbfd7160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) did not practice Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eae-d294-a19b-fefe23e20000</link>
      <description>That’s three straight DNPs for Decker this week. Decker underwent offseason shoulder surgery and the Lions are being cautious with his practice reps. Head coach Dan Campbell was non-committal on Friday when talking about Decker’s Week 2 availability. Offensive coordinator John Morton, however, said on Thursday that the team is expecting Decker to play. The Lions are playing this one close to the vest, but it sounds like Decker is going to give it a go on Sunday, though he may be listed as questionable on the final run of the injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eae-d294-a19b-fefe23e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed K Jake Moody, formerly of the 49ers, to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eb2-dc44-a9d9-3ff607380000</link>
      <description>Moody was waived by the 49ers after missing two field goals in San Francisco’s Week 1 win over the Seahawks. He will now provide some much-needed competition for Cairo Santos, who missed one of his two field goal tries in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eb2-dc44-a9d9-3ff607380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Brooks Kubena reports Dallas Goedert (knee) did not practice Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ecc-d294-a19b-fefcaa2b0000</link>
      <description>Things could change when the Eagles drop their final injury report, but it certainly looks like Goedert will be out for Week 2 versus the Chiefs. That will elevate Grant Calcaterra to the starting role, though Kylen Granson could also be involved. Either way, this just means more work for A.J. Brown and Devonta Smith, both of whom posted quiet box scores in Week 1. This goes without saying, but Brown and Smith remain clear starts in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ecc-d294-a19b-fefcaa2b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
