<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette caught 2-of-3 targets for 31 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 5 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b673-deb6-a7fd-f7ff35310000</link>
      <description>Legette was a disaster in his first two games of the year, turning 15 targets and one carry into an embarrassing eight total yards. He then missed Week 3 and Week 4 with a hamstring issue. The time off may have helped clear his head as he put his best football on the field this week, albeit on a limited target total. Legette caught a diving touchdown in the back of the end zone to get the Panthers on the board in the second quarter. Though he isn’t on the fantasy radar heading into Week 6, Legette will look to build on this performance versus the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b673-deb6-a7fd-f7ff35310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheem Mostert rushed seven times for 22 yards in the Raiders’ Week 5 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b680-deb6-a7fd-f7df8ef10000</link>
      <description>Mostert is up to 12 touches over the past two weeks after previously not handling the ball, but five of his carries this afternoon came on the Raiders’ meaningless final series. Ashton Jeanty has actually been consolidating work during Mostert’s emergence, not shedding it. The 33-year-old veteran would be part of a committee were Jeanty to go down with injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b680-deb6-a7fd-f7df8ef10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 3-of-9 targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 5 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b682-deb6-a7fd-f7df7d260000</link>
      <description>Goedert also drew an 18-yard DPI in the game’s waning moments. Goedert’s two-yard touchdown in the second quarter was his fourth in three weeks. His nine targets were also a new season high ... as his 19 yards were a new season low. It’s just been that kind of year in the Eagles’ passing attack, which tried to open itself up on Sunday but still largely failed. A floor-based option on the TE1/2 borderline, Goedert has a short-week Thursday night date with the Giants on tap for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b682-deb6-a7fd-f7df7d260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals TE Tip Reiman (leg) was carted off in Week 5 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b67f-dca3-a9fb-bfffe7540000</link>
      <description>Reiman injured his leg in the third quarter against the Titans. He was sliding on a target from Jacoby Brissett and his leg got caught and bent on the play. Reiman was immediately put in an air cast and carted off the field as he gave the crowd a thumbs up. The 24-year-old isn’t fantasy relevant but is a key blocker for the Cardinals’ run scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b67f-dca3-a9fb-bfffe7540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 6-of-8 targets for 73 yards in the Panthers’ Week 5 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b682-d95b-addb-fec674360000</link>
      <description>T-Mac was Bryce Young’s favorite target once again, leading the team with a 27 percent target share. McMillan has been remarkably consistent this year, falling between 60 and 75 yards in three of his five games. He has an impressive floor of 48 yards but a rather underwhelming ceiling of 100. The Panthers’ struggles on offense have prevented him from hitting a true spike week, but they have also led Young to pepper his rookie wideout with targets. That role will hold into Week 6 against the Cowboys, keeping McMillan in the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b682-d95b-addb-fec674360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 8-of-10 targets for 99 yards in the Broncos’ Week 5 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b68a-d6e9-af9d-be9a07c80000</link>
      <description>Sutton’s catches and targets were both new season highs after he entered the break with just 2/11. He went to work on Quinyon Mitchell in the second half, helping the Broncos rally from a 17-3 deficit for a 21-17 victory. Having gone at least 5/60 in 4-of-5 games so far this season, Sutton has established a high floor and reasonable ceiling. He’s a strong WR2 ahead of a Week 6 matchup with the Jets’ struggling defense in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b68a-d6e9-af9d-be9a07c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared OLB K’Lavon Chaisson, DT Eric Gregory, G Caedan Wallace, WR Efton Chism, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 5 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b68d-deb6-a7fd-f7df7ea20000</link>
      <description>Chaisson is the only real surprise here as the Patriots enter Week 5 as one of the healthier teams in the league. They’ll need all 53 playing a near spotless game to knock off the Bills on the road and close the gap atop the AFC East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b68d-deb6-a7fd-f7df7ea20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 3-of-5 targets for 35 yards in the Broncos’ Week 5 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b695-deb6-a7fd-f7df0d040000</link>
      <description>Franklin posted his second lowest yardage total of the season as Courtland Sutton took over after the half and Evan Engram finally woke up for a touchdown. Franklin is playing a valuable real life role as the Broncos’ No. 2 “conventional” wideout, but it isn’t providing steady-enough WR4 returns in fantasy. That being said, Week 6 against the Jets will be a plus matchup, especially with Sauce Gardner likely to find himself preoccupied with Sutton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b695-deb6-a7fd-f7df0d040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
