<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Ravens LB Roquan Smith (hamstring) will miss a few weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96de-d6e9-af9d-9edee8b00000</link>
      <description>Will the last Ravens front seven defender available please turn out the lights at the practice facility? Baltimore will be leaning heavily on its depth against the Texans, making the main starters (Woody Marks, Nico Collins) on one of the league’s worst offenses at least defensible plays. Jake Hummel played linebacker in relief of Smith last week and figures to be one of a few options that could step in against Houston in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96de-d6e9-af9d-9edee8b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Javontae Jean-Baptiste will be out “a while” with a pectoral injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d8-d6e9-af9d-9ed839ac0000</link>
      <description>Jean-Baptiste’s injury was reported after the team’s Week 4 loss to the Falcons. The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala said on Sunday that the team’s fear is that Jean-Baptiste tore his pec, which would likely result in a season-ending injury. We’ll see if Quinn gives us a more definite timeline for Jean-Baptiste’s absence in the coming days, but at the very least, he sounds like a candidate for the IR at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d8-d6e9-af9d-9ed839ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said WR Terry McLaurin (quad) is “trending in the right [direction].”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9707-d6e9-af9d-9f9742820000</link>
      <description>It’s a rather nondescript update for the wideout’s status. We’ll probably have to wait until Wednesday’s injury report to get a real sense of how likely McLaurin is to play, but empty positive words are better than a gutting “not this week.” Deebo Samuel hogged targets in McLaurin’s absence last week and would be a top-tier WR2 play if McLaurin missed again in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9707-d6e9-af9d-9f9742820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed K Riley Patterson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9713-d95b-addb-ff5705380000</link>
      <description>After elevating Patterson from the practice squad the previous three weeks, the Dolphins had no choice but to sign him if they hoped to elevate him again for Week 4 against the Jets. The veteran kicker is 2-for-2 on field goal attempts this season and has made all six of his extra point attempts. He seems like a safe bet to remain the Dolphins’ kicker as long as Jason Sanders (hip) remains sidelined. It’s worth noting that Sanders will be eligible to come off injured reserve after this week, so Patterson’s stay on the 53-man roster could be short-lived.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9713-d95b-addb-ff5705380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys beat writer Calvin Watkins reports Tyler Booker (ankle) was seen without a protective boot on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-975c-deb6-a7fd-d7dfcb590000</link>
      <description>Booker was projected to miss 4-6 weeks with the ankle injury he suffered in Week 3. While his shedding of the boot is notable, the rookie is still likely to face a multi-week absence barring a sudden turn of events. It’s worth noting, however, that the team did not place him on injured reserve, leaving the possibility of an early return on the table if he continues to progress well in his recovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-975c-deb6-a7fd-d7dfcb590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewars, CB Ethan Bonner, CB Storm Duck, WR Tahj Washington, and DT Zeek Biggers inactive for Week 4 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9771-d6e9-af9d-9ff145870000</link>
      <description>Miami continues to trudge on with numerous key injuries in their secondary, and Week 4 is no different. Three starters will not be with the team for their matchup against the Jets, in addition to regular backup Ethan Bonner. Garrett Wilson could be in for a big fantasy outing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9771-d6e9-af9d-9ff145870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer said S Malik Hooker could miss a few weeks with a toe injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9760-dca3-a9fb-bff96d270000</link>
      <description>Hooker picked up the injury in Sunday night’s game against the Packers. He was limited to a season-low 30 defensive snaps as a result of the injury, and could now miss a few weeks to recover. The Cowboys’ defense currently ranks among the worst in the league through four weeks, allowing the second-most points per game (33.0) and the passing yards per game and yards per attempt (8.5) through the air. His absence won’t do anything to help a team that already needs help in the secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9760-dca3-a9fb-bff96d270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared WR Tyler Johnson, TE Jelani Woods, DT Leonard Taylor, OT Esa Pole, DE Jermaine Johnson, RB Kene Nwangwu, and DB Jarvis Brownlee inactive for Week 4 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9774-dca3-a9fb-bffdbfd80000</link>
      <description>Johnson appears to be the only surprise after ranking second on the team in snaps through the first three weeks. The Jets take on the 0-3 Dolphins in a battle to avoid the dreaded 0-4 start, but get quarterback Justin Fields back following a one-game absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9774-dca3-a9fb-bffdbfd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) was listed as a DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9778-d95b-addb-ff7ea8910000</link>
      <description>Here we go again. Just over 24 hours after making his return from a toe injury that sidelined him for two weeks, Purdy is now dealing with a flare up of the same injury that could cost him another game this week. To amplify matters, the 49ers play on Thursday against the Rams, making for a short turnaround time for the Niners’ QB1 to get right and suit up. It’s early, but fantasy managers hoping to have Purdy this week should prepare for another Mac Jones start if his absence extends further into the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9778-d95b-addb-ff7ea8910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
