<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 22:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 13 times for 82 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 7 loss to the Browns, adding three receptions for 16 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe52-d651-a9df-ff57140b0000</link>
      <description>Achane had the Dolphins’ only good play of the day on their second series, finding the edge and gaining 46 yards. For whatever reason, he wasn’t an offensive focus in wet-and-windy conditions, as coach Mike McDaniel suffered through three Tua Tagovailoa interceptions for the second consecutive week. Running it is easier said than done behind this woeful line, but it felt like an inexcusable game plan to the naked eye, especially since the Browns found success pounding Quinshon Judkins between the tackles. Although his big-play upside is undercut by his bottom-barrel offensive environment, Achane will remain in the low-end RB1 mix for Week 8 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe52-d651-a9df-ff57140b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dalton completed 4-of-6 attempts for 60 yards in the Panthers’ Week 7 win against the Jets, adding two rushes for -2 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe52-d99b-a1dd-fe5eb2330000</link>
      <description>Dalton came in for Bryce Young after Young sustained an apparent ankle injury in the second half and managed the offense well in a low-scoring affair against an opponent that didn’t pose much of a threat. One of the better backups QBs in the league, Dalton should be picked up in superflex leagues this week in case Young misses time with his injury. Dalton would take on a beatable Bills secondary if he gets the Week 8 start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe52-d99b-a1dd-fe5eb2330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 3-of-5 targets for 33 yards in the Panthers’ Week 7 win against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe56-df81-ab9b-fed717080000</link>
      <description>McMillan had one of the quietest game of his otherwise impressive rookie campaign as Sauce Gardner shadowed him for much of the game. The Panthers were even more run heavy than usual in this one, logging 32 rushes and 32 pass attempts. McMillan saw an end zone target in the first half but could not convert. He’ll have a plus matchup in Week 8 against a poor Buffalo secondary. It won’t really matter for McMillan whether Bryce Young (ankle) or Andy Dalton is under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe56-df81-ab9b-fed717080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 1-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 7 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe57-d99b-a1dd-fe5f76590000</link>
      <description>Rock bottom. One of Waddle’s missed connections was a late sail job by new No. 2 Quinn Ewers. Waddle skied then landed awkwardly and was in a world of pain. He eventually made it to the sideline unassisted and avoided the blue tent, suggesting it was a mere wind knocking. Before Ewers’ insertion, Waddle suffered through three awful Tua Tagovailoa picks. This was a bad matchup in worse weather, but this is an offense coming apart at the seams. Waddle is probably best left outside the top 18 for Week 8 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe57-d99b-a1dd-fe5f76590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin Jr. caught 4-of-5 targets for 36 yards in the Browns’ Week 7 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe5b-df81-ab9b-fedf2c3f0000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers will be disappointed by the paltry catch total in David Njoku’s absence, but the Browns attempted only 18 passes in wet, windy conditions as they rode the running game and the Dolphins self destructed on the other side of the ball. 4/36 is probably also about Fannin’s floor. With or without Njoku, he should be needed for more in Week 8 as the Browns head on the road to face the upstart Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe5b-df81-ab9b-fedf2c3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allen Lazard caught 2-of-3 targets for 16 yards in the Jets’ Week 7 loss against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe62-df81-ab9b-fee74e8b0000</link>
      <description>It was a new season high in targets for the little-used Lazard, who has missed game action in 2025 due to personal issues. Lazard operated as the team’s No. 2 wideout behind Josh Reynolds in this one. He ran a route on 26 of the Jets’ 39 drop backs against the Panthers and could have some value in deep fantasy formats if Tyrod Taylor takes over at QB after Justin Fields was benched in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe62-df81-ab9b-fee74e8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 2-of-4 targets for 17 yards in the Browns’ Week 7 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe6d-da18-a39b-fe7f46e40000</link>
      <description>Jeudy’s third sub-20 yard outing of the year came as the Browns rode the run game and Tua Tagovailoa turnovers to smash the Dolphins 31-6 in wet and windy conditions. Dillon Gabriel attempted only 18 passes, but this was still a somewhat disastrous outcome with David Njoku on the shelf. The Browns are going to need more passing volume in Week 8 against Drake Maye’s Patriots, but Jeudy is barely even pushing for WR4 status at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe6d-da18-a39b-fe7f46e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Johnson caught all three of his targets for 60 yards in the Jets’ Week 7 loss against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe69-d99b-a1dd-fe6d01e60000</link>
      <description>With Garrett Wilson (knee) sidelined, Johnson led the team with 60 receiving yards. He had the biggest play of the day — a 35-yard catch from Tyrod Taylor in the second half. Arian Smith, Allen Lazard, and Josh Reynolds operated as the three top wideouts for the Wilson-less Jets. It was Johnson who made the big play though (while running just 12 routes). Johnson could be an interest waiver add this week ahead of a matchup with a beatable Bengals coverage unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe69-d99b-a1dd-fe6d01e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Davis had two rushes for ten yards in the Jets’ Week 7 loss against the Panthers, adding two catches for 22 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe71-da18-a39b-fe7316040000</link>
      <description>Davis continued playing well behind Breece Hall, who had 13 touches in the loss. With Braelon Allen sidelined, Davis would likely operate as the Jets’ lead back should Hall miss time or get traded before the league’s trade deadline. He’s someone to stash in deeper fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe71-da18-a39b-fe7316040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
