<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said there was “a focused effort” to get Xavier Legette more targets on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9394-d45b-affe-d796a2b40000</link>
      <description>Well, hard to argue with the results after a 4/83/1 line on eight targets against the Falcons helped lead to a 30-points explosion, but a bit of a weird flex since Legette has been useless for most of the fantasy season. This does give Legette some FLEX appeal in Week 12 against the 49ers, but it also comes with the warning that he exited Sunday’s game with a hip injury that bears monitoring this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9394-d45b-affe-d796a2b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said he’s “not going to get into any of that right now” when asked if there was a level of performance that would lead J.J. McCarthy to get benched.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9398-d713-ad9e-ffdc0f1a0000</link>
      <description>Maybe McCarthy will turn it around next start and maybe these reps are necessary, but it sure feels awkward to watch Sam Darnold perform well again in Seattle while McCarthy putters around needing major fourth-quarter comebacks to crack the 100-yard mark. The fact that media members are already asking about a benching for McCarthy says a lot more than the box score has, and the box scores were already suggesting some dire things about McCarthy’s performance. It’s hard to suggest that an O’Connell-coached quarterback is a true bottom-rung superflex QB2, especially in a week where we’re talking about Shedeur Sanders starting, but the circumstances are whispering it strongly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9398-d713-ad9e-ffdc0f1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said “initial news is really positive” on LG Grey Zabel’s knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-939f-d673-a39e-b79f635e0000</link>
      <description>Zabel left Week 11’s loss to the Rams after 74 snaps (they played 84, if that seems high for a mid-game exit) and did not return. The rookie left guard has struggled as a run blocker early in his career, but has put up a 60.2 PFF pass block grade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-939f-d673-a39e-b79f635e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said “it’s fair to say [the offense will] look different” with Kirk Cousins as the starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93a2-d713-ad9e-fff60f5f0000</link>
      <description>Cousins has made three disastrous appearances this year, combining for 250 passing yards, no touchdowns, and no picks in 52 attempts. With Drake London reportedly to be sidelined in Week 12 against the Saints, look for the Falcons to lean heavily into the running game. Cousins is one of several quarterbacks competing for the bottom rung of the superflex ranks in Week 12 with four teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93a2-d713-ad9e-fff60f5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Josh Jacobs is dealing with a knee contusion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9392-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa1eed0000</link>
      <description>When asked if there was a chance Jacobs could play in Week 12 against the Vikings, LaFleur said, “Potentially. We’ll see where he’s at.” Jacobs is not a candidate for injured reserve, meaning any potential absence should fall inside the four-game minimum that’s required of any player who is placed on IR. Jacobs is reportedly dealing with a decent amount of swelling due to the hard blow dealt to his knee by the turf at MetLife Stadium. If Jacobs is unable to go in Week 12, Emanuel Wilson will be in line to handle the majority of the backfield touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9392-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa1eed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Broncos are “optimistic” that Patrick Surtain (pectoral) can return after their Week 12 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b2-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa10830000</link>
      <description>Ditto Alex Singleton (illness), who had surgery aimed to remove testicular cancer that feels a little bigger than the (illness) tag implies. These would be two major defensive pieces back for the stretch run. It’s possible each of them return for Week 13 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b2-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa10830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said K Eddy Pineiro (hamstring) has a strain and is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b5-d45b-affe-d7b7b81a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers will have a kicker workout on Tuesday or Wednesday. Given the 49ers’ offensive firepower and how often Shanahan is willing to settle for field goals, whoever the 49ers sign could be worthy of fantasy consideration in Week 12 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b5-d45b-affe-d7b7b81a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said LB Tatum Bethune (ankle) has a high-ankle sprain and will miss “a few” weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b7-d673-a39e-b7b78ba00000</link>
      <description>Curtis Robinson was the main replacement for Bethune, who left Week 11’s game against the Cardinals after 24 snaps. Bethune, who took the middle linebacker mantle for the injured Fred Warner, played some pretty decent run defense as a fill-in. He’s expected to avoid injured reserve at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b7-d673-a39e-b7b78ba00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Ja’Marr Chase has been suspended for one game for spitting on Steelers DB Jalen Ramsey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93bd-d713-ad9e-fffd14a00000</link>
      <description>Tape don’t lie. Shortly after he denied spitting on Ramsey in Week 11’s loss to the Steelers, videos emerged that clearly showed Chase spitting on Ramsey during a scuffle between the two in the fourth quarter. Ramsey was ejected for punching Chase following the incident, but the league appears to have sided with him in this matter. Chase can and will appeal the league’s decision to suspend him if he chooses to do so, but the evidence is pretty convincing. Chase will miss Week 12’s game against the Patriots if the suspension is upheld.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93bd-d713-ad9e-fffd14a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams S Quentin Lake (elbow) will be “sidelined for an undetermined amount of time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93c0-d673-a39e-b7d1f7820000</link>
      <description>The Rams are having testing done on Lake’s elbow and have said it’s possible that he’ll be placed on injured reserve. Sean McVay said he was “bummed out for him,” which seems to forecast a significant injury. Lake played 32 snaps in Week 11’s win over the Seahawks, with Jaylen McCollough and Josh Wallace getting extra work after he left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93c0-d673-a39e-b7d1f7820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
