<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Kenny Moore (Achilles) won’t play in Indianapolis’ Week 6 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf13-db72-a199-ff5bb0e00000</link>
      <description>That makes it three weeks in a row for Moore, who has not practiced since the Thursday ahead of Week 5. He’s a potential IR candidate over the weekend. With Mike Hilton on practice squad IR, the Colts cornerback corps shouldn’t be able to limit what little there is to limit of the Raiders passing attack. Backup RB Tyler Goodson (groin) joined Moore on the rule-out list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf13-db72-a199-ff5bb0e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) is doubtful for Cincinnati’s Week 6 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf1c-d94a-a79d-cf1df75d0000</link>
      <description>Stewart had gotten in limited practices on Wednesday and Thursday, so it’s possible he dealt with a setback. It’s also possible he just wasn’t ready. The rookie hasn’t played since Week 2 and is now at “a standard IR stint” level of missed games assuming the doubtful listing holds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf1c-d94a-a79d-cf1df75d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said Shedeur Sanders will be the team’s No. 2 quarterback for Week 6’s game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf20-d94a-a79d-cf2d1dea0000</link>
      <description>We’re one bad Dillon Gabriel hit away from watching Sanders — based on his preseason play — take a lot of sacks against Pittsburgh. Sanders has held off fierce competition from *checking notes* Bailey Zappe to take over as the No. 2 after Joe Flacco was dispatched to Cincinnati in a mercy mission. If you are the type of fantasy football dynasty manager who believes in Sanders’ college tape, he’ll make a worthwhile stash in deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf20-d94a-a79d-cf2d1dea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (quad/hip) “will be sidelined at least five weeks”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf1f-db72-a199-ff5f94850000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, Strange’s injury “includes a ligament tear suffered in Monday night’s game against the Chiefs,” however, the third-year tight end is not believed to need surgery. Strange was already slated to miss an automatic four games after the Jaguars placed him on injured reserve earlier this week, but we can now expect his absence to extend beyond the four-game minimum. Strange leads the Jaguars in receptions (20) this season and appeared to be on the verge of a breakout season prior to going down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf1f-db72-a199-ff5f94850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said WR Jalen McMillan (neck) is still in a neck brace.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf2c-db72-a199-ff6f82b10000</link>
      <description>Bowles said he doesn’t know when the receiver will return to practice and could only provide an “I hope so” when asked if McMillan would play this season. He was projected to be out past the Week 9 bye, so this isn’t exactly a negative update, but it’s clear that we’re not a lot closer to McMillan making a debut this season and it wouldn’t be surprising if he didn’t play at all in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf2c-db72-a199-ff6f82b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans K Joey Slye (calf) will not play in Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf2e-db72-a199-ff6f3e0e0000</link>
      <description>Calf injured his calf in the Titans’ Week 5 win over the Cardinals and was a DNP all week. The veteran kicker will be sidelined for Sunday’s game against the Raiders as a result, giving way for Matthew Wright to see his first action of 2025. Wright split time between three teams in 2024, including the Titans, going 15-for-16 on his field goal attempts while making all tries inside of 50 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf2e-db72-a199-ff6f3e0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) is questionable for Tennessee’s Week 6 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf30-dd4c-afb9-eff162370000</link>
      <description>After missing four games in a row, Latham has a chance to be back to man the right side for the Titans. Tennessee’s replacement tackles were John Ojukwu (42.8 PFF offensive grade) and Oli Udoh (52.3 PFF offensive grade), so perhaps a healthy Latham can give Cam Ward some more room to operate in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf30-dd4c-afb9-eff162370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Allen Lazard (personal) won’t play in New York’s Week 6 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf34-db72-a199-ff7f655a0000</link>
      <description>No actual reason was given by Aaron Glenn at a presser on Friday. Lazard has been a bit player the last three weeks, managing 33.2 percent of the snaps and six targets against the Buccaneers, Dolphins, and Cowboys. He’ll clear a little space for the lower rung of the Jets depth chart in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf34-db72-a199-ff7f655a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said WR Christian Watson (knee/PUP) will not play this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3b-dd4c-afb9-effbdd8c0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur noted that Watson looked “pretty damn good” but decided to hold the talented receiver back another week. It’ll be Romeo Doubs and Dontayvion Wicks as the main receivers against the Bengals in Week 6. Cincinnati hasn’t quite been as bad as the Cowboys this year, but it’s still a plus matchup for both wideouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3b-dd4c-afb9-effbdd8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) got in a limited practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3a-db72-a199-ff7b9bdd0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the Falcons were just taking it easy on the veteran wideout after he left Week 4’s game with the hamstring injury. We’re probably trending towards Mooney either being a questionable for Monday Night or, perhaps, off the injury report entirely with another upward trend on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3a-db72-a199-ff7b9bdd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
