<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>KaVontae Turpin caught his only target for an 86-yard touchdown in the Cowboy’s Week 17 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5760-d968-a19b-5ff1b3730000</link>
      <description>It took all of one target for Turpin to make his mark felt in the win as he broke free of primary coverage and split the safeties deep down the middle for an 86-yard, catch-and-run score. Turpin continues to play behind Jalen Tolbert but his flashy touchdown demonstrates his big play ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5760-d968-a19b-5ff1b3730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 4-of-5 targets for 78 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 17 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5762-d968-a19b-5ff370210000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Dak Prescott completed only 19-of-37 passes while taking six sacks against a Commanders defense that rose to the occasion, with Pickens checking in third on the team in targets behind alpha CeeDee Lamb and Jalen Tolbert. It was a disappointing end to the enigmatic receiver’s fantasy season after erupting for 130 yards and a score against the Chargers a week ago. Pickens played the 2025 season on the final year of his contract and could be the source of significant contractual drama this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5762-d968-a19b-5ff370210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 5-of-10 targets for 46 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 17 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5765-d968-a19b-5ff558060000</link>
      <description>Lamb and quarterback Dak Prescott were disconnected throughout, with the bulk of his receptions going for short yardage. His game-high was only a 24-yard catch, while positive game script against the Commanders allowed Dallas to ride the ground game in the second half. It was a disappointing end to an up-and-down, injury-impacted season for the veteran alpha receiver, who could fall to the tail end of the first round in coming fantasy drafts this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5765-d968-a19b-5ff558060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Johnson completed 15-of-23 passes for 198 yards in the Commanders’ 30-23, Week 17 los to the Cowboys, adding 10 yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5768-d56e-afff-f7e8561d0000</link>
      <description>Johnson’s final stat line is a bit misleading as over 20% of his production came on a short catch-and-run completion to Deebo Samuel, who gained 41 yards on the gadget play. The Commanders ran only 41 offensive plays, leading to the low pass volume for the veteran journeyman. Washington limps to the offseason in one of the more injury-ravaged seasons in recent memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5768-d56e-afff-f7e8561d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 11 times for 105 yards and two touchdowns in the Commanders’ Week 17 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576b-dc7a-af9b-dfffe7d60000</link>
      <description>The end result vastly underplays his contributions on an afternoon the Commanders ran only 41 offensive plays in a game completely dominated by the Cowboys. The rookie back scored early from 10 yards out before springing free off tackle for his 72-yard trip to the paint. Croskey-Merritt finishes up an inconsistent rookie season with a road meeting with the Eagles in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576b-dc7a-af9b-dfffe7d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 2-of-4 targets for 68 yards in the Commanders’ Week 17 loss to the Cowboys, adding 25 yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5bff0000</link>
      <description>Samuel was the primary cog of the offense before the break, turning a short reception into a booming 41-yard, catch-and-run gain to bring the ball to the six on the team’s opening possession. He would add another short catch and 25 yards on two carries in the first half before not seeing a touch after the break. Seemingly a perfect fit for offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury’s horizontally spread offense, Samuel heads into a Week 18 matchup against the Eagles with a relatively disappointing fantasy showing relative to his draft capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5bff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 5-of-7 targets for 63 yards in the Commanders’ Week 17 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5772-d35e-a1bf-57f2f7130000</link>
      <description>It was a quiet afternoon for the entirety of the Washington offense, with the final box scores entirely underselling how poor the team performed against their divisional rivals. The team ran only 41 offensive plays and would have been handily blown out if not for a 72-yard touchdown by rookie running back Jacory Croskey-Merritt and a 41-yard, catch-and-run gain by Deebo Samuel. McLaurin heads into a Week 18 meeting with the Eagles at the tail end of a disappointing fantasy season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5772-d35e-a1bf-57f2f7130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams (hamstring) was listed as a non-participant for Thursday’s practice ahead of the Rams’ Week 17 matchup against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576b-d968-a19b-5ffb9a250000</link>
      <description>The Rams didn’t practice on Christmas Day, so this was an estimate from the club. Adams seems unlikely to be able to play in the Monday Night Football tilt against Atlanta, and there’s a chance we won’t see the 33-year-old until the postseason. That should lead to more targets for Konata Mumphield for these final two contests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-576b-d968-a19b-5ffb9a250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed TE Marcedes Lewis from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-577f-d56e-afff-f7ff71460000</link>
      <description>Lewis is 41 years old, and probably will play forever. It will no longer come with any fantasy relevance, but it will be infinite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-577f-d56e-afff-f7ff71460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal (neck) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5781-d56e-afff-f7e9551b0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimate with the team having Christmas Day off. Vidal did not practice at all this week, and the Chargers will take on the Texans on Saturday. It’s certainly possible Vidal will play, but it seems very unlikely, and very unwise to have him in a fantasy lineup regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5781-d56e-afff-f7e9551b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
