<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports that Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase is a finalist for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e22f-d968-a19b-faff2f3d0000</link>
      <description>Schultz notes that the situation is “very fluid” and that there is “a good chance they add another name or two to the mix.” Scheelhaase will reportedly have his second interview with the team next week. The Browns are said to be targeting a young head coach. Scheelhaase, 35, fits the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e22f-d968-a19b-faff2f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports that the Browns hope to retain DC Jim Schwartz in his current role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e23c-dc7a-af9b-efbf78160000</link>
      <description>It sounds like he is no longer a candidate for their head-coaching vacancy. The Browns are said to be targeting a young candidate for the role, though Schultz notes that the team is not sure how Schartz would “react” to such a hire. The Browns have a win-now defense. It is possible that Schwartz is not interested in waiting around to see if an unproven candidate pans out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e23c-dc7a-af9b-efbf78160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said he would be “very surprised” if Mac Jones isn’t on the team next year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e23b-d968-a19b-fafb06c70000</link>
      <description>Jones went 5-3 as the 49ers’ starter while Brock Purdy was out with a foot injury. He finished the regular season ranked 10th in EPA per play. He is a great backup for Shanahan’s system, but the 49ers could also get a haul in return for Jones on the trade market. Both the free agent pool and the draft class are thin at quarterback, and plenty of teams will need one this offseason. With one year left on his current deal, a desperate team would likely send a Day Two pick to San Francisco for Jones’s services. For now, it looks like the team will keep him in the fold, but that could change once offers start rolling in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e23b-d968-a19b-fafb06c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said RB George Holani (hamstring) is “readying” himself for the “role behind” RB Kenneth Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e241-d56e-afff-e6e948570000</link>
      <description>Macdonald’s phrasing suggests Holani, not RB Cam Akers nor RB Velus Jones, would operate as the team’s No. 2 running back behind Walker, with former No. 2 RB Zach Charbonnet sidelined by a season-ending ACL tear. Macdonald adds that it is “realistic” for Holani to play this week. He has a chance to take on pass-protection duties while chipping in as a rotational ballcarrier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e241-d56e-afff-e6e948570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e243-d35e-a1bf-e7c3841f0000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo, Nagy is exploring a few OC openings. In other words, none of the head coaching interviews worked out. That dream died when the Titans passed on him in favor of Robert Saleh. With his contract in Kansas City up and Eric Bieniemy expected to fill that role, Nagy is now on the search for a new OC gig. The Eagles are in desperate need of a creative coordinator to invigorate their stagnant offense, but it’s hard to see Nagy as the man for the job. He just coached Patrick Mahomes for three seasons and failed to finish better than 15th in points scored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e243-d35e-a1bf-e7c3841f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Chiefs assistant general manager Mike Bradway for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e254-d56e-afff-e6fcd65f0000</link>
      <description>Bradway served as the Chiefs’ assistant director of player personnel from 2018-2020. He was promoted to the senior director of player personnel in 2021 and promoted again, to his current role, last offseason. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport refers to Bradway as “a top lieutenant” to general managers Brett Veach and believes Bradway “is next in a line of top KC personnel minds to explore a big job.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e254-d56e-afff-e6fcd65f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said Gus Bradley is “the obvious one” to replace Robert Saleh as the team’s defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e25a-dc7a-af9b-efff738f0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan did say the team will cast a wide net in their search for Saleh’s replacement, but all signs point to Bradley taking over as defensive coordinator. Bradley joined the team a year ago as an assistant head coach after a three-year stint with the Colts. He has over a decade of experience as a DC in the NFL, spanning four teams. The 49ers ranked 13th in points allowed this year despite losing several key defenders to various injuries. Bradley has big shoes to fill with Saleh getting another shot at a head coaching gig, this time in Tennessee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e25a-dc7a-af9b-efff738f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said he anticipates Tank Dell (knee) “being ready for the start of the offseason program.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26e-d968-a19b-faffc6d80000</link>
      <description>As expected, Dell missed the entirety of the 2025 season after suffering a catastrophic knee injury in the playoffs last year. Dell suffered a torn ACL, which required surgery. He also underwent procedures on his MCL and LCL. The Texans drafted a pair of rookies on Day Two last year, but neither truly broke out in 2025. Even with Nico Collins out for the Divisional Round, Houston leaned on Christian Kirk and Xavier Hutchinson in their final game of the year. Getting Dell back could meaningfully improve the team’s receiver rotation for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26e-d968-a19b-faffc6d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers DL Nick Bosa (knee) and DL Mykel Williams (knee) are expected to return sometime “around” training camp this summer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26f-dc7a-af9b-effff7c60000</link>
      <description>The news comes straight from 49ers general manager John Lynch, though the 49ers’ injury updates have been less than reliable this season. Bosa, 28, tore an ACL on September21st. Williams, a 21-year-old first-round rookie, tore his on November 2nd. Williams also notably injured his knee on August 7th, suffering what was believed to be a hyperextension. Follow-up reports did not specify whether this was accurate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26f-dc7a-af9b-effff7c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e28b-d968-a19b-fafb44450000</link>
      <description>Prior reporting on Wattenberg’s injury has been proven accurate. He missed the first two weeks of the playoffs, as expected, and will now attempt to make his return in time for Denver’s AFC Championship Game against the Patriots. Wattenberg is an all-around talented blocker. His potential return is great for the Broncos’ offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e28b-d968-a19b-fafb44450000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
