<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed RB D’Ernest Johnson off the Cardinals’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3101-d4ed-a9de-778f9fa90000</link>
      <description>Johnson will go from Arizona’s practice squad directly to their 53-man roster. Johnson hasn’t seen any action in 2025 but should be active for New England once he gets up to speed on the playbook. His signing could send things from bad to worse for rookie TreVeyon Henderson, who has played sparingly this year and coughed up a fumble late in New England’s Week 8 win over the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3101-d4ed-a9de-778f9fa90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3118-d4ed-a9de-779ef62b0000</link>
      <description>Flacco’s status is up in the air because of an AC joint sprain he suffered versus the Jets. He briefly went into the locker room late in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss but did manage to return without missing a snap. His absence would put Jake Browning back under center. Browning struggled mightily as the starter earlier this year, forcing the Bengals to trade for Flacco. His return to the lineup would be a massive downgrade for all Cincy pass-catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3118-d4ed-a9de-779ef62b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (concussion) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-311f-d321-a5bf-b3df0c3d0000</link>
      <description>Collins failed to practice at all last week before being ruled out ahead of Sunday’s game versus the 49ers. His return means that he is progressing through the league’s concussion protocol. Barring a setback, Collins should be cleared by the end of the week. He will reclaim a spot at the end of the WR1 ranks versus a Denver defense now playing without shutdown corner Pat Surtain this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-311f-d321-a5bf-b3df0c3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk (hamstring) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3123-d321-a5bf-b3f7c0420000</link>
      <description>Kirk did not practice at all last week, so this is a step in the right direction. We will assume it’s a limited practice for Kirk until the Texans officially release their first injury report of the week. Nico Collins is also expected to return in Week 9 after missing last week’s game with a concussion. With Collins and possibly Kirk back in the lineup versus Denver, Houston’s rookies—Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins—will likely go back to part-time roles on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3123-d321-a5bf-b3f7c0420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Mike Reiss reports that the Patriots will “most likely” target a running back and a veteran pass rusher in the trade market before the November 4th deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3122-d48c-ad9f-fd6f7d5f0000</link>
      <description>Reiss’ article was published this morning, and the Patriots signed former Cardinals practice squad player, RB D’Ernest Johnson, directly onto the active roster this afternoon, so it is possible the front office focuses on adding a pass rusher at this point. Regardless, the fact that the team has identified the running back position as an area of need is unfortunate for starting RB Rhamondre Stevenson and rookie backup RB TreVeyon Henderson. Fellow backup RB Terrell Jennings has also somewhat worked his way into the rotation, creating a fantasy-unfriendly situation. Hopefully, the Patriots stand pat with their current group and eventually allow Stevenson and Henderson to work in a usable rotation for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3122-d48c-ad9f-fd6f7d5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said TE Josh Oliver (foot) will not play in Week 9 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-312c-d321-a5bf-b3ff5a750000</link>
      <description>Oliver is dealing with a sprain in his foot. The Vikings signed Ben Sims earlier this week as a potential replacement for him. Oliver hasn’t caught more than two passes in a game this year. He does, however, have two touchdowns to his name. His absence could slightly boost T.J. Hockenson’s odds of getting in the end zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-312c-d321-a5bf-b3ff5a750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3140-d48c-ad9f-fd4d6e9d0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Dave Canales told reporters the team will make a decision on Young in the coming days. With Andy Dalton now banged up, there might not be much of a decision to make. Dalton struggled in his only start, throwing for 175 yards and an interception in a blowout loss to the Bills. Young’s return will be a slight upgrade for Tetairoa McMillan’s fantasy stock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3140-d48c-ad9f-fd4d6e9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell told reports that QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) “is healthy and is expected to have a full week of practice before playing” in Week 9 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3130-de12-a19e-3730d7780000</link>
      <description>Great news. O’Connell has remained steadfast in his position on McCarthy’s health and readiness, saying he will not allow the young quarterback to resume playing without being fully healthy. McCarthy has apparently reached O’Connell’s desired rehab benchmarks and will start against the division rival Lions this weekend. McCarthy’s play was volatile in his two active games this season, though he intriguingly showcased fantasy-friendly rushing traits, totaling 25 yards on the ground in both games. His proper ranking should crystallize as the week progresses. The Lions entered their Week 8 bye with myriad injuries in the secondary, the current status of which could prove pivotal for McCarthy’s passing performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3130-de12-a19e-3730d7780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dalton (right thumb) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3149-d4ed-a9de-77cffdef0000</link>
      <description>Bryce Young practiced in full after missing Week 8 with an ankle injury. All signs point to Young drawing the start in Week 9 against the Packers. Superflex managers can safely send Dalton back to the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3149-d4ed-a9de-77cffdef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RT Taylor Moton (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-314d-d48c-ad9f-fd4d7e510000</link>
      <description>Moton left the Panthers’ Week 8 loss to the Bills with the knee issue and did not return. A DNP to start the week puts him on the wrong side of questionable for Sunday’s game against the Packers. Yosh Nijman will take his spot in the lineup if he can’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-314d-d48c-ad9f-fd4d7e510000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
