<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:11:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) is not practicing Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d62-d56e-afff-efea2b820000</link>
      <description>He left Denver’s Week 16 game against the Jaguars with a non-contact hamstring injury and currently has no timetable for a return. It definitely sounds like he won’t be suiting up against the Chiefs on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d62-d56e-afff-efea2b820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d6d-d968-a19b-5dfd82010000</link>
      <description>He was “day-to-day” per Ian Rapoport’s reporting, but the Chargers signed RB Jarret Patterson back to the active roster earlier today. It’s probably more likely than not that Vidal misses Week 17’s game against the Texans based on this practice status and that transaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d6d-d968-a19b-5dfd82010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d7a-dc7a-af9b-cfff05f70000</link>
      <description>Schultz popped up on the injury report with a knee issue, but was still listed as a limited practice participant. Given it is the first practice of the week, it is possible the knee was just banged up in Sunday’s win over the Raiders. Fantasy managers should stay tuned for the rest of the week’ practice reports, but Schultz is still tracking to be on the TE1 borderline for Week 17 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d7a-dc7a-af9b-cfff05f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans OT Trent Brown (ankle/knee) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d84-d56e-afff-efec970c0000</link>
      <description>Brown left in Week 16 against the Raiders and now starts out the week not practicing. He is listed with ankle and knee issues and would be a notable loss if he cannot go Week 17 against the Chargers. With Aireontae Ersery (thumb) getting surgery, the Texans need healthy offensive tackles for their final playoff push. Brown still has a couple days to get a practice in and play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d84-d56e-afff-efec970c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (back) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d89-d56e-afff-efe98dc40000</link>
      <description>The Ravens held a walkthrough on Tuesday, so the injury report is just an estimate. However, Jackson being listed as the only non-participant does not bode well for his status in Week 17. Head coach John Harbaugh said on Monday that Jackson is day-to-day with a back contusion that forced him out of Sunday’s game against the Patriots; fantasy managers should stay tuned for the practice reports later in the week to see if he can get a practice in. It is a shorter week than usual for the Ravens as they play on Saturday against the Packers. For now, Jackson is on the wrong side of questionable and Tyler Huntley may be starting in Week 17 for Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d89-d56e-afff-efe98dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (calf) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d97-d35e-a1bf-4dd7ab800000</link>
      <description>Mitchell is dealing with a calf issue and got a limited designation after the Ravens’ walkthrough practice. The speedy 23-year-old is second in the Ravens’ running back rotations, but Derrick Henry will get even more carries should Mitchell miss time. However, fantasy managers can plan on Mitchell still playing in Week 17 against the Packers for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d97-d35e-a1bf-4dd7ab800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d99-d35e-a1bf-4ddbc08c0000</link>
      <description>Though he did not practice at all last week, Jacobs played through his knee injury in Week 16. He was inefficient and sidelined late with the injury still clearly hampering him. It is an encouraging sign that Jacobs is listed as limited Tuesday, though the practice report should be taken with a grain of salt as the Packers held a walkthrough and an ankle injury was added to his designation. Jacobs plays through injury as much as possible, so the limited designation indicates he is planning to play again in Week 17 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d99-d35e-a1bf-4ddbc08c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d9f-d56e-afff-efff81930000</link>
      <description>McDuffie is listed as DNP for the second straight day. He has been dealing with the knee issue since Week 14 and may not play the rest of this season with the Chiefs eliminated from playoff contention. Fellow CB Jaylen Watson (groin) was also DNP for the second straight day. Both are on the wrong side of questionable with a Christmas game against the Broncos on the horizon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d9f-d56e-afff-efff81930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Steelers WR DK Metcalf’s two-game suspension was upheld upon appeal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4dcb-dc7a-af9b-cfff362d0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was suspended by the NFL for the final two games of the regular season after an altercation with a fan in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions. He appealed the ruling, having previously reported the fan to Seahawks team security prior to his trade to the Steelers. An appeals officer jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA upheld Metcalf’s suspension and he will now miss Weeks 17 and 18 against the Browns and Ravens. It is costly in two ways for Metcalf; he will lose $555K in salary and has $45 million guaranteed voided, while the Steelers will not have him for a stretch run in which a win clinches the AFC North for them. Roman Wilson is in line for increased opportunities with Metcalf out, though we do not recommend him for fantasy lineups in the fantasy championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4dcb-dc7a-af9b-cfff362d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Jordy Nelson, jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA, upheld Chargers LB Denzel Perryman’s two-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4e0c-d35e-a1bf-4fce08080000</link>
      <description>Perryman was suspended for repeated violations of the playing rules intended to protect the health and safety of players. The NFL dealt out his punishment given Perryman’s history of suspension due to rule safety violations, with a previous two-game suspension coming in 2023 for the same reason. The NFL has made it clear they will not tolerate repeated risky hits from players. Perryman will miss the final two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4e0c-d35e-a1bf-4fce08080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
