<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) and S Kyle Hamilton (shoulder) were limited in Tuesday’s practice after initially announced to be full participants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdcd-db57-afda-ffff2e6b0000</link>
      <description>Head coach John Harbaugh had announced both Bateman and Hamilton to be full participants on Tuesday, but the team’s official injury report has them listed as limited participants. It’s not the first time Harbaugh and the Ravens have had discrepancies in practice reporting, but we’ll take the official limited listing as the truth for now. Bateman opens the week with back-to-back limited practices and has a shot to return to his starting role on Thanksgiving against the Bengals. Meanwhile, Hamilton has played through injuries before and we would not rule out the same happening again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdcd-db57-afda-ffff2e6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Justice Hill (neck) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdd1-d90e-a9da-bfdffc0c0000</link>
      <description>Hill pops up on the injury report with a neck issue. It is presumably new, given he was not on the injury report Monday. A new neck injury is cause for concern in terms of game status and Hill is in jeopardy of missing the Ravens’ Thanksgiving game against the Bengals. If he does miss, Keaton Mitchell will get a bump in pass-catching duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdd1-d90e-a9da-bfdffc0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed C Luke Wattenberg to a four-year, $48 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdd4-d6c4-abfb-ffd78f2f0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’sTom Pelisseroalso reports Wattenberg’s extension also includes $27 million guaranteed. The 28-year-old has been an anchor of the Broncos’ offensive line, starting all 24 games played over the last two seasons. He ranks among the top-15 centers in both PFF pass blocking and run blocking grades, allowing one quarterback hit and nine hurries this season. Wattenberg gets rewarded with a deal that keeps him in Denver through 2029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdd4-d6c4-abfb-ffd78f2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Burrow said he’s not going to play in Week 13 and beyond “scared” of further injuries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c04d-d6c4-abfb-d64fb17c0000</link>
      <description>Burrow will return to the 3-8 Bengals on Thursday night against the Ravens after missing two and a half months with a toe injury. “I’m not going to ever go to somebody and say, ‘yeah, I’m healthy, but I don’t think I should play.’ That doesn’t make a lot of sense to me,” Burrow said Tuesday. “I’m not going to live my life and play this game scared of something happening. … Yeah, I’ve had injuries. It’s not a lot I can do about that. I worked really hard to have that not happen, but what I can do is when it does happen I can control how I’m attacking my rehab.” The Athletic’s Mike Silver said Burrow is “comfortable” with his injured toe and will manage the pain during games. The return of Burrow doesn’t change the prospects of Bengals pass catchers all that much in Week 13. Burrow should be considered a top-12 fantasy play against Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c04d-d6c4-abfb-d64fb17c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Aaron Rodgers (wrist) will return in Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c05c-d82c-a79a-f3dc660a0000</link>
      <description>It was trending this direction after Rodgers narrowly missed last week’s loss to the Bears. Rodgers suffered a left wrist fracture in Week 11 but the team believes he can play through it. The injury might require Rodgers to operate from the shotgun more than usual to avoid the impact of taking a snap from under center. That would change Arthur Smith’s play-action heavy offensive scheme until Rodgers is fully healed. Rodgers will be a superflex-only option against Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c05c-d82c-a79a-f3dc660a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chiefs G Trey Smith (ankle) won’t play in Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c067-d90e-a9da-df6f994a0000</link>
      <description>Smith sustained two sprains on the same ankle in the team’s Week 12 game against the Colts and did not practice Tuesday ahead of KC’s Thanksgiving matchup with the Cowboys. It’s a blow to the Chiefs offense, as Pro Football Focus grades Smith as the NFL’s tenth best pass-blocking guard this season. The Dallas front seven has been much improved over the past three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c067-d90e-a9da-df6f994a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Patriots LT Will Campbell (knee) will miss at least four weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c06c-d90e-a9da-df6fb7750000</link>
      <description>Campbell went down with an MCL injury in Week 12 against the Bengals. Russini said Campbell, who has excelled as a pass protector this season, “will most likely land on injured reserve” and could return for the postseason. Losing Campbell could mean more pressure on Drake Maye, who in Week 12 struggled against pressure. On the season Maye has completed 55 percent of his throws when facing pressure and has averaged 8.2 yards per attempt, the third highest mark in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c06c-d90e-a9da-df6fb7750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (concussion) is not expected to play in Week 13 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c071-d6c4-abfb-d673d4940000</link>
      <description>After another catastrophic outing in Week 12 against the Packers, McCarthy was placed in the league’s concussion protocol. Rookie QB Max Brosmer is slated to start for Minnesota against a tough Seattle defense. It’s hard to imagine Brosmer playing any worse than McCarthy has over the past few weeks. Look for the Vikings to remain a run-heavy offense in Week 13 and beyond. Brosmer should be rostered in superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c071-d6c4-abfb-d673d4940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports George Pickens (calf/knee) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c075-d6c4-abfb-d677bd5e0000</link>
      <description>Pickens practiced Tuesday ahead of the Cowboys’ Thanksgiving Day matchup against the Chiefs. He should be a full go and remain in fantasy lineups. Pickens this season is second in the NFL in receiving yards — trailing only Jaxon Smith-Njigba — and sixth in air yards. He has functioned as the team’s No. 1 wideout for most of the past month while CeeDee Lamb struggles with drops. Look for the Cowboys to go pas heavy against a KC defense that has been tough against the run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c075-d6c4-abfb-d677bd5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs (knee) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c092-d82c-a79a-f39612210000</link>
      <description>Dealing with a bone bruise on his knee, Jacobs was limited in Tuesday’s practice and should be good to go for Thanksgiving Day against Detroit. Whether he’ll see his usual massive workload remains to be seen, especially after Emanuel Wilson acquitted himself well as the Packers’ starting back in Week 12 against the Vikings. Jacobs, who has at least 17 carries in seven games this season, should be locked into all fantasy lineups for Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c092-d82c-a79a-f39612210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
