<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 17 times for 61 yards in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears, adding one catch for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-d94a-a79d-e9bd910c0000</link>
      <description>“Bill” also lost a fumble, and should have been credited with another fumbled loss on a missed handoff from Jaden Daniels. The 24-year-old tailback found very little room against the Chicago front seven with a long gain of just 11 yards in a middling fantasy effort that wasn’t saved with a touchdown. It’s disappointing after he looked so solid against the Chargers in Week 5, but fantasy managers shouldn’t panic too much from this one. He’s still a RB2 for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-d94a-a79d-e9bd910c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed five times for 19 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders, adding one catch for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-d94a-a79d-e9bd0d700000</link>
      <description>Monangai got his usual handful of carries, but each one seemed like a waste with D’Andre Swift looking so good with 175 total yards. The 23-year-old will assuredly be Swift’s backup again for Week 7 against the Cowboys, and would need something unforeseeable to be a fantasy option at this point in redraft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-d94a-a79d-e9bd0d700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy McNichols rushed two times for seven yards in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears, adding three catches for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-db72-a199-fafb98f90000</link>
      <description>McNichols could have had a bigger receiving game if not for an egregious drop with no one near him in the fourth quarter. The 29-year-old will remain the backup to Jacory Croskey-Merritt, and completely off the fantasy radar for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-db72-a199-fafb98f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke McCaffrey caught his lone target for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-def2-abdb-fdf1a3f80000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey took advantage of a busted coverage to walk into the end zone and give the Commanders a 24-16 lead. The second-year wideout has an impressive 41.5 yards per reception over the last two weeks, but it’s hard to be too excited about that when you’ve touched the ball twice. He’ll be off the radar for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b0-def2-abdb-fdf1a3f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 6-of-6 targets for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f513fd0000</link>
      <description>A very nice bounceback from Ertz after he failed to bring in a single catch against the Chargers in Week 5. The veteran tight end worked his way into the back of the end zone to give Washington a 17-16 lead on a connection with Jayden Daniels. Ertz doesn’t have elite upside — nor anything close — but despite his bagel in Week 5, he remains a TE2 for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f513fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 4-of-5 targets for 19 yards in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f519e00000</link>
      <description>There were a lot of factors going against Samuel for this one — bad weather, a heel issue, a defense focused on him with no Terry McLaurin — but regardless, it was a dud for the 29-year-old wideout. He had a long gain of nine on the day, and he was targeted exclusively underneath the Chicago secondary. Samuel has been excellent to begin his tenure with Washington, but this wasn’t an example of it — again, for a variety of reasons. He’ll get a chance to rebound against the Cowboys in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-dd4c-afb9-e7f519e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Moore caught 3-of-5 targets for 46 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 6 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-def2-abdb-fdf521400000</link>
      <description>Yes, that Chris Moore. With Terry McLaurin out and Deebo Samuel clearly hampered by a hamstring issue, Moore ended up second in targets behind Zach Ertz during the Monday Night Football contest, and led the team in yardage. It’s a fun story for a player who has hung around for an awfully long time, but even with the trip to the end zone, he can’t be trusted in fantasy for Week 7 against the Cowboys. Or any other week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0b4-def2-abdb-fdf521400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden caught 4-of-4 passes for 51 yards in the Bears’ Week 7 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c7-db72-a199-facf91b00000</link>
      <description>Burden ended up leading the Bears in catches and yardage, which is a vast improvement over the negative-four yards he put up against the Raiders. The shifty 21-year-old rookie did most of his damage on a 37-yard connection to set up a score. There is considerable upside in Burden’s profile, but there just aren’t enough touches to suggest he’s worth a fantasy roster spot right now in redraft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c7-db72-a199-facf91b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 3-of-5 passes for 42 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c8-dd4c-afb9-e7c907ca0000</link>
      <description>Another quiet yardage day for Moore, and no trips to the end zone. The 28-year-old has now gone under 50 yards in four-straight games, and he hasn’t made up for it with touchdowns as seen in just one in 2025. Moore could find room against the Saints’ weak secondary in Week 7, but he is more FLEX play than someone who has to be in lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0c8-dd4c-afb9-e7c907ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 2-of-5 targets for 32 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</link>
      <description>Odunze nearly had his fantasy day saved with an 11-yard touchdown, but that was negated by a penalty. It was a quiet day for the second-year wideout in a contest where the Bears relied heavily on D’Andre Swift in the run game. Expect Odunze to bounce back with more touches — and a potential trip to the end zone — against the Saints in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
