<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OL coach Bill Callahan resigned.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3be-d94a-a79d-ebbfd3500000</link>
      <description>Not a huge surprise, after all, they did fire his son from the head-coaching role. Callahan will be a coveted offseason coaching free agent and has a long history of success turning around bad offensive lines despite not delivering on that promise with the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3be-d94a-a79d-ebbfd3500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens released C.J. Gardner-Johnson from their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d0-def2-abdb-fff1eb970000</link>
      <description>The 27-year-old safety asked for his release after the Ravens traded for Alohi Gilman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d0-def2-abdb-fff1eb970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons LT Jake Matthews (ankle) left Atlanta’s Week 6 game against the Bills and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d5-d94a-a79d-ebddcec70000</link>
      <description>It’s one injury to watch ahead of Week 7, though it wasn’t like the Falcons had major problems on the offensive line without the 33-year-old veteran. Mike Jerrell played left tackle in Matthews’ absence for most of the second half on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d5-d94a-a79d-ebddcec70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is getting “closer and closer” to returning to practice and mentioned Week 10 as a “rough estimate.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3dd-def2-abdb-fffd53d40000</link>
      <description>The 49ers head coach added that there’s no set date yet. Shanahan also estimated that Aiyuk would return in Week 6 in August. You may be aware that it is Week 7. While we’re sure to see some positive movement on Aiyuk over the next month, until we get word that the 49ers are going to open his 21-day return window, it’s hard to trust that he’s going to be back any time soon. We’d anticipate that Week 10 would be about the earliest he’d return based on how the 49ers have handled it thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3dd-def2-abdb-fffd53d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Jordan Watkins (calf) is expected to resume practicing this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3ed-dd4c-afb9-e7edbe950000</link>
      <description>We were just thinking the 49ers wideout projections needed another variable to deal with. Watkins briefly wowed in training camp before dealing with a high-ankle sprain and later this calf issue. It’s possible he cuts into some veteran playing time if the 49ers wideout room remains unsettled, but he’s not someone to rush and pick up in re-draft leagues without seeing some real signs of fantasy life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3ed-dd4c-afb9-e7edbe950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Joshua Palmer (ankle) is “week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e457-d94a-a79d-ed5f095b0000</link>
      <description>We may not see him playing out of the bye, in other words. Palmer left Week 6’s game against the Falcons and did not return. Tyrell Shavers saw extra opportunities down the stretch in Palmer’s absence and would seem to be next man up at the position if Palmer can’t get healthy ahead of Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e457-d94a-a79d-ed5f095b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e459-d94a-a79d-ed5da1b80000</link>
      <description>We would be surprised if Kincaid weren’t back after Week 7’s Bills bye week — he missed Week 6’s game against the Falcons despite practicing in all three days ahead of it. It’s possible the Bills simply held out Kincaid to be cautious.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e459-d94a-a79d-ed5da1b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans placed EDGE Oluwafemi Oladejo (calf) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45b-db72-a199-fe5bfd180000</link>
      <description>The second-round pick will miss at least the next four weeks. Oladejo played 241 defensive snaps in the first six games of the season, failing to generate a sack and notching 13 combined tackles and two tackles for loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45b-db72-a199-fe5bfd180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WR David Bell retired from the NFL after three seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45f-dd4c-afb9-e7df31760000</link>
      <description>The 24-year-old noted that he was dealing with an “off-field injury that was beyond my control, which put my football future in jeopardy.” We know that Bell underwent hip surgery in September of 2024. He had 41 catches for 408 yards in three seasons with the Browns, and looked like he was in the mix to be a starter at times. Alas, the 2022 third-rounder could not get back to full health and walks away from the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45f-dd4c-afb9-e7df31760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed G Matt Peart (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e47a-db72-a199-fe7b6e640000</link>
      <description>Peart filled in for Ben Powers, who went on injured reserve last week, against the Jets in London. Denver will need to go back to the bench for Week 7’s game against the Giants. Peart will miss at least the next four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e47a-db72-a199-fe7b6e640000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
