<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 11 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8428-d1e7-a1fa-deea5d170000</link>
      <description>Both Decker and Lions RT Penei Sewell (ankle) were sidelined on Friday after practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday. The coaching staff may just be giving their bookend blockers the day off to get right ahead of a big matchup against the Eagles’ pass rush, but we do not know for sure. Hopefully, both players are good to go come Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8428-d1e7-a1fa-deea5d170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns DT Maliek Collins (oblique) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 11 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-842d-d673-a39e-a4bd68a70000</link>
      <description>Collins “felt something” during practice on Friday per Kevin Stefanski and left early. Collins has been one of the better player on the Browns defense this year, notching a 90.4 PFF pass rush grade. His absence would be felt if he didn’t suit up on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-842d-d673-a39e-a4bd68a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8432-d45b-affe-d5b65ef40000</link>
      <description>Jurgens, along with LG Landon Dickerson (quad) and RT Lane Johnson (ankle), practiced fully on Friday. This is great news. The Eagles’ stud center has been sidelined by a knee injury suffered in Week 7. If this unit can continue improving its health, it should help the team’s fantasy stars return positive results down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8432-d45b-affe-d5b65ef40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (shoulder/illness) is not on Houston’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-843d-d673-a39e-a4bd17c60000</link>
      <description>Schultz was a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday, but it is clear the Texans trust him enough to manage him in practices. He’ll be a low-end TE1 against the Titans this week. Elsewhere in Texans TE land, Cade Stover (foot) is questionable in his first week of practices since opening his 21-day window, but with Harrison Bryant (neck/shoulder) officially out, Stover seems to be likely to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-843d-d673-a39e-a4bd17c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans OL Ed Ingram (knee) is questionable for Houston’s Week 11 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-843f-d673-a39e-a4bf8d480000</link>
      <description>Ingram, one of Nick Caserio’s better OL scrapheap finds this year, missed last week’s game with the injury but had limited practices on Thursday and Friday after a full on Wednesday. Juice Scruggs wound up seeing most of the time at right guard after an ugly debut series from Sidy Sow. Tytus Howard (concussion) cleared protocol and will start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-843f-d673-a39e-a4bf8d480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks ruled out WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) for Week 11 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8444-d1e7-a1fa-deeea55b0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Horton was unable to practice on Thursday after getting in a limited session on Wednesday. That pattern typically suggests that a player suffered a setback. On Friday, Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters that they are considering placing Horton on injured reserve. Bad news. The Seahawks (7-2) vie for the NFC West’s top spot against the Rams (7-2) on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8444-d1e7-a1fa-deeea55b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-844c-d713-ad9e-ec5cb81f0000</link>
      <description>Fannin played through the injury in Week 10 and remained limited on Wednesday and Thursday this week. He upgraded to full on Friday, which is great news. The Ravens have been enjoying improved health since their Week 7 bye. Fannin can be treated as a low-end TE1, whose upside is admittedly limited by veteran TE David Njoku.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-844c-d713-ad9e-ec5cb81f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83ee-d45b-affe-d7fe43c40000</link>
      <description>Bond and WR Cedric Tillman (glute) both practiced in full on Friday and logged limited sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. Unfortunately, neither player is reliable enough to make their way into 12-team re-draft starting lineups. Both generally occupy a similar field-stretching role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83ee-d45b-affe-d7fe43c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) is not on San Francisco’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-845f-d713-ad9e-ec5f63e30000</link>
      <description>After such a long layoff, it’s hard to fully understand what Pearsall will give us from a fantasy perspective against the Cardinals. He figures to be a main target in the pecking order, but what we saw of Pearsall was mostly without George Kittle early in the season. We have FLEX expectations given the long layoff, but WR3 isn’t out of the question. His return effectively quashes the fantasy value of Jauan Jennings by moving Jennings lower in the pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-845f-d713-ad9e-ec5f63e30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
