<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) practiced in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c741-d90e-a9da-df4f3fad0000</link>
      <description>It’s his first such showing since aggravating a quad injury in Week 8. McLaurin has missed the bulk of the previous eight games with the injury but appears to be on the precipice of a return for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c741-d90e-a9da-df4f3fad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 18-of-30 passes for 234 yards and four touchdowns in the Packers’ 31-24, Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c743-d6c4-abfb-d74326110000</link>
      <description>The Packers’ first drive ended in a field goal, but it nearly ended in a scramble-drill touchdown. Love escaped pressure and almost completed a pass to Bo Melton down the right sideline but the pass grazed Melton’s fingertips before hitting the turf. Love linked up with WRs Romeo Doubs, Christian Watson and Dontayvion Wicks, but it was the latter two who routinely showed up, making big plays from start to finish. Love is a borderline QB1/2 against the Bears next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c743-d6c4-abfb-d74326110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught 6-of-7 targets for 94 yards and two touchdowns in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c754-d82c-a79a-f7d4d2080000</link>
      <description>Wicks got going on the Packers’ first drive with a six-yard catch-and-run. He really made his presence felt on the Packers’ third drive, though, hauling in an acrobatic 22-yard touchdown after DB Brian Branch bailed on his coverage assignment in the end zone, thinking the safety had things covered. He was wrong. Wicks seemingly tweaked his left ankle as he came down with the ball while keeping his feet in bounds, but he showed no ill effects after that. Wicks put the game away by beating Branch late in the fourth quarter, picking up a first down on a 4th-and-3 reception in which Branch stepped on the back of Wicks’ cleat, causing the Packers’ wide receiver to literally jump out of his own shoe as he went airborne to secure the pass. Wicks is back to boom-bust FLEX territory against the Bears next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c754-d82c-a79a-f7d4d2080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 4-of-10 targets for 80 yards and one touchdown in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c767-d82c-a79a-f7f71e1a0000</link>
      <description>Watson’s day could have been bigger had a missed defensive pass interference call not prevented him from securing a would-be 12-yard, first-down catch on the Packers’ seventh drive. Two of Watson’s four receptions were impressive sideline grabs. He scored a 51-yard touchdown on the Packers’ fifth drive by running out, and up the right sideline, right past Lions’ CB Amik Robertson, before hauling in the basket catch for the score. Watson warrants WR2 treatment against the Bears next week, though his performance can be reliant on downfield chunk gains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c767-d82c-a79a-f7f71e1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c769-d6c4-abfb-d76b4b900000</link>
      <description>The nature of Hampton’s injury and the fact he has yet to return to a full practice decrease his chances of returning in Week 13 against the Raiders, likely needing a full session before being cleared by team doctors. The Chargers could be looking at another week with Kimani Vidal as the clear lead back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c769-d6c4-abfb-d76b4b900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 4-of-4 targets for 20 yards and one touchdown in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c76e-d90e-a9da-df6f0ae50000</link>
      <description>Doubs was his typically reliable self in this one. He simply took a backseat to Christian Watson and Dontayvion Wicks. Doubs scored his touchdown from two yards out in the second quarter. The Packers sent him in motion from right to left, where he lined up out wide and ran a short out route. He got open, caught the pass easily and dove in for the score. Doubs is a WR3/WR4 against the Bears next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c76e-d90e-a9da-df6f0ae50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks Rb Kenneth Walker (glute) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c76d-d82c-a79a-f7fd9c280000</link>
      <description>Walker popped on the injury report last Friday with the glute issue but managed to play through the ailment, leading the backfield in snaps and opportunities in the process. He certainly appears to be trending towards another questionable tag unless he manages a full session Friday, but fantasy managers can expect him to be on the field come Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c76d-d82c-a79a-f7fd9c280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 1-of-1 targets for 23 yards in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c764-d6c4-abfb-d7671c7f0000</link>
      <description>Musgrave was barely involved as the Packers’ wide receivers stole the show against the Lions. Packers QB Jordan Love did give him one opportunity, flinging a play-action pass his way on the fourth drive. Musgrave dove and successfully secured the pass, bringing the ball down to the Lions’ 11-yard line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c764-d6c4-abfb-d7671c7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 17 times for 83 yards in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions, adding one reception for eight yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c77d-db57-afda-d77f76b50000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was left out of the touchdown-oriented fun, as Packers WRs Romeo Doubs, Christian Watson and Dontayvion Wicks stole the show. Jacobs missed time after taking a hard hit on his left thigh from Lions DB Brian Branch, but he returned for the following drive. Jacobs looked good in this one and showed no ill effects from the recent bone bruise in his knee. He is a locked-in RB1 against a Bears defense that could be without multiple linebackers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c77d-db57-afda-d77f76b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions head coach Dan Campbell told reporters that WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) “could be” sidelined for “a week or two, if we’re lucky.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c784-db57-afda-d7b630eb0000</link>
      <description>That is bad news. Campbell adds that the Lions should know more tomorrow, but St. Brown’s injured right ankle is expected to sideline him for some time. The Lions face the Cowboys, Rams, Steelers and Vikings in Weeks 14-17. Hopefully, he can at least return in time for the latter two contests. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c784-db57-afda-d7b630eb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
