<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed LT Tyler Guyton (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51bd-d968-a19b-59fd39cc0000</link>
      <description>Guyton’s season is over. The team signed DB Corey Ballentine from their practice squad to the 53-man roster in a corresponding move. Guyton suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12 and hasn’t played since. The team was likely holding out hope that he could return late in the year if they were still in the playoff hunt. Dallas was eliminated from postseason contention last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51bd-d968-a19b-59fd39cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c3-d56e-afff-f7eb1a9e0000</link>
      <description>Bills K Michael Badgley kicked in Prater’s stead last week, converting 2-of-3 extra points and 1-of-1 field goals. Prater injured his quad in Week 15. Pending QB Josh Allen’s (foot) availability, this game could be a fantasy-friendly environment, though Badgley’s recent showing hardly instills confidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c3-d56e-afff-f7eb1a9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams (neck) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c9-d968-a19b-59f9ce720000</link>
      <description>Williams was limited in practice on Monday and Tuesday. The team upgraded him to a full practice today before clearing him for action. Williams’ efficiency has fallen over the second half of the season, but he is still operating as the top back on an offense that should have no issues putting up points versus a horrific Washington defense. Williams will close out the fantasy season as an RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c9-d968-a19b-59f9ce720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DE Joey Bosa (hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c7-d968-a19b-59f7d61e0000</link>
      <description>Bosa dealt with a hamstring injury earlier this month. It is unclear whether this one threatens his Week 17 availability. The Bills were also without S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) and DT Jordan Phillips (ankle) on Wednesday. Defensive players who were limited include CB Taron Johnson (quad), S Cam Lewis (hamstring) and LB Shaq Thompson (neck).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c7-d968-a19b-59f7d61e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulders) resumed practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51d0-d56e-afff-f7f861350000</link>
      <description>Carter is practicing, as expected, theoretically putting him on track to play in Week 16 against the Bills. The Eagles’ difference-making interior defender has been sidelined since undergoing procedures on both shoulders on December 1st. The Eagles (10-5) are jockeying for playoff position. His return is consequential. Eagles LB Nakobe Dean (hamstring) is not practicing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51d0-d56e-afff-f7f861350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Flournoy (knee) is questionable for Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51d5-dc7a-af9b-dfff33be0000</link>
      <description>Flournoy was estimated to be a limited participant for Monday’s walkthrough. The team then listed him as DNP on Tuesday. He remained a DNP today, though it was another walkthrough. We don’t like his odds of suiting up for the Cowboys’ Christmas game against Washington. KaVontae Turpin has been cleared for Week 17 and would take over as the team’s No. 3 receiver if Flournoy can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51d5-dc7a-af9b-dfff33be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c3-dc7a-af9b-dfff1d0b0000</link>
      <description>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (calf) was also not seen practicing. Dickerson played last week, while Johnson sat out, though Johnson is expected to play in Week 17 against the Bills. Having both players on the field would be great for the Eagles’ offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51c3-dc7a-af9b-dfff1d0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts LT Bernhard Raimann (elbow) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51db-d968-a19b-59fbefad0000</link>
      <description>Raimann missed Week 16’s game with the elbow issue. A limited practice to open the week is a good sign for his Week 17 availability. Center Tanor Bortolini is currently in the league’s concussion protocol and did not practice today. He is likely out for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51db-d968-a19b-59fbefad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LT Tristan Wirfs (toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51e2-d35e-a1bf-55e24b3a0000</link>
      <description>The injury is not believed to be a long-term issue, but a DNP today puts Wirfs at risk of missing Week 17. If he can’t go, Graham Barton would likely move from center to left tackle to fill Wirfs’ spot in the lineup. Barton made three starts at left tackle to open the year while Wirfs was sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51e2-d35e-a1bf-55e24b3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins S Minkah Fitzpatrick (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51e9-d968-a19b-59f9fdb30000</link>
      <description>Fitzpatrick picked up the calf issue in the Dolphins’ Week 15 loss to the Steelers. He did not suit up last week and a DNP today puts him on track to miss Week 17 as well. Fitzpatrick has been one of the few bright spots on a dismal Miami defense this year. The Dolphins got lit up by the Bengals last week and will likely be an easy target for Baker Mayfield and the Bucs on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51e9-d968-a19b-59f9fdb30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
