<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 03:28:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab0-da9b-a9bf-debd5d140000</link>
      <description>McConkey seems to have picked up a foot injury from Monday’s Week 14 game against the Eagles and gets a limited listing to start out Week 15. The Chargers held a walkthrough, so this is just an estimation, but McConkey should get at least a limited practice with pads before the end of the week in order to play against the Chiefs. The Chargers passing game has been rough since LT Joe Alt was ruled out for the season, making McConkey a borderline WR2 for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab0-da9b-a9bf-debd5d140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers QB Justin Herbert (hand) was limited in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab7-da9b-a9bf-debfc2c30000</link>
      <description>Herbert had hand surgery and played just a week later in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles. He took several shots in the game after rushing 10 times. Herbert had ball security issues with his left hand rendered innate as a ball-carrier and will get a limited workload in practice as the hand heals. Expect Herbert to start again in Week 15 against the Chiefs, where he will be a high-end QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ab7-da9b-a9bf-debfc2c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Kalif Raymond (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aba-da9b-a9bf-debf8c180000</link>
      <description>Raymond practiced in a limited fashion for the first time since suffering his ankle injury in Week 12. The 31-year-old barely maintains fantasy relevance, with a 4/49 line going for his best of the season. However, when he is active, he tends to take routes from the rookie touchdown-generator Isaac TeSlaa. Neither Raymond or TeSlaa are surefire fantasy plays, but fantasy managers should move TeSlaa out of their deep league lineups if Raymond plays Week 15 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0aba-da9b-a9bf-debf8c180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0abe-d005-a9bf-dabeada60000</link>
      <description>Adams has been nursing the hamstring for a week now, but played through it in Week 14 against the Cardinals. He starts out the week as a non-participant, but if he is on the same schedule as last week, Adams will still be good to go for Week 15. Fantasy managers should not worry about Adams being inactive just yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0abe-d005-a9bf-dabeada60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulders) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ac0-da9b-a9bf-decdec670000</link>
      <description>Carter underwent procedures on his shoulders last Monday and not back to practicing just yet. The Eagles’ franchise defensive tackle is a key presence in the middle of the defense, but is trending on the wrong side of questionable for Week 15. Any practice time he can get in this week is more likely to contribute to Carter ramping up to play in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ac0-da9b-a9bf-decdec670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OT Lane Johnson (foot) did not practice in Wednesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ac8-d005-a9bf-dafcaa0e0000</link>
      <description>Johnson was reported to be targeting a Week 15 return from his Week 11 foot injury, but is still not back to practicing. He will have the rest of the week to get practice time in as he is currently trending to miss Week 15 against the Raiders. OL Landon Dickerson (calf) was listed as limited on Wednesday, leaving the Eagles offensive line in a continuous shuffle amidst the team’s offensive struggles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ac8-d005-a9bf-dafcaa0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Geno Smith (shoulder/back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ad2-d005-a9bf-daf6a91e0000</link>
      <description>Smith adds a back injury to his initial shoulder injury suffered in Week 14. He was already unlikely to start Week 15, but the DNP listing with a second back injury indicates this could turn into a multi-week absence. Kenny Pickett will start with Smith out Week 15 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ad2-d005-a9bf-daf6a91e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’ practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ad5-da9b-a9bf-dedda8ab0000</link>
      <description>Mayer has not played since suffering the ankle injury in Week 12. He returns to practice in a limited fashion on Wednesday with the hope of playing in Week 15 against the Eagles. Meanwhile, fellow tight end Ian Thomas, who has taken on more snaps in Mayer’s absence, did not practice on Wednesday due to a calf injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ad5-da9b-a9bf-dedda8ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Denver Post’s Parker Gabriel reports Broncos QB Sam Ehlinger declined the Colts’ offer to sign him to their active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0adf-d8cf-affb-beffa6860000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger was originally drafted by the Colts and spent four seasons with the team. He toldThe Denver Postthat he and his agent talked to the Colts for two days before turning down the offer and sticking with the Broncos’ practice squad. The Colts were going for familiarity to fill their quarterback role by trying to get Ehlinger while also getting Philip Rivers. Ehlinger chooses to stay with the Broncos, where he is the third quarterback behind Bo Nix and Jarrett Stidham.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0adf-d8cf-affb-beffa6860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed WR/KR Xavier Gipson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0b5c-d8cf-affb-bf7e5b990000</link>
      <description>Gipson was released by the Eagles on Monday and has had a journeyman season. Starting the season with the Jets, Gipson has been on the Giants, Eagles, and now Giants again. He joins the practice squad as depth for the Jets’ special teams and wide receiver groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0b5c-d8cf-affb-bf7e5b990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
