<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:30:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LT Rasheed Walker was arrested at LaGuardia Airport in New York after he tried to check in a bag that contained a firearm on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f06d-dc7a-af9b-ffff1c9e0000</link>
      <description>Walker was charged with two counts of second-degree criminal possession of a weapon and criminal possession of a firearm. The 25-year-old left tackle appeared in Queens County Criminal Court on the gun charge and was later released. He is due back in court on March 19. A seventh-round pick by the Packers in 2022, Walker is set to hit free agency for the first time this offseason. His pending court appearance could impact his free agency as the legal negotiating period for pending free agents starts on March 9, and players can officially sign deals with new teams on March 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f06d-dc7a-af9b-ffff1c9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports Jets will interview Wink Martindale in-person for their open defensive coordinator position on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f0eb-d56e-afff-f6ebeb490000</link>
      <description>Martindale was crowned the early favorite for the defensive coordinator role earlier this week by another Jets beat writer, ESPN’s Rich Cimini. Hughes also replied to a fan comment on Twitter about the Jets not letting Martindale leave Saturday with, “I doubt they do.” Martindale has previously held the DC title with the Giants, Ravens and Broncos in the NFL as well as at the University of Michigan on the college level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f0eb-d56e-afff-f6ebeb490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots downgraded RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) and DT Joshua Farmer (hamstring) to out for the Conference Championship against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f132-d35e-a1bf-f5f223f70000</link>
      <description>Both players came into the weekend listed as questionable but will ultimately be held out for the team’s Conference Championship game against the Broncos. Jennings was not activated from injured reserve after being placed there in Week 13 with a concussion. Expect veteran journeyman D’Ernest Johnson to be active on Sunday and serve in an emergency role behind Rhamondre Stevenson and TreVeyon Henderson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f132-d35e-a1bf-f5f223f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports 49ers OC Klay Kubiak has removed himself from head coaching vacancies and will remain in San Francisco.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f136-dc7a-af9b-ffbf2f080000</link>
      <description>Russini adds that Kubiak simply preferred to remain in San Francisco to coach under offensive guru Kyle Shanahan, something that could prove fruitful further into his coaching career and could give the up-and-coming coach greater longevity. For now, Kubiak will remain the team’s offensive coordinator and continue his tutelage without calling offensive plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f136-dc7a-af9b-ffbf2f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Steelers are working to hire Mike McCarthy for their vacant head coaching position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f146-dc7a-af9b-ffff99900000</link>
      <description>Pelissero reported yesterday that he believed that veteran quarterback Aaron Rodgers would be most likely to play for one coach in 2026, naming Mike McCarthy as that coach. Not 24 hours later and the Steelers are reportedly working to hire McCarthy as their next head coach following the departure of Mike Tomlin. The dominoes certainly appear to be falling into place to get the franchise what they want, which appears to be Aaron Rodgers for another season. McCarthy last served as the head coach of the Dallas Cowboys between 2020 and 2024 but coached Rodgers for 13 years in Green Bay at the beginning of the aging veteran’s career. It also serves as a homecoming for the 62-year-old coach, who grew up in the Pittsburgh area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f146-dc7a-af9b-ffff99900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders interviewed former Giants HC Brian Daboll for their vacant head-coaching position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f14f-d968-a19b-f9ff856f0000</link>
      <description>Daboll has made his rounds during this coaching cycle, apparently drawing significant interest from multiple franchises in need of either a head coach or offensive coordinator. Still no hire, but the former Giants head coach appears to be close to landing on his feet after being fired during the 2025 regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f14f-d968-a19b-f9ff856f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots activated WR Mack Hollins (abdomen) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f153-d56e-afff-f7fb21150000</link>
      <description>Hollins makes his return from injured reserve in time to face the Broncos in the AFC Championship game, likely returning to a semi-featured role due to his run-blocking abilities. It is likely we see undrafted free agent Efton Chism the odd man out due to Hollins’ return, with DeMario Douglas and Kyle Williams joining Hollins, Stefon Diggs, and Kayshon Boutte as the active wide receivers come Sunday. Hollins’ red zone acumen and deep-threat abilities warrant consideration in DFS on the short slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f153-d56e-afff-f7fb21150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins promoted senior passing game coordinator Bobby Slowik to offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f1df-d35e-a1bf-f5dfeabc0000</link>
      <description>Slowik drew fleeting interest in the offensive coordinator market after a failed stint in the same position with the Texans, interviewing with the Eagles and Dolphins for their respective vacancies. He ultimately remained with the Dolphins following a year as their senior passing game coordinator, giving the Kyle Shanahan protege his second look at play calling duties at the professional level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f1df-d35e-a1bf-f5dfeabc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Steelers OC Arthur Smith is expected to accept the same position at Ohio State.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e8f0-d35e-a1bf-edf255760000</link>
      <description>Alrighty then. The former Titans OC and Falcons head coach had been riding the NFL interview circuit, meeting with clubs about both head-coaching and play-calling vacancies, but evidently wasn’t gaining the traction he hoped for. He now (reportedly) heads to what has become a coaching turnaround factory in Columbus, somewhat hilariously forming a coordinating tandem with Matt Patricia. 43-year-old Smith has extremely limited NCAA experience aside from low-level, one-year stints at UNC and Ole Miss. It’s not an amazing hire on paper, but talent trumps all at OSU. Smith will have enough of it to be positioned for success.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e8f0-d35e-a1bf-edf255760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Titans have requested permission to interview Texans DBs coach Dino Vasso for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f289-d35e-a1bf-f7cb6ecb0000</link>
      <description>Texans DC Matt Burke is reportedly pushing for Vasso to get the promotion. It’s unclear if Vasso would actually get to call plays under defensive-minded head coach Robert Saleh, but it would inarguably be a promotion. 38-year-old Vasso has been bouncing around NFL coaching staffs since 2013, starting under Andy Reid in Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f289-d35e-a1bf-f7cb6ecb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
