<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Dalton Kincaid (knee/hamstring) “plans to try to play” in Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90e-d8cf-affb-fd2edb2e0000</link>
      <description>When a player is ready to go, Schefter and most other reporters will say they are “expected to play.” That Schefter didn’t use those words means Kincaid still has some hurdles to clear before getting the green light. The team will likely test out his hamstring and knee during warmups before making a final call. Assuming all goes well, Kincaid will return for a game teeming without shootout potential. Even in his first game since Week 10, Kincaid will push for a TE1 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90e-d8cf-affb-fd2edb2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mike Evans is “pushing to play as soon as Thursday night vs. the Falcons.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f915-d005-a9bf-f93548bd0000</link>
      <description>Evans is currently on injured reserve while recovering from the broken clavicle he suffered in Week 7. The team opened his practice window earlier this week, allowing him to return to the practice field as he prepares to play. Evans has been ruled out for Week 14 already, but it sounds like Week 15 is on the table. If not, fantasy managers can assume he will be back in the lineup for Week 16 versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f915-d005-a9bf-f93548bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there now is a real chance” Trey Benson (knee) will not be activated from injured reserve this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f91d-d005-a9bf-f93d5d1d0000</link>
      <description>Benson is entering the final week of his 21-day practice window. If he isn’t activated before the 21 days are up, the Cardinals are forced to leave him on injured reserve for the remainder of the season. Benson practiced on Wednesday two weeks ago but has been listed as a DNP ever since. He appears to have suffered a setback while recovering from the meniscus injury that has sidelined him since Week 4. At this point, it looks more likely than not that he is done for the year. Bam Knight will close out the season as Arizona’s top back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f91d-d005-a9bf-f93d5d1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Bucs are not expected to have LT Tristan Wirfs (oblique) for Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f922-d77b-adfa-fba34a540000</link>
      <description>The same is true of rookie corner Benjamin Morrison, who is dealing with a hamstring injury. Wrifs got in one limited practice this week before being listed as questionable. He was always going to be a long-shot to play after missing the first two practices of the week. The fact that he returned on Friday at least indicates that he could be back for Week 15 versus Atlanta. Graham Barton moved from center to left tackle when Wirfs missed time at the start of the year. The Bucs will likely make that move again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f922-d77b-adfa-fba34a540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f927-da9b-a9bf-ff2fd71e0000</link>
      <description>Left guard Donovan Jackson remains questionable with an ankle injury. Getting Darrisaw back will be a huge sigh of relief for Vikings fans. J.J. McCarthy is returning to the lineup this week and his struggles under pressure have been well-documented. Even at less than full strength, Darrisaw will shore up McCarthy’s blindside versus Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f927-da9b-a9bf-ff2fd71e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Parker Washington (hip) will not play in Week 14 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f934-da9b-a9bf-ff3d6eb60000</link>
      <description>Washington was held out of Wednesday’s practice before returning for limited work on Thursday and Friday. The team officially listed him as questionable for Week 14. His absence will free up more slot work for Brian Thomas Jr., who has struggled to get much going this year. With Washington inactive, Dyami Brown should return to the lineup this week. Brown was made a healthy scratch in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f934-da9b-a9bf-ff3d6eb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Texans CB Kamari Lassiter (foot) “is planning to play” in Week 14 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f939-da9b-a9bf-ff3d46b00000</link>
      <description>Despite getting in just one practice this week, the Texans were reportedly optimistic about him playing. While he still needs to get the final go-ahead after testing things out this morning, it looks like Lassiter will suit up for a must-win bout with the Chiefs. Lassiter has 10 pass breakups and two interceptions this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f939-da9b-a9bf-ff3d46b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals WR Jermaine Burton has been ruled out for non-injury related reasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f93c-d8cf-affb-fd3e7db00000</link>
      <description>Burton was questionable for Week 14 versus the Bills because of an ankle injury. He has previously been made a healthy scratch after missing team meetings and hasn’t appeared in a game this year. We have likely seen the last of Burton in a Bengals uniform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f93c-d8cf-affb-fd3e7db00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Browns OC Tommy Reese interviewed with Penn State for their head coaching vacancy before they hired Iowa State head coach Matt Campbell.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f943-d005-a9bf-f97734720000</link>
      <description>Rees replaced Ken Dorsey as the Browns’ offensive coordinator this season. He also took on play-calling duties in the middle of the year, though it’s hard to say if anything has changed since he took over. Rees got his start in the college ranks and went on to serve as the offensive coordinator at Notre Dame and Alabama. While Penn State ultimately went in another direction, it wouldn’t be surprising to see other college programs make a run at Rees in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f943-d005-a9bf-f97734720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said he “wouldn’t be surprised” if the Vikings brought in a veteran quarterback next year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f95d-da9b-a9bf-ff5d95860000</link>
      <description>Rapoport doesn’t cite any sources, but it’s hard to imagine the Vikings going into 2026 without a better plan at quarterback than they had for 2025. J.J. McCarthy has struggled mightily and may have already played himself out of the starting job for next year. The team tried out Carson Wentz as the veteran backup to McCarthy and it ended in disaster. Wentz was ineffective as a passer and could not protect himself, resulting in a season-ending shoulder injury. The Vikings will undoubtedly spend more on a veteran passer next time around. Expect a true quarterback competition next summer unless McCarthy turns things around in the final month of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f95d-da9b-a9bf-ff5d95860000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
