<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4b-d77b-adfb-cfcb33c10000</link>
      <description>So it continues. Kamara has not practiced since spraining his MCL in Week 12. He looks doubtful to play in Week 15 after two more missed practices to open the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4b-d77b-adfb-cfcb33c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (abdomen) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4c-d005-a9bf-df7c469c0000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if Neal didn’t play on Sunday after back-to-back practices, and he likely has a chance to be cleared from the injury report on Friday. Neal would make for an interesting RB3/FLEX play against the Panthers, though it’d surely help out if he caught more passes in the flow of the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4c-d005-a9bf-df7c469c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (neck) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4a-da9b-a9bf-df4fe91b0000</link>
      <description>That makes two missed practices for Taylor. Brutal. The rookie tight end led the team in targets (eight) just last week and leads the team across the full season with 64. Theoretically, his potential absence would put more work on WR Adonai Mitchell’s plate, though Mitchell flopped by catching just 1-of-6 targets for 24 yards last week and he could be stuck catching passes from QB Brady Cook in Week 15 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4a-da9b-a9bf-df4fe91b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f53-d005-a9bf-df77de490000</link>
      <description>As long as Lamb remains symptom-free, he should be good to go for the Cowboys’ Week 15 game against the Vikings. The Cowboys last played on Thursday night, in Week 14, allowing Lamb extra time to rest before practicing this week. It seemingly paid off. He can be started as a WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f53-d005-a9bf-df77de490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder believes the Colts are “prepping” QB Philip Rivers to start in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d8cf-affb-bf6ebeeb0000</link>
      <description>Per Holder, “it isn’t difficult to tell who a team is prepping to start. That player is Rivers.” Whether this helps the pass-catching corps remains to be seen. Rivers has not played football since 2020. One hard hit from a Seahawks pass rusher could send the 44-year-old back to the sofa. Backup QB Riley Leonard suffered a PCL sprain in his knee last week, though he is currently practicing in full. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d8cf-affb-bf6ebeeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks waived RB Cam Akers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d005-a9bf-df75d1cd0000</link>
      <description>Akers rushed five times for five yards and caught 0-of-1 targets in his time with the Seahawks. Griffin recorded zero pass breakups and zero interceptions on 56 coverage snaps. Both players could find spots on practice squads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d005-a9bf-df75d1cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived TE Marcedes Lewis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d77b-adfb-cfe344270000</link>
      <description>In four games with the Broncos, the 41-year-old tight end chipped in as a blocker, but earned zero targets this season. He could find a spot on a practice squad after this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d77b-adfb-cfe344270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f6c-d005-a9bf-df7ce0680000</link>
      <description>Demercado could need another week to rehab his high-ankle sprain, but Friday’s report will clarify things. Cardinals RB Bam Knight has out-touched RB Michael Carter in each of the last three games, totaling 38 touches to Carter’s 23. Should Demercado return this week, he could reduce both players’ workloads. With all three on the field in Weeks 10-11, Knight totaled 20 touches while Demercado handled 14 and Carter took 10. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f6c-d005-a9bf-df7ce0680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (illness) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f81-dbbb-ab9b-7fef0d7c0000</link>
      <description>Players rarely miss games due to illness. We fully expect McCaffrey to play in Week 15 against the Titans. If the 49ers were to jump out to a healthy lead, it is possible the coaching staff gives RB Brian Robinson a little extra work in the fourth quarter, but McCaffrey should be viewed as an elite RB1, regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f81-dbbb-ab9b-7fef0d7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbffe2e0000</link>
      <description>Reed is on track to play in a tough matchup against the Broncos this week. The Packers’ slot receiver ran a route on 60.0% of the pass plays last week, which was encouraging. Reed is on the FLEX radar once again, though his target volume is likely capped. Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) was also limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbffe2e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
