<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:29:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Eagles wide receivers A.J. Brown and Devonta Smith are frustrated with their roles in the offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb0-d6e9-af9d-afb02c1b0000</link>
      <description>You didn’t need a paid subscription to the Athletic to figure out Brown was unhappy this year, he made that clear in the postgame press briefing after totaling seven yards on nine targets in Week 4. Smith hasn’t been as vocal, but his underwhelming numbers this year have come on even less targets (20) than Brown has received (28). The Eagles are 4-0 and there’s been no indication Philadelphia intends to lean more towards the pass going forward. They face the Broncos’ top secondary in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb0-d6e9-af9d-afb02c1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell will be active for Week 5 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb8-d6e9-af9d-afb83e350000</link>
      <description>Mitchell impressed in the preseason with reports that he solidified himself as the No. 3 back in the Ravens’ offense. Once the season began, coach John Harbaugh made it clear that wasn’t a valued role as Mitchell was deemed a healthy scratch since the opening week. With Lamar Jackson sidelined for Week 5 and the Ravens turning to Cooper Rush, Mitchell is going to be active and could provide a spark in Lamar’s absence. He still doesn’t have much fantasy value as a contingent back or otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb8-d6e9-af9d-afb83e350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) could potentially miss multiple games.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0b8-deb6-a7fd-f3ff57710000</link>
      <description>Austin’s injury required a stay in the hospital, with the only update passed by the team being that his X-Rays came back clean. Even so, the team labeled him “week-to-week” as they catch their breath on bye in Week 5, meaning he could be facing a multi-game absence starting in Week 6 against the Browns. Roman Wilson, Scotty Miller, and Ben Skowronek could all be tasked with increased roles in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0b8-deb6-a7fd-f3ff57710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB/TE Taysom Hill (knee) is expected to play in Week 5 and “have a role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0bb-deb6-a7fd-f3ffd11c0000</link>
      <description>This comes from Saints Beat Reporter Nick Underhill via X. It remains unclear what that role will be, although Underhill speculates that the team could look to get the veteran involved at both quarterback and tight end. Juwan Johnson is questionable with an ankle injury while Foster Moreau has yet to be activated from the PUP list, potentially opening up additional room for Hill to serve as a quasi-tight end against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0bb-deb6-a7fd-f3ffd11c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans activated RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c1-d6e9-af9d-bad169410000</link>
      <description>The move sets the stage for Spears to make his season debut against the Cardinals in Week 5, although he continues to be listed questionable by the team. Fantasy managers likely have better options available than a committee back coming off injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c1-d6e9-af9d-bad169410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders downgraded TE Michael Mayer (concussion) to out for Week 5 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c3-d95b-addb-f8c7fe530000</link>
      <description>Fellow tight end Brock Bowers is listed as questionable after going limited-DNP-DNP in practice this week, potentially leaving veteran Ian Thomas in line to operate as the featured tight end against the Colts. Fantasy managers will want to track the situation through inactives 90-minutes prior to the team’s afternoon kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c3-d95b-addb-f8c7fe530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is “trending toward not playing” in Week 5 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c6-d95b-addb-f8c6fc300000</link>
      <description>Fellow tight end Michael Mayer was ruled out Saturday, potentially leaving the position in the hands of veteran Ian Thomas. The team elevated Albert Okwuegbunam. Fantasy managers in a bind could do worse than adding Thomas for a spot start considering expected game flow against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c6-d95b-addb-f8c6fc300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints activated TE Foster Moreau (knee) form the Physically Unable to Perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c9-d6e9-af9d-bad975d80000</link>
      <description>The team also activated Taysom Hill, setting the stage for both to make their season debuts against the Giants. It could not have come at a better time considering fellow tight end Juwan Johnson is listed as questionable with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0c9-d6e9-af9d-bad975d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0d3-dca3-a9fb-bddbd14c0000</link>
      <description>Brown missed the previous two games while tending to a shoulder injury but will make his return to the active roster ahead of a Week 5 meeting with the Chiefs. His return should push Parker Washington back into a complementary role considering the health of Brian Thomas Jr and Travis Hunter. Fantasy managers can treat Brown as a touchdown-dependent FLEX option moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0d3-dca3-a9fb-bddbd14c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Cardinals will “ride hot hand” Sunday against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0d7-d6e9-af9d-bad75ba10000</link>
      <description>Fowler then speculates that the early-down work is what will primarily be split into the “hot hand,” while Emari Demercado is likeliest to see clear passing situations. That leaves Michael Carter and Bam Knight likely fighting for the same role on early downs, with the eventual victor potentially siphoning goal line work as well. The report seems to back up head coach Jonathan Gannon’s words earlier in the week that all three backs would have a role. This appears to be a messy situation for fantasy purposes, one that managers should avoid unless absolutely necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b0d7-d6e9-af9d-bad75ba10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
