<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions CB Brian Branch (toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9df1-d673-a39e-bdf171ee0000</link>
      <description>Cornerback Terrion Arnold remains on the sidelines while in the league’s concussion protocol. Per usual, the Lions are banged up on defense. Losing Branch in addition to Arnold, who looks unlikely to play this week, would be a big blow to the unit. Branch has five pass breakups, 2.5 sacks, and one forced fumble this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9df1-d673-a39e-bdf171ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Burrow (toe) is practicing fully for Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e02-d713-ad9e-fe564df00000</link>
      <description>Last we heard, Burrow was hoping to return in time for the Bengals’ Week 13 game against the Ravens. He is not guaranteed to suit up this week despite his full Wednesday session, but Bengals head coach Zac Taylor was reportedly not “definitive” on whether QB Joe Flacco would start this week. Flacco sat out Wednesday’s practice, per usual, nursing the AC joint sprain in his right, throwing shoulder. If Burrow is available, add him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e02-d713-ad9e-fe564df00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e00-d1e7-a1fa-deea7daf0000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor suffered the hamstring issue in Week 11 against the Texans. He played through it after a brief check from the medical staff, but it looks like that might not be the case this week. Chimere Dike is dealing with a chest injury but is practicing in full. He should be good to go for Sunday’s game against the Seahawks. Dike has some low-end FLEX appeal for Week 12. No other Tennessee pass-catcher is worth a look for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e00-d1e7-a1fa-deea7daf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals designated TE Mike Gesicki (pec) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e09-d45b-affe-df9f4f9e0000</link>
      <description>Gesicki practiced fully on Wednesday, theoretically putting him on track to play in Week 12 against the Patriots. His return is a positive for the offense, but it muddies the water for fantasy purposes. He would only be up for TE2 consideration, were he to be active this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e09-d45b-affe-df9f4f9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e0e-d713-ad9e-fe5ec16d0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens really kept this one close to the vest. Jackson sat out last Wednesday due to knee soreness before returning to practice as a full participant on Thursday and suiting up on game day. Head coach John Harbaugh spoke with reporters earlier today, indicating that Jackson would be on a similar trajectory this week. He did not, however, reveal that Jackson is now dealing with an ankle injury. Assuming Jackson indeed resumes practicing fully, he can be kept in the high-end QB1 ranks, though the injuries do seem to be impacting his box score successes. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e0e-d713-ad9e-fe5ec16d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e0d-d1e7-a1fa-deefb97a0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson has missed the past two weeks because of the toe issue. A limited practice to open the week puts him on track to play on Sunday, but this is one of the injury report situations fantasy managers should keep close tabs on this week. Stevenson was also limited in practice last week but was ruled out before the weekend. TreVeyon Henderson has exploded in Stevenson’s absence, racking up 243 yards and five scores over the past two weeks. Henderson has presumably earned the right to be the lead back even once Stevenson is healthy, but the best-case scenario is still a committee approach from the Pats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e0d-d1e7-a1fa-deefb97a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (calf) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e08-d45b-affe-df9eac160000</link>
      <description>Likely’s disappointing season continues to involve nagging lower-body injuries. He still has time to get right ahead of his team’s Week 12 game against the Jets, but he does not warrant TE1 consideration if active. Fellow Ravens TE Mark Andrews would likely add a target or two to his workload if Likely sits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e08-d45b-affe-df9eac160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e15-d673-a39e-be95f8f80000</link>
      <description>Boutte has missed the past two games with the hamstring issue. A full practice today puts him on track to be a full-go for Sunday’s game. Boutte has thrived as Drake Maye’s deep threat this year. He leads the Pats with five receiving touchdowns despite the missed time. Barring a setback, Boutte will be a boom/bust WR4 for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e15-d673-a39e-be95f8f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Hooper (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e1a-d1e7-a1fa-defa6a8a0000</link>
      <description>Hooper will need to get in a full practice before being cleared from the league’s concussion protocol. He should be able to do so over the next two days. Hooper has stolen the occasional chunk gain from Hunter Henry this year, but he is not on the fantasy radar for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e1a-d1e7-a1fa-defa6a8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Knight (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e1c-d1e7-a1fa-defed6ab0000</link>
      <description>Emari Demercado has already been ruled out with an ankle injury of his own. Trey Benson, on the other hand, has been designated to return from injured reserve. He could return this week, but the Cardinals don’t have to activate him for three more weeks. If he isn’t ready to suit up, Knight will get first crack at the early-down work for Arizona. Michael Carter would operate as the team’s top option on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e1c-d1e7-a1fa-defed6ab0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
