<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Davis Mills completed 16-of-30 passes for 153 yards and two touchdowns in the Texans’ 23-19, Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4b3-db57-afda-f6b3762a0000</link>
      <description>After downing the Jaguars and Titans in his first two starts, Mills got a much tougher matchup on Thursday night against the Bills, but did just enough to will his team to a third-straight win. In what was easily his worst start of the season, Mills and the Texans converted only 2-of-12 third down tries, but a 24-yard pass to Nico Collins in the second quarter helped set the Texans up for their first touchdown on the night, which came on a two-yard reception by Christian Kirk, and Mills would later complete passes of 19 and 33 yards on a drive that ended with an eight-yard score by Jayden Higgins. Mills was solid in his three starts, throwing for 719-5-1 while keeping the Texans in the thick of the playoff race. He’ll likely head back to the bench for Week 13’s game against the Colts, with C.J. Stroud (concussion) expected to return, but Mills proved to be more than serviceable after making multiple starts for the first time since the 2022 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4b3-db57-afda-f6b3762a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 17 times for 116 yards and one touchdown in the Bills’ Week 12 loss to the Texans, adding three receptions for 13 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4bc-d90e-a9da-bfbf58d50000</link>
      <description>Cook had a solid day on the ground that was buoyed by a 45-yard touchdown run on the Bills’ opening drive. The speedster carefully navigated through the line before breaking into and then past the Texans’ secondary nearly untouched on the way to his eighth rushing touchdown of the season. It was the sixth 100-plus yard performance of the season for Cook, who has now topped 1,000 rushing yards for the third straight year and is on pace to surpass his career-high of 1,122 yards as early as next week. The Bills’ bell cow will be firmly on the RB1 radar in Week 13’s game against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4bc-d90e-a9da-bfbf58d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 8-of-10 targets for 110 yards in the Bills’ Week 12 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4c2-d413-ad9f-b5df133b0000</link>
      <description>Shakir took a lateral from Josh Palmer 33 yards late in the fourth quarter to convert a 4th and 27. It would have been his most memorable play of the day if not for a fumble he lost in the third quarter that the Texans were able to turn into what proved to be a much-needed field goal. Shakir was far more involved in this week’s game after Week 11’s one-catch dud against the Buccaneers. Thursday night’s game against the Texans resulted in a new season high in receiving yards for Shakir, who hadn’t gone for more than 88 yards in any game this season entering the contest. Shakir’s 10 targets led all Bills players, and were six more than the next closest receiver. His Week 13 target volume will partly depend on whether or not Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) is back in the mix, but Shakir should be on the WR2/WR3 radar for next week against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4c2-d413-ad9f-b5df133b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Davis caught 1-of-2 targets for 22 yards in the Bills’ Week 12 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4c8-d413-ad9f-b5dd66a30000</link>
      <description>Davis’ first and only reception on the day came on a 22-yard strike from Josh Allen late in the first quarter. The veteran receiver nearly turned in a game-winning touchdown catch late in the fourth quarter, however, but was unable to keep both feet in-bounds on his way down after leaping to make the catch. Davis has been active for each of the last two weeks with Keon Coleman being a healthy scratch, but has just four catches for 64 yards to show for his efforts. He isn’t on the Week 12 fantasy radar for next week’s game against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4c8-d413-ad9f-b5dd66a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught 3-of-4 targets for 17 yards in the Bills’ Week 12 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4cd-db57-afda-f6ffd16c0000</link>
      <description>In back-to-back games without Kincaid, Knox has failed deliver any kind of meaningful production for fantasy managers. The veteran tight end is sitting on a 4-40-0 line on seven targets over the last two weeks, and can be left on waivers for Week 12’s game against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4cd-db57-afda-f6ffd16c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 16 times for 74 yards in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4cf-d413-ad9f-b5dfe7dc0000</link>
      <description>Marks continues to lead the Texans backfield in volume but the production remains inconsistent. The rookie running back has totaled double-digit touches in six-straight games but has only two touchdowns to show for that, and his 74 yards on Thursday set a new season/career-high. His lack of upside in the passing game continues to make him a boom-or-bust RB2 heading into Week 13’s game against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4cf-d413-ad9f-b5dfe7dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk caught 5-of-6 targets for 54 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4dc-db57-afda-f6fe7c910000</link>
      <description>Week 12 marked one of the more productive days for Kirk, whose two-yard touchdown reception in the second quarter gave the Texans their first lead of the day. The veteran receiver later hauled in a 33-yard reception in the in the same quarter to help set Jayden Higgins up for an eight-yard touchdown to give the Texans the lead entering the half. It’s only the second time this season that Kirk has topped 26 receiving yards, and his five receptions were a new season high. Despite the decent showing, fantasy managers shouldn’t be rushing to start him in Week 13 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4dc-db57-afda-f6fe7c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 4-of-9 targets for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e1-d90e-a9da-bfefc4910000</link>
      <description>Higgins continues to be a key contributor in the red zone, scoring this time on an eight-yard touchdown just before halftime to give the Texans the lead. The rookie remains heavily involved in the offense with Davis Mills under center, but was seeing decent target volume from C.J. Stroud before his injury. The yardage has been underwhelming, but Higgins is clearly viewed as a reliable option in the passing game, averaging 7.7 targets per game in his last three games. Higgins will be on the WR4/WR5 radar in Week 13’s game against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e1-d90e-a9da-bfefc4910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 1-of-4 targets for eight yards in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e6-d90e-a9da-bfef650d0000</link>
      <description>Thursday’s game against the Bills was easily the worst of the season for Schultz, who had gone for 50-plus yards in five of his last six games entering the night. The Texans saw the majority of their production come in the second quarter of Thursday’s win, but struggled to sustain drives for much of the night. Schultz should be in store for a better Week 13 against the Colts, we’re he’ll profile as a fringe TE1/TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e6-d90e-a9da-bfef650d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
