<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:29:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans (hamstring) is active for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</link>
      <description>Evans was trending in this direction all week, but will officially return on Monday night against the Lions. The veteran receiver will pair up with rookie Emeka Egbuka, who is going to attempt to play through a hamstring injury of his own after going down in Week 6 against the 49ers. Assuming they’re both in top shape, Evans and Egbuka should give Baker Mayfield plenty to work with in a game that is expected to feature a lot of scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed J.J. McCarthy (ankle) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</link>
      <description>Just over 24 hours ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said “don’t be surprised” if Carson Wentz starts in Week 8. The decision to start Wentz will be spun as one that came down to the health of McCarthy’s ankle, but ever since McCarthy was unexpectedly diagnosed with a high-ankle sprain after a Week 2 loss to the Falcons, questions have been raised about the team’s commitment to him as their starter. McCarthy was limited in all of practice last week. Another week of limited practices would suggest he is close to a return even if Wentz draws another start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz (shoulder) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</link>
      <description>The injury is to Wentz’s non-throwing shoulder, which should be a good sign for his availability overall. Whether or not Wentz plays in Week 8 against the Chargers likely comes down more to the health of J.J. McCarthy (ankle) than his own and whether or not the Vikes are ready to hand the keys back to the 2024 first-rounder. Wentz has thrown for 1,072-5-4 in four games for the Vikings this season but struggled mightily in his last outing against the Eagles (313-0-2). He’ll be a fantasy QB2 if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Brock Purdy (toe) “will continue like he did last week” when asked about his Week 8 availability.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-039f-df81-ab9b-7fdf54340000</link>
      <description>Purdy practiced in a limited capacity all of last week and ultimately didn’t suit up for Week 7’s game against the Falcons. Based on Shanahan’s comments Monday, we would assume Purdy will again be a limited participant in practice this week, but it could be too early to say if Mac Jones will again be under center when the Niners take the field in Week 8 against the Texans. Purdy’s status remains one to watch, but we’ll wait for official confirmation from the team before ruling him out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-039f-df81-ab9b-7fdf54340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspended Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw for one game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b3-da18-a39a-dbb371460000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw was seen sprinting up to the official after the team’s game-winning field goal in their historic comeback victory against the Giants. A flag was immediately thrown on the field and the league levied a one-game suspension Monday after reviewing the incident. Greenlaw is likely to appeal but he is currently slated to miss the team’s Week 8 game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b3-da18-a39a-dbb371460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Titans released WR Tyler Lockett.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b5-d651-a9df-6bb5f4e30000</link>
      <description>The veteran receiver asked for, and was granted, his release from the team Monday. Lockett managed just 51 total offensive snaps the previous three games as the team turned to their youth, with rookie slot man Chimere Dike seeing a corresponding jump in usage during that span. Lockett will be free to sign with another team at 4 pm ET Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b5-d651-a9df-6bb5f4e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said DL Bryce Huff (hamstring) will miss two weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03ce-d651-a9df-6bdf61e90000</link>
      <description>Huff suffered a hamstring strain in the team’s Week 7 win over the Falcons and will miss the next two games. The 49ers continue to struggle through injuries up and down their roster, yet still remain tied with the Rams atop the NFC West.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03ce-d651-a9df-6bdf61e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out WR Mike Evans (concussion, shoulder) in the second quarter of Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0425-d651-a9df-6d35362f0000</link>
      <description>Evans appeared to come down with a long reception late in the second quarter but went limp after hitting the ground, adding insult to injury as the pass fell incomplete and the receiver on the turf. Evans was returning from three missed contests with a hamstring injury. He also reportedly suffered a shoulder injury that left him in clear agony. Evans could be looking at another extended absence. He failed to catch any of his four targets prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0425-d651-a9df-6d35362f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LB Derick Hall, LB Jared Ivey, TE Nick Kallerup, DB Devon Witherspoon, OT Mason Richman, S Julian Love, and QB Jalen Milroe inactive for Week 7 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0428-df81-ab9b-7eef21cd0000</link>
      <description>Seattle will be slightly shorthanded in the secondary after both Witherspoon and Love were unable to go in Week 7. That could become an issue considering the defensive struggle we expect in the final game of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0428-df81-ab9b-7eef21cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Christian Kirk, RB Dameon Pierce, DE Darrell Taylor, QB Graham Mertz, OG Jarrett Kingston, and OT Trent Brown inactive for Week 7 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-042e-d99b-a1df-3e2e5ef30000</link>
      <description>Kirk made it all of two-and-a-half games before suffering another injury after starting the season as an inactive. His absence should allow for more opportunities for rookie Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel. Dameon Pierce remains inactive as the team has shifted their focus towards rookie Woody Marks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-042e-d99b-a1df-3e2e5ef30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
