<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce Jr. (back) is active for Week 14 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bdd93d0000</link>
      <description>Right guard Chris Lindstrom is also active. Pearce Jr. was a surprise addition to the injury report on Friday because of a back issue. He was listed as questionable but is good to go. Inactive for the Falcons are WR Drake London, CB Cobee Bryant, RB Nathan Carter, DL Brandon Dorlus, OL Michael Jerrell, and WR Casey Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bdd93d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared CB Sauce Gardner (calf), RB DJ Giddens, DE Tyquan Lewis (ankle), S Reuben Lowery III, TE Will Mallory, S George Odum and OT Luke Tenuta inactive for Indianapolis’ Week 14 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-da9b-a9bf-ffafbd4f0000</link>
      <description>Gardner and Lewis were ruled out on Friday. Everyone else is a healthy scratch. Giddens has fallen behind a now-healthy Tyler Goodson in the battle to be the caddy that Jonathan Taylor doesn’t actually have.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-da9b-a9bf-ffafbd4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewers, WR Tahj Washington, OT Kendall Lamm, DT Matthew Butler, LB Andre Carter II, and CB A.J. Green III inactive for Week 14 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d77b-adfa-fbaf61a60000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have a set of healthy inactives for Week 14. Quinn Ewers will serve as the team’s emergency third quarterback with Zach Wilson (illness) officially active against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d77b-adfa-fbaf61a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared CB Jalyn Armour-Davis (Achilles), S Jerrick Reed II, G Drew Moss, C Lloyd Cushenberry III (foot) and DT Shy Tuttle (concussion) inactive for Tennessee’s Week 14 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9af-d8cf-affb-fdaf482a0000</link>
      <description>Tuttle was the only one of the three injured players on the questionable line, and he’s inactive despite practicing in full all week. Moss and Reed are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9af-d8cf-affb-fdaf482a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (ankle) is active for Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d8cf-affb-fdaf9c670000</link>
      <description>Jackson returned to practice Friday after being downgraded with his lingering ankle issue on Thursday. He hasn’t been himself for more than a month now as the Ravens offense stagnates in ways we haven’t seen since Jackson became the team’s starting quarterback. They’ll look to get back on track against a Steelers defense sporting one of the NFL’s most porous rush defenses. Ravens declared WR Devontez Walker, QB Cooper Rush, DT Aeneas Peebles, G Ben Cleveland, and T Joseph Noteboom inactive for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d8cf-affb-fdaf9c670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring/knee) is active for Week 14 vs Bengals</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c2-d77b-adfa-fbc39e2d0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid will be active for the first time since Week 10. The Bills can certainly use him with Josh Palmer (ankle) out, and their WR corps lacking consistent producers. Kincaid was the Bills’ most reliable receiving option prior to injury, and with snow falling in this one, he could be heavily targeted over the middle of the field. For what it’s worth, Bills beat writer Joe Buscaglia predicted that Kincaid would play under 50% of the snaps today but would be on the field in most passing situations. Kincaid is probably somebody you want to start unless you have a locked in top five TE option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c2-d77b-adfa-fbc39e2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Joshua Palmer, OT Spencer Brown. OT Chase Lundt, DE Joey Bosa, DT Phidarian Mathis, LB Terrel Bernard, and S Darnell Savage inactive for Week 14 vs Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c4-d005-a9bf-f9f491130000</link>
      <description>The Bills’ offensive line held up well last weekend, even with Brown and left tackle Dion Dawkins (concussion) out. Dawkins is back for this one, but the Bills will still be down their starting right tackle in a snow game, where they could rely on James Cook and the rushing attack a lot. Joey Bosa continues to be week-to-week, but his loss is a big one for this pass rush, and Shaq Thompson will start again with Terrel Bernard out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c4-d005-a9bf-f9f491130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared QB Jake Browning, WR Jermaine Burton, DE Trey Hendrickson, TE Cam Grandy and DT Jordan Jefferson inactive for Week 14 vs Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c9-d77b-adfa-fbcb73da0000</link>
      <description>No surprises here. Burton was suspended earlier this morning, and Hendrickson was ruled out earlier in the week with a hip injury. Browning is the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9c9-d77b-adfa-fbcb73da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (groin) is questionable to return in Week 14 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa11-d77b-adfa-fa933d0d0000</link>
      <description>Taylor left in the first quarter against the Dolphins with an apparent groin injury. He headed to the locker room after throwing an interception; with Justin Fields (knee) inactive for this game, former Missouri Tiger Brady Cook is making his NFL debut at quarterback. Taylor is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa11-d77b-adfa-fa933d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Daniel Jones (Achilles) left Indianapolis’ Week 14 game against the Jaguars and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa23-d77b-adfa-faa394830000</link>
      <description>He immediately reached for the Achilles on the dropback near the end of the first quarter, it was non-contact. Jones slammed his helmet on the turf multiple times before gingerly limping off with trainers and heading to the blue tent. He then followed them to the locker room. Jones had been 5-of-7 for 60 yards and an interception in the early going, but that is not the main concern for the Colts now. Riley Leonard took over at quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa23-d77b-adfa-faa394830000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
