<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rasheed Shaheed didn’t catch his lone target while adding one rush for 31 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3501-da28-afbb-f57d9fea0000</link>
      <description>Shaheed didn’t make much of a contribution outside of an end-around to set up a score late in the game on offense, but he showed off his sensational returning skills by returning a punt for 58 yards for a score in the middle of the fourth quarter. It’s a disappointing receiving day after Shaheed had made real progress over the previous two contests, but at least the trip to the end zone helps compensate. Shaheed should be more involved in Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3501-da28-afbb-f57d9fea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 4-of-6 targets for 49 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3502-da28-afbb-f57f53e60000</link>
      <description>Barner — not exactly known for his elite athleticism — made Kam Kitchens look silly on a wide-open touchdown connection with Sam Darnold in the fourth. The 23-year-old is the clear top tight end in the passing game with Elijah Arroyo unavailable, but it was the case even with Arroyo healthy. Barner will again be on the TE1 cusp for Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3502-da28-afbb-f57f53e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) was seen warming up for Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf19570000</link>
      <description>Higgins has been limited in the first two practices to start the week. He still needs to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to suit up for Week 16 against the Dolphins, but three-straight practices, even if in a limited capacity, suggest he’s trending toward a return. We should have the final word on his availability when the team releases its injury report later in the day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf19570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Garrett Wilson (knee) will not return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3772-da28-afbb-f77f2cf90000</link>
      <description>Glenn had been reluctant to say in recent weeks whether Wilson would return this season, but he has finally confirmed that his WR1 will be shut down for the remainder of the season. Wilson suffered a knee sprain in Week 6 against the Broncos and re-aggravated that same injury in Week 11. The Week 11 injury landed Wilson on injured reserve, meaning he wouldn’t be eligible to return until Week 15. With the Jets in the final weeks of another lost season, there was little reason to force Wilson back on the field and risk another injury. Wilson caught 36 passes for 395 yards and four touchdowns in the seven games he appeared in this season while averaging 8.4 targets per game. This will mark the first time in his four-year career that Wilson failed to go for 1,000 yards, but there’s little reason to believe he won’t be ready to bounce back next season. The Jets have a lot to figure out this offseason, especially at the quarterback position following the failed Justin Fields experiment. Despite the question marks in the team’s QB room, Wilson should profile as a high-upside WR2 in fantasy next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3772-da28-afbb-f77f2cf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McVay said Dalton Kincaid (knee) is trending toward playing in Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3784-d087-addf-b7f457df0000</link>
      <description>Speaking with the media on Friday, McVay said Kincaid will practice and confirmed the third-year tight end has not suffered any setbacks from the knee injury that has sidelined him for the first two practices of this week. Kincaid played through his knee injury in Week 15’s win over the Patriots, catching 3-of-4 targets for 34 yards. We’ll get a final update on his game status later in the day, but if Kincaid can play in Week 16, he’ll be on the TE1 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3784-d087-addf-b7f457df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks (ankle) was spotted at Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-378d-d087-addf-b7fd843d0000</link>
      <description>Texans beat writer Jonathan Alexander said Marks was seen at practice with a helmet, a good sign that he should log at least a limited session on Friday. The rookie running back was a DNP for the first two practices to start the week, but he could draw a questionable tag if he’s able to practice on a limited basis before the weekend. We will provide an update on his official status when the team releases its final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-378d-d087-addf-b7fd843d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals placed DT Kris Jenkins (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-379b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf399c0000</link>
      <description>Jenkins suffered an ankle injury in last week’s loss to the Ravens and will now miss the remainder of the season. The second-year tackle has totaled 36 tackles, two TFLs, and 1.5 sacks this season while starting four of the 14 games he appeared in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-379b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf399c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Shemar Stewart (knee) will play in Week 16 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37a6-d087-addf-b7f63a7f0000</link>
      <description>Stewart was designated for a return from injured reserve last week and will now take the field against the Dolphins this weekend. The rookie pass-rusher has totaled just six tackles in the five games he’s appeared in this season and is still in search of his first career sack. In addition to Stewart, Taylor also said DT B.J. Hill (ankle) will be available to play in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37a6-d087-addf-b7f63a7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) is questionable for Week 16 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37ad-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0f380000</link>
      <description>Higgins still hasn’t cleared concussion protocol, but the questionable designation suggests he could have a chance to clear it before Sunday’s game. His status will be one to watch heading into the weekend, but if Higgins is unable to go, Mitchell Tinsley would again see an expanded role in his absence. While Higgins is questionable, TE Noah Fant (ankle), DE Joseph Ossai (ankle), and WR Charlie Jones (ankle) have all been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37ad-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said Michael Carter will start at RB in Week 16 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37b8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf37030000</link>
      <description>This news doesn’t come as much of a surprise, but we appreciate the clarity. With Bam Knight (ankle) now on injured reserve, Carter will get the opportunity to handle RB1 duties against a Falcons defense that ranks 25th in rushing yards allowed and 24th in yards per carry allowed. Carter played on 53 offensive snaps last week compared to Emari Demercado, who was in on just seven snaps. Carter will have some appeal as a FLEX play in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-37b8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf37030000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
