<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:34:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys listed WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-481b-d56e-afff-eefba01a0000</link>
      <description>Flournoy drawing a limited designation to start the week is a surprisingly good sign. The second-year receiver was knocked from Week 16’s game against the Chargers and ruled out almost immediately after leaving the field. It’s too early to say if he’ll be good to go for Week 17 against the Commanders, but it looks like he’s on track to log a few practices before Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-481b-d56e-afff-eefba01a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf has been suspended for two games for “conduct detrimental to the NFL for initiating a physical confrontation with a fan during Sunday’s game against the Lions.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4822-d56e-afff-eeeaed4b0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf will have a chance to appeal the league’s decision and plans to do so, but if the two-game suspension is upheld, the Steelers’ WR1 will miss Week 17 against the Browns and Week 18 against the Ravens. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero notes that Metcalf reported the same fan to security last season after an interaction with the fan while he was with the Seahawks, but things escalated this time, as Metcalf could be seen pulling the fan’s shirt and later swiping at him before walking away. The Steelers currently sit at 9-6 on the season and are in first place in the AFC North. They can secure their spot in the playoffs with a win on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4822-d56e-afff-eeeaed4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed J.J. McCarthy (hand) as DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483a-d35e-a1bf-4dfa7f8b0000</link>
      <description>We are still waiting for an official word on McCarthy’s injury after it was reported earlier that he would undergo an MRI. Monday’s DNP isn’t a good sign for his Week 17 availability against the Lions, but there’s still time for things to change. If he’s unable to go, Max Brosmer would be in line to make his second career start. Brosmer threw four interceptions in his first start and would not be on the fantasy radar in any format if he gets the nod.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483a-d35e-a1bf-4dfa7f8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed Jordan Mason (ankle) as DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483c-d968-a19b-58fd3ab00000</link>
      <description>Mason was carted to the locker room in the Vikings’ Week 16 win over the Giants. A DNP to open the week isn’t a good sign for his Week 17 availability, and his absence would lead to a larger role for Aaron Jones (ankle) if he can suit up. This is only an estimated practice report, we’ll see if Mason’s status changes on Tuesday when the Vikings take the field for the first time on a short week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483c-d968-a19b-58fd3ab00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed Aaron Jones (ankle) as DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf111a0000</link>
      <description>With Jordan Mason (ankle) listed as a DNP to start the week, the Vikings will hope Jones can get on the field for Week 17 against the Lions. Jones rushed 21 times for 85 scoreless yards in Week 16’s win over the Giants, and added another two catches for eight yards. Jones would profile as a fringe RB2/RB3 if he can go this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-483d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf111a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) was listed as a non-participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4854-d968-a19b-58f5d2cf0000</link>
      <description>This makes sense after Bryant was subject to a debilitating hit late in the team’s Week 16 loss to the Jaguars, requiring immobilization and the cart to be removed from the field. We wouldn’t expect him to clear concussion protocol in time to appear against the Chiefs in Week 17, although fantasy managers will want to monitor his status the rest of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4854-d968-a19b-58f5d2cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Rashee Rice (concussion) remains in the league’s concussion protocol Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4856-d56e-afff-eefece680000</link>
      <description>The same can be said of Tyquan Thornton as each wide receiver was listed as a “DNP” on Monday’s estimated practice report. Both players will first need to be asymptomatic before returning to the practice field in some capacity, remain asymptomatic through a full session, and then be cleared by an independent neurologist in order to play on Christmas Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4856-d56e-afff-eefece680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) remained sidelined on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4870-d56e-afff-eef8c7160000</link>
      <description>McDuffie, who missed the team’s Week 16 loss to the Titans, continues to deal with a knee injury sustained in Week 14, which is a massive blow to a defense that operates primarily from nickel. It remains to be seen if McDuffie will make it back this season or if the team will simply place him on season-ending injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4870-d56e-afff-eef8c7160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared RB Isaac Guerendo, WR Ricky Pearsall, DL Robert Beal Jr, DL Kevin Givens, LB Curtis Robinson, CB Renardo Green, and CB Chase Lucas inactive for Week 16 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4874-dc7a-af9b-cfff18140000</link>
      <description>Pearsall’s absence should thrust Kendrick Bourne into a primary perimeter role opposite Jauan Jennings, the latter of whom is likeliest to see his volume boosted slightly. Furthering that potential is the absence of Indianapolis cornerback Sauce Gardner, likely shifting the Colts’ defense back into heavy rates of Cover-3 after utilizing man coverages at one of the highest rates in the league with Gardner on the field this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4874-dc7a-af9b-cfff18140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared CB Sauce Gardner, LB Jaylon Charlies, RB DJ Giddens, WR Anthony Gould, S Reuben Lowery III, TE Will Mallory, and T Bernhard Raimann inactive for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4876-d968-a19b-58f714c60000</link>
      <description>Gardner’s absence is likely the most detrimental after the Colts shifted away from a Cover-3-heavy structure in favor of increased rates of man coverage after acquiring the standout cornerback at the trade deadline. Expect the team to turn back to a Cover-3 base in his stead in what amounts to a must-win game for the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4876-d968-a19b-58f714c60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
