<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders interviewed Vikings defensive coordinator Brian Flores for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be09-d56e-afff-fee938e90000</link>
      <description>Flores also has an interview with the Steelers lined up. Flores’ contract with the Vikings is up, meaning he is free to interview and sign anywhere this offseason. The Vikings are reportedly trying to sign him to a new deal, so he may wind up back in Minnesota despite being a highly-coveted defensive mind. Flores also has a head coaching interview lined up with the Ravens. We would expect him to take any head coaching job he is offered. Flores has been the Vikings’ defensive coordinator for three seasons. They are coming off back-to-back years with a top-10 defense. The team’s lowest finish by points allowed under Flores is 13th.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be09-d56e-afff-fee938e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be19-d56e-afff-fef961080000</link>
      <description>Weaver’s other interview requests in this current hiring cycle have come from the Falcons, Cardinals and Ravens. Weaver, 45, interviewed for the Saints and Bears’ head-coaching vacancies last year and was considered a finalist for the former team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be19-d56e-afff-fef961080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel and former New York Giants head coach Brian Daboll are “at the top” of the Eagles’ list for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be2e-d968-a19b-fefffc1f0000</link>
      <description>Both McDaniel and Daboll are interviewing for head-coaching vacancies elsewhere. Accepting a lesser role with a respected organization like the Eagles could be worth it for the former head coaches. Earlier today, The Philadelphia Inquirer’s David Murphy opined that McDaniel is the “perfect” offensive coordinator candidate for the Eagles. He certainly would bring a fresh offensive perspective.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be2e-d968-a19b-fefffc1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (foot/knee/finger) is practicing in full for the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be35-d56e-afff-fefd4bbe0000</link>
      <description>Allen was never at any risk of missing this game, but it’s still good to see him get in a full practice this early in the week. He took a beating in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jags and was limited in yesterday’s practice. Even against a tough Denver defense, Allen will be the top fantasy quarterback for the upcoming DFS slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be35-d56e-afff-fefd4bbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles reached out to former Giants head coach Brian Daboll about interviewing for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be32-dc7a-af9b-ffbf97260000</link>
      <description>Daboll and former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel are said to be “at the top” of the Eagles’ list for the position. Just yesterday, it was reported that Daboll will interview for the Titans’ head-coaching vacancy, so a lateral move remains possible for him. Signing on with an organization like the Eagles is certainly enticing, though even in a lesser role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be32-dc7a-af9b-ffbf97260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3d-d56e-afff-fefd51ef0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens have completed 10 interviews with potential head coaches and Minter, himself, is up to eight interview requests. He notably served on the Ravens’ defensive coaching staff from 2017-2020 and spent the 2022-2023 seasons with Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh at Michigan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3d-d56e-afff-fefd51ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be37-d35e-a1bf-fff7af590000</link>
      <description>Kincaid was spotted in a walking boot after the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jags. He has been banged up all year, and things won’t be any different in the Divisional Round. He is, however, likely to suit up after getting in a pair of limited practices so far this week. Expect another part-time role for him versus Denver. Just like last week, Kincaid will be a touchdown-or-bust fantasy bet for the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be37-d35e-a1bf-fff7af590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Johnosn (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be45-dc7a-af9b-ffff8d4f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed the Wild Card Round because of the ankle issue. Two DNPs to open this week suggest he will sit for at least one more game. Ray Davis didn’t touch the ball last week and Frank Gore Jr. caught his only target. Johnson’s likely absence will simply mean more snaps for James Cook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be45-dc7a-af9b-ffff8d4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad/calf) is practicing in full for the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be53-dc7a-af9b-ffff7d5d0000</link>
      <description>Prater was listed as a DNP for Tuesday’s walkthrough but should be good to go now. He nailed both of his field goal tries in the Wild Card Round. The Bills will continue to ease his workload with Mitch Wishnowsky handling punts in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be53-dc7a-af9b-ffff7d5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders completed an interview with Seahawks DB coach and pass game coordinator Karl Scott for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf92160000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s John Keim notes that Scott is the Commanders’ only defensive coordinator candidate lacking prior defensive coordinator experience. Scott was brought onboard in his current roles under former head coach Pete Carroll in 2022. While Scott lacks defensive coordinator experience, he has spent the last four seasons learning from two of the NFL’s most well-respected defensive minds in Carroll and current head coach Mike Macdonald.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf92160000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
