<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers placed S DeShon Elliott (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</link>
      <description>Elliott was considered week-to-week with a knee injury he suffered in Week 8 against the Packers. However, with the Steelers acquiring Kyle Dugger from the Patriots, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Elliott will be placed on injured reserve. He will miss a minimum of four games and could return later in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed EDGE Clelin Ferrell to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers continue to add to their pass rush, signing Ferrell to the practice squad after trading for Keion White. Ferrell began his career with the Raiders and has bounced around the last three years, appearing in one game for the Chargers this season. He brings 17.0 career sacks over six seasons to the 49ers practice squad, including 3.5 sacks during a 2023 stint with the 49ers. San Francisco continues to add pass rush depth with Nick Bosa (ACL) out for the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jets S Andre Cisco suffered a pectoral tear in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</link>
      <description>Cisco reportedly tore his pectoral muscle in the Jets’ Week 8 win over the Bengals. The 25-year-old signed with the Jets in the offseason and started all eight games, tallying 41 combined tackles on the season. Cisco’s pectoral tear needs repair and he will be sidelined for some period of time, leaving the Jets to turn to Isaiah Oliver and Tony Adams for help at the safety spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed CB C.J. Gardner-Johnson, formerly of the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</link>
      <description>Gardner-Johnson will reunite with Bears defensive coordinator Dennis Allen, who coached him in New Orleans from 2019 to 2021. The mercurial cornerback will join a Chicago defense that has allowed the NFL’s fourth highest drop back success rate and the second highest completion rate over expected this season. Look for Gardner-Johnson, who has 18 interceptions over 77 NFL games, to primarily play slot corner in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) faces a 4-6 month recovery period.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</link>
      <description>The dislocated ankle Skattebo suffered in Week 8 against the Eagles came with a fibula fracture and deltoid ligament rupture, according to Rapoport. The rookie was taken to a local hospital and underwent season-ending surgery. Rapoport seems confident Skattebo will be ready for the team’s offseason program, though his recovery will be worth tracking in the coming months. Tyrone Tracy will take over as the Giants’ lead back in Skattebo’s absence. Tracy had 39 yards on ten rushes and two catches for 14 yards against the Eagles last Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB John Wolford, formerly of the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</link>
      <description>Wolford will join the team’s practice squad ahead of Minnesota’s Week 9 game against the Lions. The Vikings last week lost Carson Wentz to a season-ending shoulder injury and will be forced to start J.J. McCarthy in Week 9. McCarthy has missed nearly two months with an ankle injury. Wolford will likely serve as the team’s QB3 behind McCarthy and Max Brosmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio believes the Eagles are “shopping A.J. Brown without officially shopping” him ahead of the NFL’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</link>
      <description>Florio said he’s heard of several contending teams that are interested in acquiring Brown if the Eagles are willing to part with the star wideout. That includes, per Florio, the Patriots, whose head coach — Mike Vrabel — coached Brown in Tennessee. “This to me feels like an effort by the Eagles to shop A.J. Brown without shopping A.J. Brown, to wait for the phone to ring, to not be the one who picks up the phone” to engage in trade talks before the November 4 league deadline. “Something’s been going on there,” Florio said of Brown, who has complained for years about his lack of opportunities in the run-heavy Philadelphia offense. Brown’s fantasy prospects would see a slight bump if he were to land with a more pass-first team, and his exit from the Eagles offense would make DeVonta Smith a borderline elite fantasy option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers opened the 21-day practice window for G Chandler Zavala (knee).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</link>
      <description>Zavala has been on injured reserve with a knee injury since October 1. The Panthers, struggling to protect the passer in recent weeks, could use Zavala back in action this week against a ferocious Packers front seven. Pro Football Focus grades Carolina’s offensive line as the 12th worst pass blocking unit through Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Flacco’s (shoulder) Week 9 status is “up in the air.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</link>
      <description>Flacco is dealing with an AC joint sprain, per Rapoport. He sustained the injury late in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss against the Jets and could miss this week’s game against the Bears. That would force Jake Browning back under center for the Bengals, a huge hit to the fantasy prospects of every Cincy pass catcher, including Ja’Marr Chase. Fantasy managers should keep a close eye on Flacco’s Thursday and Friday practice status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed TE Marcedes Lewis, formerly of the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</link>
      <description>The Broncos are looking for some tight end depth with Nate Adkins potentially missing time with injury. Lewis, 41, has played 19 NFL seasons. He has six receptions over his past three years in the league. It’s safe to say he won’t have any fantasy usefulness in Denver’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
