<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea1c-d94a-a79d-eb1d2dc10000</link>
      <description>Pearsall remains out with a knee injury after missing all of last week’s practices as well. He has missed the 49ers’ last two games and is now trending to miss Week 7 against the Falcons. Also out was WR Skyy Moore (ankle). With Jauan Jennings (ankle/rib/shoulder) playing through injury, Kendrick Bourne is in line to be the No. 1 wideout for the 49ers this week, unless Pearsall can return to practice in some capacity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea1c-d94a-a79d-eb1d2dc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/rib/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea22-def2-abdb-ff63ef170000</link>
      <description>Jennings told reporters Sunday that he is playing with five broken ribs and high and low ankle sprains. Adding a shoulder injury to his practice designation, Jennings is far from 100-percent. The injuries will hinder the 28-year-old from being the team’s No. 1 wideout and though he will likely play through them, Jennings is at best a FLEX option for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea22-def2-abdb-ff63ef170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea28-def2-abdb-ff69fc8c0000</link>
      <description>Mooney has been out since injuring his hamstring in Week 4 and did not log a practice last week. He returns to start out Week 7 practicing in a limited capacity. The 27-year-old field-stretcher has seven receptions for 79 yards in three games this season and holds low-end WR3 value when healthy. If Mooney does return against the 49ers, Drake London would take a hit from fantasy WR1 down to high-end WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea28-def2-abdb-ff69fc8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Ashton Dulin (chest) did not participate in Wednesdays’ practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea35-dd4c-afb9-eff56be90000</link>
      <description>Dulin took over the WR4 role for the Colts in Week 6, though he did not record a target against the Cardinals. Interestingly enough, he did record a pass rush rep on defense. He starts out this week not practicing due to a chest injury. With Josh Downs (concussion) also out, Adonai Mitchell might find his way back into the lineup Week 7 against the Chargers. Also out for Wednesday was RB Tyler Goodson (groin).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea35-dd4c-afb9-eff56be90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip/groin) did not participate in Wednesday’s walk-thru practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea3f-d94a-a79d-eb3fb99e0000</link>
      <description>Moore spent the night in a hospital after the Bears’ Monday night win over the Commanders due to a groin issue. He now is listed as a non-participant with hip and groin issues for the Bears’ Wednesday walk-thru. Though he played the full game on Monday, the hospitalization and short week for a Sunday showdown against the Saints is reason to believe he may miss Week 7. If Moore cannot go, Luther Burden is in line for more opportunities as a potential FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea3f-d94a-a79d-eb3fb99e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Brashard Smith (illness) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea44-def2-abdb-ff650bda0000</link>
      <description>Smith has been the Chiefs’ No. 3 running back and is mainly a pass-catcher out of the backfield. He misses practice to start the week, though he was listed with an illness. Smith should still be good to go for Week 7 as long as he can practice later in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea44-def2-abdb-ff650bda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea45-db72-a199-fa4fe6120000</link>
      <description>Meyers was listed as a non-participant with knee and toe injuries. The 28-year-old has had a disappointing stretch of games, with three straight games under 40 yards. He is rumored to be on the trade block as the trade deadline approaches soon, but Meyers is now dealing with knee and toe injuries as well. Fantasy managers should stay tuned to see if Meyers can practice the rest of the week; both his Week 7 status and status as a Raider are in question. Tre Tucker and Jack Bech will see a boost if Meyers does not suit up for Las Vegas this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea45-db72-a199-fa4fe6120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea4e-d94a-a79d-eb4f6c5e0000</link>
      <description>It is becoming increasingly likely that Bowers sits until after the Raiders’ Week 8 bye. Fantasy managers have not gotten the expected production out of an injured Bowers and will now have to pivot as he continues to miss time. Michael Mayer is now the sole No. 1 tight end for the Raiders and will be a low-end TE1 in Week 7 should Bowers remain out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea4e-d94a-a79d-eb4f6c5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea5c-db72-a199-fa5fcda10000</link>
      <description>Watson is nearing a return from the PUP list after tearing his ACL late last season. He was limited in last week’s practices and not activated for Week 6, but starts out Week 7 logging another limited session. Watson will likely need a full practice before he is officially activated and certainly could get there for this week’s matchup against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea5c-db72-a199-fa5fcda10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Jordy Nelson upheld Lions S Brian Branch’s one-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea62-dd4c-afb9-efe39e980000</link>
      <description>Branch was given a one-game suspension by the NFL for starting an on-field fight between the Chiefs and Lions on Sunday night. Nelson, best known for his career as a wide receiver with the Packers, was jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA to hear Branch’s appeal. He upholds the suspension, keeping Branch out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea62-dd4c-afb9-efe39e980000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
