<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:02:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Smith was not targeted in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f888-dc7a-af9b-ffbff0200000</link>
      <description>What Smith did do was lose his footing on a punt return, letting the ball bounce off his chest and arms and right to the Seahawks. It immediately led to a touchdown in what finished as a four-point loss. Kyren Williams replaced Smith afterwards. Smith battled Tutu Atwell for a roster spot all season and eventually won out because of his work on special teams. Welp. An exclusive rights free agent in 2026, Smith was mostly a shot-play weapon and doesn’t figure to have a real fantasy role next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f888-dc7a-af9b-ffbff0200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Mevis made his only field-goal attempt in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f88c-dc7a-af9b-ffbfd3f00000</link>
      <description>Mevis finishes the year 12-of-13 on field goals — missing one against the Seahawks in Week 16 — and hit all 39 of his regular season extra point attempts. He was perfect in the playoffs on five field goals and nine extra-point attempts. The 23-year-old was a find for the Rams and should enter the starting kicker conversation in most fantasy leagues that use kickers in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f88c-dc7a-af9b-ffbfd3f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Philip Rivers has withdrawn his name from consideration for the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa69-d35e-a1bf-ffebedcd0000</link>
      <description>Less than 24 hours ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that the interest between Rivers was“real” and “not a joke.”Now, Rivers is officially out of the search, removing himself from consideration after his first interview. This shouldn’t be an indictment on Rivers or the Bills, but it’s clear he wasn’t ready to move into full-time head-coaching duties just yet. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo notes that a head coaching gig could be in his future but added “now isn’t the right time for him and his family.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa69-d35e-a1bf-ffebedcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Bills are expected to interview Broncos pass game coordinator Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa73-d968-a19b-faf31dae0000</link>
      <description>Webb doesn’t have any experience as an offensive play-caller, but he does have close ties to Buffalo. The former QB turned coach spent three seasons with the Bills from 2019 to 2021, and is a close friend of Josh Allen, which could give him an inside edge on landing the job. Webb got his start in coaching in 2023 with the Broncos as their quarterbacks coach, and added the role of pass game coordinator to his resumé this season. He’s also considered a “prime candidate” for the Raiders head-coaching job, so Webb has multiple suitors. Whether or not he lands a gig is still to be determined, but there’s no denying he’s viewed as an up-and-comer in coaching circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa73-d968-a19b-faf31dae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed Dolphins OC Frank Smith for the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fab4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf458d0000</link>
      <description>Smith served as the Dolphins’ offensive coordinator from 2022 to 2025 and was named the NFL’s top offensive coordinator in 2023. The longtime coach did not serve as the Dolphins’ primary play-caller under former head coach Mike McDaniel, but his time with the team has earned him multiple interviews over the years. Smith is one of multiple offensive coordinator candidates to meet with the Eagles, who are hoping to improve after ranking 19th in points scored and 24th in total yards last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fab4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf458d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars OC Grant Udinski withdrew his name from consideration for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</link>
      <description>Udinski becomes the third coach to remove his name from consideration for the Browns job, joining Mike McDaniel and Jesse Minter. Udinski was a finalist for the job, but is now eyeing the Bills as a potential landing spot for his first head coaching gig. If he doesn’t join the Bills, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Udinski and the Jaguars already have a new deal in place for him to remain with the team. Udinski, 30, has emerged as one of the hottest names on the market and would become the youngest head coach in NFL history if hired by the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans QB coach Jerrod Johnson will interview for the Eagles’ offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</link>
      <description>Johnson interviewed for the Dolphins’ offensive-coordinator vacancy earlier this month but ultimately lost out to Bobby Slowik. Johnson has served as the Texans’ quarterbacks coach since 2023, and worked with the Colts (2020-2021) and Vikings before that. Should he leave for Philly, Johnson, who has never served as an offensive coordinator, would benefit from having proven veterans like Jalen Hurts and Saquon Barkley already in the building.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears offensive coordinator has removed his name from the Eagles’ offensive-coordinator search.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb09-d56e-afff-ffe9c3680000</link>
      <description>Doyle won’t be making the lateral move to Philly. The opportunity to join the Eagles did come with play-calling duties, something Doyle doesn’t have in Chicago, but the 30-year-old coach who landed his first OC role this offseason will remain with the Bears for 2026, taking more time to learn under Ben Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb09-d56e-afff-ffe9c3680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver is having a second interview with the Cardinals for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb15-d35e-a1bf-ffd7d2850000</link>
      <description>Weaver remains one of the hottest names in the league’s head coaching searches. The 45-year-old coach recently had a second interview with the Steelers, and was also a finalist for the Ravens’ job before they opted to go with Jesse Minter. He was also a finalist for the Saints’ head coaching job last year. Weaver has spent the last two seasons as the Dolphins’ defensive coordinator and was previously with the Ravens from 2021-2023. It seems like only a matter of time before he secures his first head-coaching gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb15-d35e-a1bf-ffd7d2850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers hired former Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb2f-d968-a19b-fbffff830000</link>
      <description>McDaniel continued to entertain head coaching offers even after it was rumored he would join the Chargers. Now, after much deliberation, McDaniel is officially joining the Chargers to pair with Justin Herbert and company. McDaniel’s offense finished 11th or better in points scored in two of his four seasons with the Dolphins, but his final two seasons proved forgettable as Tua Tagovailoa’s limitations became apparent and defenses took advantage. McDaniel gets a top-flight QB and talent young playmakers in Ladd McConkey and Omarion Hampton to help guide his offense into 2026. All will make for enticing fantasy picks, and Herbert should enjoy a bounce back if his offensive line can stay healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb2f-d968-a19b-fbffff830000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
