<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said “I didn’t do a good enough job of [getting Tetairoa McMillan the ball] last week and we’ll make sure that that comes alive.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc9-dc7a-af9b-efff2c690000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers who started McMillan in Week 17 are wondering if this could have been brought to Canales’ attention before yesterday’s 1/5 dud. Carolina’s passing game appears to go through fits and starts. McMillan remains a good WR2 bet for those of you playing in Week 18 leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc9-dc7a-af9b-efff2c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn told reporters that it’s “still a stretch” that Marcus Mariota (quad/Hand) plays in Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd1-d56e-afff-eff964520000</link>
      <description>Quinn did say that “there’s still hope” that Mariota can get back on the field for the finale against Philadelphia. Assuming Mariota isn’t able to get back on the field, it’ll be Josh Johnson under center again for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd1-d56e-afff-eff964520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A “prominent NFL agent” told The Athletic’s Mike Sando that “The biggest story of the offseason is going to be Lamar [Jackson]. That is going to be crazy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bcf-d35e-a1bf-6fcf65c00000</link>
      <description>Jackson did not agree to a contract extension with the Ravens ahead of the season and is set to have a $74.5 million cap hit in 2026, a year in which the Ravens have plenty of other contracts to get ahead of. We don’t necessarily know if we believe a Lamar Jackson trade will be a big offseason storyline, but it’s not the first time the sourced have brought us the idea of a Lamar Jackson trade this December — Dan Graziano and Jeremy Fowler talked about it last week. Certainly between his injury-plagued and disappointing season, the fact that he is his own agent, and the fact that he turns 29 in January, there is room for a value disagreement between the Ravens and Jackson. You can see how both sides could come to the understanding that their futures would be better apart. Usually cooler heads prevail. It’s certainly worth noticing that there is some potential for a Jackson trade this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bcf-d35e-a1bf-6fcf65c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles coach Nick Sirianni said “we’re still thinking through” whether the team would play their starters in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd9-d56e-afff-eff91d8e0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles can climb as high as the No. 2 seed, guaranteeing themselves a game against the Packers in the Wild Card round and getting a second home game should they advance. Meanwhile, the No. 6 seed will be the third-place NFC West squad. Philadelphia is locked into No. 2 or No. 3. Ultimately, with Josh Johnson on the other sideline, the Eagles probably have a little room to dabble with Tanner McKee if they really want to in Week 18. It doesn’t sound like we’ll know for sure until Wednesday or Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd9-d56e-afff-eff91d8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons elvated WR Chris Blair and EDGE Khalid Kareem from the practice squad for Week 17 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd4-d35e-a1bf-6fd680990000</link>
      <description>Blair was also up for Week 16 against the Cardinals, and played nine total snaps. He’ll likely see a similiar amount of playing time Monday against Los Angeles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd4-d35e-a1bf-6fd680990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (foot) is “dealing with some soreness” and is “maybe in a slightly better spot” than he was last week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bf6-d968-a19b-7bf711da0000</link>
      <description>McDermott said that it is “too early in the week” to share who is playing and who is not against the Jets. Buffalo can finish as high as the No. 5 seed, but would only host a playoff game if chaos ensued in the AFC bracket. They also are probably a fair bet to beat the Jets even with some backups on the field. Allen’s status sounds like it’s yet to be fully determined, but if the Bills do decide to play him, fantasy managers shouldn’t have any hesitation jamming in the lineup beyond the fact that he could get pulled early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bf6-d968-a19b-7bf711da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans activated WR Justin Watson (Achilles) off injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bf2-dc7a-af9b-efff52330000</link>
      <description>Watson will get his first chance to play since being placed on injured reserve in the middle of September. The 29-year-old wideout will be a depth piece for the finale against the Colts and Houston’s postseason run. Solomon Byrd was waived to make room on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bf2-dc7a-af9b-efff52330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Terrel Bernard (calf) will not play in Buffalo’s Week 18 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bfa-dc7a-af9b-efff5f4d0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t bode well for his playoff status either. Bernard left Week 17’s game against the Eagles and was questionable to return, but never did. Bernard has only played in 11 games this year while dealing with a number of injuries. He has 65 tackles and three passes defensed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bfa-dc7a-af9b-efff5f4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers HC Jim Harbaugh told reporters that Justin Herbert (hand) will not start in Week 18 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bfa-dc7a-af9b-efffe75d0000</link>
      <description>Herbert took a beating against the Texans in Week 16 and looked to be in significant pain at the end of that contest, and the Chargers don’t have much to play for in the finale before the playoffs. It’ll likely be Trey Lance starting against Denver, and his dual-threat ability makes his an intriguing — but risky — fantasy play for that finale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bfa-dc7a-af9b-efffe75d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Marvin Harrison (heel) “hurt his other foot” in Week 17’s loss and will play in Week 18 “if he is healthy enough to play.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6c18-d56e-afff-eef8a5190000</link>
      <description>It certainly seems like forcing Harrison to play through this heel injury isn’t helping anybody — he’s caught one ball in two games since returning, leaving each of them early — but Gannon refused to rule it out. Either way, Trey McBride and Michael Wilson are the Cardinals you actually want to start in fantasy leagues in Week 18. Harrison would be hard to trust if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6c18-d56e-afff-eef8a5190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
