<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:09:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (ankle) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</link>
      <description>Winters did not practice Wednesday or Thursday and was not seen by media on Friday. The 49ers will give him every hour he can to be healthy as he’s the main incumbent with a chance to play this week. If not, the 49ers will have to turn to Eric Kendricks, Garret Wallow, and possibly new signing Kyzir White in the middle against the Eagles. CB Renardo Green (foot) and DE Keion White (groin/hamstring) are also questionable for the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Bears assistant GM Ian Cunningham for their “president of football” position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4c7-d968-a19b-fcf71f0c0000</link>
      <description>We assume that Cunningham is a front runner to be whatever they want to call him in the front office in Atlanta, we’ll stick with “guy who picks the players” next to Matt Ryan’s Tony Boselli-esque role with the club. Cunningham had been reported to be interviewing for the GM job, not the “president of football” gig. Regardless, he’s a front runner for a job in this front office and the Falcons are the last GM gig still available after the Dolphins filled their vacancy earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4c7-d968-a19b-fcf71f0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions scheduled an interview with Seahawks passing game coordinator Jake Peetz for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-dc7a-af9b-efbf48df0000</link>
      <description>Peetz spent the 2022 season working under Rams head coach Sean McVay as an offensive assistant before being promoted to passing game assistant in 2023. He has served in his current role with the Seahawks since 2024. Lions executive vice president and general manager Brad Holmes spent 2003-2020 as a member of the Rams’ personnel department before accepting his current role in Detroit. Peetz is a natural fit for this job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-dc7a-af9b-efbf48df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions and Commanders scheduled interviews with Ravens QB coach Tee Martin for their offensive coordinator vacancies next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</link>
      <description>Per Jordan Schultz, “has done extensive work for Baltimore’s passing game as a whole” over the last three seasons, “helping propel Lamar Jackson to the 2023 NFL MVP.” Martin coach the Ravens’ wide receivers in the two prior seasons. These are the first reported interviews scheduled for Martin this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders hired David Blough as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</link>
      <description>The former NFL quarterback was on the Lions’ practice squad as recently as 2023. Blough, 30, has just two years of coaching experience, both with the Commanders as their assistant quarterbacks coach. The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala notes that Blough “helped fill in when QBs coach Tavita Pritchard left for Stanford” in November. The Commanders were evidently impressed with Blough’s ability to rise to the occasion. The Lions had requested an interview with Blough for their vacant offensive coordinator role earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers are expected to interview Falcons OC Zac Robinson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a507-d35e-a1bf-e5c778da0000</link>
      <description>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud notes that Robinson spent five seasons with the Rams, “rising from assistant quarterbacks coach to passing game coordinator/QB coach” under head coach Sean McVay. Robinson served as the Falcons’ offensive coordinator from 2024-2025. The Falcons notably denied the Cowboys’ request to interview DC Jeff Ulbrich for their defensive coordinator vacancy. Perhaps, things will work out differently for Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a507-d35e-a1bf-e5c778da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys completed their interview with Browns S coach Ephraim Banda for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a542-dc7a-af9b-efff54f50000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys completed two defensive coordinator interviews today, having met with Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones earlier on. Tomorrow, they are set to speak with Broncos assistant head coach and defensive passing game coordinator Jim Leonhard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a542-dc7a-af9b-efff54f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State S Caleb Downs declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a566-d35e-a1bf-e5e661770000</link>
      <description>Downs began his college career at Alabama in 2023. He transferred to Ohio State the following season and helped the Buckeyes win the 2024 College Football Playoff Championship. In 2023, he was a second-team All-American, the SEC Freshman of the Year and first-team All-SEC. In both 2024 and 2025, Downs was a Unanimous All-American, the Big Ten Defensive Back of the Year and earned first-team All-Big Ten honors. In 2025 alone, he won the Lott Trophy and Jim Thorpe Award. The Athletic’s James Boyd notes Downs is Colts WR Josh Downs’ younger brother and “is widely considered to be a potential top-10 pick.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a566-d35e-a1bf-e5e661770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ Pro Football Talk reports that the arraignment in Patriots WR Stefon Diggs’ criminal case “has been delayed from January 23 until February 13.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a58d-dc7a-af9b-efbf16370000</link>
      <description>The arraignment will now occur five days after Super Bowl LX, making it “virtually certain,” per Mike Florio, that the NFL will not place Diggs on the commissioner exempt list before the Super Bowl. Diggs is “the subject of a criminal complaint” that accuses him of “felony strangulation or suffocation and misdemeanor assault and battery.” Nothing is guaranteed, but it appears as though Diggs will be available for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a58d-dc7a-af9b-efbf16370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed their interview with Matt Ryan for their president of football vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a5de-dc7a-af9b-efffaefa0000</link>
      <description>ESPN previously reported that “many believe” the position was “created” for Ryan. It is safe to say he is the favorite to land the role. Per team owner Arthur Blank, the president of football will lead the interview process as the team searches for its new head coach and general manager. Both positions will report directly to the president of football, who reports directly to Blank. The trio “will work collaboratively as a football leadership team on all football decisions.” While the head coach and general manager “remain the primary decision-makers” in their respective roles, “final decision-making authority will rest with the president of football.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a5de-dc7a-af9b-efffaefa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
