<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 5-of-9 targets for 55 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 9 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d21-d45b-affe-5db7e1600000</link>
      <description>McBride took a backseat to Marvin Harrison Jr. in the first half, with the team appearing intent on getting the second-year receiver going early by feeding him four targets on their first possession. He would find paint to start the third quarter from 12 yards out for his fifth score of the season, just one fewer receiving touchdown than he compiled in his first three years in the league combined. McBride remains an elite fantasy asset ahead of a divisional showdown with the Seahawks in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d21-d45b-affe-5db7e1600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 3-of-4 targets for 61 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 9 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d26-d45b-affe-5db6d6a20000</link>
      <description>Wilson checked in second on the team in receiving on the back of a 50-yard reception on the first play from scrimmage of the second half, leading to a touchdown that allowed the Cardinals to double down on the Cowboys around the half to break the game open. Wilson continues to start opposite Marvin Harrison Jr. in two-wide alignments but generally lacks enough weekly volume to be a consistent fantasy contributor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d26-d45b-affe-5db6d6a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 24-of-39 passes for 250 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Cowboys’ 27-17, Week 9 loss to the Cardinals, adding 34 yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d2a-d673-a39e-edbb64cd0000</link>
      <description>Mistakes on offense were the deciding factor for the Cowboys, who turned the ball over on downs twice in the red zone in addition to the three turnovers committed. Even through all the struggles, the Dallas defense blocked a punt and returned it for a touchdown to be down only 10-7 in the second quarter. The wheels fell off after the Cowboys allowed the Cardinals to double them up around the half to go up 24-7 just two minutes after the break. The Cowboys appeared to be threatening late but an ill-timed fumble from running back Javonte Williams sealed the game for the Cardinals in the fourth quarter. The Cowboys fall to 3-5-1 and are now 2.5-games behind the division-leading Eagles as they head to their bye. They next take the field on the road in Week 11 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d2a-d673-a39e-edbb64cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams rushed 15 times for 83 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals, adding one reception for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d30-d45b-affe-5db642450000</link>
      <description>Williams ran hard and saw all but one running back opportunity on a night the team made rookie Jaydon Blue a healthy inactive, leaving only Malik Davis as backfield depth. That hard work was overshadowed by a fourth quarter fumble as the team was driving the field to attempt to close a 10-point deficit, effectively sealing the game for the Cardinals in the process. Williams has vastly outperformed preseason expectations in a both the real world and a fantasy setting, and he should remain a consistent RB2 when the Cowboys return from their bye to face the Raiders on the road in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d30-d45b-affe-5db642450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 7-of-12 targets for 85 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d33-d45b-affe-5db7e1bf0000</link>
      <description>Lamb was mostly unable to shake loose from tight coverage outside of a 33-yard gain on a scramble drill in the second half. Both his 12 targets and 85 yards led the team on a night the Cowboys notched just 333 yards of total offense, but two turnovers on downs in the red zone and three giveaways capped his fantasy upside. The Cowboys now head to their bye week losers of three of their last four games, now sitting 2.5-games behind the division-leading Eagles in the NFC East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d33-d45b-affe-5db7e1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 6-of-9 targets for 79 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d37-d45b-affe-5db7e7610000</link>
      <description>Pickens finished second on the team in targets, receptions, and yards behind alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb but was held out of the end zone, capping his fantasy upside on a night the team turned the ball over on downs twice inside the red zone and committed three giveaways. He was flagged for unsportsmanlike conduct following a six-yard reception on the team’s penultimate possession as they looked to claw back from a 10-point deficit, highlighting his weekly range of outcomes as a player that still needs to mature. The Cowboys head to their bye week losers of three of their last four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d37-d45b-affe-5db7e7610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-7 targets for 50 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d3c-d713-ad9e-6d7c66740000</link>
      <description>Fantasy’s overall TE1 through the first half of the season went through a four-game stretch where he scored six times but has since been targeted only eight times in two games. He is likely to continue to go as the team goes with his most recent poor outings both coming in losses where the Cowboys were held to 24 points or fewer. He was targeted in the red zone once in this one but an overthrow from quarterback Dak Prescott in the face of pressure hit off the veteran tight end’s hands and fell incomplete. The truth likely lies somewhere in the middle for Ferguson, who is equal parts unlikely to finish the season atop the tight end ranks as he is to continue his recent downswing in production. Fantasy managers will need a fill-in in Week 10 as the Cowboys head to their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d3c-d713-ad9e-6d7c66740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Flournoy caught both targets for 12 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d44-d713-ad9e-6d54ddb00000</link>
      <description>His touchdown came in the fourth quarter with the team down 27-10, but it was arguably his catch earlier in the drive that was more worthy of a highlight reel. He managed to hang on through full arm extension in tight coverage and through contact to extend the drive that would ultimately lead to his touchdown. Flournoy isn’t playing enough snaps to warrant weekly fantasy consideration but remains a name to watch should another injury occur to someone ahead of him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d44-d713-ad9e-6d54ddb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys acquired LB Logan Wilson from the Bengals in exchange for a seventh-round draft pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f1b-d45b-affe-5f9f3b290000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are looking to salvage their season with a defensive boost after being shredded by Jacoby Brissett and the Cardinals on Monday night. Wilson, 29, has two years remaining on a four-year, $36 million extension he signed with the Bengals in July 2023. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Cowboys did not “rework his deal to facilitate a trade.” Thomas, who was benched by the Bengals in Week 6, will join a Cowboys defense that ranks second in QB pressure rate while giving up the fifth most yards per play through Week 9. Dallas has allowed the second highest rate of possessions that end with a score.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f1b-d45b-affe-5f9f3b290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said QB Kyler Murray remains the team’s starter when healthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f51-d45b-affe-5fd726640000</link>
      <description>Gannon committed to Murray after Monday night’s upset win over the Cowboys and Arizona’s best three-game offensive stretch in memory. Jacoby Brissett has averaged 88 more passing yards per game than Murray this season, turning Marvin Harrison Jr. into a weekly top-12 fantasy play and Trey McBride into an elite, touchdown-scoring weapon. The Cardinals, for better or worse, are committed to Murray based on salary alone, even if the team’s offense is markedly worse with Murray, among the NFL’s worst passers. Murray, purportedly dealing with a serious foot injury, practiced throughout last week but did not get the start against Dallas. Arizona plays the Seahawks in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f51-d45b-affe-5fd726640000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
