<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:01:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released WR/KR Ihmir Smith-Marsette.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e749-de13-afdc-e7cbe0c30000</link>
      <description>Ihmir Smith-Marsette fared well as a returner in the preseason, averaging 23.0 yards per kick return and 10.0 yards per punt return. He could be a practice squad candidate for the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e749-de13-afdc-e7cbe0c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints released DE Jonah Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e738-dbe3-a9bb-f77b369b0000</link>
      <description>Williams was signed in March as a depth piece, but his stay in New Orleans appears to be a short one. The 6-foot-5, 275-pound defender could find a new home before the start of the 2025 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e738-dbe3-a9bb-f77b369b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears waived WR Tyler Scott.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e742-de13-afdc-e7cb4f770000</link>
      <description>Scott was squeezed out of playing time in 2024 after the Bears brought in DJ Moore, Keenan Allen and Rome Odunze, and further squeezed out of the picture this year by the additions of Luther Burden and Olamide Zaccheaus. He has 459 NFL snaps in two seasons and is only 24. Scott played 109 snaps this preseason and registered a 67.8 PFF offensive grade. Scott could catch eyes on the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e742-de13-afdc-e7cb4f770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived RB Deuce Vaughn.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e75b-db7b-a5dd-e75f233d0000</link>
      <description>Vaughn had six carries for 37 yards in Week 18 last year, but hasn’t played more than 22 offensive snaps in a regular season game yet. He’s performed well in preseason play and is likely a practice squad candidate — he had a 67.6 PFF run grade in 52 snaps this year. This may be a sign that Dallas plans to keep Miles Sanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e75b-db7b-a5dd-e75f233d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints acquired T Asim Richards and a 2028 seventh-round pick from the Cowboys for a 2028 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e76d-db7b-a5dd-e76d02cf0000</link>
      <description>Another tackle trade goes down. Richards will likely fill a swing tackle role behind Kelvin Banks and Taliese Fuaga. Richards played 111 snaps for the Saints this preseason and had a 75.5 PFF pass block grade. He started a game for the Cowboys last year and appeared in 21 others in his two seasons with the team. This is the first noted exchange of 2028 draft picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e76d-db7b-a5dd-e76d02cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions released S Morice Norris.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e772-d332-a1fd-f776f9630000</link>
      <description>Norris was injured in the team’s first preseason game when his head snapped back on a tackle. The game was suspended before Norris was reported to be in stable condition following the scary on-field incident. He was making a push to crack the final 53-man roster in Detroit prior to the injury but will now be subject to the waiver process before he can return on the team’s practice squad while he heals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e772-d332-a1fd-f776f9630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (hamstring) will avoid opening the season on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e754-db7b-a5dd-e7541e280000</link>
      <description>The Bears have not changed their stance on Johnson’s expected return date, so he is theoretically on track to suit up against the Vikings in Week 1. He was initially sidelined in July, however, and he has not yet returned to practice. Bears cornerbacks are tasked with containing Justin Jefferson in prime time on Monday night to open the season. They will have a tough time doing so if their star coverage defender is absent or playing at less than full health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e754-db7b-a5dd-e7541e280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released Jeff Wilson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e77d-db7b-a5dd-e77d6e120000</link>
      <description>Wilson was signed in early August, but with the trade of Brian Robinson to the 49ers, Wilson figured to be no higher than fourth on the depth chart at the moment. It wouldn’t be surprising if Wilson resurfaced with the 49ers after initial cuts are done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e77d-db7b-a5dd-e77d6e120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released DT Casey Rogers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e755-db7b-a5dd-e75544830000</link>
      <description>Rogers was signed in May after being waived by the Giants. He’s a practice squad candidate who could see time with the Bills if he doesn’t procure a job with a new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e755-db7b-a5dd-e75544830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released S Darrick Forrest.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-db7b-a5dd-e7868cd60000</link>
      <description>Forrest played extensively throughout the preseason, which was a bad sign. He registered four tackles for his efforts. Forrest will likely sign onto a practice squad, if not an active roster elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-db7b-a5dd-e7868cd60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
