<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</link>
      <description>As expected, Adams was listed with a DNP for the Rams’ Tuesday walkthrough. Sean McVay did not rule Adams out for Thursday’s game against the Seahawks and said he could be a game-time decision. Adams re-aggravated his hamstring injury in Week 15 and getting healthy on a short week will be difficult. Colby Parkinson emerges as a red zone target for the Rams if Adams is out for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes Giants QB Jaxson Dart “has a target on his back as a runner.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28e6-d8cf-affb-bceeb9880000</link>
      <description>Duggan pointed to comments from Commanders head coach Dan Quinn ahead of Washington’s Week 15 game against Dart and the Giants as evidence that New York opponents are targeting Dart based on his willingness to take big hits, even to the head. “The quarterback is a very competitive dual-threat guy. He will try to run the ball like a running back,” Quinn told his defense last week. “He will try to run you over. He will try to stiff-arm. He doesn’t really run out of bounds. He doesn’t slide a whole bunch. We can get the ball off of him.” Dart took yet another shot to the head in the Giants’ Week 15 loss to the Commanders and was checked for a concussion before re-entering the ballgame. Dart has missed time with brain injuries this season and continues to lower his head as a rusher in the open field. It’s something he’ll need to change if he wants to have a long NFL career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28e6-d8cf-affb-bceeb9880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed TE Jeremy Ruckert to a two-year contract extension worth $10 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2cb3-d77b-adfb-eeb3ad890000</link>
      <description>The new deal includes a maximum of $11 over the 2026 and 2027 seasons. Ruckert, drafted by the Jets in 2022, has 55 receptions on 75 targets over four NFL seasons, including 20 catches for 163 yards and a touchdown in 2025. Ruckert has seen some more involvement in the Jets offense of late, recording two receptions in each of the past three contests. The team’s commitment to Ruckert could raise questions about how the Jets see TE Mason Taylor, a rookie with 44 receptions for 369 yards and a score this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2cb3-d77b-adfb-eeb3ad890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins QB Quinn Ewers will start in Week 16.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d08-d005-a9bf-fd3cb1b20000</link>
      <description>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel meant it when he said everything was on the table after Miami’s humiliating Monday night loss to the Steelers. Tua Tagovailoa will take a seat in Week 16 — and perhaps beyond — after his dismal play throughout 2025. Tagovailoa ranks 27th out of 33 qualifying quarterbacks in adjusted yards per attempt, 14th in drop back success rate, and 26th in EPA per drop back through Week 15. He has just three TD passes over his past four games in the run-heavy Miami offense. Ewers in the preseason completed 23 of 43 attempts for 273 yards and two touchdowns. He was sacked on nearly half of his pressures. Ewers should be considered a fringe superflex option for Week 16 against a miserable Bengals defense allowing two passing scores per game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d08-d005-a9bf-fd3cb1b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa was benched in favor of Quinn Ewers for Week 16 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d0f-d005-a9bf-fd3fcd490000</link>
      <description>The move comes after the Dolphins’ crushing defeat against the Steelers on Monday night. Tagovailoa’s struggles have persisted for the better part of two seasons, and this year he ranks 27th out of 33 qualifying quarterbacks in adjusted yards per attempt, 14th in drop back success rate, and 26th in EPA per drop back. Since losing Tyreek Hill to a season-ending leg injury in September, Tua is one of the least efficient QBs in the league. His contract with Miami doesn’t have a potential out until 2027, meaning the team might have no choice but to pay him $56.4 million in 2026 even if he’s not the starter. There won’t be many teams inquiring about Tua’s services after he was thoroughly exposed in the absence of the game-breaking Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d0f-d005-a9bf-fd3fcd490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released EDGE Matthew Judon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d19-d77b-adfb-ef9bb35f0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are moving on from entrenched veterans with their season officially over following Monday night’s blowout loss to the Steelers. The team benched QB Tua Tagovailoa on Wednesday shortly after releasing Judon, who a ten-year veteran pass rusher who has just 9.5 sacks over the past three seasons combined. In Judon’s 13 appearances with the Dolphins, Judon racked up 19 combined tackles, one tackle for loss and three quarterback hits. He did not have a sack over those 13 games. Judon will almost certainly sign with a contending team in need of a rotational pass rusher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d19-d77b-adfb-ef9bb35f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d39-d8cf-affb-bd3b1fb60000</link>
      <description>It’s a positive sign for London’s Week 16 availability against the Cardinals, though head coach Raheem Morris cautioned against assuming London will play Sunday. “Looking forward to seeing how much he’ll be able to give us this week,” Morris told reporters Wednesday. London has bee sidelined with a knee injury since the middle of November. The Falcons, eliminated from postseason contention, don’t have much reason to rush back (or play) their star receiver in the season’s final weeks. If London suits up in Week 16, he will be an elite option against an Arizona secondary that has been shredded of late. London’s return would put something of a damper on Kyle Pitts’ emergence and would make David Sills V unplayable in most formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d39-d8cf-affb-bd3b1fb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said WR Christian Watson (chest) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5b-d77b-adfb-efdb457d0000</link>
      <description>Three days after Watson was transported to a nearby hospital for evaluation of an upper body injury he sustained against the Broncos, he’ll practice in a limited capacity. “He’s improving. We’ll just see how he’s feeling out there,” LaFleur said. It’s a good sign for his Week 16 availability against the Bears. Watson has emerged as Green Bay’s WR1 over the past month, seeing 20 percent of the team’s targets for 35 percent of the air yards over that stretch. If Watson is sidelined in Week 16, Matthew Golden would have some intrigue as a volatile WR4 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5b-d77b-adfb-efdb457d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison, Jr. (heel) will practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5f-d1bc-a3fb-ad7f26480000</link>
      <description>Harrison, who sat out in Week 15 with the heel issue, could make yet another return to the Arizona lineup in time for a good matchup against a burnable Atlanta secondary dealing with myriad injuries going into Week 16. Harrison, who has 40 receptions over ten games this season, would profile as a WR3 play if he suits up and plays a full complement of snaps against the Falcons. The dominant Michael Wilson would go from a locked-in WR1 to an iffy WR3/4 with MHJ back in the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5f-d1bc-a3fb-ad7f26480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes began rehab following surgery to repair his injured knee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d72-d77b-adfb-eff3bc8c0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs said Mahomes, who went down in Week 15’s loss to the Chargers, underwent surgery on Monday to repair the LCL part of his ACL/LCL ligament and immediately started his rehab. Mahomes has a shot to be under center for Kansas City to start the 2026 season, though it will be a close call considering he suffered the ACL injury in mid-December. ESPN’s Adam Schefter has said “it will be a surprise” if Mahomes is not ready for Week 1 in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d72-d77b-adfb-eff3bc8c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
