<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs left Colts’ practice early after suffering a hamstring injury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</link>
      <description>This is somewhat concerning. A soft tissue strain suffered in mid-August could have early-season ramifications. The Athletic’s James Boyd reports, Downs “came off during one of the team periods complaining about pain in his hamstring” and headed straight toward the team’s trainers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the NFL “will continue its own investigation” into Browns RB Quinshon Judkins’ misdemeanor domestic battery charge.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</link>
      <description>If Judkins begins practicing with the team before the regular season kicks off, he can still seize the team’s lead rushing role. The NFL’s investigation could still result in a suspension, however, though the expected timeline for said investigation is currently unknown. Nos. 2 and 3 RBs, Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson, make for precarious fantasy football draft picks at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jalen Nailor will undergo further evaluation after suffering a hand injury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa66-d90d-a5bd-aa7f28420000</link>
      <description>Nailor was expected to function as the Vikings’ fill-in No. 2 wide receiver with Jordan Addison suspended for the first three games of the season. Justin Jefferson is sidelined by a hamstring injury and Rondale Moore recently suffered a season-ending knee injury. The Nailor news leaves the wide receiver corps worryingly thin, and early-July reports on dynasty darling, rookie WR Tai Felton, indicated he may be best suited to special teams work in year one. The Vikings could make a move to acquire a proven, if unexciting, veteran to the mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa66-d90d-a5bd-aa7f28420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets worked out free agent QB C.J. Beathard on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa76-d05a-adda-aaf6634c0000</link>
      <description>The Jets also worked out QB Nathan Peterman, with backup QB Tyrod Taylor sidelined for the rest of the preseason after undergoing surgery on his injured knee. Beathard last took regular season snaps with the Jaguars in 2023, while Peterman did so with the Bears that same year. The Jets also worked out WR Tyreik McAllister and TE Kole Taylor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa76-d05a-adda-aaf6634c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When asked if Matthew Stafford’s (back) inability to practice is related to function or pain tolerance, Rams head coach Sean McVay said he thinks it is “probably a little bit of both.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa8d-df63-a199-fbafbdf20000</link>
      <description>NFL players frequently play through pain when function is not an issue, so McVay’s response is unsurprising. Still, having the supposition confirmed is never ideal. Stafford is scheduled to participate in a workout on Saturday, which will determine his practice availability next week. Fingers crossed that at least his functionality improves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa8d-df63-a199-fbafbdf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Bosa (neck soreness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa95-df63-a199-fbbf89fb0000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan “hopes” Bosa will be back next week, per ESPN’s Nick Wagoner. The 49ers’ defensive line is a little banged up. Defensive line rookies, DL Mykel Williams and DT CJ West, both recently hyperextended their knees. Hopefully, all three get fully healthy in time for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa95-df63-a199-fbbf89fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland’s Mary Kay Cabot reports that the Browns “are doing their diligence” on former Texas WR Isaiah Bond and have not signed him “yet.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aaac-d05a-adda-aaae86cf0000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported that “the sexual assault case against former Texas wide receiver Isaiah Bond has been no-billed and he faces no further criminal charges.” Shortly thereafter, Bond posted a message on social media ostensibly indicating that the Browns had signed him. In the post, Bond thanked the Browns for giving him “this opportunity,” and committed to “learning this offense” and building strong relationships with his “teammates.” Cabot follows up Bond’s post by saying Bond has not been signed “yet and it’s not happening today.” This story will likely continue to unfold in the coming hours and days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aaac-d05a-adda-aaae86cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said that most starters will play in preseason Week 2 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aacc-df63-a199-fbef46610000</link>
      <description>Mike Evans and Lavonte David are the only starters who will not play. This game could provide insight into Baker Mayfield’s connection with rising rookie WR Emeka Egbuka, as well as the Buccaneers’ backfield usage with Rachaad White (groin) likely sidelined. Mayfield did not play last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aacc-df63-a199-fbef46610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed FB Wesley Steiner, formerly of the Raiders, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aad4-d90d-a5bd-aadf31ea0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders briefly rostered Steiner after he went undrafted earlier this year. Steiner will technically be listed as the FB3, with standout rookie FB Robbie Ouzts penciled in as the starter and FB Brady Russell spending half his time at TE. The signing reinforces the notion that Seattle is committed to establishing the run this season, which is good news for both Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet. The team correspondingly waived LB Michael Dowell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aad4-d90d-a5bd-aadf31ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reports that Rashee Rice’s hearing and potential suspension could impact “the back half of the Chiefs’ season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aae2-d45c-a7fc-aafa894f0000</link>
      <description>Rice’s case regarding a multi-car crash will be heard by independent arbitrator Judge Sue L. Robinson, who previously issued Deshaun Watson’s initial six-game suspension after considering the matter for more than a month in 2022. Two weeks later, the NFL appealed Robinson’s suspension and agreed to an 11-game suspension with the NFLPA. Judge Robinson’s lengthy previous deliberation period could be an issue for Rice and the Chiefs. The NFL has again shown a willingness to operate on the Judge’s time, scheduling Rice’s hearing for September 30th because that is when her schedule allowed it. The Chiefs face the Ravens on September 28th, in Week 4. Should a similar timeline play out, it is possible Rice’s potential suspension is not imposed until after the Chiefs’ Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aae2-d45c-a7fc-aafa894f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
