<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 12:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is not on San Francisco’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8461-d1e7-a1fa-deebfaed0000</link>
      <description>Purdy will be a borderline QB1/QB2 off the long layoff. It’s worth noting that when he last played in Week 4, Purdy didn’t exactly look phenomenal while completing just 58 percent of his passes and throwing two interceptions. The long layoff makes us a little skittish to rank him as a QB1, but if his form from last season returns, he should post good numbers in his first start since Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8461-d1e7-a1fa-deebfaed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8454-d713-ad9e-ec546b540000</link>
      <description>Barner practiced in full all week, so he should be good to go for his typical workload against the Rams. Barner has played well in the Seahawks’ low-volume passing offense, and this should be a fantasy-friendly game environment. Barner can be treated as a touchdown-dependent TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8454-d713-ad9e-ec546b540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) is questionable for Week 11 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8454-d673-a39e-a4d563380000</link>
      <description>Knight inefficiently led the backfield with 11 touches last week. His questionable tag would seemingly elevate RB Emari Demercado, who played efficiently, to the touch-leader role. The 49ers’ defensive front is fairly banged up, so it is possible for one of these backs to return FLEX value. If Knight is inactive, Demercado can be started, though his fantasy-scoring ceiling remains in question.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8454-d673-a39e-a4d563380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins will not play in Week 11 against the Chiefs and could be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-846b-d673-a39e-a4fbfb720000</link>
      <description>Rapoport ambiguously states that Dobbins “is believed to be out for the foreseeable future” as he works through his options regarding his injured foot. Dobbins was injured while being hip-drop tackled by a Raiders defender in Week 10. Broncos rookie RB RJ Harvey steps into lead back duties with Dobbins sidelined, while receiving specialist RB Tyler Badie chips in behind him. Fellow backup RB Jaleel McLaughlin will likely be active on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-846b-d673-a39e-a4fbfb720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out CB Pat Surtain II (pec) for Week 11 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8468-d673-a39e-a4f95a690000</link>
      <description>Surtain has been out since injuring his pec in Week 8. The Broncos will also be without LB Alex Singleton, who recently underwent a successful procedure to remove a tumor, and LB Jonah Elliss (hamstring). These are tough losses for a defense tasked with containing the Chiefs’ offense, but the unit as a whole remains strong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8468-d673-a39e-a4f95a690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8477-d45b-affe-d5f7ab2d0000</link>
      <description>The Broncos get their erratically productive wide receiver back after a two-game absence. The Chiefs’ defense is very good, and Mims is hardly reliable, but this should be a fantasy-friendly game environment. Consider Mims a volatile FLEX option, reliant on a big play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8477-d45b-affe-d5f7ab2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals ruled out CB Will Johnson (back/hip) for Week 11 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8478-d45b-affe-d5feb2070000</link>
      <description>Johnson and LB Baron Browning (concussion) remained sidelined all week. The team is also without LB Mack Wilson (ribs). The three defenders will be missed against the 49ers, whose offensive health is improving. Both QB Brock Purdy (toe) and WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) will return to action this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8478-d45b-affe-d5feb2070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Tyler Lockett (knee) practiced fully on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-848f-d673-a39e-a49fb4910000</link>
      <description>The savvy, old wide receiver was back at it, practicing in full on Friday. Raiders head coach Pete Carroll has let Lockett play ahead of rookie WR Jack Bech, and that will likely continue this week against the Cowboys on Monday night. Lockett barely warrants FLEX consideration despite the soft matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-848f-d673-a39e-a49fb4910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina head coach Bill Belichick has “not and will not pursue any NFL head coaching vacancies.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8492-d673-a39e-a49358670000</link>
      <description>On Friday, Belichick released a statement on social media addressing “circulating rumors” linking him to the Giants’ vacant head coaching job. Although Belichick has “great respect and genuinely cares for the New York Giants organization and both the Mara and Tisch families,” his commitment to the UNC Football program has not wavered. The Tar Heels’ head coach’s “focus remains solely on continuing to improve this team,” developing its players and building a program that makes fans proud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8492-d673-a39e-a49358670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Ollie Gordon (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8549-d713-ad9e-ed5d8c910000</link>
      <description>Gordon practiced fully on Friday, which is good news. The rookie running back played behind RB Jaylen Wright in the Dolphins’ rotation last week, though Gordon was initially listed as questionable to play. This week should clarify which running back currently occupies the No. 2 spot. Neither one is terribly value as a bench stash, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8549-d713-ad9e-ed5d8c910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
