<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders have requested an interview with Raiders DC Patrick Graham for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d35e-a1bf-ddee67990000</link>
      <description>The Raiders had a bumpy year, but Graham’s defense allowed the 11th-fewest yards per play (5.1) to opponents this season. Graham interviewed for the Jaguars, Chargers and Seahawks head-coaching vacancies in 2025. The Commanders’ defense struggled under defensive-minded head coach Dan Quinn this year. Adding Graham to his staff could be a very smart move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d35e-a1bf-ddee67990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys co-owner Stephen Jones said re-signing RB Javonte Williams to a multi-year extension is “at the top of the list” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d968-a19b-d9ff94950000</link>
      <description>Williams, 25, produced multiple career-bests this season, notably rushing for more than 1,000 yards for the very first time. A multi-year extension could keep Williams in a Cowboys uniform through the rest of his prime. Hopefully, the team can get the No. 2 RB role sorted out in 2026 to help keep Williams fresh down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d968-a19b-d9ff94950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager reports that Rams OC Mike LaFleur “keeps coming up” as a head coaching candidate.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99b4-d968-a19b-d9f5f2d10000</link>
      <description>Teams cannot yet request to interview LaFleur, but it seems as though he may have a few suitors when he is made available via the NFL’s interview rules. LaFleur has served as the Rams’ offensive coordinator since 2023. The offense boasts two top-four finishes in yards per play across the full NFL season during that span. They rank second this season (6.2) and lead the NFL in passing touchdowns (46).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99b4-d968-a19b-d9f5f2d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager reports that Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase has “some legit buzz.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99cb-d968-a19b-d9fbdfaa0000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase interviewed for the Jaguars and Buccaneers’ offensive coordinator vacancies last offseason before the Rams promoted him from offensive assistant and passing game specialist to passing game coordinator. Schrager did not specify whether Scheelhaase’s buzz is in relation to offensive coordinator vacancies once again, but we believe this is the case. Rams QB Matthew Stafford led the league with 4,707 passing yards and 46 passing touchdowns this season. Stafford, of course, deserves a ton of credit, but Scheelhaase’s tactics were undoubtedly valuable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99cb-d968-a19b-d9fbdfaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers designated WR Jacob Cowing (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e3-dc7a-af9b-dfff91090000</link>
      <description>The team now has 21 days to observe Cowing in practice before officially activating him from injured reserve. The move comes at the right time. 49ers WR Ricky Pearsall aggravated his knee injury in Week 17 and was unable to play in Week 18. Cowing is not a full-on replacement for Pearsall, if the latter player remains sidelined, but having another wide receiver available is at least mildly helpful. The team also signed LB Milo Eifler to a reserve/future contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e3-dc7a-af9b-dfff91090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ec-dc7a-af9b-dfff8abd0000</link>
      <description>Darn. Per Shanahan, Pearsall aggravated the PCL sprain in his knee during the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears. He was unable to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks, though “he did participate in the 49ers’ 3 light practice sessions last week.” Hopefully, Pearsall resumes practicing tomorrow. Pearsall was recently listed with an ankle injury as well. The 49ers have not yet released the official injury report, so we do not know whether that is also an issue this week. 49ers beat reports on the matter vary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ec-dc7a-af9b-dfff8abd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said LT Trent Williams (hamstring) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99f6-d968-a19b-d9f7fd210000</link>
      <description>Williams still has a chance to play this week, but we were hoping to see him resume practicing today. Williams is dealing with his first recorded hamstring injury, suffered as he clocked 17.6 miles per hour on his team’s first play from scrimmage in Week 17. The 49ers face the Eagles this weekend. Getting Williams back would be a great development for QB Brock Purdy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99f6-d968-a19b-d9f7fd210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (ankle) will be limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</link>
      <description>While we would prefer to see Kittle begin the week with a full practice, we cannot complain about this outcome. Kittle made it through Week 18 without suffering any reported setbacks. His early-week participation puts him on track to play in the 49ers’ Wild Card Weekend game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks designated TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</link>
      <description>Arroyo missed the last four games after suffering a knee injury. The 22-year-old notably fell in the 2025 NFL Draft due to concerns over knee-related issues, but Arroyo is not yet being relied upon as a featured pass catcher. The Seahawks should be able to bring him along slowly, given starting TE AJ Barner’s presence and their first-round playoff bye. Thus far, Arroyo has caught 15-of-24 targets for 179 yards and one touchdown. The Seahawks have 21 days to evaluate him in practice before officially activating him from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles designated OLB Azeez Ojulari (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles have 21 days to observe Ojulari in practice before making a decision on whether they will officially activate him from injured reserve. They face the 49ers on Sunday, though. Ojulari would likely operate as an infrequently used situational pass rusher if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
