<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tee Higgins cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b50-d673-a39e-efd1810a0000</link>
      <description>Higgins left the fourth quarter of Sunday’s wild affair with the Bears with an unknown injury, but it appears to have just been a concussion evaluation. Higgins will get a week off with Cincinnati’s bye upcoming in Week 10 and should be considered likely to be available in Week 11 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b50-d673-a39e-efd1810a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Samaje Perine is week-to-week with a high ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b52-d45b-affe-5fd693090000</link>
      <description>The injury Perine suffered in Week 9’s loss to the Bears didn’t look good, so a week-to-week diagnosis is fairly good news. That said, it sounds like he’s a lock to miss at least one week, meaning backup Tahj Brooks would theoretically be in line to see more work behind Chase Brown. Brooks handled only one carry in Sunday’s loss and didn’t see a target. With the Bengals now entering their bye, we’ll see if Perine is able to bounce back in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b52-d45b-affe-5fd693090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Shemar Stewart (knee) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b52-d45b-affe-5fd658440000</link>
      <description>Following a decleating fourth-and-1 piledriver by Darnell Wright and being sealed off several times by wideout Olamide Zaccheaus, we wouldn’t have been surprised if Stewart saw his playing time reduced naturally. Playing through an injury could help explain how poor he looked in Week 9. Stewart has missed most of his rookie season with injury and has a startling 36.9 PFF defensive grade in 177 defensive snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b52-d45b-affe-5fd658440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports 49ers EDGE Mykel Williams (knee) suffered a torn ACL and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b57-d713-ad9e-6f57c1850000</link>
      <description>This was the fear following Sunday’s loss. San Francisco loses yet another young EDGE player as they try to piece together some pass rush in the absence of Nick Bosa. Williams finishes the year with a 53.9 PFF grade, but flashed some impressive tools despite not putting it all together. He should be penciled in as a 2026 starter in the second year of his rookie deal assuming rehab goes well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b57-d713-ad9e-6f57c1850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marshon Lattimore suffered a torn ACL in Week 9’s loss to the Seahawks, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b58-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa6c4d0000</link>
      <description>It was reported early on Monday that the Commanders believed Lattimore tore his ACL in Sunday’s defeat, but the worst has now been confirmed. The veteran corner, who is likely to be released at the end of this season, has had a mostly disappointing stint since the Commanders acquired him from the Saints last season. Once known for his abilities as a shutdown corner, Lattimore has struggled to keep pace with opposing receivers over the last two seasons and is among the most penalized corners in the league. He will be 30 at the start of next season and should still have plenty of suitors once he’s healed up from this setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b58-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa6c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Patriots are shopping LB Anfernee Jennings ahead of Tuesday’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b5f-d1e7-a1fa-5bff4d340000</link>
      <description>Jennings started 30 games for the Patriots from 2023 to 2024 but has been relegated to a backup role under head coach Mike Vrabel. Jennings has totaled eight tackles and one sack in the six games he’s appeared in this season, but could still help some teams in need of a boost on the defensive side of the ball. Last season he totaled 78 tackles in 16 games while totaling 2.5 sacks, and seven TFLs and earning a PFF defensive grade of 66.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b5f-d1e7-a1fa-5bff4d340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Christian Mahogany (knee) broke a bone in his leg and could return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b61-d713-ad9e-6f75d5f90000</link>
      <description>Mahogany was one of three sneaky Detroit offensive line injuries that held down their running game against the Vikings, with Taylor Decker and Penei Sewell also missing time. Campbell said it will be “touch and go” for both tackles this week in the lead-up to Detroit’s game against the Commanders, and that they likely wouldn’t practice Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b61-d713-ad9e-6f75d5f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports EDGE Dayo Odeyingbo tore his Achilles and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b67-d713-ad9e-6f777abc0000</link>
      <description>Odeyingbo had just one sack this season, accomplished in Week 1, but had 21 tackles and four quarterback hits in his first year with the Bears after signing a big free-agent contract. The 26-year-old will probably be a candidate for the PUP list in training camp based on the timing of this injury. The Bears could conceivably get off his 2026 $20.5 million cap hit without much damage to their cap space. In year two of a three-year deal, the guess is that Odeyingbo will stick with the Bears this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b67-d713-ad9e-6f777abc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said there is “no timetable” for Jayden Daniels’ (elbow) return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b68-d713-ad9e-6f7cef5c0000</link>
      <description>Quinn isn’t placing a timetable on Daniels’ return at the time, but said the team is still working on gathering information on the injury. Quinn, who said the decision to play Daniels in the fourth quarter of a blowout loss was “100 percent on me,” later added that he should be able to provide a clearer update by Wednesday or Thursday. Daniels didn’t suffer a fracture to his non-throwing arm, which is a great sign, but there is still concern about any potential ligament damage, and the option of surgery remains up in the air. A trip to injured reserve seems likely at this point, but we’ll wait for Quinn to provide an update before drawing any conclusions. Marcus Mariota will start as long as Daniels is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b68-d713-ad9e-6f7cef5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said he “doesn’t foresee” Terry McLaurin (quad) playing in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b74-d673-a39e-eff506000000</link>
      <description>“Knowing it’s game-game-bye, that has an affect. But I don’t have a timetable today,” Quinn added. Fantasy managers should be prepared based on this update to be without McLaurin until Week 13. It’s rather inconvenient for fantasy purposes that the Commanders won’t just put him on injured reserve. The star receiver has been dealing with the quad injury since leaving Week 3’s win over the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b74-d673-a39e-eff506000000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
