<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) was ruled out in Week 13 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6ec-d6c4-abfb-d6ef93af0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown’s right ankle got rolled up from behind by Lions fill-in starting C Trystan Colon and LG Kayode Awosika as he was dutifully blocking in the run game. He immediately headed to the locker room for further examination and was initially listed as questionable to return. He caught 0-of-1 targets before exiting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6ec-d6c4-abfb-d6ef93af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared LT Tyler Guyton, RB Jaydon Blue, CB Caelen Carson, WR Jonathan Mingo, DT Jay Toia and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive for Week 13 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6f5-d6c4-abfb-d6f743d80000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are without their left tackle, who suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12 against the Eagles. He was unable to practice at all this week. Blue, the once exciting rookie running back, is only a mildly intriguing bench stash at this point. His explosive traits are not in doubt, but he seemingly has a way to go before the Cowboys trust him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6f5-d6c4-abfb-d6f743d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared RG Trey Smith, TE Noah Gray, S Chris Roland-Wallace, RB Elijah Mitchell, WR Jalen Royals, OT Esa Pole and CB Kristian Fulton inactive for Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6f7-d6c4-abfb-d6f7b87d0000</link>
      <description>Losing Smith for this one is unfortunate. The capable pass blocker will be missed against an ascending Cowboys pass-rush unit. Both Mitchell and Royals are healthy scratches. Gray was unable to practice this week, due to a concussion. This matchup should produce a high-scoring game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6f7-d6c4-abfb-d6f7b87d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs exited Week 13 against the Lions after suffering an apparent leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6fb-d6c4-abfb-d6fbbe5c0000</link>
      <description>Lions DB Brian Branch dove low in an attempt to wrap up Jacobs on a third-quarter run. Branch’s left shoulder slammed into the lower section of Jacobs’ thigh, and potentially his knee, before he hit the ground. Jacobs was limping immediately after the play as he headed off the field to meet with trainers. It is possible this is just a thigh contusion. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6fb-d6c4-abfb-d6fbbe5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6c6-d90e-a9da-dfcffc6c0000</link>
      <description>Atwell practiced fully yesterday as well, putting him on track to return from injured reserve in Week 13 against the Panthers. The downfield wide receiver relies on big plays, making him a highly volatile FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6c6-d90e-a9da-dfcffc6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c70c-db57-afda-d73ea5050000</link>
      <description>The Giants face the Patriots on Monday Night Football, giving Robinson an extra day to rehab the ankle issue. His limited session puts him on track to play. The shifty slot receiver is a WR3 with upside. Giants QB Jaxson Dart has cleared the concussion protocol and will play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c70c-db57-afda-d73ea5050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (leg) returned to Week 13 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c710-d90e-a9da-df1f6fbf0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs is back on the field. The Packers’ star running back took a hard hit from Lions DB Brian Branch on his left leg, and he immediately limped his way to the blue medical tent for a quick exam. He was later seen studying plays on the bench, which was a good sign. Jacobs is currently averaging 5.5 yards per carry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c710-d90e-a9da-df1f6fbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c70f-db57-afda-d73f81170000</link>
      <description>Slayton delivered underwhelming results last week, but he made it through the game without suffering a re-injury, slightly increasing his outlook for this week. Slayton will have QB Jaxson Dart (concussion) back on the field this week as the Giants take on the Patriots on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c70f-db57-afda-d73f81170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill reports that Saints WR Chris Olave is day-to-day with back spasms.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c715-db57-afda-d737d18e0000</link>
      <description>Olave has handled a huge workload this season, so back spasms are unsurprising. The Saints’ No. 1 wide receiver is second in the NFL with 111 targets entering Week 13. He left practice early on Wednesday and was unable to practice today. Olave has a chance to suit up, but this is a situation worth following closely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c715-db57-afda-d737d18e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c719-d90e-a9da-df1fb57f0000</link>
      <description>Kamara has dealt with the ankle injury for weeks. He sprained an MCL last week though, and is heading toward an absence in Week 13. Rookie RB Devin Neal (ankle) is expected to start in Kamara’s stead. Neal can be treated as an RB2/3, though TE Taysom Hill will factor in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c719-d90e-a9da-df1fb57f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
