<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 7 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f35d-d99b-a1dd-fb5d7f640000</link>
      <description>A dispiriting DNP on the Friday report has us on the pessimistic side of questionable with Mooney. The Falcons No. 2 receiver at least avoided the early rule-out this week, but after two limited practices on Wednesday and Thursday the momentum is turning away from him playing in Week 7. He’d be a WR3 candidate if he’s able to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f35d-d99b-a1dd-fb5d7f640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons ruled out EDGE Jalon Walker (groin) for Week 7 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6e-d651-a9df-ef7fab870000</link>
      <description>Falcons rookie DB Billy Bowman Jr. (hamstring) will also be out this week. Losing two standout rookies for a bout with the 49ers’ efficient passing attack is unfortunate, but the Falcons’ defense as a whole has played well this year. Walker has totaled nine tackles, eight quarterback pressures and one sack. Bowman boasts 13 tackles, one pass breakup and one interception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6e-d651-a9df-ef7fab870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he was “very optimistic” Puka Nacua (ankle) will play after the team’s Week 8 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f362-df81-ab9b-ffe7f8b00000</link>
      <description>“I think it’ll serve him well and I have confidence in our other receivers to be able to step up.” The second this injury popped up, skipping Week 7 always made plenty of sense to give Nacua a two-week break. His status will be important ahead of Week 9, but based on the quotes we think there’s a good chance that Nacua will merely miss one game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f362-df81-ab9b-ffe7f8b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (hip) is not on New Orleans’ final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f367-df81-ab9b-ffe7169b0000</link>
      <description>He got in a full practice on Thursday, and while we don’t have Friday’s report yet, it seems unlikely he’ll do worse than a limited based on being taken off the injury report. Olave will remain a WR2/WR3 tweener as mostly a possession-based receiver in an offense that doesn’t seem to be generating a lot of runway to get him space in the open field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f367-df81-ab9b-ffe7169b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 7 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f365-d651-a9df-fb7588940000</link>
      <description>Kamara led the team with 15 touches in Week 6 while managing the ankle injury that he suffered in Week 5. No. 2 RB Kendre Miller and TE Taysom Hill have put a dent in his workload, though, keeping Kamara stuck in fantasy RB2 land. The Bears field a fantasy-friendly defense for opposing running backs. The veteran back has caught four or more passes in three straight games, and has decent odds of extending that streak this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f365-d651-a9df-fb7588940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) is doubtful for New York’s Week 7 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f370-d99b-a1dd-fb7cb7b10000</link>
      <description>He did not practice in any session this week and hasn’t practiced since injuring himself in Week 5’s loss to the Saints. It would not be surprising if Slayton were placed on injured reserve ahead of Week 7’s game, but if he’s not, he enters Week 8 as a firm question mark. Lil’Jordan Humphrey led all Giants with eight targets last Thursday and is an interesting desperation FLEX play in a #RevengeGame against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f370-d99b-a1dd-fb7cb7b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears K Cairo Santos (thigh) will not play in Chicago’s Week 7 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f378-da18-a39b-fb7bdf850000</link>
      <description>It’s another Jake Moody week, for those of you in two-kicker leagues or contemplating a stream against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f378-da18-a39b-fb7bdf850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals GM Monti Ossenfort was non-committal when asked if Kyler Murray remains the starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f36e-df81-ab9b-ffefa8230000</link>
      <description>Ossenfort’s response leaves room for interpretation. He explains that the team is “going to continue to try and get Kyler where he can get back to doing the things he can do on the field,” and “when he’s doing that, he’ll be out there.” It is unclear whether Ossenfort is simply referring to Murray’s foot injury or if he is also taking Murray’s inconsistent play in Weeks 1-5 into account. While Murray remained productive on the ground, rushing for 25-plus yards in all five games, he averaged just 6.0 yards per passing attempt and never threw for more than 220 yards in a single game while taking 16 sacks. In Week 6, Jacoby Brissett threw for 320 yards, two touchdowns and one interception, averaging 7.3 yards per passing attempt, taking two sacks and running for 19 yards on the ground. While we do expect Murray to return as the starter at some point, one wonders if the coaching staff might slow-play his return from the foot injury he suffered in Week 5, while helping Murray fine-tune his pre-game preparations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f36e-df81-ab9b-ffefa8230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip/groin) is not on Chicago’s final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f37b-d651-a9df-fb7f14940000</link>
      <description>Moore got in a full session on Friday and will not even be on the questionable line against the Saints in Week 7. We’re not quite at “full send DJ Moore” out there now in fantasy leagues as Rome Odunze has become the No. 1 wideout in the offense and Moore has been held under 50 yards in each of his last four appearances, but he can at least be played as a WR3/FLEX against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f37b-d651-a9df-fb7f14940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f37c-df81-ab9b-ffff58370000</link>
      <description>Swift practiced in full on Wednesday before being downgraded to limited on Thursday and Friday. The Bears’ starting running back has played through quad and hip injuries already this season, playing through questionable designations in Weeks 3 and 4. Given his past availability, it seems likely that he suits up against the Saints this weekend, though following monitoring reports leading up to kickoff will be worthwhile. Backup RB Kyle Monangai is a recommended bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f37c-df81-ab9b-ffff58370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
