<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns EDGE Myles Garrett (ankle) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a63f-deb6-a7fd-f7ff175e0000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session, but it suggests there’s not much concern about Garrett’s ability to play on Sunday in England. Kevin Stefanski called Garrett “day to day” yesterday, and Garrett has already played off DNPs ahead of Week 1 when he was dealing with a hip injury. Garrett is more than likely going to make Carson Wentz’s life miserable in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a63f-deb6-a7fd-f7ff175e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a641-dca3-a9fb-bfd977320000</link>
      <description>We have no concerns about Njoku suiting up on Sunday. He likely will be removed from the final injury report without a setback on Friday. Njoku figures to be a low-floor, low-ceiling option against the Vikings in Week 5 as Dillon Gabriel makes his NFL debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a641-dca3-a9fb-bfd977320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Greg Newsome (hamstring) was limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a643-d95b-addb-ee47cfa10000</link>
      <description>We never love to see a mid-week downgrade and unfortunately that’s what happened with Newsome today. It’s possible this is a blip, but it also could be a mid-practice injury that sends him to the inactives for Week 5. We’ll check in on him again tomorrow. If Newsome were out, it would increase the appeal of Minnesota’s wideout room as Cleveland’s depth corners behind Denzel Ward and Newsome are not well-regarded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a643-d95b-addb-ee47cfa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Kenny Moore II (Achilles) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a630-d6e9-af9d-aeb096630000</link>
      <description>The Colts’ stalwart slot defender may still be a week or two away from suiting up on game day, but this is a promising first step. Moore sat out Indianapolis’ Week 4 game against the Rams after playing a season-high 50 snaps in Week 3. They face the Raiders this week, whose interior pass catchers, WR Jakobi Meyers and TE Brock Bowers, are the receiving corps’ strong points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a630-d6e9-af9d-aeb096630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle’s Jon Alexander reports “there is no one who has told me they expect [Joe Mixon] (ankle/foot) to return this season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a645-deb6-a7fd-f7df6c0c0000</link>
      <description>“And if he was, someone would tell me,” Alexander concludes. It amazes us that Mixon has somehow gone off the grid enough to not have a realistic report on his ankle/foot injury at any point in the last three months, but here we are. Mixon does not look to be a long-term threat to Woody Marks consolidating the backfield in 2025. Mixon is due a $10.5 million cap hit in 2026 and may be a restructure or release candidate coming off a lost year and entering his age-30 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a645-deb6-a7fd-f7df6c0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a666-d6e9-af9d-aef6208a0000</link>
      <description>Mid-week injury report additions are typically a bad sign. Pittman may have strained his hamstring during today’s practice. If he remains limited on Friday, he will have a chance to suit up, but it could come down to the dreaded game-time decision. The Colts are expected to get field-stretching WR Alec Pierce (concussion) back this week, though the two play very different roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a666-d6e9-af9d-aef6208a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a68d-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdc550000</link>
      <description>Assuming he dodges a questionable listing on Friday, Taylor looks likely to be a TE2 against a Cowboys defense which has been picked on by everybody, even Russell Wilson, in Week 5. Taylor was also limited on Wednesday. He had a 5/65 game against the Dolphins in Week 4 and could be establishing himself as the No. 2 receiver in this limited passing offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a68d-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdc550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a697-d6e9-af9d-ae9758790000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session, but it is a big step towards playing in Week 5 against the Giants. Johnson managed to play through the Bills game with the injury but spent a lot of time with the training staff. This doesn’t have the look of something serious enough to keep him out, but we wouldn’t be surprised if he finished the week on the questionable line. Friday will be huge for Johnson’s status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a697-d6e9-af9d-ae9758790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB/TE Taysom Hill (knee) and TE Foster Moreau (knee) were both limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a699-deb6-a7fd-f7df9c470000</link>
      <description>They maintain the same status. We don’t yet know if Hill or Moreau will be active for Week 5 — either could cut deeply into Juwan Johnson’s fantasy value if officially activated from the PUP list after being designated to return on Monday. The Saints have a 21-day window from Monday to do it, so there’s not necessarily an urgency to activating Hill or Moreau for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a699-deb6-a7fd-f7df9c470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots DT Milton Williams (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ac-deb6-a7fd-f7ffde8e0000</link>
      <description>Williams was limited yesterday, which could indicate that he suffered the injury in practice. His absence on Thursday casts doubt on his Week 5 availability. Williams ranks third on the team in both quarterback pressures (11) and sacks (two), and ties for the sixth-most defensive stops (six). The Patriots will have a tough time containing the Bills’ ground game if Williams is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ac-deb6-a7fd-f7ffde8e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
