<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Packers “plan to work out RB Josh Jacobs” before determining his status for Week 12 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0d2-d90e-a9da-bfdf57850000</link>
      <description>Jacobs is dealing with a knee contusion but is pushing to play in Week 12. He was initially expected to miss at least one week, but the veteran back returned to practice on Thursday and was listed as questionable at the end of the week. He is a true game-time call versus Minnesota. That game takes place in the early window, meaning fantasy managers will know Jacobs’ status before all of Sunday’s games kick off. Emanuel Wilson will draw the start if Jacobs is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0d2-d90e-a9da-bfdf57850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived WR Brandin Cooks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0d7-db57-afda-f6f7eb280000</link>
      <description>For real this time. Cooks was reportedly waived earlier in the week, but contract issues stalled the move. The Saints were cutting the veteran wideout to allow him to sign with a contender of his choosing. They restructured his contract before cutting him to make it more unappealing, ensuring no one would claim him on waivers. That is explicitly prohibited by the NFL. This issue has since been resolved and Cooks is now able to be claimed by teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0d7-db57-afda-f6f7eb280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Kenneth Walker (glue) is expected to play in Week 12 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0dd-d82c-a79a-b3dd99160000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as head coach Mike Macdonald said as much on Friday. Walker was a surprise addition to the injury report. He did not practice on Friday and was listed as questionable, but Macdonald quickly called the absence precautionary and assured us fantasy managers that Walker would be out there on Sunday. Even if his workload is slightly reduced because of the injury, Walker is still in the RB2 ranks for a great matchup against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0dd-d82c-a79a-b3dd99160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Alvin Kamara (ankle) is expected to play in Week 12 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0e0-d413-ad9f-b5fdc6e70000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been playing through the ankle injury for most of the 2025 season. He hasn’t missed time because of it yet and was limited in practice throughout the week. Kamara never appeared to be at any risk of missing Week 12 despite the questionable tag. As a slight favorite of the Falcons this week, the Saints might actually get the chance to establish their ground game. Kamara hasn’t been efficient between the tackles this year, but a solid workload will keep him in the RB3 ranks for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0e0-d413-ad9f-b5fdc6e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bucky Irving (toe/shoulder) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0e5-d90e-a9da-bfef049c0000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, Irving looked strong in practice and “might have been able to play” in Week 12 versus the Rams, but the Bucs decided to give him one more week of rest. Sean Tucker and Rachaad White will hold down the backfield for one more week. Tucker took over the backfield last week, seeing 19 carries to White’s 10. Tucker ran for 106 yards and two scores. He also found the end zone once through the air. Tucker will push for an RB2 rank this week while White is nothing more than a low-end RB3 in PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0e5-d90e-a9da-bfef049c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Xavier Worthy (aknle) is expected to play in Week 12 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0f0-d413-ad9f-b5fdc81c0000</link>
      <description>Worthy was held out of Wednesday’s practice but steadily made progress throughout the week. He was listed as a full participant on Friday before being given a questionable tag. Worthy has fallen by the wayside with Rashee Rice back. He has topped 40 yards one time since Week 7, Rice’s first game of the year. Worthy hasn’t scored with Rice active. He is stuck in the WR4 ranks for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0f0-d413-ad9f-b5fdc81c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Aron Rodgers (wrist) “has been pushing to play Sunday vs. the Bears.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0fa-d82c-a79a-b3fedd870000</link>
      <description>Rodgers is dealing with a fracture in his left wrist. As Schefter notes, Pittsburgh’s doctors have been more cautious in regards to the injury. Rodgers suffered the injury in Week 11 versus the Bengals. He managed a light week of practice before being listed as questionable for today’s game. Per Schefter, “If the decision is left to Rodgers, he will play.” Mason Rudolph will draw the start if Rodgers is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b0fa-d82c-a79a-b3fedd870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Chris Godwin (fibula) “will likely be on something of a pitch count” in Week 12 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b102-d82c-a79a-b39663b20000</link>
      <description>Godwin has been out since Week 5 with a fibula injury that is now reported to be a hairline fracture. He has been back at practice for a few weeks and managed a full session on Thursday. The team downgraded him to limited on Friday, though that was likely planned ahead of time to keep his workload in check. Godwin is listed as questionable for Week 12 but is expected to play. Fantasy managers will likely want to keep him on the bench for a week until he gets ramped up to a full-time role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b102-d82c-a79a-b39663b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Ravens are going to think about resting Lamar Jackson “every single Wednesday just to keep him fresh.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b129-d90e-a9da-bf2f50ee0000</link>
      <description>This blurb largely exists to prevent fantasy managers from panicking when Jackson is inevitably held out of practice next Wednesday. Jackson has missed the past two Wednesday practices with ankle and knee injuries. Neither injury cost him any time, but a hamstring issue earlier in the year did sideline him for a few games. Jackson is averaging a career-low 5.6 rush attempts per game. That, combined with a 5.8 yards per carry mark that is slightly below his career average, has him at just 32.3 rushing yards per game. He posted 52.3 rushing yards per week in 2024. The non-stop injuries have forced him to stay in the pocket more, crushing his elite rushing output. Jackson remains a QB1 for fantasy purposes, but he may struggle to contend for the top overall spot if he isn’t the league’s most productive quarterback on the ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b129-d90e-a9da-bf2f50ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the franchise tag is “the more likely option” compared to free agency for George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b131-d413-ad9f-b5fd23910000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s sources are saying in more words that the Cowboys won’t let Pickens walk out the door in the spring. He is set to be an unrestricted free agent after the season, but the Cowboys will make a push to extend him before he hits the open market. If Pickens doesn’t agree to a deal, the franchise tag is likely headed his way. Pickens currently ranks second in the NFL in receiving yards (908) and third in touchdowns (seven). The franchise tag would cost Dallas roughly $28 million. It’s a steep price to pay, but one that is more than fair for a receiver with Pickens’ production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b131-d413-ad9f-b5fd23910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
