<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars released TE Quintin Morris.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e805-dbe3-a9bb-f857d6570000</link>
      <description>The blocking tight end couldn’t unseat Johnny Mundt or Hunter Long on the tight end depth chart, but he should have a chance to find a spot elsewhere this season. The Jaguars also released: OL Tremayne Anchrum, WR Trenton Irwin, S Daniel Thomas, and QB John Wolford. They waived TE Shawn Bowman, WR Chandler Brayboy, WR Cam Camper, DL James Carpenter, OL Jerome Carvin, DE Myles Cole, LB Branson Combs, TE John Copenhaver, DE Ethan Downs, OL Javon Foster, RB Kevin Harris, QB Seth Henigan, TE Patrick Herbert, RB Ja’Quinden Jackson, DL Jordan Jefferson, DL Tyler Lacy, WR Darius Lassiter, OL Ricky Lee, CB Keni-H Lovely, DE Jabbar Muhammed, LB Chad Muma, CB De’Antre Prince, DL Keivie Rose, DB Cam’Ron Silmon-Craig, WR Dorian Singer, DB Doneiko Slaughter, DB Aydan White and OL Sal Wormley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e805-dbe3-a9bb-f857d6570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles released WR Terrace Marshall.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e807-dbe3-a9bb-f85770860000</link>
      <description>Marshall was unable to secure a roster spot with John Metchie III now in the fold. The Eagles also released LS Charley Hughlett, OLB Patrick Johnson, T Kendall Lamm, CB Parry Nickerson, WR Avery Williams. The Eagles waived WR Ife Adeyi, LB Chance Campbell, CB Tariq Castro-Fields, WR Elijah Cooks, LB Lance Dixon, DT Joe Evans, LB Dallas Gant, G Kenyon Green, S Maxen Hook, TE E.J. Jenkins, CB Brandon Johnson, RB Montrell Johnson, TE Cameron Latu, OLB Ochaun Mathis, QB Kyle McCord, WR Taylor Morin, TE Nick Muse, T Hollin Pierce, RB ShunDerrick Powell, OLB Antwaun Powell-Ryland, CB Eli Ricks, DE Jereme Robinson, RB Keilan Robinson, DT Justin Rogers, S Andre Sam, WR Ainias Smith, DT Jacob Sykes, T Laekin Vakalahi and CB A.J. Woods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e807-dbe3-a9bb-f85770860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent CB Mike Hilton will visit the Colts on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e816-d332-a1fd-fe3609f10000</link>
      <description>After being cut by the Dolphins on Monday, Hilton was of immediate interest to the Colts with their battered DB room. They already added Xavien Howard earlier this month. Now Hilton could be another veteran addition as Lou Anarumo tries to reunite with his old slot cornerback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e816-d332-a1fd-fe3609f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed WR Brandon Aiyuk (knee) on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e81a-de13-afdc-eedb5fc30000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four weeks of the season, but that’s no surprise. The latest expectations we had from Kyle Shanahan on Aiyuk’s return were “around Week 6" — it’s certainly possible that Aiyuk may be ready to practice when his forced stint on the PUP list is up based on that timeline. It’s also possible that Aiyuk misses more than just four weeks. We’re sure Shanahan will be asked about it often starting in Week 4. The 49ers also placed S Malik Mustapha on the PUP list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e81a-de13-afdc-eedb5fc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers released RB Trey Sermon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e818-de13-afdc-eedba4260000</link>
      <description>The Steelers also released Chuck Clark, CB James Pierre, OG Max Scharping, WR Ke’Shawn Williams, WR Brandon Johnson, DT Domenique Davis and waived CB Beanie Bishop and S Sebastian Castro. The Steelers placed CB Cory Trice on injured reserve with a designation to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e818-de13-afdc-eedba4260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released OG Cole Strange.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b8-db7b-a5dd-e7bcddc50000</link>
      <description>This comes just four months after the Patriots declined Strange’s fifth-year option. Strange lost most of the 2024 season due to a torn patellar tendon, limiting him to just two starts. He will now be subject to waivers should any team feel frisky enough to gamble on his underwhelming profile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b8-db7b-a5dd-e7bcddc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released DL Tanoh Kpassagnon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e821-d332-a1fd-fe373a910000</link>
      <description>The Dennis Allen acolyte was signed for training camp but did not make the team. The Bears also released WR Miles Boykin and TE Stephen Carlson. They waived WR Maurice Alexander, RB Brittain Brown, LS Luke Elkin, DL Jonathan Ford, DB Mekhi Garner, DL Jamree Kromah, OL Jordan McFadden, DL Zacch Pickens, WR JP Richardson, WR Tyler Scott and OL Ricky Stromberg. They waived/injured DB Tysheem Johnson, OL Doug Kramer Jr. and OL Bill Murray — the real Groundhog Day is watching Murray get waived over and over again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e821-d332-a1fd-fe373a910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed Jason Sanders (hip) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e826-db7b-a5dd-e826feb10000</link>
      <description>As expected, he’ll miss the next four games. Adam Schefter said yesterday that his timeline to return was “4-5 weeks” and the Dolphins worked out a few kickers and are expected to sign a new one sometime in the next few days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e826-db7b-a5dd-e826feb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed LS Matt Orzech to a three-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e82a-de13-afdc-eeeb97220000</link>
      <description>This snapper of balls that go longer than the average ball decided to cut a deal on an extension on the same day that everyone else got cut. That’s not a very savvy move for awareness of Orzech’s brand, but then again, snappers with the capability to snap the ball long distances are not known for bringing attention to themselves. They are known for snapping the ball long distances, to be clear, and that is what Orzech will continue to do for the Packers going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e82a-de13-afdc-eeeb97220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants waived WR Dalen Cambre.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e824-d332-a1fd-fe365af00000</link>
      <description>Cambre caught 2-of-5 targets for 45 yards in two preseason games. The Giants also released WR Da’Quan Felton, OL Stone Forsythe, DL Jeremiah Ledbetter, DL Jordon Riley and K Jude McAtamney. The Giants also placed RB Eric Gray and OLB Victor Dimukeje on the reserve/physically unable to perform list. They will be eligible to return after four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e824-d332-a1fd-fe365af00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
