<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:02:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 23-of-27 passes for 224 yards and two touchdowns in the Steelers’ 28-15, Week 15 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2579-d8cf-affb-bd7b5e6b0000</link>
      <description>Multiple records and milestones were reached in this one. First off, offensive coordinator Arthur Smith was full-on Arthur Smith-ing as the Steelers became the first team in NFL history with rushing scores by two different tight ends in the same game, the first scored by Connor Heyward on Pittsburgh’s version of the tush push from one yard out and the second a rushing score by former Dolphins tight end Jonnu Smith for the revenge narrative. Second, the Steelers scored on four consecutive possessions for the first time since 2018 to break the game open in the third quarter. Third, their defense held the Dolphins to -20 total yards in the third quarter, the fewest for any team in a quarter since at least 2019. And finally, Rodgers moved into third in career games with two or more touchdown passes after connecting with Marquez Valdes-Scantling and DK Metcalf in the third quarter. Rodgers was not tasked with much while attempting only 27 passes due to the defensive battle and remains an uneasy start in fantasy circles in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2579-d8cf-affb-bd7b5e6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed 13 times for 80 yards in the Steelers’ Week 15 win over the Dolphins, adding 46 yards on seven receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2582-d1bc-a3fb-a5a683fc0000</link>
      <description>Gainwell drew the start with Jaylen Warren battling an illness, although the two backs would share primary duties throughout. It was Gainwell that was the much more efficient back, gaining 126 total yards to the 48 yards of Warren on five more touches. The Pittsburgh backfield remains one of interest considering Arthur Smith is at the helm, with the biggest detractor being a typical timeshare between the top two options. Gainwell’s eruption in the first week of fantasy playoffs highlights the upside if one of the two sees more primary usage, making Warren’s status one to monitor in the coming week of practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2582-d1bc-a3fb-a5a683fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught all three targets for 55 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 15 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2587-d005-a9bf-fdb739b50000</link>
      <description>Metcalf’s modest target total was a product of a game environment in which the Steelers were really never pushed, with their defense holding the Dolphins to just three points through the first three quarters. He salvaged his fantasy outing by turning into a one-man wrecking ball in the third quarter, catching a pass over the middle of the field between two defenders before bouncing off one, stiff-arming another, and out-running two more on his way to the end zone. Metcalf has returned modest fantasy production in the low-volume Pittsburgh offense this season, potentially cratering his dynasty value moving forward. That said, he gets the pass-funnel Lions in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2587-d005-a9bf-fdb739b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught both targets for 12 yards in the Steelers’ Week 15 win over the Dolphins, adding 14 yards and a touchdown on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-258c-d8cf-affb-bdae0cc60000</link>
      <description>Smith scored the second of two rushing touchdowns by Pittsburgh tight ends, setting a new NFL record as the first team in history with two rushing scores by different tight ends in the same game. Leave it to Arthur Smith to be responsible for a record like that. Smith’s outing was otherwise far from noteworthy while playing in a four-man rotation at tight end for the Steelers, with all of Smith, Pat Freiermuth (three catches for 45 yards), Darnell Wshington (three catches for 25 yards), and Heyward (four carries for four yards and a touchdown) getting in on the action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-258c-d8cf-affb-bdae0cc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets waived WR Allen Lazard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2753-d1bc-a3fb-a77720380000</link>
      <description>The news was first reported by Pro Football Talk. Lazard will reportedly look to sign with a contender. We wish him luck in that endeavor. Lazard has 10 catches on 18 targets over ten games this season in a Jets offense that has been desperate for wideout production. He has been targeted on 13 percent of his pass routes through Week 15. Lazard could always land with longtime friend and former teammate Aaron Rodgers in Pittsburgh if the Steelers are looking to add more receiver depth ahead of the postseason. Jets beat writer Connor Hughes said Lazard had “questionable practice habits, and rubbed some teammates the wrong way with way he acted once Aaron Rodgers arrived” in 2023. Lazard’s departure from New York could open up more playing time for electric WR Isaiah Williams, who had six receptions for 53 yards last week against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2753-d1bc-a3fb-a77720380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson said he’s “feeling better” after dealing with multiple injuries this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-27eb-d005-a9bf-ffff4cd70000</link>
      <description>Jackson has appeared more like his normal, electric self over the past two weeks. In Week 15 against the Bengals Jackson threw for 150 yards and two touchdowns while rushing for 26 yards. He appeared far more mobile and elusive than he did in the Ravens’ Thanksgiving night loss to the Bengals. “I believe I told you guys early on in the week that I was feeling better, like Thursday,” Jackson told reporters after Baltimore’s Week 15 win. “I guess you guys had to see it to believe it.” Apparently recovered from ankle and hamstring injuries he suffered this season, Jackson should be an excellent fantasy option in Week 16 against the Patriots in what could be a high-scoring affair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-27eb-d005-a9bf-ffff4cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed WR Noah Brown (ribs) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2802-d77b-adfb-ea83d9280000</link>
      <description>Brown’s 2025 season is over. He sustained the rib injury in Week 15 against the Giants on a 28-yard reception. Brown landed hard and needed help getting to the sideline. The oft-injured veteran ends the season with five catches for 83 yards over four games. Brown had spent time on IR earlier this season with a groin injury. He’s unlikely to remain with the Commanders in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2802-d77b-adfb-ea83d9280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (ankle) is eligible to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-280a-d005-a9bf-f83e00b10000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Nate Atkins said Higbee is unlikely to be active for Thursday night’s game against the Seahawks, however. Higbee has bee on IR since mid-November following a serious ankle injury against Seattle. His absence has opened up routes and targets for Colby Parkinson, who should be treated as a legit streaming option in Week 16. Parkinson and TE Terrance Ferguson led the Rams in pass routes last week against the Lions in an LA offense that uses two and three tight end sets at the NFL’s highest rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-280a-d005-a9bf-f83e00b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said WR Davante Adams (hamstring) could be a game-time decision for Week 16 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-280d-d1bc-a3fb-ad2d44e80000</link>
      <description>McVay on Tuesday refused to rule out Adams following his apparently serious hamstring injury in Week 15’s win over the Lions. McVay acknowledged on Sunday night that Adams’ was in doubt for the Thursday night game, however. With almost no shot to suit up against Seattle, fantasy managers should make other plans at wideout for Week 16. The Rams are likely to be more run heavy with Adams sidelined, creating more touch-based upside for both Kyren Williams and Blake Corum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-280d-d1bc-a3fb-ad2d44e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) is eligible to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2847-d1bc-a3fb-ad6746870000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Havenstein remained unlikely to suit up for Thursday night’s matchup against the Seahawks. He would have a real shot to play in Week 17, however. Havenstein has dealt with ankle issues for much of the season and has been on IR since mid-November. He would be a needed addition to the Rams offensive line for the team’s postseason push.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2847-d1bc-a3fb-ad6746870000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
