<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Matthew Stafford (back) will work out on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa2d-d90d-a5bd-aa7f5b9a0000</link>
      <description>The workout will be similar to what he did on August 9th, when he threw more than 60 passes. The team used that workout to assess whether Stafford was ready to resume practicing. Unfortunately, he wasn’t. McVay hopes Stafford’s back “responds a little bit better” this time around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa2d-d90d-a5bd-aa7f5b9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Scherff retired after 10 seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa33-df63-a199-fb3b379f0000</link>
      <description>Scherff retires with five Pro Bowl nominations, one first-team All-Pro honor and a 2015 PFWA All-Rookie Team award on his mantle. He spent his first seven seasons in the NFL playing for the Commanders, who drafted him fifth overall. He spent his remaining three seasons with the Jaguars. The former offensive guard was recently inducted into the Iowa Athletics Hall of Fame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa33-df63-a199-fb3b379f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy will not play in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa3e-df63-a199-fb3fb2f00000</link>
      <description>McCarthy played well last week, and the Vikings no doubt want to avoid him suffering another preseason injury. The strong-armed Howell gets the start instead, which should make for fun viewing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa3e-df63-a199-fb3fb2f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said most starters, including Justin Herbert, will play in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa46-d90d-a5bd-aa5f8d420000</link>
      <description>Observing Herbert’s connection with his recently revamped receiving corps will be worthwhile for fantasy managers. Keenan Allen’s return to the lineup could have a fantasy-unfriendly effect on players like Quentin Johnston, Tre’ Harris and KeAndre Lambert-Smith. Derwin James and Khalil Mack are the only two starters who will not play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa46-d90d-a5bd-aa5f8d420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs left Colts’ practice early after suffering a hamstring injury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</link>
      <description>This is somewhat concerning. A soft tissue strain suffered in mid-August could have early-season ramifications. The Athletic’s James Boyd reports, Downs “came off during one of the team periods complaining about pain in his hamstring” and headed straight toward the team’s trainers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the NFL “will continue its own investigation” into Browns RB Quinshon Judkins’ misdemeanor domestic battery charge.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</link>
      <description>If Judkins begins practicing with the team before the regular season kicks off, he can still seize the team’s lead rushing role. The NFL’s investigation could still result in a suspension, however, though the expected timeline for said investigation is currently unknown. Nos. 2 and 3 RBs, Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson, make for precarious fantasy football draft picks at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jalen Nailor will undergo further evaluation after suffering a hand injury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa66-d90d-a5bd-aa7f28420000</link>
      <description>Nailor was expected to function as the Vikings’ fill-in No. 2 wide receiver with Jordan Addison suspended for the first three games of the season. Justin Jefferson is sidelined by a hamstring injury and Rondale Moore recently suffered a season-ending knee injury. The Nailor news leaves the wide receiver corps worryingly thin, and early-July reports on dynasty darling, rookie WR Tai Felton, indicated he may be best suited to special teams work in year one. The Vikings could make a move to acquire a proven, if unexciting, veteran to the mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa66-d90d-a5bd-aa7f28420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets worked out free agent QB C.J. Beathard on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa76-d05a-adda-aaf6634c0000</link>
      <description>The Jets also worked out QB Nathan Peterman, with backup QB Tyrod Taylor sidelined for the rest of the preseason after undergoing surgery on his injured knee. Beathard last took regular season snaps with the Jaguars in 2023, while Peterman did so with the Bears that same year. The Jets also worked out WR Tyreik McAllister and TE Kole Taylor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa76-d05a-adda-aaf6634c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed WR Isaiah Bond to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa7e-d45c-a7fc-aa7eee400000</link>
      <description>Bond announced the signing on social media shortly after ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported that “the sexual assault case against former Texas wide receiver Isaiah Bond has been no-billed and he faces no further criminal charges.” Bond went undrafted out of Texas this year following his arrest and subsequent charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa7e-d45c-a7fc-aa7eee400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When asked if Matthew Stafford’s (back) inability to practice is related to function or pain tolerance, Rams head coach Sean McVay said he thinks it is “probably a little bit of both.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa8d-df63-a199-fbafbdf20000</link>
      <description>NFL players frequently play through pain when function is not an issue, so McVay’s response is unsurprising. Still, having the supposition confirmed is never ideal. Stafford is scheduled to participate in a workout on Saturday, which will determine his practice availability next week. Fingers crossed that at least his functionality improves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa8d-df63-a199-fbafbdf20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
