<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson rushed 14 times for 82 yards in the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f4b-d35e-a1bf-7fcbb3e80000</link>
      <description>Even with Josh Jacobs attempting to play through his knee injury, Wilson worked his way into the mix a bit more than normal. He eventually took over for Jacobs, who played only two snaps after a lost fumble in the third quarter, and wound up out-gaining Jacobs 82-36 on the ground. Wilson ran hard and efficiently for the Packers all afternoon, and could be in line for a big role in Week 17 if Jacobs’ knee injury proves too bad to play on. Wilson will be worth rostering wherever available and would be view as a high-end RB2 against the Ravens if Jacobs is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f4b-d35e-a1bf-7fcbb3e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift rushed 13 times for 58 yards in the Bears’ Week 16 win over the Packers, adding two receptions for 12 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f4c-dc7a-af9b-ffffe3c40000</link>
      <description>Swift played just ahead of rookie Kyle Monangai in this one, but didn’t offer much to a Bears offense that struggled for most of the night. Swift’s biggest gain of the night came on a nine-yard run in the fourth quarter that helped set the Bears up for a 51-yard field goal by Cairo Santos, but this was a classic floor game for Swift. His lack of work in the passing game continues to make Swift a touchdown-dependent RB2, which is what he should be viewed as in Week 17 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f4c-dc7a-af9b-ffffe3c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 2-of-6 targets for 17 yards in the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f59-d35e-a1bf-7fdbd1ce0000</link>
      <description>Watson briefly left this game with an injury but returned after only a few plays. The Packers’ speedster struggled to get much going in the air, but had a chance to score on the game’s opening drive were it not for a pass being broken up near the Bears’ goal-line. Watson tied for the Packers’ lead with six targets on Saturday, but struggled to produce much with Malik Willis under center for most of the day. Watson will be a boom-or-bust WR3 in Week 17’s game against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f59-d35e-a1bf-7fdbd1ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught 3-of-3 targets for 35 yards in the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5a-da28-afbb-ff7f615c0000</link>
      <description>Were it not for a 31-yard reception made by Reed in overtime, the third-year receiver would have been looking at an even more underwhelming stat line. Reed saw just three targets in this one, which tied Luke Musgrave for third most on the team. Reed has gone for 35 or fewer yards in two of his three games since returning from injury in, and won’t profile as anything more than a WR4 win Week 17 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5a-da28-afbb-ff7f615c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 3-of-3 targets for 38 yards in the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5b-d087-addf-bffb08070000</link>
      <description>Musgrave’s 38 receiving yards mark his second-highest total of the season and come on the heals of the 4/52/0 receiving line he had last week. Musgrave has yet to find the end zone this season and is averaging just 2.0 targets per game. He won’t be on the fantasy radar for Week 16 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5b-d087-addf-bffb08070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed nine times for 50 yards in the Bears’ Week 16 win over the Packers, adding three receptions for 43 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5b-da28-afbb-ff7fc1120000</link>
      <description>Monangai led the Bears’ backfield in total yards this weekend, with a large portion of those coming on a 34-yard pass early in the third quarter. Monangai continues to split backfield work with D’Andre Swift, and appeared on just 10 fewer snaps than Swift. Monangai is a touchdown-dependent option who hasn’t scored since Week 13. Fantasy managers shouldn’t view him as anything more than low-end RB2 in Week 17 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5b-da28-afbb-ff7fc1120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahdae Walker caught 2-of-3 targets for 15 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 16 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5c-dc7a-af9b-ffffaa160000</link>
      <description>Walker, a UDFA out of Texas A&amp;M, found himself in an increased role on Saturday with Rome Odunze and Luther Burden both sidelined. Walker got on the board with his first career catch on the Bears’ opening drive, and scored his first touchdown on a six-yard pass near the end of regulation to tie the game at 16-16. Saturday’s performance was a nice outing for the rookie UDFA, but he won’t have any fantasy value heading into Week 17 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5c-dc7a-af9b-ffffaa160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 3-of-4 targets for 30 yards in the Bears’ Week 16 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5d-dc7a-af9b-ffff9a660000</link>
      <description>Even with Rome Odunze and Luther Burden both out, Loveland was unable to stand out in a passing game that was largely devoid of talent. Loveland saw just four targets on the day and turned them into 30 forgettable yards. Fantasy managers shouldn’t view him as anything more than a TE2 in Week 17 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f5d-dc7a-af9b-ffff9a660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon McManus went 3-for-3 on his field goal attempts in Week 16’s loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f6d-da28-afbb-ff7d75e40000</link>
      <description>McManus also converted on his only extra point of the evening. The veteran kicker nailed field goals from 26, 22, and 28 yards in this one, helping hold off the Bears just long enough for the Packers to build a 16-6 lead, but that evaporated in the final minutes of the fourth quarter. McManus has now converted on 22 of his 28 field goal attempts this season and will be a solid Week 17 option against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f6d-da28-afbb-ff7d75e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cairo Santos went 3-for-3 on his field goal attempts in Week 16’s win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f70-d087-addf-bff0af250000</link>
      <description>Santos came up clutch late for the Bears when he nailed a 51-yard field goal with just under 11 minutes to go in the fourth quarter, only come back and knock down a 43-yard field goal at the two-minute warning in the same quarter. Santos hit the Bears’ only PAT of the night to send them to overtime and has now made 24-of-29 field goals this season. He will be on the kicking radar in Week 16 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f70-d087-addf-bff0af250000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
