<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e857-dd4c-afb9-efd789020000</link>
      <description>Njoku would appear to be a long shot to suit up this week against the Dolphins. He left Week 6’s loss to the Steelers with the knee issue, and head coach Kevin Stefanski on Monday did not provide an update on his status. Harold Fannin would likely see an increase in routes and targets if Njoku is sidelined against Miami. The Browns have targeted the tight end position at a 33 percent rate this season, the second highest mark in the NFL. Fannin in Week 6 had seven receptions for 81 yards on ten targets. He’s an intriguing fantasy option against a Dolphins defense allowing 7.5 targets per game to opposing tight ends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e857-dd4c-afb9-efd789020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals palced TE Mike Gesicki (pec) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e85f-dd4c-afb9-efdf07e40000</link>
      <description>Gesicki will miss at least four games after sustaining a knee injury last week against the Packers. Noah Fant and Tanner HUdson split tight end routes after Gesicki exited the game; Hudson saw five targets while Fant saw four from Joe Flacco. Fant would be the slight favorite to be the team’s nominal TE1 going forward, as he’s been targeted on a strong 30 percent of his pass routes in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e85f-dd4c-afb9-efdf07e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter said Browns QB Deshaun Watson (Achilles) is “a good month away from being cleared for any football activity.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e870-db72-a199-fa7b5e310000</link>
      <description>That doesn’t mean, of course, that Watson will be ready to step in and start games for the Browns in December. But being cleared for football activities means he’s inching closer to a return after tearing his Achilles tendon twice over the past year. Watson, 30, has 19 touchdowns and 12 interceptions for the Browns over his three seasons with the team. It would be something of a surprise if the Browns gave him a start in the final month of the regular season. Dillon Gabriel remains the team’s starter for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e870-db72-a199-fa7b5e310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts head coach Shane Steichen said there’s no timetable for Anthony Richardson (eye) to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e881-def2-abdb-fde112b80000</link>
      <description>Richardson suffered a serious eye injury before the Colts’ Week 6 game against the Cardinals when an elastic workout band snapped and broke his orbital bone. The team placed Richardson on injured reserve, meaning he’ll miss at least one month. Steichen’s comments point to that absence being longer, however. Richardson, a former first-round draft pick, may have played his final game as a Colt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e881-def2-abdb-fde112b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Rashee Rice will have a “heavy workload” in Week 7 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e895-dd4c-afb9-efd5bf5c0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs have no plans to ease Rice back into the starting lineup after he was suspended for the season’s first six games. Rice, according to Fowler, “has been in the building for weeks, had an excellent training camp and is in peak physical shape. A team source says Rice will be ‘full bore’ this week as he gets back onto the practice field.” It sound like fantasy managers can expect something close to a full route share and Rice’s normal role as a dominator of intermediate targets from Patrick Mahomes against a vulnerable Vegas secondary. Rice’s return will likely hurt Travis Kelce’s targets as he loses out on those intermediate looks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e895-dd4c-afb9-efd5bf5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Chuba Hubbard and Rico Dowdle will split the workload in the team’s backfield.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e89a-db72-a199-fadbc36d0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers, per Fowler, “are taking the approach that both players will get their touches regardless of who gets the first snap. Both fit the Panthers’ tough-minded, grind-it-out mold.” The Panthers “want to be a run-first team, and since it’s a long season, they will need both players.” The Panthers before Hubbard’s calf injury would give him two drives, them Dowdle would get one. Those “rotations will inevitably change due to Dowdle’s star turn,” Fowlers said. It’ll be tough for the Panthers to sideline Dowdle after he racked up 473 total yards over his two starts. It wouldn’t be a shock if Dowdle functioned as the team’s nominal lead back for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e89a-db72-a199-fadbc36d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Reynolds (undisclosed) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3fb7d0000</link>
      <description>We’re not quite sure what injury Reynolds is dealing with ahead of the Jets’ Week 7 game against the Panthers. He was set to operate as the team’s WR1 over the next couple weeks with Garrett Wilson (knee) sidelined. If he’s unable to practice later in the week, the Jets could enter Week 7 with Arian Smith as their top wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3fb7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Puka Nacua (ankle) is a “long shot” to play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b2-dd4c-afb9-eff3cb120000</link>
      <description>Nacua in Week 6 against the Ravens “avoided major damage to his ankle ... but the people I’ve talked to believe he is a long shot Sunday against Jacksonville.” The team, according to Fowlers, is considering holding him out this week due to his physical playing style that might lead to further injury. Davante Adams, who leads the NFL in air yards, will be a top-10 fantasy option if Nacua is sidelined. The Rams could lean on Kyren Williams in a more run-heavy game plan if Nacua is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b2-dd4c-afb9-eff3cb120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowlers reports NFL teams “believe the Raiders are open to trading wide receiver Jakobi Meyers but are not actively trying to move him.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b7-d94a-a79d-e9bf29eb0000</link>
      <description>Meyers requested a trade back in August and has since played in all six of the team’s regular season game as a secondary and tertiary option for Geno Smith. “The sense is the Raiders would prefer to play out the season before making major determinations about the roster,” Fowlers said. Meyers hasn’t eclipsed 60 receiving yards since Week 3 and doesn’t have more than four receptions in any of his past three outings. Unless he’s dealt in the coming weeks, Meyers will be nothing more than a desperation flex play in a massively run-heavy Vegas offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b7-d94a-a79d-e9bf29eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8bb-d94a-a79d-e9bfe51a0000</link>
      <description>It’s yet to be determined whether McLaurin will be a full or limited practice participant ahead of the Commanders’ Week 7 game against the Cowboys. With his status very much up in the air, fantasy managers should have backup plans in case they have to go one more week with McLaurin sidelined. If he suits up, he’ll be a solid option against the league’s worst coverage unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8bb-d94a-a79d-e9bfe51a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
