<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 17 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</link>
      <description>Flowers was just able to get across the pylon on a connection with Tyler Huntley in the fourth quarter. The 25-year-old was a bit of an afterthought during Saturday’s contest, but that was true for every Raven not named Drrick Henry. He should again be the top option in the passing attack whether it’s Huntley or Lamar Jackson (back) throwing him the ball in Week 18 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 4-of-4 targets for 28 yards in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</link>
      <description>Andrews’ biggest play was drawing the Packers offsides while lining up under center on a fourth-and-inches play late in the contest. The Ravens only threw the ball for 107 yards in this contest, so there wasn’t much chance for Andrews, Isaiah Likely (3/27) or any of the Baltimore receivers in this one. He’ll be back in Week 18 against the Steelers in a game that’s meaning will be determined by what happens in Week 17 between Pittsburgh and the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins didn’t catch his only target in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-632d-d56e-afff-e7ed87bb0000</link>
      <description>Hopkins got a target in the end zone from Tyler Huntley that wasn’t partciularly close. The Ravens’ passing game did almost nothing in this contest, but didn’t need to with Derrick Henry scoring four times and rushing for 216 yards. Hopkins likely will have a similiar amount of chances in Week 18 against the Steelers even if Lamar Jackson (back) returns to action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-632d-d56e-afff-e7ed87bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 5-of-6 targets for 113 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6331-d56e-afff-e7f9580d0000</link>
      <description>Watson scored on a 39-yard connection with Malik Willis on the Packers’ first drive of the game. The two made a few more connections in the contest in a solid effort where Watson didn’t appear to be bothered by his shoulder or the illness he picked up earlier in the week. Watson and the Packers get a game with essentially zero playoff ramifications against the Vikings in Week 18 to end the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6331-d56e-afff-e7f9580d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed four times for three yards in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens while adding one catch for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6336-d56e-afff-e7fe790a0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was off the injury report after dealing with knee and ankle issues in previous weeks, but whether it was due to those ailments, a faltering offensive line or a great effort from the Baltimore front — likely a combination of all three — the 27-year-old tailback was able to get nothing done. The Packers have nothing to play for in Week 18 against the Lions, so no one should be surprised if it is Emmanuel Wilson (3/16) who gets most of the touches in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6336-d56e-afff-e7fe790a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 3-of-3 targets for 62 yards in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633b-dc7a-af9b-efbf3b3b0000</link>
      <description>Doubs did most of the damage on a 40-yard connection in the first quarter with Malik Willis that set up a touchdown pass to Christian Watson. The 25-year-old played fiddle between Watson and Jayden Reed for the rest of the contest, but fantasy managers at least got the one long reception. He’ll be back at it in Week 18 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633b-dc7a-af9b-efbf3b3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught 4-of-4 targets for 41 yards in the Packers’ Week 18 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633d-d968-a19b-7bfd29170000</link>
      <description>Reed picked up the overwhelming majority of the yards on a 30-yard pass from Malik Willis. The 25-year-old was second among Packers’ receivers in targets behind the six to Christian Watson, but he picked up just 11 yards on his other three receptions. Reed and the Packers will finish off the regular season against the Vikings in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633d-d968-a19b-7bfd29170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) will play in Week 17 against the Bengals, but his snaps will be managed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-651b-dc7a-af9b-efbf997a0000</link>
      <description>Harrison Jr. played through the heel issue last week. He was on a pitch count for that game as well, taking the field for 29-of-47 offensive snaps. MHJ was largely subbed out on running plays. He still logged a route rate of 79 percent. The biggest change in the offense with his return was the decline of Michael Wilson, who had been putting up WR1 numbers in MHJ’s absence. Wilson was relegated to field-stretching duties, though he did manage to find the end zone on one of his two grabs. MHJ is barely a WR5 after seeing just three targets last week. Wilson isn’t much higher in the ranks, having also seen three looks in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-651b-dc7a-af9b-efbf997a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Ashton Jeanty will play in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6521-dc7a-af9b-efbfc8ab0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty isn’t dealing with any injuries right now. The Raiders are simply tanking so effectively that Schefter felt the need to mention he won’t be getting the day off. Vegas has already shut down Brock Bowers and Maxx Crosby. Both players had been playing through their respective injuries for weeks. The Raiders’ game versus the Giants today will determine the No. 1 overall pick, making Week 17 the perfect time for the team to put the pair of star players on ice. With no injuries of note this year, the Raiders couldn’t find a reason to do the same for Jeanty. Coming off a 188-yard, two-score explosion in Week 16, Jeanty is back in our RB1 good graces versus New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6521-dc7a-af9b-efbfc8ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports George Kittle “will test out his ankle pregame to see if he can go” in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6528-d56e-afff-e7e86d5b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added that Kittle is intent on testing out his ankle. He didn’t mention whether or not the 49ers wanted him to give it a go. Kittle didn’t practice once this week, which is typically a sign that a player won’t suit up. It sounds like Kittle is pushing to play, but we wouldn’t be surprised if the team forces him to take the week off. If Kittle is ultimately inactive, Jake Tonges would take over the starting job for Week 17. Tonges would have some TE2 appeal in a possible shootout with Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6528-d56e-afff-e7e86d5b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
