<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) is not expected to play in Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d86c-dd4c-afb9-ffed74840000</link>
      <description>Sanders is still working his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. He got in a full practice on Thursday but returned to a limited status on Friday before being listed as questionable. The Panthers are being cautious with his return, but he should be available in Week 7. Tommy Tremble and Mitchell Evans will split the tight end snaps versus Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d86c-dd4c-afb9-ffed74840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers activated S Malik Mustapha (knee) from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d870-d94a-a79d-d97d6a2e0000</link>
      <description>Mustapha aggrevated a previously torn ACL late last year and opened the 2025 season on the PUP list while recovering. He practiced in full three times this week before being cleared for action. Mustapha appeared in 16 games with a rookie and was credited with 12 starts. He broke up five passes and stole one interception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d870-d94a-a79d-d97d6a2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Brock Bowers (knee) is “unlikely” to play in Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d877-def2-abdb-dd77c18f0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders get their bye in Week 8. Bowers is dealing with a PCL injury and a bone bruise in his knee. He tried to play through them for a few weeks but eventually needed to be sat down. Assuming he misses Week 7, Bowers will get a month to recover from the knee issues. That is likely what should have happened in the first place. Michael Mayer will start in his place until Bowers returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d877-def2-abdb-dd77c18f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports “there have been no serious discussions about benching” Geno Smith.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d87c-dd4c-afb9-fffd7f320000</link>
      <description>Pete Carroll’s “I am not benching Geno Smith” shirt is raising a lot of questions already answered by the shirt. Geno has nine interceptions and 16 sacks this year. He leads the league in picks and isn’t far off in sacks. The Raiders, in turn, are riding a four-game losing streak. Smith will get benched if this level of play continues, but turning to Kenny Pickett isn’t going to turn the Raiders’ season around. Carroll will give Smith every opportunity to right the ship before pulling the plug in favor of Pickett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d87c-dd4c-afb9-fffd7f320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Bengals “checked in on” Derek Carr before trading for Joe Flacco.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d882-dd4c-afb9-ffc3d50b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport noted that Cincy called nearly every team with three viable quarterbacks on the roster, so Carr was simply one of many names on a long list. Rapport also mentioned Sam Howell and Davis Mills as options. It’s unclear if the Bengals moved on from Carr after he told them he plans to stay retired or if the Saints turned down a potential trade. New Orleans still holds Carr’s rights despite his retirement. Either way, the fact that Carr didn’t come out of retirement to throw to Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins suggests he truly is done with football. If there were ever going to be a situation to lure him off the coach, it would have been this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d882-dd4c-afb9-ffc3d50b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Ravens are “hopeful” Lamar Jackson (hamstring) returns after the team’s Week 7 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d888-dd4c-afb9-ffc974970000</link>
      <description>Jackson is out again this week as he nurses the hamstring issue. Jackson has yet to practice since suffering the injury, but Pelissero did note that he has been doing rehab work at the Ravens’ facility. It isn’t expected to be a long-term issue, and the bye week should give Jackson enough rest time to get back on the field in Week 8 versus the Bears. Cooper Rush will start against the Rams this week. Rush was picked apart by Houston in his first start, throwing three interceptions in a 34-point loss. He isn’t on the fantasy radar, even in Superflex leagues, for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d888-dd4c-afb9-ffc974970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Saints are not expected to trade Alvin Kamara.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d88e-d94a-a79d-d98fb8690000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Saints GM Mickey Loomis asked Kamara directly if he wanted to be traded. The star running back told him he wants to stay in New Orleans for the entirety of his career. Kamara has been the subject of trade rumors for years and the team has already received calls about him this season. At 1-4, it makes sense for them to look toward the future and move on from aging veterans, but Loomis isn’t exactly known for win-later deals. A Kamara trade would mean a workhorse role for Kendre Miller, but that doesn’t appear to be happening anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d88e-d94a-a79d-d98fb8690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Omarion Hampton (ankle) is expected to miss “more than four weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d894-def2-abdb-ddf5f2d30000</link>
      <description>The Chargers placed him on injured reserve after he went down with an ankle injury in Week 5. That means he is required to miss at least four games, though that should now be considered the floor for how many weeks he misses. Fantasy managers should plan on being without the rookie for well over a month. Hassan Haskins will draw the start this week, but the Chargers are reportedly interested in trading for a running back to backfill the losses of Hampton and Najee Harris. Haskins could only be the starter for a week if the team makes a move after Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d894-def2-abdb-ddf5f2d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Chargers RB Hassan Haskins “is expected to be the lead back” in Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d89b-d94a-a79d-d99f1a9c0000</link>
      <description>Garafolo noted that Kimani Vidal will also “get some action.” While we’re still expecting a committee in LA, Haskins is the clear bet to make for fantasy purposes. He should handle the bulk of the carries and is facing a Miami defense that was just gashed for 206 yards by Rico Dowdle. Haskins is a high-variance RB3 this week while Vidal is buried in the RB5 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d89b-d94a-a79d-d99f1a9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports CeeDee Lamb (ankle) “has a chance to play” in Week 7 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d8a0-d94a-a79d-d9ad1c7a0000</link>
      <description>One of Pelissero’s sources describes his odds of playing as 50/50. Lamb went down with the ankle injury in Week 3 and has been out ever since. He hasn’t returned to practice yet but is reportedly making progress. George Pickens has stepped up in Lamb’s absence with 10 catches for 191 yards and three scores over the past two weeks. He will get at least one more game as a high-end WR2 today versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d8a0-d94a-a79d-d9ad1c7a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
