<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) is questionable to play in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fca-d713-ad9e-7fde01d30000</link>
      <description>Barner has emerged as a weekly, touchdown-dependent TE1 candidate while rookie TE Elijah Arroyo (elbow) plays efficiently behind him. Arroyo is good to go this week, so if Barner is ultimately ruled out, the rookie can be treated as a streaming TE1 option against the Cardinals. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fca-d713-ad9e-7fde01d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans T Tytus Howard (concussion) will not play in Houston’s Week 10 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603f-d673-a39e-e4bfd0140000</link>
      <description>Neither will Ed Ingram (knee), making way for Juice Scruggs and Blake Fisher to join the starting lineup. Davis Mills’ supporting cast isn’t going to be doing the quarterback any favors in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603f-d673-a39e-e4bfd0140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb (foot) is not on Houston’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6041-d45b-affe-75d719300000</link>
      <description>He’ll take his normal load as Houston’s RB1. The Texans will probably try to lean on the run more than usual against the Jaguars with Davis Mills under center, but unless they catch an early lead, it’s hard to see Chubb returning more than touchdown-or-bust FLEX value this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6041-d45b-affe-75d719300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE Elijah Arroyo (elbow) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603f-d45b-affe-75bfaef80000</link>
      <description>Arroyo finally banked a top-12, hall-PPR positional finish against the Commanders last week. He has a chance to do so again if veteran TE AJ Barner (calf), who is questionable to play, sits out this week. Should Barner suit up, Arroyo would be dropped back into the touchdown-dependent TE2 category. The promising rookie is averaging 1.52 yards per route run to Barner’s 1.53.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603f-d45b-affe-75bfaef80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) is not on Houston’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6042-d45b-affe-75d656e80000</link>
      <description>The veteran tight end was able to practice in full each of the final two days of the week. Houston’s non-Nico Collins options in the passing game tend to be matchup-prone and Davis Mills’ ascension shouldn’t make anyone feel great about riding with Schultz as a TE1 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6042-d45b-affe-75d656e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans EDGE Will Anderson (quad) is not on Houston’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6043-d1e7-a1fa-7aebf17c0000</link>
      <description>He will be around to harass Trevor Lawrence on Sunday. Jalen Pitre (concussion) was ruled out, giving some extra space for Parker Washington to move around in the slot against Houston’s backup cornerbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6043-d1e7-a1fa-7aebf17c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Chargers</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603e-d45b-affe-75beb6740000</link>
      <description>The Steelers will have their EDGE defender on the field in this one. Highsmith has totaled 15 quarterback pressures, four sacks and 16 tackles this year, while the Steelers attempt to restore their defense’s reputation. Doing so against the Chargers is no small feat, and should perhaps be viewed as unlikely to happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-603e-d45b-affe-75beb6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6048-d713-ad9e-6c5c9f470000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars will have one of their starting perimeter wide receivers on the field this week. Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) and WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee, injured reserve) are both out. Brown sneaks onto the FLEX radar against a stout Texans defense this week, earning targets against slot WR Parker Washington and newcomer WR Jakobi Meyers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6048-d713-ad9e-6c5c9f470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars ruled out TE Hunter Long (hip/knee) for Week 10 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6046-d45b-affe-75d6a07e0000</link>
      <description>Long has been filling in for TE Brenton Strange (hip/quad), but has yet to earn more than three targets in a game, so his absence is hardly consequential. Jaguars TE Johnny Mundt is the next man up, though he should not be considered for TE1 purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6046-d45b-affe-75d6a07e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) will not play in Arizona’s Week 10 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6052-d1e7-a1fa-7afa50780000</link>
      <description>Neither will (inhale): CB Max Melton (concussion), LB BJ Ojulari (knee), or LB Mack Wilson (ribs) — the good news is that Budda Baker (hamstring) upgraded to full today and has been removed from the injury report. Arizona’s defense looked good against the Cowboys on Monday night, but their cornerback depth will be tested against Jaxson Smith-Njigba and Rashid Shaheed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6052-d1e7-a1fa-7afa50780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
