<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE Josh Oliver (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5afe-d45b-affe-5ffeba950000</link>
      <description>That makes two more DNPs in a row for Oliver, who has not practiced since hurting the foot in Week 8. He doesn’t seem to be on track for a return this week, but Kevin O’Connell said he’d begin working on a side field at some point this week. Perhaps Week 11 is a more realistic timetable for the veteran tight end at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5afe-d45b-affe-5ffeba950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5af7-d1e7-a1fa-5aff89280000</link>
      <description>Fannin was not seen practicing with the team earlier today. Now we know why. A full Thursday downgrade suggests he is highly unlikely to play in Week 10 against the Jets, vaulting TE David Njoku up the TE1 ranks. Browns WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) should also return from injured reserve this week, though he profiles as only a boom-bust FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5af7-d1e7-a1fa-5aff89280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b01-d713-ad9e-7f550db00000</link>
      <description>We haven’t heard much on Stevenson over the past few days, but there’s also likely no good news to report. Stevenson feels overwhelming likely to be ruled out and cede carries to TreVeyon Henderson and Terrell Jennings again this week. Henderson will have an RB2 case against the Buccaneers, while Jennings’ red zone role makes him a viable FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b01-d713-ad9e-7f550db00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b0e-d713-ad9e-7f5e2c070000</link>
      <description>It’s looking increasingly likely that the veteran outside receiver will sit out this week. Rookie Kyle Williams saw increased run behind Boutte last week after Boutte’s injury and figures to be the main replacement, but there’s no rush to pick him up in fantasy leagues since he hasn’t contributed much to the offense thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b0e-d713-ad9e-7f5e2c070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE Leonard Floyd (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b0c-d673-a39e-ff9d7a060000</link>
      <description>Floyd ties for a team-high 19 quarterback pressures, with two sacks to boot. He also has just two tackles, but remains an impactful pass rusher nonetheless. The Falcons were also without LG Matthew Bergeron (ankle) on Thursday. They play the Colts overseas in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b0c-d673-a39e-ff9d7a060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans EDGE Will Anderson (quad) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b12-d713-ad9e-7f5689580000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade for Anderson after Wednesday’s DNP, it seems like there’s a real chance he’ll be one of the few Texans on the injury report to actually play in this week’s game against Jacksonville. Jalen Pitre (concussion) DNPed for a second day in a row, while Denico Autry (knee) also upgraded to limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b12-d713-ad9e-7f5689580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b05-d673-a39e-ff959eaa0000</link>
      <description>The Saints continue to limit Kamara in practice, though the limited reps seem to have little impact on his in-game performance. The 30-year-old running back faces the Panthers this weekend, whose star DE Derrick Brown (elbow) notably appeared on the injury report today. Were Brown to miss the game, Kamara could have an easier time running up the middle, though he would remain an RB3 in the ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b05-d673-a39e-ff959eaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (foot) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b14-d1e7-a1fa-5bfe7c5b0000</link>
      <description>Chubb is probably in line to remain the starter over Woody Marks for Houston’s do-nothing run attack in Week 10. Dameon Pierce (personal) was also limited today, and should that linger on it would likely force the Texans to get deeper into their bench if Chubb can’t go on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b14-d1e7-a1fa-5bfe7c5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b16-d1e7-a1fa-5bfe00420000</link>
      <description>He’ll be one of many secondary targets for the Texans on Sunday as Davis Mills makes his first start of the season and tries to keep the wheels from completely careening off into the ditch. No pressure, Davis. We wouldn’t excitedly start any non-Nico Collins Texans receivers in fantasy this week, though Schultz has a TE2 case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b16-d1e7-a1fa-5bfe00420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b20-d713-ad9e-7f74a86e0000</link>
      <description>Barring a setback, Brown should be available for the Jaguars’ Week 10 game against the Texans. Brown and recent acquisition, WR Jakobi Meyers, will man the perimeter while WR Parker Washington lines up in the slot. The latter player is seemingly the best bet to lead the team in targets, while WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) is expectedly stuck on the sideline after failing to practice on Wednesday and Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b20-d713-ad9e-7f74a86e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
