<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 21:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said EDGE Nik Bonitto underwent surgery because he “had a little spur” in his foot and the “goal” is to have him back next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9dd-df63-a199-f9ffd3f20000</link>
      <description>The small procedure reportedly required three stitches. Bonitto and the Broncos are currently in talks about a possible extension following his 15-sack season in 2024. Hopefully, the talented pass rusher returns without issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9dd-df63-a199-f9ffd3f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) is dealing with scar tissue but is expected to increase his training camp participation next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99e-d90d-a5bd-abdfe63d0000</link>
      <description>Payton also told us Greenlaw would return “next week” on August 1st. He has at least been spotted wearing pads at practice recently, so the claim is more plausible this time around. The fact that Greenlaw is dealing with scar tissue certainly isn’t great though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99e-d90d-a5bd-abdfe63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said the team believes DT CJ West is “going to be all right” after hyperextending his knee on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa14-df63-a199-fb3fbc070000</link>
      <description>Shanahan said West’s ACL appears to be intact after undergoing initial tests, saying West suffered an injury similar to that of DL Mykel Williams. The team used fourth- and first-round picks on West and Williams, respectively, this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa14-df63-a199-fb3fbc070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports that Browns RB Quinshon Judkins “will not face any formal charges, as prosecutors have declined to move forward with the case.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9ee-d05a-adda-abeeabdc0000</link>
      <description>Per Schultz, “this clears the way for him to return to the team,” which is likely to happen “in the near future.” Judkins was previously charged with misdemeanor domestic battery. He and his agent will ostensibly begin negotiating his rookie contract with the Browns’ front office. If Judkins rejoins the Browns and practices before Week 1, he could be the team’s primary back, limiting Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson to RB2/3 duties in what should be a pass-heavy Cleveland offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9ee-d05a-adda-abeeabdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Matthew Stafford (back) will work out on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa2d-d90d-a5bd-aa7f5b9a0000</link>
      <description>The workout will be similar to what he did on August 9th, when he threw more than 60 passes. The team used that workout to assess whether Stafford was ready to resume practicing. Unfortunately, he wasn’t. McVay hopes Stafford’s back “responds a little bit better” this time around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa2d-d90d-a5bd-aa7f5b9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Scherff retired after 10 seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa33-df63-a199-fb3b379f0000</link>
      <description>Scherff retires with five Pro Bowl nominations, one first-team All-Pro honor and a 2015 PFWA All-Rookie Team award on his mantle. He spent his first seven seasons in the NFL playing for the Commanders, who drafted him fifth overall. He spent his remaining three seasons with the Jaguars. The former offensive guard was recently inducted into the Iowa Athletics Hall of Fame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa33-df63-a199-fb3b379f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy will not play in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa3e-df63-a199-fb3fb2f00000</link>
      <description>McCarthy played well last week, and the Vikings no doubt want to avoid him suffering another preseason injury. The strong-armed Howell gets the start instead, which should make for fun viewing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa3e-df63-a199-fb3fb2f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said most starters, including Justin Herbert, will play in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa46-d90d-a5bd-aa5f8d420000</link>
      <description>Observing Herbert’s connection with his recently revamped receiving corps will be worthwhile for fantasy managers. Keenan Allen’s return to the lineup could have a fantasy-unfriendly effect on players like Quentin Johnston, Tre’ Harris and KeAndre Lambert-Smith. Derwin James and Khalil Mack are the only two starters who will not play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa46-d90d-a5bd-aa5f8d420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs left Colts’ practice early after suffering a hamstring injury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</link>
      <description>This is somewhat concerning. A soft tissue strain suffered in mid-August could have early-season ramifications. The Athletic’s James Boyd reports, Downs “came off during one of the team periods complaining about pain in his hamstring” and headed straight toward the team’s trainers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa56-df63-a199-fb7f629a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the NFL “will continue its own investigation” into Browns RB Quinshon Judkins’ misdemeanor domestic battery charge.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</link>
      <description>If Judkins begins practicing with the team before the regular season kicks off, he can still seize the team’s lead rushing role. The NFL’s investigation could still result in a suspension, however, though the expected timeline for said investigation is currently unknown. Nos. 2 and 3 RBs, Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson, make for precarious fantasy football draft picks at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa55-d45c-a7fc-aa5f621e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
