<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e78-dfde-a1bd-5efdc0290000</link>
      <description>Wednesday absences often become non-issues. Thursday absences have a much worse track record. It’s possible the Buccaneers are just exercising an abundance of caution, but fantasy managers should expect to be without Egbuka in Week 3. If the talented rookie wide receiver can somehow practice in full tomorrow, he can be started as usual. If he graduates to limited participation, this could come down to being a game-time decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e78-dfde-a1bd-5efdc0290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e7e-d93f-ad9d-5eff5fce0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like there’s much concern that Jacobs will miss Week 3, and he’ll be an easy RB1 against the Browns should he suit up. Backup runner Chris Brooks played on only 13 snaps and 11 of them were passing routes. Emanuel Wilson would likely be the head of a committee on running downs if Jacobs, for whatever reason, did not play in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e7e-d93f-ad9d-5eff5fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers placed RT Luke Goedeke (foot) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e5b-d93f-ad9d-5edf795d0000</link>
      <description>Goedeke is expected to return later this season. He will be eligible to do so after missing four games. It’s a brutal development for a Buccaneers offensive line that also lost RG Cody Mauch to a season-ending knee injury. Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (knee) has not yet suited up on game day. He remains limited in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e5b-d93f-ad9d-5edf795d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e80-d1b3-a5dd-5ff1e6b50000</link>
      <description>It would be nice to see Worthy graduate to full practice participation, but he has at least logged four straight limited sessions, dating back to last week. We expect the Chiefs to require him to practice in full before he retakes the field on game day, but it’s possible they ease him in on a limited snap count.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e80-d1b3-a5dd-5ff1e6b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8a-dfde-a1bd-5e8f8c300000</link>
      <description>Royals’ tendinitis has responded positively after a few weeks of rehab and he is now on track to at least be available for the Chiefs’ Week 3 game against the Giants. He can be speculatively stashed on fantasy benches this week, to see how things shake out. Kansas City’s passing offense is in need of reliable weapons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8a-dfde-a1bd-5e8f8c300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (wrist) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e95-d1b3-a5dd-5ff557210000</link>
      <description>Interpreting downgrades can be tricky. It’s entirely possible that the Jaguars’ coaching staff is just managing Thomas’ reps. It’s also possible he experienced irritation and/or a setback. The latter scenario seems unlikely, given the lack of alarm bells from Jaguars beat reporters. We expect Thomas to practice in full tomorrow, but this is clearly worth monitoring. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e95-d1b3-a5dd-5ff557210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (shoulder) was seen wearing a red non-contact jersey as he practiced in a limited capacity on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea3-dfde-a1bd-5eafa8f70000</link>
      <description>Tuten’s continued limited participation puts him on track to suit up in Week 3 against the Texans. The red non-contact jersey is a bit concerning, though. Hopefully, Tuten practices in full tomorrow and can safely be started as a high-upside FLEX option, operating as the Jaguars’ oft-used backup running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea3-dfde-a1bd-5eafa8f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Jeremy McNichols (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea8-d6a5-adff-feed44090000</link>
      <description>McNichols will likely get a chance to replace Austin Ekeler (Achilles) as the Commanders’ passing game specialist. He was terribly inefficient as a receiver last season, averaging just 0.20 yards per route run. He can be stashed in PPR leagues by those willing to roll the dice on a likely low-ceiling player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea8-d6a5-adff-feed44090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb1-d93f-ad9d-5ef75de80000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw practiced in full yesterday, but The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reported earlier this week that Darrisaw is not guaranteed to play in Week 3 against the Bengals. We think today is likely just a rest day in his long-running rehab program. Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) remains sidelined, as does backup LT Justin Skule (concussion).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb1-d93f-ad9d-5ef75de80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb5-d6a5-adff-fef5ae600000</link>
      <description>Goedert is clearly still bothered by the knee injury but his continued limited participation puts him on track to play in Week 3 against the Rams. The two talented offenses could produce a pass-heavy game environment. If active, Goedert can be started as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb5-d6a5-adff-fef5ae600000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
