<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:05:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Olamide Zaccheaus (illness) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-d968-a19b-7efb1cd40000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus was sidelined by the illness in Week 17. Fortunately, he is now on track to play. Whether Zaccheaus warrants long-shot FLEX consideration depends largely on his teammates’ health and availability. Bears WR Luther Burden (quad) was limited today, while WR Rome Odunze (foot) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-d968-a19b-7efb1cd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769b-d56e-afff-f6fb77820000</link>
      <description>Goedert dealt with a knee issue much earlier in the year. It’s unclear if the two injuries are related. Either way, we fully expect him to get the week off. Nick Sirianni has already said he will rest some of his starters for a mostly meaningless Week 18 contest. Now dealing with a knee injury, Goedert is the perfect candidate to spend a week on the bench. Grant Calcaterra will take his place in the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769b-d56e-afff-f6fb77820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers will ponder his future in the NFL after the 2025 season ends.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769a-d968-a19b-7efb9cb20000</link>
      <description>Rodgers told ESPN’s Brooke Pryor that he has not yet “thought about” whether he would like to return to the Steelers, or even continue playing in the NFL, next year. The Steelers (9-7) sit atop the AFC North. If they beat the Ravens (8-8) this week, they punch their ticket to the postseason. Once the Steelers’ season comes to a close, the veteran quarterback will begin considering his options. He signed a one-year, $13.65 million contract with the Steelers last offseason and will enter free agency at the end of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769a-d968-a19b-7efb9cb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Breece Hall (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76a6-d968-a19b-7ef787700000</link>
      <description>Hall told reporters that his knee was fine post-game. Hopefully, this is just a maintenance day, but his practice participation is worth following. His backup, RB Isaiah Davis (concussion), was also sidelined on Wednesday. The Jets list RBs Kene Nwangwu (quad) and Khalil Herbert in the Nos. 3 and 4 spots, respectively. Nwangwu is practicing fully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76a6-d968-a19b-7ef787700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Isaiah Davis (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76a6-d35e-a1bf-77e6c6c90000</link>
      <description>Starting RB Breece Hall (knee) was also sidelined by a knee injury, though he told reporters post-game that his knee is fine. Whether he can play on Sunday remains to be seen. Jets RB Kene Nwangwu (quad) is listed as the next man up, with RB Khalil Herbert seated behind him on the depth chart. Nwangwu is practicing fully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76a6-d35e-a1bf-77e6c6c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (illness) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ac-dc7a-af9b-ffbf12c40000</link>
      <description>Players infrequently miss games due to illness, so we expect Olave to be active on game day. This is worth keeping an eye on, though. The Saints’ No. 1 wide receiver has earned a career-high 151 targets this season, the third-most in the NFL. He is a WR1 against the Falcons, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ac-dc7a-af9b-ffbf12c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ba-d968-a19b-7efb58ff0000</link>
      <description>Kamara has neither practiced nor played since spraining his MCL in Week 12. He was already dealing with an ankle injury at that time. We expect him to remain sidelined in Week 18 against the Falcons. Saints RB Audric Estime will again operate as the team’s starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ba-d968-a19b-7efb58ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders LT Kolton Miller (ankle) reverted to injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ba-d56e-afff-f6fa50e60000</link>
      <description>Miller’s 21-day practice window expired. His season is over. It is yet another unfortunate development in the Raiders’ lost 2025 season. Miller has been sidelined since suffering a high-ankle sprain and a hairline fracture in Week 4 against the Bears. His 89.8 PFF pass-blocking grade ranks second among offensive tackles with at least 250 blocking snaps. He turns 31 in September 2026. Hopefully, he can return to form next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ba-d56e-afff-f6fa50e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll said Geno Smith (ankle) will not play Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c6-dc7a-af9b-ffffce3f0000</link>
      <description>It appears as though Smith’s season is over. Earlier today, Vegas Nation’s Vincent Bonsignore reported that the Raiders will use “a combination of Kenny Pickett and Aidan O’Connell” this week. Neither player should be in starting lineups, in what sounds like some sort of game-day platoon. In his first season with the Raiders, Smith completed 302-of-448 passes for 3,025 yards, 19 touchdowns and 17 interceptions, while rushing 41 times for 109 yards. He is under contract through 2027, though he is owed no money that season. If the Raiders were to cut him this offseason, it would cost them $18.5 million in dead money while saving them $8 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c6-dc7a-af9b-ffffce3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jack Bech (back) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d9-d56e-afff-f6f944b30000</link>
      <description>Bech is back. Whether that means much for the Raiders’ Week 18 outlook remains to be seen. The underwhelming rookie will at least have a chance to put a good game on film for whichever coaching staff is there to review it in 2026, though. Bech is a low-floor FLEX this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d9-d56e-afff-f6f944b30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
