<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested to interview Eagles DB coach and pass game coordinator Christian Parker for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdb2-d968-a19b-fdf3166e0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Todd Archer notes that Parker is the seventh known candidate for the position. Parker interviewed for the Saints’ defensive coordinator vacancy last year, after his first season in his current roles with the Eagles. He previously coached the Broncos’ defensive backs from 2021-2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdb2-d968-a19b-fdf3166e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said he anticipates CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) will be on the practice field today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdbb-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3c460000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez is currently in the league’s concussion protocol and will presumably be limited in today’s practice. Still, it’s a step in the right direction from one of New England’s best defenders. Gonzalez suffered the brain injury versus the Chargers in the Wild Card Round and did not return. He tallied 10 pass breakups and 69 combined tackles during the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdbb-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed S Darrick Forrest, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdae-d35e-a1bf-fdee28ea0000</link>
      <description>Forrest spent time on the Bills, Colts and Steelers’ practice squads this season. He was on the Commanders’ roster from 2021-2024, posting career-bests in pass break-ups (five), interceptions (four) and tackles (66) in 2022. The 49ers also signed TE Hayden Rucci to the practice squad, released WR Javon Baker and signed WR Colton Dowell to a reserve/future contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdae-d35e-a1bf-fdee28ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons will interview former Raiders head coach Antonio Pierce for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdbd-dc7a-af9b-ffbf09be0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo notes that Pierce previously worked with Falcons president of football Matt Ryan at CBS Sports. Pierce served as the Raiders’ head coach in the NFL in 2024, after assuming interim head-coaching duties in 2023. His 2024 Raiders squad went 4-13, and he was fired in January 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdbd-dc7a-af9b-ffbf09be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdc0-d35e-a1bf-fdc223230000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase has quietly become a popular man on the head coaching circuit. The Ravens, Raiders, and Browns have all requested interviews with him. He received multiple offensive coordinator interviews last offseason but chose to stay with the Rams, at which point the team promoted him to his current position. The move, or lack thereof, proved prescient. LA led the league in scoring this year and Matthew Stafford is likely going to earn his first career MVP award. Scheelhaase would be a stark departure from the style of Mike Tomlin, but maybe that’s what Pittsburgh needs after nearly a decade without a postseason win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdc0-d35e-a1bf-fdc223230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdc9-d968-a19b-fdf979190000</link>
      <description>The Steelers are also interviewing Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase. Smart moves. Shula has worked his way up the Rams’ coaching ranks since signing on as the team’s assistant linebackers coach in 2017, serving in his current position since 2024. Shula’s 2025 defense allowed 5.2 yards per play in the regular season, the 14th lowest number in the NFL, while generating pressure at the league’s fourth-highest rate (41.1 percent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdc9-d968-a19b-fdf979190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (concussion) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bde6-d35e-a1bf-fde6e1390000</link>
      <description>Collins’ head slammed into the ground during the third quarter of the Texans’ Wild Card Round win over the Steelers. He rode a cart to the locker room, did not return, and has since entered concussion protocol. Assuming he doesn’t make a late appearance at practice today, Collins looks unlikely to suit up for the Divisional Round. Christian Kirk erupted for 144 yards and a touchdown on eight grabs last week. He is in line for WR1 duties if Nico is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bde6-d35e-a1bf-fde6e1390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested an interview with Giants interim DC Charlie Bullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdf3-d35e-a1bf-fdf3bb480000</link>
      <description>Bullen was promoted from OLB coach to interim defensive coordinator and assigned play-calling duties in Week 13. The Giants allowed the third-most yards per play in Weeks 1-12 (6.1) while ranking 23rd in quarterback pressure rate (32.9 percent). With Bullen at the helm, the Giants reduced the former figure to 5.1 and increased the latter to 39.9 percent. This could be a smart move for the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdf3-d35e-a1bf-fdf3bb480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers president Art Rooney II said he is “not sure why you waste a year of your life not trying to contend” when asked about the team taking a year to rebuild.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdef-dc7a-af9b-ffffce910000</link>
      <description>The Steelers desperately need a year or two to retool the roster, but it should surprise no one that Rooney isn’t willing to commit to an uncompetitive 2026. He did, however, acknowledge the fact that the team isn’t always in a position to win a Super Bowl, saying, “I think you try every year. Some years you have the horses to really get there. Some years you don’t, but you try every year, in my view.” The Steelers are interviewing both Rams coordinators and will bring in plenty of other big names in the next few weeks. Assuming Aaron Rodgers is gone, they will also need to figure out their quarterback situation once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdef-dc7a-af9b-ffffce910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports the Giants are making a “massive push” to sign John Harbaugh for their head coaching vacancy today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdff-d968-a19b-fdff8ffd0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh is currently in New York, meeting with Giants ownership, and they clearly don’t want him walking out of the building without a deal. Per Hughes, “They’re willing to not only pay him, but also whatever his staff wants.” A blank check plus a roster with the quarterback position already figuired out will be hard to turn down. Harbaugh, however, is also being pursued by the Titans and Falcons. Neither job looks as enticing on paper, but it would make sense for him to hear them out, even if that is just to drive up his asking price for the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bdff-d968-a19b-fdff8ffd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
