<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Essentially Sports’ Tony Pauline reports the “overwhelming belief” from people he has spoken to is that the Dolphins favor signing free agent QB Malik Willis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b35-d990-a1de-ef7f7fa40000</link>
      <description>It’s not a typical source for us, but what Pauline is reporting aligns with the already widely-held belief that newly minted head coach Jeff Hafley and general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan, who were previously with the Packers, would pursue Willis in free agency. Pauline also notes that many believe Willis will ultimately sign with the Cardinals, who are expected to move on from Kyler Murray. Willis had a solid two-year stint with the Packers and flashed in limited action. So much so, that he’s expected to sign a multi-year deal this offseason and be the unquestioned QB1 for a team in 2026. Willis threw for 972-60-0 on 89 pass attempts in two seasons with the Packers while adding another 42-261-3 on the ground. Wherever he signs, his next team will hope the tremendous improvement he showed in a small sample size will translate into long-term success for him and their organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b35-d990-a1de-ef7f7fa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essentially Sports’ Tony Pauline reports Dolphins OC Bobby Slowik “is a big fan of Quinn Ewers.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b49-d89c-a1be-afdf24e20000</link>
      <description>According to Pauline, Ewers could be the Dolphins’ preferred option at QB in 2026 if the team is unable to sign Malik Willis this offseason. Ewers threw for 622-3-3 in four games with the Dolphins last season while making three starts. The rookie seventh-rounder was also sacked eight times on just 31 pressures and fumbled the ball three times. Slowik and the Dolphins could have limited options available to them to improve their QB room this offseason, so it wouldn’t be surprising if Ewers did work his way into the starting lineup if the Fins are unable to land their preferred option at QB in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b49-d89c-a1be-afdf24e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports the Jets “would like to sign Breece Hall to an extension” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b5c-d629-a1bc-bb5d72ae0000</link>
      <description>Cimini notes that this would be the ideal situation for the Jets, while also pointing out that Hall has “been dropping hints for months that he might want to move on” from Gang Green. Hall’s impending free agency includes a handful of scenarios that could play out. While he could re-sign with the Jets outright, it’s also possible the team lets him walk, uses the franchise tag to keep him in place and potentially buy time for a long-term deal or a trade, or they could use the transition tag which allows Hall to seek other deals while giving the Jets the right of first refusal to match any offer Hall may receive. Hall would be a coveted running back on the open market, and has bell cow back traits that allow him to stay on the field for all three downs. He’ll only be 25 at the start of this season, and has appeared in 16 or more games in each of the last three seasons since tearing his ACL as a rookie in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b5c-d629-a1bc-bb5d72ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team will place the franchise tag on George Pickens some time next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b81-d990-a1de-efcff4850000</link>
      <description>All signs have pointed to the Cowboys tagging Pickens before the deadline to do so, but whether that results in him staying with the team on a long-term deal remains in question. Jones said the team thinks “the world” of Pickens and wants him to stay a Cowboy, but declined to comment on when an extension could get done. Pickens enjoyed a career year in 2025, catching 93 passes for 1,429 yards and nine touchdowns — all career-highs. His pairing with CeeDee Lamb made for one of the most dynamic receiver duos in the league, but for the right price, it’s possible the Cowboys opt to tag and then trade Pickens for draft picks to improve their roster elsewhere. We’ll have a better sense on where things are headed after Pickens is tagged, but things could be setting up for a long offseason of negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b81-d990-a1de-efcff4850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Falcons plan to use the franchise tag on TE Kyle Pitts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8ba6-d629-a1bc-bbbf69d30000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, the plan “is to work out a long-term deal” rather than force Pitts to play on the tag. If he does play on the tag, the veteran tight end would receive a guaranteed $15 million next season. Pitts had his best season as a pro in 2025, posting career-highs in receptions (88) and receiving touchdowns (5) while also totaling 928 receiving yards. The 25-year-old playmaker struggled to live up to the lofty expectations he set as a rookie in 2021 when he went for 68-1026-1, but his breakout performance last season made him a player the new regime hopes to hang out to for the foreseeable future. Pitts and the Falcons now have until July to hammer out a new contract before playing on the tag becomes a real possibility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8ba6-d629-a1bc-bbbf69d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team is open to trading one of its two first-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bdc-d89c-a1be-afdf47300000</link>
      <description>This could be a big nothing burger, but Jones said the team is “open-minded” to the idea of trading a pick. The Cowboys currently hold the No. 12 and No. 20 overall picks in this year’s draft, but have plenty of needs to address with those picks, especially on the defensive side of the ball. As is often the case in these situations, anything can be had for the right price. We’ll see if anything piques the Cowboys’ interest as offers are likely to come in their direction in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bdc-d89c-a1be-afdf47300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Najee Harris was seen running five months after undergoing surgery to repair a torn Achilles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bf0-d89c-a1be-afff0f510000</link>
      <description>In a video posted to social media, Harris was reportedly “running with ease at 15 MPH.” The veteran running back still has a long way to go in his recovery since going down in Week 3 of last season, but with free agency looming, Harris is hoping to prove to a team that he’s worth taking a chance on this upcoming season. Whether or not he’ll sign before fully healthy is unknown, but Harris, 27, should have plenty of suitors lining up to bring him in on a one-year prove-it deal this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bf0-d89c-a1be-afff0f510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “it would take a Micah Parsons type package” if the Raiders were to trade Maxx Crosby this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bfa-d042-afbc-fffa95c60000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys received defensive lineman Kenny Clark and two first-round draft picks in exchange for Parsons last offseason. Parsons was also entering his age-26 season when he was traded and is the better defensive player, while Crosby will be 29 at the start of next season. Age will be a factor in any deal regarding Crosby, who totaled 10 sacks and one interception for the Raiders last season, and is among the most feared defenders in the league. We still don’t know if the Raiders will trade Crosby this offseason, but we would expect him to fetch a decent trade offer, even if the “Parsons deal” is a bridge too far for most teams. The Raiders should get a better gauge on potential suitors during this weeks’ NFL Scouting Combine, which could lead to a deal developing sooner than later if they decide a trade is in their best interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bfa-d042-afbc-fffa95c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs released DE Mike Danna.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</link>
      <description>Danna was selected by the Chiefs in the fifth-round of the 2020 NFL Draft. The veteran pass rusher totaled 21.5 sacks, 25 TFLs, and one interception in 87 games with the Chiefs and was a part of two Super Bowl-winning teams. The release of Danna, who will be 28 at the start of next season, saves the Chiefs $8.940 million against the cap. He should have plenty of suitors on the market as a pass-rushing specialist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released RB Antonio Gibson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</link>
      <description>Gibson suffered a torn ACL in Week 5 of last season and had one year remaining on the three-year deal he signed in 2024. The Patriots will save $3.140 million against the cap with the release of Gibson, who rushed for 25-106-1 in limited action last season. During his two years with the Patriots, Gibson rushed 145 times for 644 yards and two touchdowns while adding another 25-212-0 through the air. The soon-to-be 28-year-old back who had totaled 984 touches in his career should land elsewhere this upcoming season, but he’ll likely have to battle for playing time wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
