<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports, TE Daniel Bellinger is “expected to play a significant role” with Giants shorthanded at wide receiver in Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cab6-d94a-a79d-cbbf79f70000</link>
      <description>Bellinger led the Giants in receiving yards last week, catching 4-of-4 targets for 52 yards against the Saints. The Giants lost Malik Nabers (knee) in Week 4 and Darius Slayton (hamstring) after 55 snaps in Week 5. Head coach Brian Daboll used two-tight end sets at the sixth-highest rate last week (39.7 percent). While Bellinger is perhaps unlikely to post gaudy receiving sums, both he and TE Theo Johnson are viable TE1 streamers against the Eagles, thanks to their expectedly decent involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cab6-d94a-a79d-cbbf79f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Brian Branch (foot) is scheduled to undergo an MRI after he was limited in practice for the second straight day on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cac4-d94a-a79d-cbcdc6df0000</link>
      <description>The Detroit Free Press’ Dave Birkett reports that Branch “worked out on the side during individual drills at practice Wednesday and had a noticeable limp as he left the locker room Thursday.” The Lions’ secondary could be extremely short-staffed against the Chiefs on Sunday night. Birkett notes that starting CBs, D.J. Reed and Terrion Arnold, are out indefinitely with hamstring and shoulder injuries. The Lions placed backup CB Khalil Dorsey on injured reserve this week and No. 3 safety Avonte Maddox “showed up on the injury report Thursday with a hamstring injury.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cac4-d94a-a79d-cbcdc6df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Miles Sanders (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cacd-db72-a199-facf24350000</link>
      <description>While it is possible that this is a rest day, it appears as though Sanders may have suffered a setback. He practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday. If Sanders is unable to play in Week 6 against the Panthers, it would give rookie RB Jaydon Blue another uncontested opportunity to operate as the Cowboys’ No. 2 running back behind Javonte Williams. Blue should be stashed on benches at this time. He notably fared well in pass protection last week, which yields no fantasy points but goes a long way toward earning the coaching staff’s trust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cacd-db72-a199-facf24350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca8b-db72-a199-facbbc590000</link>
      <description>Lamb remains sidelined as he rehabs the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. However, ESPN’s Todd Archer reports that “Lamb continues to make progress” in his rehab program and tells readers not to rule Lamb out for the Cowboys’ Week 7 game against the Commanders. For now, expect to be without him for Week 6. Sending a buy-low trade offer for Lamb could pay off quickly, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca8b-db72-a199-facbbc590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cad8-def2-abdb-dff970410000</link>
      <description>Turpin was curiously listed with an ankle injury recently, so this is either a new or related issue. Regardless, the Cowboys’ No. 3 wide receiver and return specialist appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 6 against the Panthers, giving WR Ryan Flournoy a chance to operate as a passing game contributor. Flournoy is a boom-bust FLEX option this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cad8-def2-abdb-dff970410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (thigh) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cacc-def2-abdb-dfedb4790000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Monangai reportedly entered the Bears’ Week 5 bye with a clean bill of health, so it is unclear as to when this injury occurred. The rookie running back won the No. 2 role behind D’Andre Swift in training camp. If he is unable to return in time for his team’s Monday Night Football game against the Commanders this week, No. 3 RB Roschon Johnson could get an opportunity to fight for the primary backup job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cacc-def2-abdb-dfedb4790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cae3-dd4c-afb9-efe3bfc80000</link>
      <description>Loveland is coming off a Week 5 bye. It would have been nice to see him practice in full today, but his early-week participation does put him on track to play in the Bears’ Week 6 Monday Night Football game against the Commanders. Unfortunately, he can only be stashed on benches at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cae3-dd4c-afb9-efe3bfc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cae6-d94a-a79d-cbef3f0a0000</link>
      <description>That makes two limited sessions for Kamara, who reportedly injured his ankle in Week 5 against the Giants. He left practice early on Wednesday after experiencing soreness. The injury is not believed to be serious and his continued participation puts him on track to play in Week 6 against the Patriots. Assuming he is good to go come Sunday, he can be treated as an RB2, though it would be unsurprising to see Kendre Miller handle a near-even workload with him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cae6-d94a-a79d-cbef3f0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cad2-dd4c-afb9-efd37ba00000</link>
      <description>Johnson is firmly on track to play in Week 6 against the Patriots, but with Taysom Hill and Foster Moreau back in the lineup, Johnson is now just a high-end TE2 in re-draft formats. If Johnson can produce a high-end TE1 finish in the coming weeks, it would be wise to try to sell high on him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cad2-dd4c-afb9-efd37ba00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caef-def2-abdb-dfef835d0000</link>
      <description>This is likely just a maintenance day for Spears, who returned from injured reserve last week. Earlier this week, Titans head coach Brian Callahan said Spears will see an increased role going forward, though expectations should be held in check. He ran the ball four times and earned zero targets. Spears in closer to a bench stash than he is a reliable FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caef-def2-abdb-dfef835d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
