<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions claimed S Jalen Mills off waivers from the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a43-d77b-adfb-cac334d70000</link>
      <description>Mills was released by Houston earlier this week. He appeared in four games for the Texans this year, logging four tackles while playing a mix of special teams and defense. With the Lions seemingly losing a new defensive back to injury every week, Mills will give the team some extra depth on defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a43-d77b-adfb-cac334d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a47-d005-a9bf-da779a380000</link>
      <description>A limited session this early in the week is nothing to worry about with a veteran like Ferguson. Barring a setback, he should be good to go for Week 15 versus Minnesota. Ferguson is quietly fantasy football’s TE2 this year. That has largely been due to him playing all 13 games so far, but he is also a reliable check-down option on a pass-first offense. He will remain near the top of the TE1 ranks for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a47-d005-a9bf-da779a380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes (knee) is practicing in full for Week 15 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a4e-d8cf-affb-be6ea0bd0000</link>
      <description>Mahomes picked up the knee injury late in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans. The good news is that a full practice means he is good to go for Week 15. The bad news is that every game is now a must-win spot for Kansas City. The Chiefs will need some outside help, even if they run the table through the end of the season. Mahomes tends to run more when things get dire, but the knee issue could limit his mobility. He will shuffle into the middle of the QB1 ranks versus LA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a4e-d8cf-affb-be6ea0bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a5b-d8cf-affb-be7b8e510000</link>
      <description>MHJ missed Week 14’s game with the heel issue and is on track to sit for at least one more week after being held out of today’s practice. Michael Wilson has been utterly dominant in three starts without MHJ. He most recently went for 142 yards and a pair of touchdowns versus the Rams on Sunday. Assuming MHJ remains out this week, Wilson will hold a spot in the WR1 ranks versus Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a5b-d8cf-affb-be7b8e510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a5d-da9b-a9bf-de5dbfe00000</link>
      <description>Demercado has been out since Week 11 with a high-ankle sprain. He returned to practice last week but didn’t suit up on Sunday. He has a shot at returning this week. Demercado would be in the mix for work on passing downs alongside Michael Carter, taking both players off the fantasy roster for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a5d-da9b-a9bf-de5dbfe00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Tutu Atwell (hamstring) will be activated from injured reserve this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a6c-d005-a9bf-da7cf2c30000</link>
      <description>Atwell has been back at practice for a few weeks and is finally ready to return to action. He will play a part-time role on offense unless something happens to Puka Nacua or Davante Adams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a6c-d005-a9bf-da7cf2c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a74-d77b-adfb-caf706eb0000</link>
      <description>Bryant had been quietly earning more work in the Denver offense in recent weeks. He has 17 targets over his past three games and has flipped Troy Franklin in the pecking order for routes. Bryant was added to the injury report on Thursday last week but participated in at least a limited capacity throughout the week. A DNP today could be a sign that his hamstring issue worsened during Sunday’s game. Franklin would reclaim his starting role if Bryant can’t suit up in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a74-d77b-adfb-caf706eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a77-d77b-adfb-caf7c06c0000</link>
      <description>Odunze missed Week 14’s game after failing to practice once throughout the week. A limited session today puts him on track to return to the lineup, but the Bears’ staff will undoubtedly want to see how he responds in practice over the next two days before giving him the green light. If active, a banged-up Odunze will be relegated to the fantasy WR3 ranks on a run-heavy Chicago offense. Luther Burden will continue to operate as the team’s top wideout if Odunze is held out versus the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a77-d77b-adfb-caf7c06c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a7c-d77b-adfb-caff35650000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus only saw three targets with Rome Odunze sidelined last week. He did, however, come up with an impressive touchdown catch to open the second half. With Odunze returning to practice this week, Zaccheaus should be off the fantasy radar for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a7c-d77b-adfb-caff35650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
