<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5572-d713-ad9e-7d760c1c0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle labored through the quad injury for most of the Panthers’ Week 9 upset of the Packers. Despite clearly playing through something, Dowdle racked up 25 carries for 130 yards and two scores. Head coach Dave Canales told reporters today that the team is trying to be smart about his injury with the DNP. He also mentioned Dowdle returning to practice tomorrow. Fantasy managers can breathe a sigh of relief. Their newfound RB1 should be good to go for Sunday’s game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5572-d713-ad9e-7d760c1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Audric Estime from their practice squad to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55a3-d673-a39e-f5b3fb540000</link>
      <description>The Saints signed Estime to their practice squad after Kendr Miller went down with a torn ACL. He will now serve as the team’s RB3 behind Alvin Kamara and Devin Neal. Estime could see work down the stretch if the Saints decide to lighten Kamara’s workload, but even dynasty managers can do better with their last bench spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55a3-d673-a39e-f5b3fb540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said QB C.J. Stroud (concussion) “will be out” in Week 10 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55b0-d1e7-a1fa-5ffa61a60000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate for all involved. Davis Mills will start in Stroud’s stead, expectedly lowering the fantasy-scoring outlooks for Texans pass catchers. Hopefully, Stroud can return in time for the Texans’ Week 11 game against the Bills. The Texans (3-5) sit four spots behind the fifth-place Bills (6-2) in the AFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55b0-d1e7-a1fa-5ffa61a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed QB Kyler Murray on injured reserve with a foot injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5579-d45b-affe-55ff57a80000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Adam Schefter, the “Cardinals say this will give Murray the chance to focus on rehabbing his foot injury and that he is committed to getting back as soon as possible.” Should Murray actually return as soon as possible, it would be against the Rams in Week 14, after he sits out the requisite four games missed on injured reserve. Whether he would return to the team in a starting role is a separate issue. The injured reserve listing coincidentally comes after the team announced journeyman QB Jacoby Brissett would take over as the team’s starter. Perhaps time off gives Murray a chance to reset and he comes back stronger than ever. Regardless, the development is seemingly a positive one for Cardinals pass catchers, who have enjoyed on-target passes with Brissett at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5579-d45b-affe-55ff57a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (groin/hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ba-d673-a39e-f5bb81e30000</link>
      <description>Moore doesn’t practice on Wednesdays anymore as he nurses the hip and groin issues. This shouldn;t be taken as a sign that he is going to miss Week 10, but fantasy managers will still want to check in on the Bears’ final injury report on Friday. Assuming things go a planned, Moore will clock in as a low-end WR3 for Week 10 versus the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ba-d673-a39e-f5bb81e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze (ankle/heel) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55bc-d1e7-a1fa-5ffe68c00000</link>
      <description>Odunze played through the heel issue last week despite missing Wednesday’s practice. The ankle injury, however, is new. It also makes it harder to say if he will suit up again for Week 10. DJ Moore and Olamide Zaccheaus would both see an uptick in targets if Odunze misses time. Luther Burden would step into the starting mix in three-receiver sets, making him worth a stash in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55bc-d1e7-a1fa-5ffe68c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Kmet (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55bf-d45b-affe-55bfef400000</link>
      <description>Kmet left Week 9’s game with the concussion and did not return. A limited session to open the week means he is already progressing through the league’s concussion protocol. With Colston Loveland breaking out to the tune of 118 yards and two touchdowns last week, Kmet won’t return to a starting role on Sunday. He can be dropped, even in deep fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55bf-d45b-affe-55bfef400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c2-d1e7-a1fa-5fea129e0000</link>
      <description>Burden missed Week 9 with the brain injury. A full practice to open the week means he should be able to clear the league’s concussion protocol ahead of the Bears’ upcoming matchup with the Giants. Burden isn’t on the fantasy radar unless one of Rome Odunze or DJ Moore, both of whom were held out of practice today, misses Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c2-d1e7-a1fa-5fea129e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (glute) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c5-d1e7-a1fa-5fefcfaf0000</link>
      <description>Pittman notably practiced in full, with a glute injury, throughout Week 2. He suited up on game day that week, catching 4-of-5 targets for 40 yards against the Broncos. Pittman plays through injury whenever he is medically cleared to do so, famously playing much of the 2024 season with a fracture in his back. His practice participation is worth following this week, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c5-d1e7-a1fa-5fefcfaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c8-d673-a39e-f5d91ad60000</link>
      <description>Kyle Monangai was limited with an ankle injury, though that is likely a precautionary measure by the Bears. Swift had been playing through the groin issue for weeks before it finally caught up with him ahead of Week 9. He failed to practice once and the team ruled him out before the weekend. Monangai drew the start and ran 26 times for 176 yards, easily besting Swift’s high-water mark for the year. The breakout performance could flip the backfield split for Week 10, or Ben Johnson could revert to Swift as the top option if he is healthy. Both backs will likely sit in the RB3 ranks versus the Giants if Swift is cleared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55c8-d673-a39e-f5d91ad60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
