<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said the team will re-evaluate OG Robert Hunt (biceps) next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f77-d45b-affe-5ff7386c0000</link>
      <description>Hunt suffered a torn biceps in Week 2 and has been on injured reserve ever since. According to Canales, the team will re-evaluate Hunt to see if he has a chance to return for the final four games of the season, meaning we shouldn’t expect to see him any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f77-d45b-affe-5ff7386c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) will not play in Cleveland’s Week 10 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f85-d1e7-a1fa-5fef5c5f0000</link>
      <description>Bond didn’t practice all week coming off the bye and probably has some shot of being sent to injured reserve this week. Cedric Tillman will likely take over his role in Dillon Gabriel’s fabled “offense that cannot throw to wideouts” and finds himself in a WR5 role for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f85-d1e7-a1fa-5fef5c5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin (hamstring) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 10 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f87-d713-ad9e-7fd7fdc90000</link>
      <description>Fannin did return to practice today in a limited session after a surprise DNP (hamstring) addition to the report on Thursday. He’s got a low-end TE1 role lined up against the Jets if he plays. If he does not play, David Njoku would consolidate Fannin’s looks into a TE1 spot given how often Dillon Gabriel has thrown the ball to tight ends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f87-d713-ad9e-7fd7fdc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedric Tillman (hamstring) is questionable for Week 10 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f86-d713-ad9e-7fd6ba930000</link>
      <description>Tillman was a full participant in practice all week, so it would be a bit surprising if the team didn’t activate him for Week 10 — although that clearly remains a possibility. Tillman caught 11 passes for 106 yards and two touchdowns in the four games he appeared in this season, but that production came with Joe Flacco under center. Dillon Gabriel has taken a far more conservative approach with the offense since being named the starter, which will likely limit any upside Tillman would normally have. If he is active, fantasy managers should take a wait-and-see approach with Tillman befor inserting him into their lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f86-d713-ad9e-7fd6ba930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) will not play in New England’s Week 10 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8b-d673-a39e-ff9b1e560000</link>
      <description>Stevenson’s absence will again yield a committee of TreVeyon Henderson and Terrell Jennings against the Buccaneers. Henderson is the preferred starter in fantasy leagues after playing the majority of the snaps last week. Don’t sleep on a Jennings takeover in the red zone though, and he is RB3/deep league FLEX viable against Tampa Bay. The Patriots have never met a running back room they couldn’t turn into a committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8b-d673-a39e-ff9b1e560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LB Carson Schwesinger (ankle) is questionable for Week 10 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8a-d673-a39e-ff9b1bd90000</link>
      <description>Schwesinger suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 8’s loss to the Patriots. The rookie linebacker avoided landing on injured reserve, but only managed to get on the field for one practice this week. The questionable designation may be a bit too optimistic for Schwesinger this week, but he’s clearly trending toward a return and could be good to go for Week 11 if not this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8a-d673-a39e-ff9b1bd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefnaski said QB Shedeur Sanders (back) will be Cleveland’s backup against the Jets in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8f-d45b-affe-5f9f6a470000</link>
      <description>Sanders was dealing with a back injury, but practiced in full and was left off the injury report. There’s no need to expect greatness at this point, but with Dillon Gabriel struggling and Tommy Rees now calling the plays, perhaps there is a bit more of an opening for Sanders to see playing time in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8f-d45b-affe-5f9f6a470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) will not play in Week 10 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8f-d673-a39e-ff9ffbc30000</link>
      <description>Boutte was unable to get on the practice field this week, so this news doesn’t come as a surprise. The third-year receiver will miss his first game of the season on Sunday when the Patriots visit the Buccaneers, making Mack Hollins the most likely candidate to see an increased workload as Drake Maye’s deep target. Vrabel called Boutte “day-to-day” to start the week, so there’s a chance he’ll be ready to go for Week 11 against the Jets, although, the short week could make that difficult.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f8f-d673-a39e-ff9ffbc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals GM Monti Ossenfort said he thinks Kyler Murray (foot) will return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f97-d673-a39e-ff97bdd30000</link>
      <description>He also added — and to be clear this is a pretty big thing for a general manager can say — “a lot can happen” when asked if Murray would be starting when he came back. Anyone without an IR spot to stash Murray in can definitely let go, and based on that frank evaluation of Murray’s prospects of getting his job back, re-draft managers with an IR spot might be able to stash someone more likely to help them this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f97-d673-a39e-ff97bdd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said the running back split will be “similar but not the same. … maybe a little bit different.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fa7-d713-ad9e-7ff7d81f0000</link>
      <description>He also noted that he and Drew Petzing have not yet discussed who will start the game. Cool, good work guys. Thanks. Neither Bam Knight nor Emari Demercado look like they’ll be in more than a pure committee situation where the hot hand takes 60 percent of the snaps. Against a Seattle run defense that’s loaded for bear, fantasy managers should probably find other solutions this week. Neither player is a confident FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fa7-d713-ad9e-7ff7d81f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
