<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:33:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught all nine of his targets for 146 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b399-d82c-a79a-b39d7aba0000</link>
      <description>It was a nice follow up to his 144-yard, one-touchdown performance in Week 11 against the Raiders, and this time it came against an elite Eagles secondary that has snuffed out opposing passing attacks over the past month. Pickens’ big day came as CeeDee Lamb had just four grabs for 75 yards on 11 targets, dropping two balls from Dak Prescott. Pickens now has five games this season with more than 80 receiving yards. He has scored at least one touchdown in eight games. Drawing targets at a higher per-route rate than Lamb, there’s an argument that Pickens is the Cowboys’ No. 1 wideout for now. He’ll take on the stingy Chiefs defense in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b399-d82c-a79a-b39d7aba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 9-of-13 targets for 70 yards in the Saints’ Week 12 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b397-d82c-a79a-b3976fc00000</link>
      <description>Olave continued to get his steady diet of intermediate targets from Tyler Shough against the Falcons. He saw a 30-percent target share but was not used inside the five-yard line, where the Saints frequently had drives stall. Lack of consistent scoring puts a cap on Olave’s ceiling, though his high volume as the WR1 in the Saints offense gives him a high floor. Olave will be a fantasy WR2 for Week 13 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b397-d82c-a79a-b3976fc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson rushed seven times for 23 yards in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders, adding two catches for 59 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b396-db57-afda-f7b68de70000</link>
      <description>Quinshon Judkins spent a few snaps on the sidelines while being evaluated for a concussion in the third quarter, briefly freeing up some work for Sampson. Seven carries is Sampson’s highest rushing total since Week 1, when Judkins was not with the team. He made the most of his extra touches with a 66-yard receiving touchdown to ice the game for Cleveland. Shedeur Sanders tossed a routine check-down to Sampson, who simply sprinted through the Vegas defense for his best play of the year. Sampson is still splitting the backup role with Jerome Ford, keeping him off the fantasy radar for Week 13. Dynaty managers, however, will appreciate this spike week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b396-db57-afda-f7b68de70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 6-of-11 targets for 89 yards in the Eagles’ Week 12 win against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b39d-db57-afda-f7bf9daa0000</link>
      <description>Smith led the Eagles in targets but came up short of A.J. Brown’s 110 yards and a touchdown against Dallas. Targeted on 24 percent of his routes, Smith came down with an incredible 41-yard grab — the longest of the night for the Eagles. It was a downfield catch that required Smith to become parallel with the ground and hold on to the ball through a hard fall to the turf. Smith last week had just one catch for eight yards as Jalen Hurts’ targets Brown relentlessly after Brown complained to team ownership about his lack of targets. Smith will be a top-30 option in Week 13 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b39d-db57-afda-f7bf9daa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson caught 6-of-7 targets for 46 yards in the Saints’ Week 12 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b39e-d90e-a9da-bf9fbf7f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson operated as the Saints’ No. 2 pass-catcher, tying Devin Neal and Devaughn Vele for second in targets on the day. He drew a key defensive pass interference in the third quarter to help get the Saints in the red zone on a drive that eventually stalled out. Otherwise, it was a lot of underneath targets from Tyler Shough as the Falcons defense prevented deeper looks. Johnson has fantasy relevance as the secondary target in the offense, though lack of scoring consistency keeps him in the high-end TE2 range for Week 13 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b39e-d90e-a9da-bf9fbf7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devaughn Vele caught 3-of-7 targets for 37 yards in the Saints’ Week 12 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a3-d82c-a79a-b3b766700000</link>
      <description>Vele saw the uptick in usage expected after Rashid Shaheed was dealt at the trade deadline. He tied for second on the team with seven targets and caught three. He primarily saw intermediate targets, totaling 37 yards, most on the season. Vele will have involvement in the post-Shaheed offense, though his upside is capped in the Saints offense. He is worth a look on waiver wires heading into a Week 13 matchup against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a3-d82c-a79a-b3b766700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints beat writer Nick Underhill reports Alvin Kamara had an MRI on his knee after Week 12’s loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a8-db57-afda-f7bab6ad0000</link>
      <description>Underhill notes that he has not received any update on the results of the MRI, but Kamara is now dealing with multiple lower-body injuries and could be at risk of missing some time even if the injury isn’t severe. We’ll likely receive an update on his status some time on Monday, but backup Devin Neal would be in line for a busy Week 13 against the Dolphins if Kamara is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a8-db57-afda-f7bab6ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Grupe converted 1-of-3 field goal attempts in the Saints’ Week 12 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a9-d413-ad9f-b7fd1da30000</link>
      <description>Grupe had a rough day for the Saints, missing two field goal attempts on the day. His misses were from 38 and 47 yards, both coming in the first half. Many Saints drives stalled in Falcons territory and Grupe’s misses put the offense in “go-for-it” territory more often than not in the second half. With the Saints’ struggles to consistently score, Grupe does not need to be rostered in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a9-d413-ad9f-b7fd1da30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 4-of-6 targets for 43 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 12 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a2-d90e-a9da-bfaf90480000</link>
      <description>Kelce almost saved the day for fantasy managers with a rushing touchdown early in the game. He lined up as the Chiefs’ quarterback at the four-yard line, kept the ball on a read option play, and ran straight into the end zone for an easy score. The play was then nixed by the refs via a questionable facemask call on Jawaan Taylor. Kelce was relegated to check-down duties for much of the remaining three quarters. Though his coutning stats have been muted by the return of Rashee Rice, Kelce is still good finding holes in zone coverage and has scored twice in his past four games. He gets a great matchup with the Cowboys’ next week, keeping him well inside the TE1 ranks for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3a2-d90e-a9da-bfaf90480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith caught all 3-of-4 targets for 31 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 12 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3b0-d82c-a79a-b3b420b60000</link>
      <description>Smith only carried the ball once. He ran for five yards. Kareem Hunt saw 30 carries and Clyde Edwards-Helaire ran five times. Smith looks like a difference-maker through the air, but the Chiefs have no interest in getting him more than four or five touches in any game. He is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3b0-d82c-a79a-b3b420b60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
