<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Chubb (foot) was added to Friday’s injury report and is questionable for Week 11 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8310-d1e7-a1fa-dbfae6220000</link>
      <description>Chubb was a surprise addition to Friday’s report and was listed as limited. It’s never a good sign when a player is added to Friday’s report, so Chubb’s status will be one to watch when inactives are announced 90 minutes before kickoff. The veteran pass rusher has totaled 28 tackles, five sacks, and five TFLs this season after missing all of 2024 due to a torn ACL. If he’s unable to go on Sunday, veteran Matt Judon could see an uptick in snaps after playing in a limited role for most of the season. In addition to Chubb, the Dolphins also listed WR Dee Eskridge (shoulder) and CB Rasul Douglas (foot/ankle) as questionable for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8310-d1e7-a1fa-dbfae6220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) has been ruled out for Week 11’s game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8331-d45b-affe-d7b7ffda0000</link>
      <description>Even with Friday’s practice still to go, McDermott didn’t hesitate to rule out Kincaid, who was a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday and viewed as a long shot to play early in the week. His absence will open the door for Dawson Knox to draw the start in Week 11, but Knox shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a desperation play for fantasy managers. Knox has caught 12 passes for 155 yards and one touchdown this season and hasn’t gone for more than 37 yards in any game. In addition to Kincaid, the Bills also ruled out Phidarian Mathis due to a shoulder injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8331-d45b-affe-d7b7ffda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Khalil Shakir (ankle) is “in a good spot” ahead of Week 11’s game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8332-d45b-affe-d7b6c2fb0000</link>
      <description>We’ll provide an update on Shakir’s official game status once it’s released, but McDermott is clearly optimistic about Shakir’s Week 11 availability after logging limited practices in back-to-back days to open the week. Shakir led the Bills with seven receptions for 58 yards in last week’s loss to the Dolphins, and would be in line for a sizable role on Sunday against the Buccaneers with Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) already ruled out. We’ll see where things go from there, but Shakir is clearly trending in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8332-d45b-affe-d7b6c2fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LB Mack Wilson (ribs) will not play in Week 11 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8354-d45b-affe-d7d6f7dd0000</link>
      <description>Wilson went down in Week 9’s game against the Cowboys and will now miss a second-straight game with this rib injury. The veteran linebacker has started all eight games he’s appeared in for the Cardinals this season, totaling 60 tackles, three TFLs, and six pass breakups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8354-d45b-affe-d7d6f7dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (knee) was seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8359-d713-ad9e-ef5db5ff0000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on the official report to confirm his Week 11 availability, but Jackson is clearly trending in the right direction for Week 11’s game against the Browns after popping up as a DNP in Wednesday’s practice with knee soreness. We’ll check back in when the Ravens’ final injury report is released, but there’s not much to be concerned about at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8359-d713-ad9e-ef5db5ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) will not play in Week 11 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-835b-d673-a39e-a7db65b00000</link>
      <description>Despite being a limited participant in practice throughout the week, Irving won’t be suiting up for Week 11. This was probably to be expected after one reporter described Irving’s Wednesday practice as a walk-through. Rachaad White will again serve as the Buccaneers’ RB1 in a game that could feature plenty of offense from both teams, making him a fringe RB1/RB2 candidate this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-835b-d673-a39e-a7db65b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) will not play in Week 11 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8364-d713-ad9e-ef74df2b0000</link>
      <description>Godwin’s first practice of the week was considered a walk-through, which should have served as a clear indicator that he would be a long shot to play in Week 11. The veteran receiver hasn’t played since Week 5 after dealing with pain in the leg that ended his 2024 season, but could have a chance to suit up in Week 12 against the Rams with another week of practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8364-d713-ad9e-ef74df2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears designated CB Jaylon Johnson (core) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-836e-d1e7-a1fa-dbee03a20000</link>
      <description>The Bears will have 21 days to activate Johnson from injured reserve, but this is a very encouraging sign for a defense in need of help in the secondary. Johnson hasn’t played since the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Lions, but would be on track to return no later than December 7th when the Bears visit the Packers in Week 14. One of the top corners in the league, Johnson totaled 53 tackles, eight pass breakups, and two intereceptions for the Bears last season and has been named to the Pro Bowl in back-to-back years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-836e-d1e7-a1fa-dbee03a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-837a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaf1aa0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle was upgraded from a limited participant to a full participant in Friday’s practice and was removed from the injury report as a result. The Panthers’ RB1 gets a juicy matchup against a Falcons run defense that ranks in the bottom five in total rushing yards allowed and yards per carry this season. Dowdle is firmly in the RB1 ranks for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-837a-d1e7-a1fa-dbfaf1aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interim HC Mike Kafka said Jaxson Dart is “on track” with where he should be in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8381-d673-a39e-a791d1120000</link>
      <description>Dart has already been ruled out for Week 11’s game against the Packers, but the rookie was on the practice field Friday and should have a chance to be cleared early next week. Jameis Winston will draw the start in Dart’s absence this week, but this is great news for Dart before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8381-d673-a39e-a791d1120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
