<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 01:29:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes the Vikings could keep QB Max Brosmer on their initial 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fb0-df63-a199-dfbba2290000</link>
      <description>“Brosmer sees the field, processing the defensive picture in a way you cannot teach. Coaches have raved about his smarts behind the scenes, too. If the Vikings don’t add him to the 53-man, they’d risk losing a reliable player at the game’s most critical position,” Lewis writes. Brosmer completed 5-of-8 passes for 47 yards and a touchdown in Minnesota’s preseason opener against the Texans. This is probably just training camp hype, but Brosmer played well enough that we should at least take it somewhat seriously — and anyone who quarterbacks Minnesota’s offense as things stand currently could have fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fb0-df63-a199-dfbba2290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper reports Najee Harris (eye) is “doing some jogging” on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fb4-df63-a199-dfbf2c850000</link>
      <description>Things have progressed at a glacial enough pace for Harris that this qualifies as an optimistic update. Until we hear anything about him doing football activities, we’d continue to assume he doesn’t stand much of a chance of getting off the PUP list before the regular season starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fb4-df63-a199-dfbf2c850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (undisclosed) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fe7-d05a-adda-bfe7f5370000</link>
      <description>The team signed UDFA RB Shane Watts on Tuesday. Perhaps it’s nothing, but with Stevenson not practicing since his 7/36 game in the preseason opener, this is a situation worth keeping an eye on. TreVeyon Henderson would undoubtedly be the lead back for New England if Stevenson was sidelined for any reason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9fe7-d05a-adda-bfe7f5370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports the Vikings confirmed Rondale Moore (knee) will be placed on injured reserve and miss the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ff2-d05a-adda-bff21e690000</link>
      <description>Moore will miss a second consecutive season due to preseason injury, which opens up the bottom of the Vikings wideout depth chart. The Vikings haven’t seem overly impressed with rookie Tai Felton on offense, which means they may need to go out and get a stopgap receiver during Jordan Addison’s early-season suspension. Moore will turn 26 next June, so his career is far from over unless he wants it to be, but he’ll likely be seeking another prove-it contract in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ff2-d05a-adda-bff21e690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker (undisclosed) is back at practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ffe-d45c-a7fc-9ffe249f0000</link>
      <description>It seems like if Walker’s foot (what he missed time with earlier in camp) is an issue, it’s one that will be long-term managed by the Seahawks. It’s probably not worth making a big deal out of at this point. Seahawks HC Mike Macdonald said “We have a plan for Ken, and we’re sticking to the plan,” when asked about Walker yesterday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ffe-d45c-a7fc-9ffe249f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Brooks Kubena believes there’s a “growing sense” that Jahan Dotson “could contribute more” than he did in 2024.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a024-d90d-a5bd-a27f8dc40000</link>
      <description>Well, it would be hard to contribute less than 19 catches for 216 yards over a full season, folks! Kubena believes Dotson’s advancement is “notable” and that the ball skills that made him a 2022 first-round pick are “showing up more” in his first full training camp in Philadelphia. We’re not expecting the Eagles to be invested in feeding Dotson after declining his fifth-year option, but it certainly would make sense for him to do better than he did in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a024-d90d-a5bd-a27f8dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OC Greg Roman said Omarion Hampton will rotate with another back in Week 1 even if Najee Harris (eye) isn’t ready to go.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a03d-df63-a199-f93fbd510000</link>
      <description>Who said back is, Roman says, is “wide open.” We’d guess the Chargers would probably go to Hassan Haskins as a between-the-tackles sledgehammer in that scenario. This isn’t exactly breaking news — every team rotates running backs — but it does look like we shouldn’t look at Hampton’s Week 1 assignment as a clear runway to 30 touches if Harris is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a03d-df63-a199-f93fbd510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OL Mekhi Becton is “working through something” after missing the last two weeks of practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a082-df63-a199-f9ab27290000</link>
      <description>Offensive coordinator Greg Roman said Becton will be fine and is “getting a lot of great meeting time, walkthrough time.” The 26-year-old signed a two-year, $20 million deal with the Chargers in the offseason and has a chance to start as a blocker for the run game. Roman said he is “not putting anything in concrete”, but Becton should be back to start the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a082-df63-a199-f9ab27290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RBs Nick Chubb (head) and Dameon Pierce (quad) split first-team snaps Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a08b-df63-a199-f9ab40500000</link>
      <description>Chubb returned to practice after a head injury and split first-team snaps with Pierce, who was a full-go in practice for the first time since he strained his quadriceps. With Joe Mixon still sidelined with ankle and foot issues, the Texans have a murky backfield split between the veterans. Chubb is a downhill runner who has lost some burst while Pierce was strictly a backup and special teamer last season. Splitting first-team snaps indicates this backfield will be a committee when Mixon is out, with rookie Woody Marks mixing in for pass-catching.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a08b-df63-a199-f9ab40500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kris Rhim reports Chargers RB Najee Harris (eye) participated in football drills Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a0af-d90d-a5bd-a2ffd4f30000</link>
      <description>It was Harris’ first time participating in football drills this training camp. Rhim reports the 27-year-old did drills with a football off to the side with an athletic trainer. He is slowly progressing back to full football activities between jogging and individual drills on Tuesday, but remains on the PUP list for now. Omarion Hampton is the Chargers’ starter, while the third-string spot still remains open for competition. Harris may not be ready for Week 1, but working with a football is an optimistic sign that he is on his way back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a0af-d90d-a5bd-a2ffd4f30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
