<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams placed WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f43f50000</link>
      <description>Even though he played through the hamstring injury in Week 8, Atwell only played 10 snaps. Jordan Whittington will be the Rams’ main No. 3 receiver going forward, but won’t have fantasy value unless Davante Adams or Puka Nacua are hurt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f43f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said DT Shemar Turner (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2752-d5d8-a3ff-ff73fd330000</link>
      <description>Turner ends his rookie year with six tackles, two TFLs, and a 34.4 PFF defensive grade. He was essentially being treated as a rotational player, maxing out at 23 snaps in Week 3. Depending on rehab, Turner may be ready for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2752-d5d8-a3ff-ff73fd330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints HC Kellen Moore said he still hasn’t decided on who will start at QB in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-d5d8-a3ff-ff7753e30000</link>
      <description>Moore pulled Spencer Rattler after a disastrous first half in Sunday’s loss to the Buccaneers and replaced him with rookie Tyler Shough. Shough didn’t fare much better in the 23-3 defeat, but speaking on Monday, Moore said the offensive failures were on the whole unit and not just Rattler. Perhaps he’ll consider going back to Rattler again despite his struggles all season, but we’ve seen coaches downplay a QB change early on only to inevitably show their hand later in the week. It would not be at all surprising if Shough was under center in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-d5d8-a3ff-ff7753e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said Olamide Zaccheaus (knee) is day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-dab4-a3fb-bf775d540000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus caught a season-high seven balls against the Ravens in Week 8 with Luther Burden ruled out early in concussion protocol. Zaccheaus is a pro’s pro, but has not cleared 42 yards receiving all year and does not need to be in fantasy consideration outside of deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-dab4-a3fb-bf775d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said Luther Burden is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2759-deb1-a39b-275fd5320000</link>
      <description>The potential absence of both Burden and Olamide Zaccheaus (knee, day-to-day) might drive the Bears to use more Colston Loveland next week against the Bengals. FLEX-hungry fantasy managers should keep in touch with Chicago’s injury report later this week to see what comes of these wideout injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2759-deb1-a39b-275fd5320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz will undergo surgery on his left shoulder, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2773-dab4-a3fb-bf73a8af0000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini was the first to report the news. Wentz’s injury is to his non-throwing shoulder, but after further evaluation of his injury, it was decided that surgery would be the best option to correct things. Wentz stepped up to start in five games for the Vikings this season after J.J. McCarthy suffered an ankle injury in Week 2. Wentz’s season ends with a 1,216-6-5 line through the air, with four of his touchdowns coming in Weeks 3 and 4. The veteran quarterback signed a one-year deal with the Vikings this offseason and will likely have a chance to earn a backup role somewhere in 2026 once he is back to full strength. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport later reported that Wentz “suffered a dislocation that tore his labrum and fractured the socket” in the Vikings’ Week 6 game against the Browns, and then gutted it out for two more weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2773-dab4-a3fb-bf73a8af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Michael Penix (knee) will be day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2781-dab4-a3fb-bff160060000</link>
      <description>Penix practiced in the days leading up to Week 8’s game against the Dolphins but was ultimately ruled out in favor of Kirk Cousins. The second-year quarterback is one of several Falcons players who are day-to-day to start the week, as Morris also said S Jessie Bates (ankle), DL Zach Harrison (knee), CB Billy Bowman (hamstring), and EDGE Jalon Walker (groin) would also be day-to-day to open the week. Penix appears to be trending in the right direction but if he’s unable to go, Cousins would again draw the start on the road against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2781-dab4-a3fb-bff160060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Drake London (hip) will be day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278c-dab4-a3fb-bffc7d840000</link>
      <description>London was a late addition to the team’s injury report last week and ended up being ruled out before Sunday’s game against the Dolphins. We don’t know much about the severity of his injury, but London was initially removed from the injury report before being added back to it over the weekend and then ruled out. It’s clear the team was hoping he could play through it, so it’s also possible the decision to sit him on Sunday was more so out of precaution. His day-to-day status to open the week suggests he’ll have a good chance of playing in Week 9 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278c-dab4-a3fb-bffc7d840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals released RB Michael Carter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278f-d5d8-a3ff-ffefaa480000</link>
      <description>Fired on his day off. Carter drew the start for the Cardinals in Weeks 5 and 6, and rushed for 18-51-2 in Week 5 against the Titans. Despite the volume, it was a relatively underwhelming day from an efficiency standpoint, which led to him being out-touched by Zonovan Knight the following week. The Cardinals clearly didn’t love what Carter had to offer — or not offer — to a running back room in need of help with James Connor and Trey Benson both sidelined. Zonovan Knight now figures to see a lead role for the Cardinals in Week 9 when they take on a Cowboys defense that has been vulnerable on the ground. Knight could be a volume-based RB2 play in what looks like a plus matchup on paper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278f-d5d8-a3ff-ffefaa480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dre Greenlaw is eligible to return from suspension in Week 9 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27a7-deb1-a39b-27af9b2b0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw served his one-game suspension for verbally threatening a referee after the Broncos’ Week 7 comeback win against the Giants. Greenlaw was sidelined for Week 8 as a result of his actions, but should be back and in the starting lineup next week when the Broncos visit the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27a7-deb1-a39b-27af9b2b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
