<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen will be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</link>
      <description>McDermott didn’t have an actual term for what Allen was dealing with on Monday beyond him being “sore,” so we’re curious what the actual designation will be. We don’t think Allen is in any real danger of missing Saturday’s game against the Broncos, but it’s not surprising that he’d take it a bit easy after Joe Brady used him like a battering ram and he spent multiple occasions in the medical tent in Buffalo’s Wild Card win over the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b91a-d35e-a1bf-fdda2bdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said RB Ty Johnson (ankle) won’t practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited practice before hitting the questionable line and being ruled out Sunday against the Jaguars. He’s probably a true question mark at this point to be ready against the Broncos on Saturday, with practice participation being the guiding light here. If all he can do is get in another limited Thursday session ahead of a tag, Johnson probably will sit again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b926-d968-a19b-f9f791620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said TE Dalton Kincaid would be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b928-dc7a-af9b-ffbfedaa0000</link>
      <description>We’re not sure yet if he’ll add a new designation after being spotted in a walking boot after the win over the Jaguars, but Kincaid’s normal status has been “knee” over the past few weeks. Kincaid will likely play through this, but remain limited throughout the week in practice. That’s been the norm over the past month or so, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b928-dc7a-af9b-ffbfedaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed FB Carson Steele to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b92a-d968-a19b-f9fb79cf0000</link>
      <description>Steele hung on the Chiefs practice squad for most of last season and will now get a chance to stick in Philadelphia. With Will Shipley and Tank Bigsby under contract, it’s hard to see Steele making any sort of fantasy noise without injuries ahead of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b92a-d968-a19b-f9fb79cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed WR Chandler Brayboy, QB Carter Bradley, G Jerome Carvin, TE Patrick Herbert, RB Ja’Quinden Jackson, WR Tim Jones, T Ricky Lee, DB Keni-H Lovely, DB Jabbar Muhammad, DT Keivie Rose, DB Cam’Ron Silmon-Craig, DB Trevian Thomas, WR Austin Trammell, G Sal Wormley and T Kilian Zierer to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b950-d56e-afff-fff8a6a20000</link>
      <description>We at Rotoworld are dedicated to giving you all the Chandler Brayboy and Keni-H Lovely updates we can. Here’s what we know: They both signed reserve/futures contracts after spending all year on the Jaguars practice squad. That’s all we got. More to come later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b950-d56e-afff-fff8a6a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed QB DJ Uiagalelei, LS Peter Bowden, WR Dalevon Campbell, DL TeRah Edwards, WR Luke Grimm, WR JaQuae Jackson, RB Amar Johnson, LB Emany Johnson, C Josh Kaltenberger, TE Tanner McLachlan, OLB Garmon Randolph, OG Branson Taylor, CB Isas Waxter and TE Thomas Yassmin to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b955-d56e-afff-fffd4c760000</link>
      <description>Uiagalelei was elevated to back up Trey Lance in Week 18, but ultimately did not play at all in Los Angeles’ exhibition to tank into the No. 7 seed. He had a 67.0 PFF grade in 69 offensive preseason snaps this past offseason and could eventually become Los Angeles’ backup quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b955-d56e-afff-fffd4c760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans scheduled an interview with former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b959-d35e-a1bf-fddbb09f0000</link>
      <description>They probably want to ask him how it felt to be the only team to lose a game to Brian Callahan this year. Gannon also has an interview on Thursday with the Commanders regarding their defensive coordinator role. Gannon’s market is now “heating up,” if that’s what you want to call it. The deposed former Cardinals coach met with the Cowboys today to interview for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b959-d35e-a1bf-fddbb09f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Lions defensive coordinator Kelvin Sheppard regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b95f-dc7a-af9b-ffff7a440000</link>
      <description>Sheppard’s unit played pretty well in his first season as defensive coordinator despite injuries hitting the unit hard. The Lions finished fifth in defensive DVOA and there was almost no dropoff from Aaron Glenn leaving for the Jets. Sheppard, 38, could be a name that picks up some more buzz before this hiring cycle is over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b95f-dc7a-af9b-ffff7a440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b963-dc7a-af9b-ffff022c0000</link>
      <description>McDaniel was interviewed during Monday’s Texans-Steelers game. It’s the third head-coaching job that McDaniel has interviewed for this cycle, along with the Titans and Browns. The interest in him as an offensive mind has been more robust than expected thus far, perhaps he actually will get a chance to get a head-coaching gig this offseason now that there are a stunning nine vacancies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b963-dc7a-af9b-ffff022c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes “it’s hard to imagine the Browns continuing to employ [Shedeur] Sanders and Dillon Gabriel after inexplicably drafting both last April.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b96c-dc7a-af9b-ffffce460000</link>
      <description>“Early signs point to Sanders getting to compete for the job, [Deshaun] Watson being stuck on the roster and another quarterback addition in the middle rounds of the draft,” Jackson continues. Guess who is being left out of that quarterback room by omission? Gabriel was reportedly a Kevin Stefanski favorite in the draft process and — our speculation, not Jackson’s — might be traded to Stefanski’s new team this offseason. It’s also possible the team gives us another four-quarterback training camp show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b96c-dc7a-af9b-ffffce460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
