<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 4-of-9 targets for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e1-d90e-a9da-bfefc4910000</link>
      <description>Higgins continues to be a key contributor in the red zone, scoring this time on an eight-yard touchdown just before halftime to give the Texans the lead. The rookie remains heavily involved in the offense with Davis Mills under center, but was seeing decent target volume from C.J. Stroud before his injury. The yardage has been underwhelming, but Higgins is clearly viewed as a reliable option in the passing game, averaging 7.7 targets per game in his last three games. Higgins will be on the WR4/WR5 radar in Week 13’s game against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e1-d90e-a9da-bfefc4910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 1-of-4 targets for eight yards in the Texans’ Week 12 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e6-d90e-a9da-bfef650d0000</link>
      <description>Thursday’s game against the Bills was easily the worst of the season for Schultz, who had gone for 50-plus yards in five of his last six games entering the night. The Texans saw the majority of their production come in the second quarter of Thursday’s win, but struggled to sustain drives for much of the night. Schultz should be in store for a better Week 13 against the Colts, we’re he’ll profile as a fringe TE1/TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a4e6-d90e-a9da-bfef650d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders team president Mark Clouse said the team will play an international game in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a707-db57-afda-f737443e0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders are fresh off an international game in Madrid, Spain, and will be set to run things back again in 2026 at a location that is yet to be decided. That said, we do know the Commanders will be the “home team” in said international game, meaning there will be one less home game for fans to attend stateside next season. Next season will mark the third time the Commanders have played internationally, and the first time they have done so in consecutive seasons. Hopefully, fans will be treated to a start by Jayden Daniels after being forced to watch Marcus Mariota vs. Tua Tagovailoa in Week 12, but regardless, it’s clear the Commanders are a team the league wants to push into international markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a707-db57-afda-f737443e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said RT OT Jonah Williams will undergo shoulder surgery and miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a734-d90e-a9da-bf3f795e0000</link>
      <description>Williams has started all nine games he’s appeared in for the Cardinals this season, but missed Week 11’s game due to his shoulder injury. The veteran tackle has allowed 21 pressures and three sacks this season while earning a PFF grade of 55.9, and is in the final year of a two-year deal he signed last offseason. Williams, 28, has 74 games of starting experience under his belt and should have plenty of suitors next season if the Cardinals don’t opt to bring him back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a734-d90e-a9da-bf3f795e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart (concussion) will not play in Week 12 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a740-d413-ad9f-b7ddf4c60000</link>
      <description>Dart logged back-to-back limited practices to open the week, but the rookie signal-caller will miss his second-straight game with his brain injury. This will put Jameis Winston in line to start against the Lions, who currently rank eighth in passing yards allowed but have also surrendered the ninth-most passing touchdowns on the season. Winston threw for 201 yards and one pick in his first start of the season, and will be in the QB2 range for fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a740-d413-ad9f-b7ddf4c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameis Winston will start in Week 12 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a74c-d82c-a79a-b7dc8c620000</link>
      <description>Winston gets the nod for a second consecutive week after Jaxson Dart was unable to clear the league’s concussion protocol. Last week against the Packers, Winston threw for 201-0-1 on 29 passes, but did punch in a short rushing touchdown to salvage an otherwise disappointing fantasy day. Winston will be on the fantasy radar as a mid QB2 with four teams on bye, but he matches up against a Lions defense that ranks eighth in passing yards allowed this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a74c-d82c-a79a-b7dc8c620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions’ HC Dan Campbell said chances of Sam LaPorta (back) returning in 2025 are “very, very slim.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a75c-db57-afda-f77e38ce0000</link>
      <description>LaPorta’s injury came as a bit of a surprise when it was first announced. Then he surprisingly landed on injured reserve last Saturday and has now more or less been ruled out for the season. Campbell confirmed on Friday that LaPorta underwent back surgery, which feels like another unexpected announcement for a player who looked perfectly fine the last time we saw him on a field in Week 10. If his season is over, LaPorta ends 2025 with a productive 40-489-3 line on 49 targets. LaPorta was on pace for a career-high 923 receiving yards before his injury, while the 92 targets he was on pace for would have narrowly topped his 2024 total (83). Assuming this isn’t an injury that lingers into the offseason, LaPorta will have plenty of upside as a high-end TE1 for fantasy managers in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a75c-db57-afda-f77e38ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said the team will take some additional time to decide if Joe Burrow (toe, questionable) will start in Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a76f-d413-ad9f-b7ff44fb0000</link>
      <description>Burrow participated in every practice this week and was taking first-team reps with the offense on Thursday. The Bengals’ QB1 was already expected to return in Week 13 against the Ravens on Thanksgiving Day, but a good few days of practice this week have him in the running to start against the Patriots. The decision to list him as questionable is a good sign entering the weekend, but the Bengals may opt to err on the side of caution for a few more days. For now, Burrow should be considered as truly questionable by fantasy managers, but the Bengals will have until 4 PM EST on Saturday to decide whether or not to activate him from injured reserve. Whether or not they do activate him should tell us all we need to know for his availability come Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a76f-d413-ad9f-b7ff44fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (toe/shoulder) will not play in Week 12 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a774-db57-afda-f776ae130000</link>
      <description>Bowles said the team is preparing Irving to return for Week 13’s game against the Cardinals, while adding that the time away from the game and the injury took a mental toll on the second-year back. Bowles noted that Irving is “in a good place” now after seeking additional support during his time away, which is of the utmost importance for any player dealing with mental health issues. Sean Tucker and Rachaad White will again split backfield duties for Week 12’s game against the Rams, with Tucker looking like the early favorite to lead the backfield after running for 19-106-2 last week in Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a774-db57-afda-f776ae130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (collarbone) returned to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a789-d413-ad9f-b7dd28b00000</link>
      <description>It’s the first time Reed has been on a practice field since breaking his collarbone against the Commanders. With his 21-day return window now opened, the Packers have three weeks before they must activate him from injured reserve, but a return in Week 12 seems unlikely at this point. Still, head coach Matt LaFleur said earlier in the week, “I sure as heck hope so,” when asked if Reed could play vs. the Vikings, so we’ll see what happens over the next 24 hours. We will check back in once the Packers have released their final injury report, which will have Reeds’ Week 12 status listed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a789-d413-ad9f-b7dd28b00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
