<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports “the odds are increasing” that Aaron Rodgers will return to the Steelers in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dbc-d355-a5bd-bffc569f0000</link>
      <description>“It would not be a surprise if Rodgers is back in Pittsburgh,” Pelissero says. Look for us to repeat some version of this blurb 20 times over the next five months, and after that perhaps we’ll get an actual resolution. Hiring Mike McCarthy — who Pelissero notes has spoken to Rodgers several times — surely put this in motion. Rodgers and the Steelers would also need to work out a contract for him to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dbc-d355-a5bd-bffc569f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Derek Carr could unretire for “the right situation and coaching staff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dc3-d89c-a1be-bfdf20d20000</link>
      <description>There’s not a real link here to hold on to yet, the sources are not chirping a specific team, but it’s unsurprising that Carr would consider giving it another go as he’s still just 35 and the quarterback market this offseason is desolate. One complicating factor is that the Saints retain his rights and may ask for something in a trade to move on from their former signalcaller. Carr is reportedly “throwing fully as part of his regular exercise routine.” At this point we’d expect someone to make the plunge on Carr, the only question is the cost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dc3-d89c-a1be-bfdf20d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Dolphins “would like to explore” trading Tua Tagovailoa but it remains unclear if a deal is “feasible.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dc6-d042-afbc-7dd6dd230000</link>
      <description>Not surprising given the tenor of the news, but as Schefter notes, the Dolphins would be hard-pressed to get anything for him. Schefter says the Dolphins are willing to pay down a portion of the contract to make a trade happen, but the most likely exit point for this remains a post-June 1 cut that would spread his dead cap hit over a couple of years ala Russell Wilson’s departure from the Broncos. Tagovailoa has a real chance to be starting elsewhere in 2026 just based on how many chairs there are to fill, but he’ll undoubtedly be an uninspiring fantasy starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dc6-d042-afbc-7dd6dd230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears named passing game coordinator Press Taylor as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dce-d629-a1bc-bddf3f230000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly an inspiring move, but Ben Johnson is the one calling the plays so we probably shouldn’t worry about it too much. Taylor played a part in Trevor Lawrence’s regression under Doug Pederson as a playcaller in Jacksonville. The only Bears out-of-house interview we’ve heard of for this job was Cardinals pass game specialist Connor Senger, who could still wind up on this staff in a lower position now that Mike LaFleur has taken over as Arizona’s head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dce-d629-a1bc-bddf3f230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Chiefs want Travis Kelce to return in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dd1-d89c-a1be-bfdf9df60000</link>
      <description>He’d be entering his age-37 season, but most of the smoke since the end of the season has pointed in this direction. The Chiefs are currently significantly over the cap and would probably need to shuffle some salaries around to get Kelce — an impending free agent — under contract. Kelce himself has reportedly been in touch with the Chiefs about a return, and Dianna Russini reported yesterday that many close to Kelce believe he will return. Rapoport says we should expect clarity “sooner, rather than later” on Kelce’s 2026 status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dd1-d89c-a1be-bfdf9df60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports a Maxx Crosby (knee) trade could happen “at the 2026 NFL Draft or prior to the season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dd5-d89c-a1be-bfdf449f0000</link>
      <description>The key to this report is Crosby’s meniscus repair, which Rapoport notes makes him unlikely to be medically cleared before free agency officially begins. Thus, any acquiring team would be taking a leap of faith on the 28-year-old’s health for the 2026 season. We would be surprised if the Raiders traded him after the draft, where they’d seem to lose a lot of leverage, but the Micah Parsons trade did just happen right before the start of the 2025 season so it can’t be entirely ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dd5-d89c-a1be-bfdf449f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed defensive backs coach Dino Vasso to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dda-d629-a1bc-bddf245f0000</link>
      <description>Vasso had been a candidate for the Browns, Raiders, Titans and Cardinals defensive coordinator openings, but will instead stay put in Houston with a contract extension. These were the first major sniffs of interest Vasso has had for a coordinator opening, but the league-wide amount of interest in him bodes well for his chances of eventually getting a job down the line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dda-d629-a1bc-bddf245f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes the Cardinals and Dolphins are “teams [he’ll] be watching” to pursue impending free agent Malik Willis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ddf-d89c-a1be-bfdfc8600000</link>
      <description>The entire Dolphins front office is now essentially a Packers front office after they hired GM Jon-Eric Sullivan and head coach Jeff Hafley away, so that’s an easy tie. Mike LaFleur, the new head coach in Arizona, can pick the brain of his brother (Green Bay’s head coach) about Willis. We’ve tied Willis to the Dolphins earlier this offseason, but it’s a little surprising to see the Cardinals as a potential suitor given how well Jacoby Brissett played down the stretch in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ddf-d89c-a1be-bfdfc8600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons fired VP of football operations Ryan Pace.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3de5-d042-afbc-7df79cd20000</link>
      <description>Pace will “have options elsewhere” per NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero. The former Bears general manager will look to rebuild the reputation in a new front office in 2026. The Falcons signaled what they thought of the current brain trust when they cleaned house after the season, and ‘president of football’ Matt Ryan clearly had no use for Pace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3de5-d042-afbc-7df79cd20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes Landon Dickerson is “no certainty to return” to the Eagles in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dea-d629-a1bc-bdffb85b0000</link>
      <description>Dickerson is just 27, but struggled through a challenging season in 2025 with two missed games while struggling through several games with ankle and quad injuries. He didn’t look right from the jump. Lane Johnson is another retirement possibility for the Eagles, and The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane believes Johnson isn’t sure his body will hold up and he’s “not sure if he’s coming back or not.” The Eagles are set up for plenty of turnover on the offensive side of the ball this offseason and likely will need to target picks on the offensive line even if Dickerson and Johnson return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dea-d629-a1bc-bdffb85b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
