<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent K Eddy Pineiro is visiting with the 49ers Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fe3-db7b-a5dd-afe783190000</link>
      <description>He’s one plausible replacement for the recently-waived Jake Moody. The 49ers kicker job generally comes with a lot of fantasy appeal, but they’re banged up enough to this point that whoever kicks for San Francisco this weekend against the Saints may not see many attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fe3-db7b-a5dd-afe783190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed P Cameron Johnston.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-300c-d332-a1fd-b63e57550000</link>
      <description>They waived Brad Robbins. Not sure why the Bills figured they’d need a punter after what we saw on Sunday night, but if they attempt any in Week 2, Johnston will be taking them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-300c-d332-a1fd-b63e57550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed OL James Daniels (pectoral) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-301b-d93a-abbb-795b9f250000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four weeks. The estimate from ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler was 3-4 weeks, so we’re not expecting a lengthy stay past the minimum required on injured reserve for Daniels. Kion Smith replaced him in Week 1 and may be looking at starter snaps in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-301b-d93a-abbb-795b9f250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed DT Tommy Togiai to a one-year extension worth up to $3.3 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3025-d332-a1fd-b6374d5f0000</link>
      <description>Togiai did not play in the opener. He had a 58.1 PFF grade for the Texans in 280 defensive snaps last year, after not playing in the NFL at all in 2023. It’s hard to call any transaction this minor a bad move, but it’s certainly a little odd. Does this team know about its own offensive line?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3025-d332-a1fd-b6374d5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (ankle) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302a-db7b-a5dd-b02e659f0000</link>
      <description>All of these reports, as usual on Tuesday, are estimations. Golden doesn’t seem like he’ll have a problem playing on Thursday against the Commanders. Perhaps getting away from Detroit’s blitz-happy scheme will open up some more underneath for Golden against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302a-db7b-a5dd-b02e659f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot) upgraded to limited in Green Bay’s Tuesday estimated practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302c-db7b-a5dd-b02cddb60000</link>
      <description>A DNP on Monday looks to be managing the existing foot issue, which Reed played on in Week 1. We’d expect Reed and Dontayvon Wicks (calf — also limited, also played through it in Week 1) to be out there for Green Bay against the Commanders on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302c-db7b-a5dd-b02cddb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) was limited in Green Bay’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302e-db7b-a5dd-b02eec550000</link>
      <description>It was a walk-thru, so this is an estimation. Parsons will surely play a small package in Week 2 after his successful debut against the Lions in Week 1. It will likely be more of the same against Washington on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302e-db7b-a5dd-b02eec550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers OL Zach Tom (oblique) and Aaron Banks (ankle/groin) did not participate in Green Bay’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3030-db7b-a5dd-b0349f810000</link>
      <description>Jordan Love was quoted earlier today as saying “we may have some guys out there who haven’t been out there” when asked about the offensive line, and it certainly appears to be trending that way on the injury report. Jordan Morgan would be a logical replacement for one of the spots. Darian Kinnard played right tackle in Tom’s absence in Week 1 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3030-db7b-a5dd-b0349f810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Austin Ekeler (shoulder) was limited in Washington’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3036-d332-a1fd-b6368fff0000</link>
      <description>They conducted walkthroughs both days and the report is an estimation. Ekeler didn’t appear on the Week 1 report and did see noticeably fewer snaps in the second half against the Giants, so it is possible that it contributed to less Ekeler down the stretch. We’d still expect him to suit up for Week 2, perhaps with a role more similar to the one he had in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3036-d332-a1fd-b6368fff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Noah Brown (knee) remained limited in Washington’s practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3039-dbe3-a9bb-307b9cee0000</link>
      <description>He played through this designation last week, logging 33 snaps for the Commanders as their third receiver. He has some DFS solo slate appeal against the Packers, but otherwise probably isn’t involved enough to consider for standard fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3039-dbe3-a9bb-307b9cee0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
