<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals QB Joe Burrow won’t be activated for Week 12’s matchup with the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aa05-db57-afda-fe3752d80000</link>
      <description>Burrow practiced all week and was even taking first-team reps by the end of the week. Still, the Bengals are making the call to hold him out for one more game with a short week coming up, leaving Joe Flacco to make another start against the Patriots in Week 12. Burrow, who will remain on injured reserve, appears to be on track to return from a toe injury that’s kept him out since Week 2 in Week 13 against the Ravens on Thanksgiving Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aa05-db57-afda-fe3752d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) is expected to play in Week 12’s matchup with the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ac1d-d82c-a79a-bf9d3ab60000</link>
      <description>Russini’s report comes on the heels of Bucs coach Todd Bowles admitting that Godwin was trending towards playing as of Friday. The 29-year-old wide receiver was mostly limited in practice this week. Godwin is a desperation FLEX play for fantasy managers given the difficult matchup with the Rams on Sunday Night Football on NBC. If Godwin can return to form before the fantasy playoffs, he could turn out to be one of the better players to stash this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ac1d-d82c-a79a-bf9d3ab60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (groin) won’t be activated for Week 12 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aca5-d413-ad9f-bdfd44540000</link>
      <description>Johnson and Kyler Gordon (hamstring) are both listed as questionable, but Fowler reports neither will be activated from injured reserve to face the Steelers in Week 12. Fowler passes along that the team is hopeful both can return in Week 13 against Philadelphia. Both cornerbacks were placed on injured reserve after suffering injuries in training camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aca5-d413-ad9f-bdfd44540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles removed C Cam Jurgens (concussion) from the injury report ahead of Week 12 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-acbe-d90e-a9da-bfbf56870000</link>
      <description>Jurgens departed the team’s Week 11 win over the Lions to be evaluated for a concussion. He increased his participation in each practice this week before drawing the questionable tag, ultimately removed from the injury report Saturday ahead of a matchup with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-acbe-d90e-a9da-bfbf56870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans elevated WR Xavier Restrepo from the practice squad for Week 12 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-acc2-d82c-a79a-bfd69f1f0000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Cam Ward’s former collegiate teammate was elevated to the active roster for the first time since signing to the team’s practice squad before the start of the season. Injuries to Calvin Ridley and Elic Ayomanor made it necessary for the team to bring up pass-catching depth, and Restrepo made the most sense. It remains to be seen how much run he will get in his first professional contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-acc2-d82c-a79a-bfd69f1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears placed LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aced-d413-ad9f-bdfdf5e20000</link>
      <description>Edmunds will miss the next four games, at minimum, leaving a gaping hole in the interior of the Chicago defense. Fellow linebacker T.J. Edwards was also ruled out for Week 12, boosting the rushing matchup for Jaylen Warren and Kenneth Gainwell for the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aced-d413-ad9f-bdfdf5e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings activated C Ryan Kelly (concussion) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad07-d82c-a79a-bf9791c60000</link>
      <description>The veteran center missed the previous six games with a nasty concussion sustained in Week 4. His return bolsters a struggling Minnesota offensive line in time for a divisional matchup with the Packers in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad07-d82c-a79a-bf9791c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars activated TE Brenton Strange (hip) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad65-db57-afda-ff77e9e40000</link>
      <description>Strange last played in Week 5 and missed the previous five games for a Jaguars team struggling through a multitude of injuries. His return comes in the wake of the signing of Jakobi Meyers as the trade deadline, meaning he is unlikely to return to the same robust receiving role he left when injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad65-db57-afda-ff77e9e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers removed WR Xavier Legette from the injury report Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad6a-d82c-a79a-bffec8cd0000</link>
      <description>That places Legette in line to play on Monday Night Football against the 49ers. Legette managed just 55% of the offensive snaps while dealing with a hip injury in Week 11 but could return to a more robust role against the injury-riddled San Francisco defense. Fantasy managers in a bind due to bye weeks can comfortably start the second-year receiver as a viable FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad6a-d82c-a79a-bffec8cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks placed WR Tory Horton (shin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad6f-d90e-a9da-bf6f7d010000</link>
      <description>Horton had already been ruled out for Week 12 after also missing Week 10 and Week 11, mean he will miss a minimum of six games while dealing with a shin injury that popped up before the team’s Week 10 contest. His absence means far less than it otherwise would had the team not traded for veteran Rashid Shaheed at the deadline, something that now looks more substantial considering Horton’s placement on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ad6f-d90e-a9da-bf6f7d010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
