<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 23:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Noah Brown (groin/IR) will not play in Washington’s Week 13 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc5b-d90e-a9da-df5fec450000</link>
      <description>Brown was full on Thursday, but did not practice on Friday with a rest designation. Zach Ertz, Terry McLaurin, and Deebo Samuel will be the only reliable Commanders fantasy options against Denver. Brown is still just in the first week of his 21-day window and it stands to reason he’ll be activated soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc5b-d90e-a9da-df5fec450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) is not on the injury report for Week 13 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc63-d82c-a79a-fff7e7100000</link>
      <description>We expect the team to announce his official activation from injured reserve soon. The speedy wide receiver practiced fully all week, so he should be ready for his typical snap share. The volatile fantasy producer cannot be counted on for FLEX value, but all it takes is one play. A classic boom-bust deep threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc63-d82c-a79a-fff7e7100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (toe) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc71-d6c4-abfb-de73ac420000</link>
      <description>He was limited on Thursday. This doesn’t look like an injury that has much of a chance to keep Henry out of MNF’s game against the Giants, where he’ll be a borderline TE1 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc71-d6c4-abfb-de73ac420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc6a-db57-afda-de7ad9fb0000</link>
      <description>Robinson is on track to play, but we are hoping to see him practice fully on Saturday. The shifty route runner’s 28.0 percent target share leads the team by 11.2 percent. Robinson is a rock solid WR3 with upside if active on Monday night against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc6a-db57-afda-de7ad9fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc7a-db57-afda-de7ae7920000</link>
      <description>Slayton is on track to face the Patriots on Monday night. Hopefully, he returns to full participation soon, and puts this hamstring strain behind him. The speedy wide receiver is on the volatile FLEX radar, catching passes from QB Jaxson Dart, who cleared the NFL’s concussion protocol earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc7a-db57-afda-de7ae7920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc7a-d82c-a79a-fffe99bc0000</link>
      <description>Njoku played through the injury last week, but earned zero targets. Rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr., meanwhile, earned six. Njoku is just a boom-bust TE2 at this point. The 49ers have allowed 637 receiving yards to opposing tight ends, the 11th-most in the NFL, which makes the veteran tight end mildly appealing. Start-sit decisions can be broken against him though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc7a-d82c-a79a-fffe99bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos CB Pat Surtain (pectoral) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc9a-d82c-a79a-ff9ecf550000</link>
      <description>Surtain takes the field on game day for the first time since Week 8. He will likely take on WR Terry McLaurin (quad), who is also making his return from a multi-game absence, when McLaurin lines up on the perimeter. It should be a good matchup. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc9a-d82c-a79a-ff9ecf550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Alex Singleton (illness) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc92-d90e-a9da-df9f65680000</link>
      <description>Singleton last played in Week 10. The following week, he underwent an operation after being diagnosed with testicular cancer. The Broncos were on bye in Week 12. Singleton’s return is one that all NFL fans can celebrate. Despite the absence, Singleton ties for a team-high 57 tackles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc92-d90e-a9da-df9f65680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Tre Tucker (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cca4-d6c4-abfb-dea792b80000</link>
      <description>Tucker holds a three-target lead (64) over his teammates, but his role is occasionally limited to running cardio, given the offense’s overall dysfunction. The team fired OC Chip Kelly earlier this week, elevating QB coach Greg Olson to the interim offensive coordinator position. Olson previously served as the Raiders’ offensive coordinator twice before. Tucker is a boom-bust WR4/FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cca4-d6c4-abfb-dea792b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders ruled out TE Michael Mayer (ankle) for Week 13 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cca4-d82c-a79a-ffb48d420000</link>
      <description>Mayer only has 30 targets to his name this year. His absence is hardly consequential, though it theoretically frees up one or two for TE Brock Bowers and WR Tre Tucker (knee) to fight for. Mayer does not need to be rostered in 12-team re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cca4-d82c-a79a-ffb48d420000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
