<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Marcel Louis-Jacques reports there’s “no major concern” about Tua Tagovailoa’s thumb and hip injuries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c97d-dd4c-afb9-effdafd90000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa was limited during Wednesday’s practice, raising concerns about his Week 6 availability against the Chargers. As long as he practices in some capacity in the coming days, Tua should be good to go against LA. Tagovailoa last week against the Panthers completed 27-of-36 passes for 256 yards and three touchdowns in the Dolphins’ first game without Tyreek Hill (knee). He’ll be a low-ceiling top-15 fantasy option in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c97d-dd4c-afb9-effdafd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said Mac Jones (knee) “should be OK” for Week 6 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c998-db72-a199-fbdb2a1a0000</link>
      <description>Jones is likely to be under center against the Bucs this weekend with Brock Purdy recovering from a setback to his toe injury. Jones was banged up in the second half of last week’s win against the Rams, struggling with a knee issue and leg cramps. Jones leads the NFL in passing yards over his past three games, throwing six touchdowns to just one interception. He should be started in superflex lineups this week against the pass-funnel Tampa Bay defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c998-db72-a199-fbdb2a1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said K Brandon McManus’ quad injury is “a major concern.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9c3-d94a-a79d-c9cfc0870000</link>
      <description>Apparently McManus recently injured his quad in practice and seems iffy — at best — for Week 6 against the Bengals. The veteran has made seven of his nine field goal tries this season and 11 of his 12 extra point attempts. The Packers may need to find a replacement for McManus if he’s unable to practice in the coming days. Whoever kicks for the Packers will be fantasy viable against a wretched Bengals defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9c3-d94a-a79d-c9cfc0870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pec) won’t practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9df-d94a-a79d-c9dfc72d0000</link>
      <description>Milano would seem like a long shot to suit up this week against the Falcons. He suffered the pec injury in Week 4. Buffalo’s defense remains of the of most injury-marred in the NFL through five weeks, making the Bills vulnerable to a run-heavy Atlanta offense that came to life in Week 4 before the team’s bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9df-d94a-a79d-c9dfc72d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB Tyler Badie (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9e2-d94a-a79d-c9efdeae0000</link>
      <description>Badie was banged up in Week 5 against the Eagles but should be OK for Week 6 after being upgraded to a full practice on Thursday. Badie hasn’t seen a carry since Week 2 but has worked in as a pass catcher out of the Denver backfield alongside JK Dobbins and RJ Harvey. Badie has four targets over the past two games. He won’t be fantasy viable unless Dobbins or Harvey miss time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9e2-d94a-a79d-c9efdeae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f0-db72-a199-fbfbe5c90000</link>
      <description>This is Johnson’s first practice since injuring his ankle in Week 2. Earlier this week, ESPN’s Rich Cimini reported that Johnson will travel with the team to London ahead of their Week 6 game against the Broncos, which suggests the Jets believe he has a chance to suit up. Today’s limited session is another step in the right direction, though his availability on Sunday is not yet guaranteed. The Jets’ 6.5 NFL sacks tie for the sixth-fewest in the league. They need him back badly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f0-db72-a199-fbfbe5c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Terry McLaurin (quad) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9fd-db72-a199-fbffc4310000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported McLaurin is “not looking good” for Week 6 against the Bears. His continued inability to practice furthers that notion. McLaurin could be seen working off to the side, without a jersey, while the rest of the team practiced in pads. Fantasy managers should expect McLaurin to miss his third straight game this weekend, unless something drastically changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9fd-db72-a199-fbffc4310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Steelers reportedly inquired about Saints WR Rashid Shaheed’s availability during Pittsburgh’s Week 5 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca02-dd4c-afb9-efc3971b0000</link>
      <description>No word yet on whether the Saints seriously entertained the inquiry. The former undrafted free agent is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill opines that a potential trade “would be a complicated deal” because the acquiring team “would have to be willing to trade for him and pay a new contract.” Shaheed was a small-school prospect who earned five college accolades as a returner and one as a wide receiver. He earned Pro Bowl and first-team All-Pro honors as a returner in 2023. Were the Steelers to acquire him, his FLEX appeal would likely take a hit. The Saints’ voluminous passing offense provides him and Chris Olave with enough opportunities for both players to remain fantasy-relevant. The Steelers’ run-oriented playcalling would likely reduce his weekly target count while reducing DK Metcalf’s reliability as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca02-dd4c-afb9-efc3971b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-db72-a199-fa5b6ca90000</link>
      <description>Jackson was labeled week-to-week after straining his hamstring in Week 4. Nearly two weeks later, he has not yet returned to practice, which makes sense. The Ravens are on bye in Week 7. If he can play in Week 6, he surely will, but at this point, it seems likely that the team holds him out until Week 8. Ideally, the extended absence allows his injured muscle to fully heal, which should set him up for immediate fantasy success upon his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-db72-a199-fa5b6ca90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
