<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f5-d4ed-a9de-77ffa8a50000</link>
      <description>Thomas Jr. went down to a light push from a Rams corner late in the team’s Week 7 loss to LA. The shove almost certainly aggravated a preexisting issue. The good news is that players tend to suit up after opening the week with a limited practice, though we suspect BTJ is nowhere near fully healthy. The shoulder issue could cause the Jags to lean on Travis Hunter more coming out of the bye. BTJ will get another week in the WR1 ranks, but his usage will be worth monitoring versus the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f5-d4ed-a9de-77ffa8a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f8-d321-a5bf-b3ffb4c50000</link>
      <description>Tim Patrick, the Jags’ No. 5 receiver, was also limited in practice. With Travis Hunter’s role expected to grow this week, Brown and Parker Washington will be fighting for the WR3 role in Jacksonville. Brown has run more routes this year but Washington has the edge in targets and most receiving stats. Washington will be a low-ceiling WR5 for the team’s Week 9 date with the Raiders. Brown is barely on the fantasy radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f8-d321-a5bf-b3ffb4c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (concussion) did not practice Wednesday,</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3211-de12-a19e-36318b390000</link>
      <description>That should not come as a surprise considering the new protocol, mandating a player be asymptomatic before returning to the practice field. All signs point to Mims missing Week 9 against the Texans unless he gets in a limited session, and subsequent full practice, the final two days of preparation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3211-de12-a19e-36318b390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones (knee) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3247-d48c-ad9f-fe4f42df0000</link>
      <description>Jones suffered a knee contusion during Sunday’s Week 8 loss to the Texans, but he’ll be ready to play. The question is if he’ll start that game with Brock Purdy (toe) potentially being ready to return, but it’s more likely than not that Jones will be under center against the Giants in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3247-d48c-ad9f-fe4f42df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua (ankle) was officially limited in his Wednesday return to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-322a-de12-a19e-362a7ed00000</link>
      <description>It would have been nice to see a “full” session, but coach Sean McVay has already said Nacua will play this week after sitting out in Week 7 ahead of the Rams’ bye. Although we suppose Nacua will be a re-injury risk, fantasy managers can slot him in for his typical production as long as he stays on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-322a-de12-a19e-362a7ed00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nate Adkins (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3243-de12-a19e-3663cf0d0000</link>
      <description>Adkins suffered a knee injury during the Week 8 win over the Jets, and is not expected to be able to play in Week 9 against the Texans. Marcedes Lewis was signed from the practice squad and will likely see most of the snaps in Adkins’ place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3243-de12-a19e-3663cf0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks DB Devon Witherspoon (knee) was listed as a full participant for Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3295-d321-a5bf-b2d7dbb10000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon has missed the last three games of the season with his knee issue, but the defender appears to be on track to return to the secondary for Sunday Night Football against the Commanders in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3295-d321-a5bf-b2d7dbb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31fe-d48c-ad9f-fdff99df0000</link>
      <description>The good news for Houston fans is that Nico Collins and Christian Kirk were both back on the practice field on Wednesday. Schultz could play this week if he returns to practice eventually, though fantasy managers may want to work on contingency plans for him. Harrison Bryant would likely draw the start in Schultz’s place if he misses Week 9 against Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31fe-d48c-ad9f-fdff99df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers (knee) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-352d-d71c-afdf-bd6d75fe0000</link>
      <description>It looks like both Meyers and Brock Bowers will be back for the team’s Week 9 matchup with the Jaguars. Meyers publicly reiterated his desire to be traded before missing Week 7’s game against the Chiefs with the knee injury. He will get one final chance to showcase his value to other teams on Sunday before the Tuesday deadline. Meyers will sit on the WR2/3 border for his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-352d-d71c-afdf-bd6d75fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed RG Brady Christensen (Achilles) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3563-d1e7-a1fa-7feb2afa0000</link>
      <description>Christensen suffered a season-ending Achilles injury in Week 8. He underwent surgery earlier this week. Christensen will hit free agency at the age of 29 after this season. The Panthers signed Mike White to their 53-man roster in a corresponding move. White could serve as Bryce Young’s backup this week with Andy Dalton banged up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3563-d1e7-a1fa-7feb2afa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
