<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 04:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus caught a six-yard pass in Chicago’s Week 12 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f8-d90e-a9da-bfff53ce0000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus’ catch in the dying moments of the second quarter proved to be his only target. With the Bears finally getting second-round rookie Luther Burden more involved, Zaccheaus has two catches for 11 yards over the past three weeks. He is back to being out of sight, out of mind in 12-team fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f8-d90e-a9da-bfff53ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders fired OC Chip Kelly.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f8-db57-afda-f7fa92fa0000</link>
      <description>Kelly’s time with the Raiders lasted just 11 games, yet this move still feels past due. The offense averaged 4.6 yards per play, 6.67 yards per pass play and 3.5 yards per carry. The Raiders’ front office signed Kelly to a contract that paid him $6 million per year, back in February, making him the NFL’s highest-paid offensive coordinator. His results were extremely disappointing. Seeing him return to the college ranks would be unsurprising.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f8-db57-afda-f7fa92fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley had ten rushes for 22 yards in the Eagles’ Week 12 loss against the Eagles, adding seven catches for 52 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f6-db57-afda-f7f618f30000</link>
      <description>Barkley saw an unusually big role in the team’s passing offense. He had never had more than four receptions in a game during his time with the Eagles, and hadn’t seen more than five targets since he was leading the Giants backfield. Though Barkley’s receptions helped salvage his fantasy day, his lack or explosion and depressed overall rushing production remains a major issue for one of the biggest fantasy disappointments in recent memory. Barkley will be a must-start in Week 12 against a Bears team that gives up the league’s highest rate of rush yards before contact, a key metric for running backs like Barkley who rely on explosive runs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f6-db57-afda-f7f618f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 6-of-9 targets for 55 yards in the Raiders’ Week 12 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f4-d82c-a79a-b3f4a9870000</link>
      <description>Bowers did fantasy managers a solid with two catches for 19 yards on a meaningless three-play drive to close the game. He had struggled to get much going before the pair of garbage-time catches. Bowers erupted for 127 yards and three scores in his first game back after missing a few weeks with a knee injury. He has since logged yardage totals of 31, 72, and 55 yards. Bowers is still one of the best fantasy tight ends in the league, but the Raiders’ struggles on offense are hurting both his floor and his ceiling. He will slot in as the TE2 overall, behind Trey McBride, in the fantasy ranks for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3f4-d82c-a79a-b3f4a9870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Kmet caught a three-yard pass in Chicago’s Week 12 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3fa-d90e-a9da-bfffd90f0000</link>
      <description>Kmet’s second quarter catch was his only official target, though he had another look nullified by penalty. Although he’s still running routes and playing plenty of critical snaps, Kmet has fallen far behind Colston Loveland in the Bears’ targets battle up the seam. With bye weeks soon coming to a close, Kmet isn’t going to find himself in the top-24 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3fa-d90e-a9da-bfffd90f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin caught 4-of-5 targets for 36 yards in the Steelers’ Week 12 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3fd-d82c-a79a-b3fd968d0000</link>
      <description>With fill-in QB Mason Rudolph checking it down left and right, Austin’s five short-area targets were third on the team behind DK Metcalf and Kenneth Gainwell. Austin has had plenty of 4-5 catch pop-up weeks, but he has exceeded 40 yards two times all season. Regardless of whether Aaron Rodgers (wrist) is back for Week 13 against the Bills, Austin hasn’t done enough to put himself on the WR4 map.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3fd-d82c-a79a-b3fd968d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Aubrey made one of his two field goal attempts and all three of his extra point attempts in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b400-d90e-a9da-bf0fc2720000</link>
      <description>Aubrey missed a 51-yarder in the second half — a rare miss for the all-world kicker — but drilled the game winner to cap a memorable Cowboys comeback against their division rival. Aubrey, who has only missed two field goal tries all season, should stay in fantasy lineups in Week 13 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b400-d90e-a9da-bf0fc2720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 3-of-3 targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 12 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b401-d82c-a79a-b79589f40000</link>
      <description>All four of Freiermuth’s 2025 scores have come since Oct. 16, but he hasn’t caught more than three passes or cleared 40 yards in any of his past five games. Rotating snaps and targets with Jonnu Smith and Darnell Washington, Freiermuth is on the outside looking in of TE2 status heading into Week 13 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b401-d82c-a79a-b79589f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 2-of-2 targets for 22 yards in the Steelers’ Week 12 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b406-db57-afda-f636129f0000</link>
      <description>Washington’s emergence — if you can call it that — has knee-capped Jonnu Smith’s TE2 prospects while making Pat Freiermuth a touchdown-or-bust option, but it hasn’t really created any roto value of Washington’s own. The big fella is a marvel to watch with the ball in his hands, but his spiked weeks are too difficult to predict to take him seriously as a TE2. The 24-year-old is a classic “more valuable in real life than fantasy” player, at least for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b406-db57-afda-f636129f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 6-of-7 targets for 51 yards in the Titans’ Week 12 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b408-d90e-a9da-bf0f78700000</link>
      <description>With the Titans coming out of their bye week, fourth-round rookie Helm’s catches and yards were both new season highs. He tied for the team lead in targets this afternoon. Good, necessary stuff from the Titans as they evaluate their young talent down the stretch, but it is going to be extremely difficult for Helm to command enough looks to make himself an every-week TE2. He’s not really worth a look for Week 13 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b408-d90e-a9da-bf0f78700000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
