<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 7-of-12 targets for 85 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d33-d45b-affe-5db7e1bf0000</link>
      <description>Lamb was mostly unable to shake loose from tight coverage outside of a 33-yard gain on a scramble drill in the second half. Both his 12 targets and 85 yards led the team on a night the Cowboys notched just 333 yards of total offense, but two turnovers on downs in the red zone and three giveaways capped his fantasy upside. The Cowboys now head to their bye week losers of three of their last four games, now sitting 2.5-games behind the division-leading Eagles in the NFC East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d33-d45b-affe-5db7e1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 6-of-9 targets for 79 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d37-d45b-affe-5db7e7610000</link>
      <description>Pickens finished second on the team in targets, receptions, and yards behind alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb but was held out of the end zone, capping his fantasy upside on a night the team turned the ball over on downs twice inside the red zone and committed three giveaways. He was flagged for unsportsmanlike conduct following a six-yard reception on the team’s penultimate possession as they looked to claw back from a 10-point deficit, highlighting his weekly range of outcomes as a player that still needs to mature. The Cowboys head to their bye week losers of three of their last four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d37-d45b-affe-5db7e7610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-7 targets for 50 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d3c-d713-ad9e-6d7c66740000</link>
      <description>Fantasy’s overall TE1 through the first half of the season went through a four-game stretch where he scored six times but has since been targeted only eight times in two games. He is likely to continue to go as the team goes with his most recent poor outings both coming in losses where the Cowboys were held to 24 points or fewer. He was targeted in the red zone once in this one but an overthrow from quarterback Dak Prescott in the face of pressure hit off the veteran tight end’s hands and fell incomplete. The truth likely lies somewhere in the middle for Ferguson, who is equal parts unlikely to finish the season atop the tight end ranks as he is to continue his recent downswing in production. Fantasy managers will need a fill-in in Week 10 as the Cowboys head to their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d3c-d713-ad9e-6d7c66740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Flournoy caught both targets for 12 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 9 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d44-d713-ad9e-6d54ddb00000</link>
      <description>His touchdown came in the fourth quarter with the team down 27-10, but it was arguably his catch earlier in the drive that was more worthy of a highlight reel. He managed to hang on through full arm extension in tight coverage and through contact to extend the drive that would ultimately lead to his touchdown. Flournoy isn’t playing enough snaps to warrant weekly fantasy consideration but remains a name to watch should another injury occur to someone ahead of him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4d44-d713-ad9e-6d54ddb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys acquired LB Logan Wilson from the Bengals in exchange for a seventh-round draft pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f1b-d45b-affe-5f9f3b290000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are looking to salvage their season with a defensive boost after being shredded by Jacoby Brissett and the Cardinals on Monday night. Wilson, 29, has two years remaining on a four-year, $36 million extension he signed with the Bengals in July 2023. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Cowboys did not “rework his deal to facilitate a trade.” Thomas, who was benched by the Bengals in Week 6, will join a Cowboys defense that ranks second in QB pressure rate while giving up the fifth most yards per play through Week 9. Dallas has allowed the second highest rate of possessions that end with a score.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f1b-d45b-affe-5f9f3b290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said QB Kyler Murray remains the team’s starter when healthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f51-d45b-affe-5fd726640000</link>
      <description>Gannon committed to Murray after Monday night’s upset win over the Cowboys and Arizona’s best three-game offensive stretch in memory. Jacoby Brissett has averaged 88 more passing yards per game than Murray this season, turning Marvin Harrison Jr. into a weekly top-12 fantasy play and Trey McBride into an elite, touchdown-scoring weapon. The Cardinals, for better or worse, are committed to Murray based on salary alone, even if the team’s offense is markedly worse with Murray, among the NFL’s worst passers. Murray, purportedly dealing with a serious foot injury, practiced throughout last week but did not get the start against Dallas. Arizona plays the Seahawks in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f51-d45b-affe-5fd726640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons released K John Parker Romo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f60-d45b-affe-5ff6ea6f0000</link>
      <description>Parker Romo sealed his fate when he missed a fourth quarter extra point last week against the Patriots. He had been shaky for a while, missing three of his 14 field goal tries since replacing Younghoe Koo as Atlanta’s kicker in September. Parker Romo, a veteran journeyman, could catch on with another kicker-needy team in the coming weeks. The Falcons are set to try Zane Gonzalez as their new kicker starting in Week 10 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4f60-d45b-affe-5ff6ea6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed K Zane Gonzalez, formerly of the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fa6-d673-a39e-efb748840000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez is set to be the Falcons’ third kicker of the 2025 season after the team parted ways with John Parker Romo following his Week 9 meltdown against the Patriots. Parker Romo had replaced Younghoe Koo as the team’s starter. Gonzalez last season with Washington made five of his seven field goal attempts and all 19 of his extra point tries. Over six NFL seasons, Gonzalez has converted 80 percent of his field goal attempts. He won’t have much fantasy appeal in Week 10 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fa6-d673-a39e-efb748840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars acquired WR Jakobi Meyers from the Raiders in exchange for fourth and sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fb7-d45b-affe-5fb7f1ab0000</link>
      <description>Meyers finally finds his way out of Vegas four months after requesting a trade to escape Chip Kelly’s offensive scheme. Meyers never gelled with Geno Smith and hardly saw an increase in usage during Brock Bowers’ extended injury absence. Meyers managed 32 catches for 352 yards and zero touchdowns over seven games with the Raiders this season. Jacksonville acquiring Meyers at the trade deadline could mean the team is anticipating a worst-case scenario for Brian Thomas, who suffered a serious ankle injury in Week 9 against the Raiders. The team is already without Travis Hunter, who last week was placed on IR with a knee injury. Meyers’ fantasy prospects likely get a boost in Jacksonville if Thomas is sidelined for a while. Meanwhile, Tre Tucker becomes the de facto WR1 in Vegas, though Bowers should continue dominating targets as he did in Week 9. The Raiders could see what they have in Jack Bech as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fb7-d45b-affe-5fb7f1ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jaguars WR Travis Hunter (knee, IR) “is not expected to be out long-term.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fc2-d1e7-a1fa-5feace420000</link>
      <description>This echoes The Athletic’s reporting that Hunter, who injured his knee last week during a practice session, avoided “long term damage” to his knee. Hunter will miss at least the next three weeks and possibly more if the Jaguars want to be careful with the No. 2 overall pick in the 2025 NFL Draft. The Jaguars could also be without Brian Thomas, who sustained an ankle injury during the team’s Week 9 win against the Raiders. Jacksonville on Tuesday acquired Jakobi Meyers from the Raiders. Meyers could immediately see significant playing time if Hunter and Thomas are sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fc2-d1e7-a1fa-5feace420000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
