<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 02:25:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers RT Luke Goedeke (foot) is expected to miss “multiple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-542e-d051-a3df-7eef56910000</link>
      <description>Goedeke came into Week 2’s game with a foot injury that he had barely practiced on, then aggravated it in-game and Charlie Heck took over at right tackle. Heck would appear to be the backup plan for the Buccaneers for the forseeable future while Goedeke is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-542e-d051-a3df-7eef56910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed RB Cam Akers to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-543d-d654-a19b-d47db7600000</link>
      <description>We’re surprised nobody thought to sign Akers so that they could squeeze a draft pick out of the Vikings this time. Akers has now been acquired midseason by the Vikings three years in a row. He’ll help fill in for Aaron Jones’ absence and could see a small share of carries if he’s in playing shape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-543d-d654-a19b-d47db7600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Jaylen Wright (knee) was “real close” to playing last week and that Mike McDaniel is “most optimistic” about Wright playing in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5443-d654-a19b-d463e3570000</link>
      <description>Of course, most optimistic is in relation to Darren Waller, who nobody should be optimistic about playing. It’s relative. But Wright did get in a limited practice on Monday and would seem to be in line to assume backup duties behind De’Von Achane if healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5443-d654-a19b-d463e3570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) is unlikely to play in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-544b-d051-a3df-7eeb1fc90000</link>
      <description>Waller did get in a limited practice on Monday but after being ruled out for Week 2, it was never exceedingly likely that he was going to make it back for Thursday Night Football. Week 4 is a more reasonable timeline for Waller after a mini-bye for the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-544b-d051-a3df-7eeb1fc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed Aaron Jones (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5457-d654-a19b-d477c0cd0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games and be eligible to return in Week 7, after Minnesota’s Week 6 bye. Jones is a worthwhile hold if your league has injured reserve spots, but you likely can’t expect him to do better than being co-head of a committee whenever he does return, and that’s assuming Jordan Mason doesn’t take advantage of this opportunity in a big way. Now in his age-31 season, Jones is firmly on the back nine of his fantasy relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5457-d654-a19b-d477c0cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Malik Washington (thumb) said he’d play in Miami’s Week 3 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5469-d606-a5db-5cf92fae0000</link>
      <description>Washington popped up on the report with a limited practice on Monday, but it sounds like the issue isn’t all that serious. If Tyreek Hill were ever to be moved, Washington would be an intriguing fantasy add. He led the team in targets in Week 1 and contributed a 74-yard punt return touchdown in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5469-d606-a5db-5cf92fae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed announced he underwent successful foot and clavicle surgeries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54a0-d051-a3df-7ee115cd0000</link>
      <description>In a post on X, Reed said he had a “successful foot and clavicle surgery.” The 25-year-old was dealing with a Jones fracture heading into the season and intended to play through it. However, he also broke his clavicle in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders. Reed gets both surgeries out of the way in an attempt to get back to full health later this season. The Packers are aiming to have their slot receiver back around November. Fantasy managers can move him to an IR spot while the murky Packers pass-catching group does not offer an easy alternative. Matthew Golden and Romeo Doubs are in the WR3/FLEX range while Dontayvion Wicks may claw his way back into fantasy relevancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54a0-d051-a3df-7ee115cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54b2-d654-a19b-d4f2a4650000</link>
      <description>Oliver hurt his ankle in practice last week and missed the Bills’ Week 2 victory over the Jets. Given reports last week that this may be a multi-week injury, it is unlikely Oliver will be ready to play the Dolphins on a short week for a Thursday game. Also sidelined Tuesday was LB Matt Milano (pectoral), who suffered the injury against the Jets. The likelihood of him suiting up for Thursday is also low and the Bills will turn to alternatives in their front seven against the Dolphins with Oliver and Milano both likely out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54b2-d654-a19b-d4f2a4650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54bd-d654-a19b-d4fd3da50000</link>
      <description>Waddle was not listed on Monday’s estimated practice report but showed up as limited on Tuesday. He suffered the shoulder injury in Week 1 and was limited throughout last week before playing in the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots. On a short week, it is likely Waddle is being limited in practice again heading into a Thursday showdown against the Bills. Expect the banged-up Waddle to play through injury again as a fantasy WR3 in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54bd-d654-a19b-d4fd3da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed LB Ja’Whaun Bentley to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5505-d654-a19b-d565e1ca0000</link>
      <description>The Steelers added Bentley to the practice squad after a visit on Tuesday. Bentley spent each of the previous seven seasons with the Patriots, starting 68-of-83 games and tallying 509 combined tackles, 10.5 sacks, and 21 tackles for loss over that time. The veteran tore his pectoral muscle last season, limiting him to two games. Bentley was released by the Pats in March and the Steelers now take a flier on him as he re-joins former teammate Jabrill Peppers in Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5505-d654-a19b-d565e1ca0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
