<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Gardner Minshew did not suffer a torn ACL in Week 16’s loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4775-d968-a19b-5ff540560000</link>
      <description>Minshew is still dealing with a knee injury, but the veteran quarterback avoided the worst in Sunday’s loss. Minshew threw for just 15 yards on eight pass attempts against the Titans and will miss Sunday’s game against the Broncos. The Chiefs have already signed QB Shane Buechele off the Bills’ practice squad. He will presumably serve as the team’s QB2 behind Chris Oladokun on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4775-d968-a19b-5ff540560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers activated EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (hamstring) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478b-d968-a19b-5ffb1d6e0000</link>
      <description>He’ll go back to his rotational pass-rush role for a team that could desperately use some juice with Nick Bosa and Mychal Williams lost for the season. Gross-Matos had played five games before suffering the injury, being held sackless in that time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478b-d968-a19b-5ffb1d6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Lamar Jackson (back) has a “significant” contusion and is “day-to-day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf018a0000</link>
      <description>“He’s in there getting treatment,” Harbaugh helpfully added. Jackson’s status for Week 17 is probably in some doubt at this point, but we’d be surprised if he didn’t try to give it a go against the Packers given the Ravens need to win to have a chance to win the AFC North. Now, whether fantasy managers should trust him at this point is — and we can’t believe we’re typing this — perhaps a different story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf018a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman has been suspended for two games for repeated violations of playing rules intended to protect the health and safety of players.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478c-d968-a19b-5ffd3a860000</link>
      <description>This is not the first time Perryman has been suspended for multiple games. In 2023, he was also suspended for two games for repeated violations of too many hits, where he initiated contact with his helmet. The veteran linebacker can appeal his suspension, but if it is upheld, he would be sidelined for Weeks 17 and 18. Perryman has started all 10 games he’s appeared in this season, totaling 47 tackles, four TFLs, and three pass breakups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-478c-d968-a19b-5ffd3a860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Kimani Vidal (neck) is considered “day-to-day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47a2-d968-a19b-5ff346790000</link>
      <description>Vidal “could miss time, but the belief is that it’s not serious,” said Rapoport. If Vidal does miss Week 17’s game against the Texans on Saturday, Hassan Haskins will likely be Omarion Hampton’s main running mate in that game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47a2-d968-a19b-5ff346790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints HC Kellen Moore said Bryan Bresee (knee) won’t play in Week 17 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47a9-d35e-a1bf-47ebadc40000</link>
      <description>Bresee suffered an injury in Week 16’s win over the Jets that will sideline him for at least one game. Moore didn’t rule out the possibility of Bresee playing in Week 18 against the Falcons to close out the season, but the third-year tackle will be on the sidelines this week. Bresee has totaled 37 tackles, five TFLs, and 2.5 sacks in the 15 games he has appeared in this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47a9-d35e-a1bf-47ebadc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The state of Kansas approved a massive subsidy deal to build the Chiefs a stadium in Kansas.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47ac-dc7a-af9b-cfbf61a60000</link>
      <description>If you didn’t know this, the Chiefs currently play in Missouri. They are now expected to cross state lines and leave the Show Me state without an NFL franchise and abandon Arrowhead Stadium. (It turns out that no matter how many times we were forced to say “GEHA Field” it wasn’t enough to create as much money for the Chiefs ownership group as a new stadium.) It’s unknown when the Chiefs will be leaving for Kansas City at this time, as the Chiefs have a lease with Arrowhead Stadium through 2031, but it appears likely to happen in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47ac-dc7a-af9b-cfbf61a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said the team will monitor Davante Adams (hamstring) throughout the week ahead of Week 17’s game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47bf-d35e-a1bf-47ffaa240000</link>
      <description>Speaking with the media on Monday, McVay did not rule out the possibility of Adams playing in Week 17 against the Falcons. McVay said Adams is making progress toward a return, but didn’t provide much additional detail. With the Rams playing on Monday night, fantasy managers will want to keep a close watch on Adams’ practice status throughout the week and have a plan in place if he enters the week with a questionable tag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47bf-d35e-a1bf-47ffaa240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR DeMario Douglas (hamstring) left New England’s Week 16 game against the Ravens and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47c7-d35e-a1bf-47c71dd70000</link>
      <description>Initially questionable, he did not actually come back to the game. We’ll see what gets said this week, but it looks like Kyle Williams absorbed most of his snaps. Williams could be a DFS flyer or low-level FLEX option in Week 17 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47c7-d35e-a1bf-47c71dd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs placed QB Gardner Minshew (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47cd-d968-a19b-5ffdf9980000</link>
      <description>Minshew received good news regarding his knee injury on Monday, but with just two weeks left in the regular season, it was apparent he would not be able to return in time to avoid the IR designation. The seventh-year signal-caller signed a one-year contract with the Chiefs this offseason but only appeared in two games. One of the better backups the league has to offer, Minshew should have no trouble finding a new home in 2026, given the current state of the quarterback landscape across the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-47cd-d968-a19b-5ffdf9980000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
