<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (Achilles) will not play in Seattle’s Week 9 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf5-d673-a39e-bff548e70000</link>
      <description>The injury is not a tear, per MacDonald, but Bobo going straight to being ruled out is not a promising sign for his short-term availability. The depth receiver has just two catches this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf5-d673-a39e-bff548e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3be9-d1e7-a1fa-7beb182e0000</link>
      <description>Havenstein will play in Week 9, as expected. The Rams’ right tackle has been sidelined since Week 4, so his return is a big deal for QB Matthew Stafford. The Saints’ pass rush has improved with EDGE Chase Young (calf) back on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3be9-d1e7-a1fa-7beb182e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) is not on Seattle’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf6-d713-ad9e-7ff6e88f0000</link>
      <description>The bye week appears to have done Seattle’s star corner good, as he participated in full on Wednesday and Thursday ahead of being cleared off the injury report. He’ll provide Seattle with better than they’d been getting from their depth against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf6-d713-ad9e-7ff6e88f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is questionable to play in Week 9 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf8-d45b-affe-7ffeb9360000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reporters that Purdy “has got a chance to be available” on Sunday, but QB Mac Jones will start. The fact that Purdy has a chance to be active as a backup on game day gives one the impression that he could return to the lineup in Week 10 against the Rams, though that cannot be viewed as a guarantee, or even likely, at this point. The 49ers are smartly committed to letting their starting quarterback fully heal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bf8-d45b-affe-7ffeb9360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports initial testing shows Travis Hunter’s ACL is intact.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bfb-d713-ad9e-7fff018f0000</link>
      <description>Hunter was placed on IR earlier on Friday and will miss at least the next four weeks. Additional testing will occur over the weekend to figure out the true extent of the problem. It’s possible that Hunter returns this season, but we simply have no idea at this point how serious the injury is. Removing the torn ACL from the equation is a good start when we consider non-contact knee injuries, but it’s not exactly the end of the gloomy scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bfb-d713-ad9e-7fff018f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 9 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bfd-d673-a39e-bffdb0fb0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall will miss yet another game because of the PCL injury. The team has provided no news beyond saying that the injury has not healed as quickly as they expected. Hopefully, Pearsall can at least return to practice next week. The 49ers face the division-rival Rams in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bfd-d673-a39e-bffdb0fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (oblique) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c02-d673-a39e-bc93a1150000</link>
      <description>Kittle appeared on Wednesday’s injury report with the new oblique issue, but he practiced in full all week and can be expected to perform as an elite TE1 against the Giants on Sunday. After a one-game clunker in his return in Week 7, Kittle caught 4-of-5 targets for 43 yards and a touchdown in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c02-d673-a39e-bc93a1150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Republic’s Theo Mackie reports Michael Carter has been the first running back working with the starters on Thursday and Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c05-d45b-affe-7d97fbe90000</link>
      <description>As usual with Arizona’s approach to running backs, nothing really matters. A guy can be released on Monday and potentially be a starter on Friday. We’d still expect to see Bam Knight get more of the workload at this point, as practice has rarely mattered for the Cardinals, but we must admit we are truly only following the vibes with this backfield and the vibes will probably continue to shift. Knight rosterers should go ahead and have Carter on their bench or at least be prepared to pick him up ahead of Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c05-d45b-affe-7d97fbe90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Republic’s Theo Mackie reports Kyler Murray threw exclusively to backup receivers during the open portion of practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c0a-d1e7-a1fa-7eeae02b0000</link>
      <description>There was a huge vibe shift in Arizona on Wednesday when Murray’s media availability was canceled and replaced later in the week with one “for an Arizona Cardinals quarterback.” Murray sure seems to be in danger of picking up another questionable tag this week, and he may sit again and watch Jacoby Brissett spread the ball around more. Murray playing would be good news for Marvin Harrison Jr., and Brissett would probably help out Trey McBride and Arizona’s secondary receivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c0a-d1e7-a1fa-7eeae02b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out EDGE Bryce Huff (hamstring) in Week 9 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bdf-d1e7-a1fa-7bff9b9e0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also ruled out EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (hamstring) and C Jake Brendel (hamstring), while labeling DT Jordan Elliott (ankle/personal matter), LB Dee Winters (knee), DL Sam Okuayinonu (ankle), OG Ben Bartch (ankle) and OL Spencer Burford (knee) questionable for Week 9. The 49ers’ defense is officially one to target for fantasy purposes and their poor health should also reinforce the offense’s passing volume.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bdf-d1e7-a1fa-7bff9b9e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
