<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:29:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught 3-of-4 targets for 13 yards and one touchdown in the Rams’ Week 9 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4732-d45b-affe-57b6672a0000</link>
      <description>Higbee salvaged his otherwise fantasy-unfriendly outing by scoring a one-yard touchdown on a quick-hitting out route on the Rams’ first drive. Higbee got an assist from fellow Rams TE Davis Allen, who was sent in motion pre-snap. Higbee did the rest of his damage on the Rams’ third drive, catching zero passes after that. The Rams are featuring tight ends with the passing game, with No. 3 WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) on injured reserve and No. 1 WR Puka Nacua (chest) now injured again. Higbee will be a touchdown-dependent fantasy starter once again next week against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4732-d45b-affe-57b6672a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette caught 1-of-3 targets for 22 yards in the Panthers’ Week 9 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-472e-d713-ad9e-6f7ecac70000</link>
      <description>Legette got drilled by a Green Bay safety Xavier McKinney on his only catch of the day. He held onto the ball but took a while to get up and off the field. He was checked for a concussion and returned later in the game. Legette erupted with a 9/92/1 line versus the Jets three weeks ago. He has three catches for 39 scoreless yards over the past two weeks combined. Fantasy managers can send him back to the waiver wire on this week’s run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-472e-d713-ad9e-6f7ecac70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 7-of-8 targets for 43 yards in a Week 9 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4735-d713-ad9e-6f75c7420000</link>
      <description>Coming out of the bye, the Bills have seemed intent on getting the ball into Shakir’s hands often. That has often taken the form of screen passes and short comebackers, where he can use his elusiveness after the catch. While fantasy managers love the volume, that scheme also means there will be games like this when Shakir plays a defense that is going to wrap up and tackle effectively. As a result, the 25-year-old is more of a WR3 in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4735-d713-ad9e-6f75c7420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davis Allen caught 3-of-4 targets for 37 yards in the Rams’ Week 9 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46e2-d713-ad9e-6ef62c220000</link>
      <description>Although the Rams secured the win, Allen had a rough day. The young tight end scored on a play-action catch-and-run sequence on the Rams’ fifth drive, but the touchdown was called back after referees viewed the replay, which clearly showed Allen stiff-arming his way down the field by pushing his would-be tackler’s facemask back and forth as the two strode together through the red zone. Rams K Joshua Klarty missed the ensuing field goal attempt wide right by a significant margin. Allen later helped fellow TE Tyler Higbee score a touchdown from one yard out by catching the defense’s attention going in motion pre-snap. Rams TE Colby Parkinson caught 2-of-2 targets for 10 yards as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46e2-d713-ad9e-6ef62c220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught both of his targets for 17 yards in a Week 9 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4738-d45b-affe-57be0b1a0000</link>
      <description>Josh Allen only had one incompletion when targeting his wide receivers on Sunday. However, he didn’t really target them often. Khalil Shakir was the only wide receiver who saw more than two targets in this game. Coleman did what was asked of him today, but his role is not fantasy-friendly at the moment, and the Bills are going to need to find a way to utilize what Coleman does best instead of making him purely a boundary receiver for contested catches. You wouldn’t be blamed for dropping Coleman in fantasy leagues right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4738-d45b-affe-57be0b1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 3-of-7 passes for 23 yards in a Week 9 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-473b-d45b-affe-57bf25cf0000</link>
      <description>To make matters worse, 18 of his 23 yards came on the final drive of the game when the Bills were in a prevent defense with the Chiefs needing to drive 60 yards in 23 seconds for a touchdown. The rest of the game, Worthy was not able to separate from the Bills’ defenders deep, and the Chiefs were unable to get him any touches over the middle of the field either. Worthy did tie for the team lead in targets, so the Chiefs clearly want to get him involved, but he has topped 55 yards receiving just once this season, which makes him just a boom-or-bust FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-473b-d45b-affe-57bf25cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 4-of-5 targets for 66 yards in a Week 9 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-473e-d713-ad9e-6f7e82c70000</link>
      <description>Kelce seemed to catch passes only when the Chiefs were desperate for a big conversion. He may now lack the athleticism to consistently get away from linebackers in coverage, but he’s tremendous at finding soft spots in the defense when Mahomes is pressured and needs to make a play off script. That’s when Kelce shone tonight, and he almost had a bigger day as Mahomes missed him in the end zone for a potential touchdown. The 36-year-old is more of a TE2 for fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-473e-d713-ad9e-6f7e82c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrance Ferguson caught 2-of-3 targets for 54 yards in the Rams’ Week 9 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4738-d1e7-a1fa-5ffafb5d0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson is one of four Rams tight ends to catch multiple passes in this one, with No. 3 WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) on injured reserve and No. 1 WR Puka Nacua (chest) now injured again. On the Rams’ third drive, Ferguson impressively froze Saints S Justin Reid in place and preserved the soft spot in the Saints’ zone coverage by breaking inward off the line before jutting back outward toward the left side of the field. The talented rookie is stuck in a deep rotation, but he remains a TE2 dart throw against the 49ers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4738-d1e7-a1fa-5ffafb5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Michael Hoecht suffered a torn Achilles in Week 9’s win over the Chiefs, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-470c-d1e7-a1fa-5fee52cf0000</link>
      <description>It’s a tough blow to Hoecht and the Bills defense. Hoecht missed the first six games of the season after violating the league’s performance enhancing drugs policy, and appeared in just two games this season. In those two games, Hoecht totaled five tackles and two sacks while also forcing one fumble. He signed a three-year deal with the Bills this offseason and will hopefully have more to offer in 2026 once he returns from his injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-470c-d1e7-a1fa-5fee52cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 2-of-4 targets for 73 yards in a Week 9 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-474e-d45b-affe-57de2d670000</link>
      <description>Both of Brown’s catches were on busted coverages, with one going for 40 yards and the other for 33 yards. It’s nice to see the veteran being used on big plays down the field, but his role remains a small one, and he really benefited from defensive lapses in this game. You can likely find better options on your waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-474e-d45b-affe-57de2d670000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
