<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:04:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LB Von Miller said he wants to play another year and remain with the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a4-d56e-afff-f6ece7f40000</link>
      <description>Miller will be 37 in March but said he wants to return for a 17th professional season, also stating that he hopes to remain in Washington. “Whoever wants me, that’s where I’ll be,” the veteran continued, stating that he understand he is no position to be making demands considering his age. Either way, Miller seems intent on playing again in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a4-d56e-afff-f6ece7f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers activated WR David Moore (elbow) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9386-d35e-a1bf-d7c6398f0000</link>
      <description>The veteran wideout has been on injured reserve since the end of September with a serious elbow injury, but could return for the postseason as the Panthers prepare to take on the heavily-favored Rams this weekend. The Panthers in a corresponding move waived veteran journeyman Hunter Renfrow, who had 25 receptions for 255 yards and two touchdowns for Carolina in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9386-d35e-a1bf-d7c6398f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers waived WR Hunter Renfrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-938c-d56e-afff-f7ec13e90000</link>
      <description>Renfrow, who was a big part of the Carolina passing offense in the season’s first couple weeks, hasn’t been active since mid-October. He ends the season with 25 receptions for 255 yards and two touchdowns, operating mostly from the slot. Renfrow, who has 103 catches for the Raiders in 2021, will likely catch on with a receiver-needy team this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-938c-d56e-afff-f7ec13e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Bears assistant GM Ian Cunningham for the team’s general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9390-d35e-a1bf-d7d259c70000</link>
      <description>Cunningham, whose career in NFL front offices including stints working closely with Howie Roseman and Ozzie Newsome, is considered a strong candidate to be Atlanta’s next general manager after the team fired former GM Terry Fontenot after a series of catastrophic draft picks and team-building decisions, including drafting Kyle Pitts and Michael Penix. Cunningham reportedly came close last year to landing the Jaguars GM job. He could join Matt Ryan, the Falcons’ new president of football operations, in rebuilding the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9390-d35e-a1bf-d7d259c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys fired defensive coordinator Matt Eberflus.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93a9-d968-a19b-dbf955da0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys had little choice but to part ways with Eberflus after a disastrous 2025 season in which the Dallas defense was once again a laughingstock. Though the Cowboys led the NFL in QB pressure rate, they allowed the league’s second highest offensive success rate — trailing only the Cardinals — and by far the highest EPA per play. Eberflus’ defense stopped neither the pass nor the run, even though the team improved in several defensive metrics without Micah Parsons. Eberflus, who flamed out as the Bears head coach before landing in Dallas, will likely find his way into another coordinator job for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93a9-d968-a19b-dbf955da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93b5-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9f910000</link>
      <description>Johnson sustained a Linsfranc fracture in mid-November but could suit up for Wild Card Weekend, according to the Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane. “Johnson has made progress in his recovery, but still has to test his right foot before the team makes a decision on his availability for Sunday’s wild card game vs. the 49ers,” McLane said. The team’s offense fell apart with Johnson sidelined as they finished the season 3-4. The Eagles are now 18-28 in games Johnson hasn’t played during his 13-year NFL career. His presence would go a long way in helping the Philly offense find its footing in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93b5-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9f910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants general manager Joe Schoen said potential head coaching hires are “excited” about QB Jaxson Dart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93cc-d968-a19b-dbfd2f590000</link>
      <description>“From the people I’ve talked to, the consensus is that there are a lot of potential head-coaching candidates that are excited about the opportunity here because of Jaxson Dart,” Schoen said when asked about what might be appealing about the Giants head coaching vacancy after the team parted ways with Brian Daboll this season. Dart’s physicality as a runner and his refusal to run out of bounds or slide to avoid a major hit was a major concern throughout the season, as Dart suffered several brain injuries. But he was solid as a passer, completing nearly 64 percent of his pass attempts for 15 touchdowns and five interceptions over 14 games. Dart will be at the center of whatever comes next for the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93cc-d968-a19b-dbfd2f590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Charlotte Carrol reports Giants QB Russell Wilson did not tell the team about a hamstring injury he sustained in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93f3-d35e-a1bf-d7f33e8c0000</link>
      <description>Wilson, 37, suffered what he described as a Grade 2 hamstring injury ahead of New York’s Week 2 game against the Cowboys. He said he felt he could not inform the team of the injury and kept it under wraps before throwing for 450 yards and three touchdowns against the Cowboys. “I couldn’t tell anybody,” Wilson said. “I had to go and play on it just because I knew the circumstances. I had to play on it, no matter what. I actually ended up going to the Dallas Mavericks’ facility, training. And, you know, just kept it quiet, just trying to get treatment on it and just knowing that I probably couldn’t run from the goal line to the 10-yard line if I wanted to, but I feel like, you know, I got to play that game.” Wilson lost the starting gig to Jaxson Dart, as expected, and will likely play elsewhere in 2026. Wilson said he wants to continue playing into his age-38 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93f3-d35e-a1bf-d7f33e8c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
