<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:11:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed WR Greg Dortch (chest) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f592-da9b-a9bf-ff9fd9a30000</link>
      <description>Dortch could return for the Week 18 finale, but it’s likely that the season is over for the 27-year-old. Assuming his campaign is done, he finishes 2025 with 29 receptions for 2026 yards and three touchdowns. Trent Sherfield has been promoted from the practice squad to take Dortch’s place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f592-da9b-a9bf-ff9fd9a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Chandler (knee) won’t play in Week 14 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59d-da9b-a9bf-ff9db42b0000</link>
      <description>Chandler will not come off injured reserve, so the Vikings will once again go with a Jordan Mason-Aaron Jones backfield for the tilt against the Commanders. Chandler likely wouldn’t have a big role/won’t have one whenever he is activated, anyways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59d-da9b-a9bf-ff9db42b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Brady Cook from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59f-da9b-a9bf-ff9fbbe20000</link>
      <description>Cook will be the backup signal-caller for the Week 14 contest against the Dolphins, as Justin Fields (knee) has been ruled out for that contest versus Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f59f-da9b-a9bf-ff9fbbe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks activated S Julian Love (hamstring) off injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5a0-d77b-adfa-ffa3df6b0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks are also activating Jarran Reed (wrist/thumb) as Seattle is getting two of their core defensive players back for the final five contests of the year. Love should be the starting free safety against Atlanta, while Reed should see plenty of snaps/could start up the middle, as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5a0-d77b-adfa-ffa3df6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB John Wolford off their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5bb-da9b-a9bf-ffbf4e260000</link>
      <description>Wolford’s signing likely means that he’ll be the backup quarterback for JJ McCarthy for Week 14 against the Commanders, with Max Brosmer the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5bb-da9b-a9bf-ffbf4e260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Johnson (foot) has been ruled out for Week 14 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5d0-d8cf-affb-fdfab7860000</link>
      <description>As expected, Johnson will miss at least one more game with his foot injury. The hope is that the All-Pro tackle will be back for the Philadelphia offense for Week 15 against Las Vegas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5d0-d8cf-affb-fdfab7860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed TE Marcedes Lewis from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5e8-d77b-adfa-ffebb89e0000</link>
      <description>Lewis gets the active roster spot after previously being elevated from the practice squad in his previous action in 2025. He remains off the fantasy radar, but most 41-year-old’s are.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5e8-d77b-adfa-ffebb89e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals elevated WR Jalen Brooks from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5fe-d77b-adfa-ffff2d9e0000</link>
      <description>Brooks is one of two wideouts who were elevated from the practice squad for Week 14 against the Rams. The 2023 seventh-round pick is unlikely to much of an impact, even in a room that is not exactly crowded with quality wideouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5fe-d77b-adfa-ffff2d9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived WR Malik Heath</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f609-d8cf-affb-fe2b3c420000</link>
      <description>With Jayden Reed (hamstring) activated off injured reserve, the Packers clear the needed room with the waiving of Heath. The 25-year-old will likely revert to the practice squad if he goes unclaimed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f609-d8cf-affb-fe2b3c420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons sign WR Deven Thompkins from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f617-d8cf-affb-fe3fd8160000</link>
      <description>Thompkins, 25, has been elevated from the practice squad twice. He likely will contribute on special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f617-d8cf-affb-fe3fd8160000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
