<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 4-of-6 targets for 16 yards in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e3-dab4-a3fb-bbf3b5380000</link>
      <description>Ertz committed two uncharacteristic drops and saw decreased involvement in the offense with the returns of Terry McLaurin and Deebo Samuel. McLaurin failed to finish the game after apparently tweaking the quad injury that forced him to miss time this season, so there could be room for Ertz to see another bump in targets when the Commanders host the Seahawks in Week 9. Treat Ertz as a low-upside TE2 for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e3-dab4-a3fb-bbf3b5380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 3-of-6 targets for 11 yards in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e6-d5d8-a3ff-f9e737be0000</link>
      <description>Samuel’s drop occurred in the red zone on the team’s first possession, with the pass going through his hands, off his face mask, and into the waiting arms of Kansas City defensive end Mike Danna. It was a forgettable performance from the veteran slot man, who also saw his usage cut into with the return of Terry McLaurin. That said, McLaurin failed to finish the game after tweaking his quad injury, something fantasy managers will want to track closely as the team prepares to host the Seahawks in Week 9. Another missed contest from McLaurin could leave Samuel as the team’s top pass-catcher yet again, a situation that could warrant WR2 potential in fantasy circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e6-d5d8-a3ff-f9e737be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 25-of-34 passes for 299 yards, three touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Chiefs’ 28-7, Week 8 win over the Commanders, adding 30 yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ea-d5d8-a3ff-f9ebd0b70000</link>
      <description>Mahomes threw interceptions on consecutive drives for the first time in his career on the Chiefs’ first two possessions of the game, the first an undercut back shoulder through by Washington corner Marcus Lattimore and the second a ball off veteran tight end Travis Kelce’s hands over the middle of the field. The Chiefs would shut out the Commanders after the break, during which time Mahomes would lead three straight touchdown drives that culminated receiving touchdowns by Kareem Hunt, Travis Kelce, and Rashee Rice. The defense would do the rest as the Chiefs coasted to a comfortable win after the early miscues. Up next for the 5-3 Chiefs is a gauntlet of opponents that begins with the Bills on the road in Week 9 before facing the Broncos and Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ea-d5d8-a3ff-f9ebd0b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed 12 times for 58 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ef-deb1-a39b-29ef4a420000</link>
      <description>The veteran ground-mover was not targeted through the air and also watched from the sideline as Kareem Hunt cashed in on two short yardage scores, the first from inside the one and the second a two-yard receiving touchdown. Pacheco also got his leg caught under him on a tackle to his knee in the fourth quarter. He would limp to the sidelines under his own power before jumping off the training table with a smile, likely indicating he avoided an injury that could cost him time. He could have his number called more frequently against the run-funnel Bills in Week 9, against whom he enters RB2 territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ef-deb1-a39b-29ef4a420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed nine times for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders, adding two yards and a touchdown on his only reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28f2-deb1-a39b-29fe37350000</link>
      <description>Hunt saw little work outside of short yardage situations until the fourth quarter, scoring from inside the one and catching a touchdown from two yards out. Both touchdowns came after Rashee Rice touches, aggravating fantasy managers in the process. Either way, Hunt maintains a highly valuable short yardage role for a Chiefs offense that has suddenly scored 28 points or more in five straight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28f2-deb1-a39b-29fe37350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith rushed three times for eight yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2916-dab4-a3fb-bb76a15e0000</link>
      <description>Smith was not targeted, leaving his fantasy value in the dumps as Kareem Hunt scored twice and Isiah Pacheco continued in the lead back role. Pacheco appeared to tweak his knee in the fourth quarter, something Smith’s fantasy managers will want to track ahead of a Week 9 meeting with the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2916-dab4-a3fb-bb76a15e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 6-of-8 targets for 99 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2918-deb1-a39b-291e4ecc0000</link>
      <description>Although Kelce returned a vintage performance in the box scores, he had yet another drop that turned into a Patrick Mahomes interception that hit him in the hands - the second such occurrence of the season. Kelce did most of his damage in the YAC department in this one, breaking free for gains of 38 and 31 yards against the beleaguered Washington defense. The offense remains centered on Rashee Rice, but Kelce brings an established red zone role to an offense that has now scored 28 points or more in five straight. That sets the veteran up well to return TE1 numbers against in Week 9 when the Chiefs face off against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2918-deb1-a39b-291e4ecc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught all nine targets for 93 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders, adding 12 yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bb7690000</link>
      <description>Rice now has consecutive games of leading the team in targets and has notched three scores in two games since returning from suspension. His fantasy day could have been even bigger had he not been tackled twice inside the two, the first on a run from wildcat inside the 10 and the second on a reception in the flat. Both of those plays resulted in short touchdowns by Kareem Hunt. Rice’s role appears to be one of the most valuable in the league considering the hefty volume and elite red zone role, all while playing for an offense that has now scored 28 points or more in five straight. He is likely to remain busy when the Chiefs take on the Bills in Week 9, keeping him firmly entrenched as a fantasy WR1 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bb7690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 5-of-7 targets for 53 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291e-d245-adfb-bd5fb6360000</link>
      <description>Worthy saw his role in the offense morph yet again following the return of Rashee Rice from suspension, this time working more short and intermediate areas of the field. He could struggle to return to the elite production he showed towards the end of his rookie season considering the elite involvement from both Rice and tight end Travis Kelce, particularly in the red zone. Consider Worthy a middling WR4 ahead of a showdown with the Bills in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291e-d245-adfb-bd5fb6360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown failed to catch his only target in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2921-deb1-a39b-292f83c10000</link>
      <description>Brown was targeted only once and took a backseat in the offense in the second game with Rashee Rice, playing well behind Rice and Xavier Worthy while splitting time with JuJu Smith-Schuster. His days of fantasy utility appear to be in the rearview mirror unless the injury bug strikes again ahead of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2921-deb1-a39b-292f83c10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
