<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa8-d713-ad9e-7efc2e3b0000</link>
      <description>Bond missed Week 10 with a foot injury but returns in a limited fashion to open Week 11. A full practice later in the week boosts Bonds’s chances of playing against the Ravens, but he does not have much fantasy relevance in the Dillon Gabriel offense. Cedric Tillman (glute) was also limited a week after coming off injured reserve. Tillman is ahead of Bond is the pass-catching order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa8-d713-ad9e-7efc2e3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a98-d713-ad9e-7edc45dc0000</link>
      <description>Strange had his 21-day practice window opened this week and was a limited participant in his first practice back. With Travis Hunter out for the season, Parker Washington dealing with a new hamstring injury, and Brian Thomas working back from an ankle injury, Strange may be in line for major usage upon his return. He tallied 23 targets from Weeks 1-4 and should be in the low-end TE1 range upon his return, whether that is Week 11 against the Chargers or Week 12 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a98-d713-ad9e-7edc45dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said RB Trey Benson (knee) is “taking it day by day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7abb-d45b-affe-7fbfef920000</link>
      <description>At this point, Benson has been out four games and is slated to miss his fifth this week. There is still no confirmation on severity of his injury or a timetable other than Gannon vaguely saying he is “doing better” last week and he is “taking it day by day” this week. It sounds like Benson’s practice window won’t be opened until next week at the earliest, so fantasy managers can expect him back on the field Week 12 at best, but more likely Week 13 against the Buccaneers, barring setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7abb-d45b-affe-7fbfef920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said RB RJ Harvey will “have more opportunities” when talking about the potential absence of J.K. Dobbins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7d8f-d45b-affe-7d9f034e0000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is dealing with a foot injury and is reportedly a candidate to be placed on injured reserve. That means he can safely be ruled out for Week 11, making Harvey the next man up. Payton noted Harvey’s size when talking about his ability to take on more work, saying, “He’s built to last, and that’s important.” Harvey has eight pounds on Tyler Badie and 18 pounds on Jaleel McLaughlin. It seems like a given that Harvey would see more work with Dobbins out, but it’s nice to hear it from Payton himself, given how fickle the head coach can be with his backfield touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7d8f-d45b-affe-7d9f034e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports, “There certainly is a possibility that Garrett Wilson (knee) gets put on injured reserve.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7d5e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffed5b80000</link>
      <description>Rapoport might just be reading the tea leaves here, but it’s a reasonable assessment of the situation. Wilson re-aggravated his lingering knee injury on Sunday and is now expected to miss 3-4 weeks. The Jets are midway through another lost year and Wilson is under contract through the 2023 season. Neither party stands to gain much from rushing him back. Wilson has already been ruled out for Week 11. Putting him on injured reserve later today would force him to miss at least three more games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7d5e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffed5b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said “the intention” is to get Brandon Aiyuk back on the field this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e03-d1e7-a1fa-7eebfc4a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers keep pushing back Aiyuk’s return date and now Lynch isn’t even putting a timeline on it. The team hasn’t designated him to return from the PUP list yet, meaning he might not even be that close to taking the field. Aiyuk is recovering from the multi-ligament knee injury he suffered in the middle of the 2024 season. The injury was more complicated than a standard ACL tear and it’s unclear when he will be ready to suit up. The question Lynch was answering was whether this could be a redshirt year for Aiyuk. He rebuffed the idea, but then ominously ended his statement with, “But we’ll see, no absolutes there.” It sounds like the 49ers have at least considered the possibility that Aiyuk doesn’t play this year. Needless to say, it doesn’t sound like Aiyuk will be returning anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e03-d1e7-a1fa-7eebfc4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Matthew Golden (shoulder) was “definitely close” to playing in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eeec6ad0000</link>
      <description>Golden was limited in practice last Wednesday before missing the final two sessions of the week. He got a questionable tag but was ruled out ahead of kickoff. Golden returned to practice yesterday for a limited session and LaFleur told reporters the team will see how things go in practice for him this week before making a final call on his availability. Golden has struggled to make much of an impact this year and a lingering injury won’t do him any favors. Fantasy managers shouldn’t feel the need to hold onto him, healthy or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eeec6ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez (shoulder) is practicing in full for Week 11 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e32-d45b-affe-7fb63d1a0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez missed most of the second half of Week 10 with the shoulder issue but managed a limited practice on Wednesday. A full practice today means he will be good to go for Week 11 versus a beatable Miami run defense. Rodriguez operated as the Commanders’ lead back in the first half of Week 10’s game. He should hold onto that role this week, putting him in the RB3 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e32-d45b-affe-7fb63d1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e36-d1e7-a1fa-7efef63d0000</link>
      <description>Gordon was also limited on Wednesday. He should be able to suit up this week, but Jaylen Wright ran as Miami’s RB2 in Week 10. Gordon’s ankle injury may have played a role in that, but the bad news is the ankle is still an issue. Neither Miami backup holds much fantasy value right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e36-d1e7-a1fa-7efef63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (hamstring) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e44-d45b-affe-7fd6e91c0000</link>
      <description>Washington was held out of Wednesday’s session, causing some concern that he could miss Week 11. Even a limited practice today puts him on track to suit up for Sunday’s game. Washington let the Jags with seven targets in Week 10. He scored once through the air and returned a punt to the house. Assuming he gets past the hamstring issue this week, Washington will slot in as a WR4 versus the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7e44-d45b-affe-7fd6e91c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
