<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike McCarthy said “Definitely, I don’t see why you wouldn’t” when asked if he’d like Aaron Rodgers to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-00df-dc7a-af9f-cfff1dcf0000</link>
      <description>Removing the part of our brain that understands what this really means is six more months of daily speculation about Aaron Rodgers coming back, it does make sense that win-now hire Mike McCarthy would want the best quarterback he could have. He has a pre-existing relationship with Rodgers, and Rodgers — clearly flawed at this point — is probably as good as the Steelers could hope to do at the position next year. Anyway, here’s to another offseason of this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-00df-dc7a-af9f-cfff1dcf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike McCarthy said he will call plays for Pittsburgh in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-00f6-d56e-afff-e6febcc80000</link>
      <description>Not exactly earth-shattering news here, especially with no offensive coordinator tied to him yet. This should always have been the expectation for McCarthy. Steelers fans should get ready to get re-acquainted with slant/flat combination routes with Arthur Smith off to Ohio State.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-00f6-d56e-afff-e6febcc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Broncos defensive pass game coordinator Jim Leonhard is “expected to be a leading candidate” for the Bills defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0107-dc7a-af9f-cfbfac560000</link>
      <description>Leonhard has been on the Packers and Cowboys radars at various points this offseason, though neither could have him in for a full interview before they settled on Jonathan Gannon and Christian Parker, respectively. The former Bills safety and Wisconsin defensive coordinator drew a lot of acclaim in coaching circles and would be a nice rebound for the Bills after they moved on from Sean McDermott.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0107-dc7a-af9f-cfbfac560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired former Falcons offensive line coach and run game coordinator Dwayne Ledford to be their offensive line coach and run-game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-010e-d56e-afff-e7ee83490000</link>
      <description>Ledford was let out of his contract by the Falcons after they brought on legendary offensive line coach Bill Callahan. The Ravens did well to poach him, and though they don’t have an offensive coordinator yet, this is a good start to Jesse Minter’s staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-010e-d56e-afff-e7ee83490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed Packers quarterbacks coach Sean Mannion for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0114-d968-a19c-59f528cc0000</link>
      <description>Entering its third week, the Eagles offensive coordinator search is taking on an eau de Browns and they are responding by adding even more candidates to the pool. Mannion, 33, a former NFL backup quarterback, has no play calling experience and has only coached for two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0114-d968-a19c-59f528cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars announced DC Anthony Campanile and OC Grant Udinski will remain with the Jaguars in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0147-d968-a19c-59f78db10000</link>
      <description>Campanile was the only one of the two that was still up for a head-coaching gig after the Bills picking Joe Brady sealed off Udinski’s final interview opportunity. Campanile will apparently say no to the Cardinals and move ahead with the Jaguars for another season. Jacksonville’s first-place schedule and sudden improvements will make them a target for regression, but keeping coaching staff continuity should help ward some of it off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0147-d968-a19c-59f78db10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers offensive coordinator Mike McDaniel said Justin Herbert “hasn’t neared the ceiling of what he is capable of.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-014d-dc7a-af9f-cfff4ba40000</link>
      <description>McDaniel was scarce on details — not surprising — but promised to rein in the signal-caller a bit. McDaniel added “I think not relying too heavily on Justin’s ability to do above and beyond I think is critical. ... That’ll be one of the first things that we’ll try to do is take a little off his plate.” Reading between the lines, it’s possible that Herbert will be instructed to run a little less in 2026. He took off a career-high 83 times for 498 yards and two touchdowns. His overall fantasy value will probably remain as it was in 2025 — or improve — due to improved schematics. But we’re hoping the Chargers keep the running plays on the table for fantasy purposes and this does not sound like a team that plans to do that after watching him play the final six weeks of the season with a left hand that was recovering from surgery to repair a fracture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-014d-dc7a-af9f-cfff4ba40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Bears offensive coordinator Declan Doyle for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0153-d968-a19c-59f375240000</link>
      <description>Doyle withdrew from the Eagles search despite the lateral move technically improving his standing by letting him call plays. We’ll see if he’s interested in actually interviewing for this one. Hard to do much better as a playcaller than starting off with Lamar Jackson, even if the Jackson we saw late last season was not playing up to his MVP standard of 2023 and 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0153-d968-a19c-59f375240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers interviewed defensive backs coach Steve Clinkscale for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0156-d56e-afff-e7fee70a0000</link>
      <description>Clinkscale was actually co-defensive coordinator with Jesse Minter at Michigan under Jim Harbaugh, so it would be a natural move for the Chargers to keep this job in-house. Whether they’ll actually do that remains up for debate. Clinkscale joined the Chargers in 2024 with Harbaugh and has coached the last two years as their defensive backs coach. He also has coordinator experience with the 2015 Cincinnati Bearcats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0156-d56e-afff-e7fee70a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers will interview Commanders defensive pass game coordinator Jason Simmons for their defensive coordinator role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-015b-d35e-a1bf-45db6e3f0000</link>
      <description>What is the first order of business for the Mike McCarthy Era? Obviously it’s interviewing his old coaches. Simmons was with McCarthy in Green Bay from 2011-2018. He’s been Washington’s defensive passing game coordinator since 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-015b-d35e-a1bf-45db6e3f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
