<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 22:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c590-d94a-a79d-cd9d96d50000</link>
      <description>The injury’s severity has not yet been disclosed. As is the case with many head coaches, Saints head coach Kellen Moore reportedly tried to keep things vague when breaking the news to reporters, but he ultimately confirmed that the veteran running back did suffer a new injury today. Kamara has played through lower-body ailments on more than one occasion, and he will undoubtedly do so again this week if the training staff clears him. In the meantime, Saints No. 2 RB Kendre Miller must be rostered in 10- and 12-team leagues at this time. Kamara narrowly out-touched him, 12-11, last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c590-d94a-a79d-cd9d96d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c599-def2-abdb-ddf91a610000</link>
      <description>The Packers opened Watson’s practice window this week, meaning he is eligible to return from injured reserve at any point. He is still recovering from the torn ACL he suffered late in the 2024 season, but it appears to be going as well as anyone could have hoped for. It’s unlikely he plays this week, but Watson is nearing a return. Fantasy managers can begin to roster him in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c599-def2-abdb-ddf91a610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Texans “still view” RB Woody Marks as “predominantly a passing-game back and one who had a bit of an injury history in college.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c587-db72-a199-ffcf46ce0000</link>
      <description>Unfortunately, this confirms what we saw last week. In games where the Texans are “up big and running the ball,” veteran RB Nick Chubb “still has the playing time edge.” Marks had seemingly made a strong case for the Texans’ lead running back role in Week 4, but the coaches view things differently than much of the fantasy community. We must now reset expectations. Marks can still return high-end FLEX value, particularly in PPR leagues, operating as a receiving back with part-time rushing duties, but treating him as a potential RB2 now appears to be unreasonable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c587-db72-a199-ffcf46ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5a4-d94a-a79d-cdad87030000</link>
      <description>Johnson played through the ankle injury in Week 5 and doesn’t appear to be at any risk of missing Week 6’s matchup with the Patriots. Johnson started the year strong with three games of double-digit PPR points. He has been held under six points in each of the past two weeks. With Foster Moreau and Taysom Hill healthy, his days as a TE1 may be at an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5a4-d94a-a79d-cdad87030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 6 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b0-d94a-a79d-cdbd82480000</link>
      <description>The ankle injury is new for Love, though a full practice suggests it’s a non-story. He will be removed from the injury report on Friday, barring a true surprise. Facing a worn-down Bengals squad, Love will push for QB1 fantasy numbers as long as he doesn’t get out to an insurmountable lead too quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b0-d94a-a79d-cdbd82480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b3-db72-a199-fffbf5d30000</link>
      <description>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Alt is doing “really well” despite his DNP status. Alt suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 4 and has already missed one game. It doesn’t look like he will be back this week, though there is at least a chance he manages to return to practice at some point this week before suiting up on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b3-db72-a199-fffbf5d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5bd-def2-abdb-ddfdd32e0000</link>
      <description>Lamb is still dealing with the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. He hasn’t practiced since going down with the injury and doesn’t look likely to suit up in Week 6 either. George Pickens will continue to operate as the team’s top wideout if Lamb remains sidelined for Week 5. Pickens came back to Earth in Week 5 with just two catches for 57 yards, but he saved the day for fantasy managers with a touchdown. He is on track for a WR2 ranking this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5bd-def2-abdb-ddfdd32e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavontae Turpin (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c3-db72-a199-ffcb27540000</link>
      <description>Both Turpin and CeeDee Lamb missed Week 5 with ankle injuries. Both wideouts also look likely to miss Dallas’s upcoming game against the Panthers. Ryan Flournoy stepped up as the team’s No. 3 receiver on Sunday and made the most of the increased role with six catches for 114 yards. He will move into the WR4 conversation if Turpin and Lamb are both ruled out before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c3-db72-a199-ffcb27540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c7-d94a-a79d-cdcf33230000</link>
      <description>Pete Carroll has insisted that Bowers is considered day to day, but all reports have him as unlikely to suit up in Week 6. Bowers is dealing with a PCL injury and a bone bruise in his knee. He suffered the pair of injuries in Week 1 and attempted to play through them for a while. The injuries eventually caught up with him and the Raiders put him on the bench for Week 5. Michael Mayer missed Week 5 with a concussion but should be available for the Raiders’ upcoming trip to Tennessee. He will be a streaming TE2 option if he is cleared for action and Bowers remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c7-d94a-a79d-cdcf33230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders (knee/ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ce-def2-abdb-ddef45d00000</link>
      <description>Sanders missed Week 5 with the injury combo. In turn, rookie running back Jaydon Blue was active for the first time this year. Blue only saw four carries and ran for just seven yards. No matter who the backup is, Javonte Williams has a stranglehold on the backfield touches in Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ce-def2-abdb-ddef45d00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
