<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sports’ Jordan Schultz reports Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) is “considered week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f52-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa5d050000</link>
      <description>Players that are “week to week” usually wind up missing their next game, and since the Bills are on Thursday night in Week 12, Kincaid could wind up missing multiple games. It’s a volume upgrade for players like Keon Coleman and Khalil Shakir as the Bills try to get their passing game on track in Week 11 against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f52-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa5d050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he wants to get Keaton Mitchell more involved in the offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f4a-d673-a39e-efdbf9790000</link>
      <description>Mitchell continues to look like one of the most explosive backs in the league whenever he touches the ball. The third-year back is averaging a blistering 6.2 YPC on 15 carries this season and has seen three of his attempts go for 12-plus yards. Mitchell won’t be taking over for Derrick Henry any time soon, but it’s hard to ignore the impact he can make on a game when given the opportunity to do so. Fantasy managers shouldn’t use this as excuse to add and start Mitchell in Week 11 against the Browns, but he’s turning into an interesting stash as a potential handcuff to Henry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f4a-d673-a39e-efdbf9790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said he will take over as defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f58-d713-ad9e-6f5c8fc40000</link>
      <description>After becoming the first team to lose four-straight games by 20-plus points since the 2002 Cardinals, Quinn decided something must be done. The Commanders’ defense has been abysmal all season, but their struggles have become more noticeable as they enter the more difficult portion of their schedule. Since Week 7, the Commanders have allowed 38.5 points per game and 451.3 yards per game. Quinn’s defenses as a head coach have never been the stellar units we’ve grown accustomed to seeing when he was a defensive coordinator, so this isn’t exactly new territory. We’ll see if this change leads to better results as the Commanders now prepare for a Week 11 game game in Spain against the Dolphins who are fresh off an upset win over the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f58-d713-ad9e-6f5c8fc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden is considered “day-to-day” with a quad bruise.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f63-d673-a39e-eff3bb9b0000</link>
      <description>It’s good news for the Chargers and Gadsden, who underwent an MRI on Monday after being knocked from Week 10’s game following a knee-to-knee collision. The day-to-day prognosis suggests the rookie could suit up in Week 11 against the Jaguars, but we’ll have to see how things look when the injury report is released later in the week. If he’s unable to go this week, the duo of Tucker Fisk and Tyler Conklin will be in line to replace him. Neither should be considered as viable fantasy options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f63-d673-a39e-eff3bb9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) won’t play in Washington’s Week 11 game with the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f65-d713-ad9e-6f75a16e0000</link>
      <description>He’ll at least head over to Spain with the team, which we guess is great news for the vibes. McLaurin will need to have a huge Week 13-17 stretch after Washington’s Week 12 bye to justify his ADP at this point. Seems like holding out for a contract extension was a pretty smart move by him, considering his 13/203/1 line probably wouldn’t have moved many general managers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f65-d713-ad9e-6f75a16e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Trey Amos (fibula) will “miss some significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d673-a39e-effb450a0000</link>
      <description>Considering how little is left of the NFL season and Washington’s placement in the standings, this is likely a season-ender. Amos had a 58.8 PFF coverage grade in 511 snaps during his first 10 games of the season, but looked rough the last two weeks as he allowed 138 yards and a touchdown while allowing 8-of-8 completions in coverage. He’ll likely head to IR in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d673-a39e-effb450a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he thinks Rashod Bateman will be “okay” after suffering an ankle injury in Week 10 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d713-ad9e-6f7e88780000</link>
      <description>Bateman suffered an ankle sprain on what appeared to be an illegal hip-drop tackle in Sunday’s win. Harbaugh said the team will “see how serious it is going forward,” and was unable to say whether or not Bateman will play in Week 11 against the Browns. Bateman has caught 16 passes for 194 yards and two touchdowns this season and has managed just six catches in his last five games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d713-ad9e-6f7e88780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Harrison Mevis will again be the team’s kicker in Week 11 against Seattle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f77-d45b-affe-7ff776880000</link>
      <description>Mevis, the “Thiccer Kicker,” did not attempt a field goal against the 49ers, settling for six made extra points. Seattle will probably force some more attempts this week against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f77-d45b-affe-7ff776880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Marlon Humphrey (finger) may need surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6f-d673-a39e-efff12140000</link>
      <description>According to Harbaugh, Humphrey would likely miss one or two games if he did need surgery. The team is still weighing that decision, but with games against the Browns and Jets on tap over the next two weeks, it’s safe to say the Ravens can afford to be without Humphrey if he does opt for surgery. Humphrey has struggled in coverage this season, allowing 32 receptions for 461 yards and two touchdowns on 45 targets, but did notch his first interception of the season in Week 10’s win over the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6f-d673-a39e-efff12140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Isiah Pacheco (knee) “may take more time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f7f-d45b-affe-7fff92270000</link>
      <description>Don’t be surprised if we aren’t seeing Pacheco at practice this week, in other words. Coming off the bye, we were expecting to see Pacheco return to the lineup, but if that doesn’t happen, Kareem Hunt will be on the RB2/RB3 borderline against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f7f-d45b-affe-7fff92270000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
