<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) was not spotted at Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cedb-dd4c-afb9-efdbfd8b0000</link>
      <description>Friday’s DNP marks the second-straight week Lamar was unable to get on the practice field. We’ll wait for official confirmation from head coach John Harbaugh, which should come shortly, but the two-time MVP appears slated to miss his second game in a row with a hamstring injury. It’s not what the 1-4 Ravens need heading into a tough matchup against the Rams, but Cooper Rush will hope to lead the team to a much-needed win with the season already on the brink.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cedb-dd4c-afb9-efdbfd8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cee1-def2-abdb-dfe10cee0000</link>
      <description>Johnson hasn’t played since injuring his ankle in Week 2. The fourth-year pass-rusher was officially upgraded to a full participant on Friday, allowing him to be removed from the injury report. Johnson has played in just four games since 2024 due to a torn Achilles suffered in Week 2 of last season. He tallied a career-high 7.5 sacks in 2023, and should provide immediate help to a Jets defense that has struggled out of the gate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cee1-def2-abdb-dfe10cee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (knee) has been removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cee6-d94a-a79d-cfefe8430000</link>
      <description>Fields was never at legitimate risk of missing Week 6’s game against the Broncos after being listed as a full participant in practice all week. The Jets’ decision to list him on the injury report was more out of formality than anything serious. Fields is officially good to go for Sunday’s matchup in London, but profiles as a risky fantasy option who has relied mostly on fourth quarter production to meet fantasy managers’ expectations. He could be in line for a tough day against a stout Broncos defense</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cee6-d94a-a79d-cfefe8430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray’s (foot) status for Week 6 will be determined in the next few days.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ceee-d94a-a79d-cfef05cb0000</link>
      <description>Murray will presumably practice in a limited capacity on Friday after being a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday. Gannon clearly isn’t in a hurry to say whether or not Murray will be available for Week 6’s game against the Colts, but it’s safe to assume he is at risk of missing Sunday’s game given how his practice week started. Still, it’s an encouraging sign that he was able to get on the field Friday, leaving the door open for him to play. Even if he’s active, Murray will be hard to trust if his foot injury is slowing his rushing ability. His status remains one to watch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ceee-d94a-a79d-cfef05cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) will not play in Week 6 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cef5-d94a-a79d-cffdd85f0000</link>
      <description>Godwin is just one of a laundry list of players who will not be active for the Buccaneers’ Week 6 game against the Niners. Godwin’s fibula injury is likely due to a reaggravation of the fractured fibula that ended his 2024 campaign, although the team has yet to confirm this. His absence on Sunday could open the door for Sterling Shepard to serve as the Buccaneers’ no. 2 target in the passing game opposite Emeka Egbuka, which could be of use to fantasy managers in deeper leagues. In addition to Godwin, the Buccaneers also ruled out CBs Zyon McCollum (thumb) and Benjamin Morrison (hamstring),</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cef5-d94a-a79d-cffdd85f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard (calf) will not play in Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefa-dd4c-afb9-effbe4a10000</link>
      <description>Hubbard will miss a second-straight game with his calf injury that sidelined him for an entire week of practice. This paves the way for Rico Dowdle to face off against his former team in what should be a bell cow role following his 23-206-1 rushing effort in Week 5’s game against the Dolphins. While we wouldn’t expect another 200-yard effort out of Dowdle, the fifth-year back does face a vulnerable Dallas defense that has allowed the most yards per game and fourth-most points per game this season, making him a must-start for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefa-dd4c-afb9-effbe4a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Jalen Coker (quad) is questionable for Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefc-def2-abdb-dffdc3d60000</link>
      <description>Coker’s practice window was opened earlier this week, and the team has yet to activate him to its 53-man roster. While it’s no guarantee he will be activated, the decision to list him as questionable comes after Coker logged a full week of practice. Even if he is active, Coker is little more than a stash heading into Week 6 against the Cowboys. He’s coming off a decent rookie campaign in which he totaled 32-478-2 in 11 games, but fantasy managers would be wise to wait and see how he is utilized before starting him in their lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefc-def2-abdb-dffdc3d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) is questionable for Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefd-def2-abdb-dffd59ba0000</link>
      <description>Sanders is dealing with a high-ankle sprain that he suffered in Week 3. He’s missed the last two games as a result, but logged a full practice on Thursday, indicating he is on the mend. He was limited again on Friday, but we’ll assume that was due mostly to load management. Still, fantasy managers considering starting him will want to check inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to ensure he is active. He won’t profile as anything more than a dart-throw TE2, after catching 11 passes for 92 scoreless yards in the three games he’s played in this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cefd-def2-abdb-dffd59ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers OT Taylor Moton (elbow) will not play in Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf03-d94a-a79d-cf0f908b0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers continue to take hits to their offensive line, with Moton being the latest starter to be sidelined following injuries to C Austin Corbett and RG Robert Hunt earlier this season. Moton has started all five games for the Panthers at right tackle this season, earning a PFF blocking grade of 73.7 while allowing 13 pressures and two sacks. Backup Yosh Nijman is listed behind Moton on the depth chart and will presumably draw the start on Sunday against the Cowboys. In addition to Moton, the Panthers have also ruled out CB Akayleb Evans (hamstring) and DT Tershawn Wharton (toe) for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf03-d94a-a79d-cf0f908b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
