<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos met with Mike Zimmer last week regarding a “senior coaching position.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</link>
      <description>The former Falcons, Bengals, and Cowboys defensive coordinator and Vikings head coach was not asked to return to the Cowboys following the 2024 season and spent the 2025 season away from coaching. The Broncos are now reportedly interested in his services in a “senior coaching position” capacity, although the extent of the position remain a mystery. The team retained defensive coordinator Vance Joseph through the 2026 hiring cycle. Stay tuned in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired former Titans GM Jon Robinson as their next Senior Personnel Executive.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</link>
      <description>Robinson will work hand-in-hand with general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan as the Dolphins careen towards a self inflicted rebuild, with the former likely playing a massive role in the direction of the franchise in the coming NFL Draft. The first order of business for the incoming front office will be finding their next quarterback after it was made evident that Tua Tagovailoa will no longer be the face of franchise moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lions will play a regular season game in Munich, Germany in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8fd1-d89c-a1be-afdf25c70000</link>
      <description>This will be the sixth regular season NFL game played in Germany as part of the league’s international series. It will feature Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown, a German-American and the centerpiece of the Detroit offense. Last year St. Brown was fifth in receiving yards and fourth in wideout receptions. The Lions will be looking to bounce back from a relatively disappointing 2025 campaign after losing OC Ben Johnson to the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8fd1-d89c-a1be-afdf25c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles general manager Howie Roseman did not dismiss the possibility of trading A.J. Brown this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-902a-d57c-a1dd-942abbd40000</link>
      <description>Roseman, who offered an “emphatic no” to teams looking to acquire Brown at the trade deadline in 2025, was more circumspect when asked this week if the Eagles would listen to trade offers for the superstar wideout, who appeared miserable in a lifeless Philadelphia offense last season. “We’re always listening,” Roseman said. “I don’t think you can go into any conversation with anyone and just shoot things down without hearing what they have to say — because you never know. ... You never know on any player. If someone’s going to give you something you didn’t anticipate and you won’t even have the conversation, I don’t think you’re necessarily doing your job, really servicing the team that you’re with.” Brown, 28, who is signed through the 2029 season, could end up elsewhere this offseason if a receiver-needy team is willing to part with major draft capital to acquire him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-902a-d57c-a1dd-942abbd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons general manager Ian Cunningham said the team will release QB Kirk Cousins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</link>
      <description>The move will be made on the first day of the 2026 NFL calendar year, according to Cunningham. This was all but confirmed last month when Cousins and the Falcons agreed to a contract modification that guaranteed he’d be gone ahead of the 2026 season. Cousins, 37, should see some interest from quarterback-needy teams in the coming months. Last year Cousins had a career-low 6.3 adjusted yards per attempt and 44.3 percent drop back success rate in five appearances (three starts) for the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens general manager Eric DeCosta said the team has offered C Tyler Linderbaum a “market setting” deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9040-d629-a1bc-b05dd4a80000</link>
      <description>DeCosta was clear about the team’s intent to keep Linderbaum as he’s expected to have several suitors in free agency this spring. The All-Pro center, perhaps the best in the league, could see interest from the Chargers and Giants, as both teams are coached by Harbaugh brothers, and John Harbaugh — Baltimore’s former head coach — is trying his best to get the band back together in New York. Pro Football Focus graded Linderbaum 23rd among centers in pass blocking last year and third in run blocking. Linderbaum has been durable, missing just two regular season games over his first four NFL seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9040-d629-a1bc-b05dd4a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears general manager Ryan Poles said teams have expressed interest in acquiring QB Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9046-d629-a1bc-b05fd5090000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals are among the teams reportedly interested in trading for Bagent this offseason after he showed flashes in preseason games and during four starts back in 2023. Bagent, if he lands with another team in the coming weeks or months, will likely have to compete for a starting job but could have a decent shot at landing one in a QB-hungry league. Bagent, entering his age-26 season, played at Division II Shepard in college, throwing for 94 touchdowns and 21 interceptions over his final two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9046-d629-a1bc-b05fd5090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Zach Ertz (ACL) intends to return for a 14th season in 2026, and that he hopes to be cleared “right around” Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904a-d57c-a1dd-944ae2360000</link>
      <description>The 35-year-old was injured in early December. Ertz had already become a catch-and-fall specialist even before his injury, but he has maintained a route-running savvy and strong pair of hands. His injury timeline makes him a tricky bet early in free agency, perhaps making it more likely he holds out for more guaranteed money on the eve of training camp. By then, teams will have a better idea of his health, as well as their own needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904a-d57c-a1dd-944ae2360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan said the team is not “actively” shopping De’Von Achane or Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904e-d042-afbc-fdde5e4e0000</link>
      <description>Sullivan spoke with reporters at the NFL Combine and didn’t exactly quash rumors that the Dolphins could part with one or both of their best players in a potential tear-down rebuild of the team. That rebuild — whatever it looks like — will certainly include parting ways with QB Tua Tagovailoa. One of the most explosive, efficient backs in the NFL, Achane could fetch a haul of draft picks if Miami moves on from him in the coming months. Waddle, meanwhile, profiles as a solid No. 2 receiver with a long history of injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904e-d042-afbc-fdde5e4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers general manager Omar Khan said he had not set a deadline for when Aaron Rodgers can decide on whether to return to the team in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9055-d89c-a1be-bfdf3d1f0000</link>
      <description>Khan told reporters at the NFL Combine on Tuesday that he has been in touch with Rodgers, 42, and doesn’t “foresee this going like it did last year,” when Rodgers drew out his decision to play for the Steelers well into the spring. ESPN reported on February 13 that Rodgers is “more likely than not” to return to Pittsburgh and play for his former Packers coach Mike McCarthy. Rodgers in 2025 showed some improvement over his play with the Jets in 2024. He ranked 23rd out of 36 qualifying quarterbacks last season in drop back EPA and 33rd in drop back success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9055-d89c-a1be-bfdf3d1f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
