<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Lions defensive coordinator Kelvin Sheppard regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b95f-dc7a-af9b-ffff7a440000</link>
      <description>Sheppard’s unit played pretty well in his first season as defensive coordinator despite injuries hitting the unit hard. The Lions finished fifth in defensive DVOA and there was almost no dropoff from Aaron Glenn leaving for the Jets. Sheppard, 38, could be a name that picks up some more buzz before this hiring cycle is over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b95f-dc7a-af9b-ffff7a440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b963-dc7a-af9b-ffff022c0000</link>
      <description>McDaniel was interviewed during Monday’s Texans-Steelers game. It’s the third head-coaching job that McDaniel has interviewed for this cycle, along with the Titans and Browns. The interest in him as an offensive mind has been more robust than expected thus far, perhaps he actually will get a chance to get a head-coaching gig this offseason now that there are a stunning nine vacancies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b963-dc7a-af9b-ffff022c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes “it’s hard to imagine the Browns continuing to employ [Shedeur] Sanders and Dillon Gabriel after inexplicably drafting both last April.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b96c-dc7a-af9b-ffffce460000</link>
      <description>“Early signs point to Sanders getting to compete for the job, [Deshaun] Watson being stuck on the roster and another quarterback addition in the middle rounds of the draft,” Jackson continues. Guess who is being left out of that quarterback room by omission? Gabriel was reportedly a Kevin Stefanski favorite in the draft process and — our speculation, not Jackson’s — might be traded to Stefanski’s new team this offseason. It’s also possible the team gives us another four-quarterback training camp show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b96c-dc7a-af9b-ffffce460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad/calf) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9aa-d968-a19b-f9fb71e40000</link>
      <description>Prater was active for the Bills’ Wild Card game, sinking both of his field goal attempts in the victory. The 41-year-old has played through a few ailments this season and will likely do so again if he can. Prater was listed as DNP for the Bills’ walkthrough, dealing with quad and calf issues. Practice reports later in the week will tell if Prater will officially go in the Saturday Divisional matchup against the Broncos, otherwise Matthew Wright will be called up from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9aa-d968-a19b-f9fb71e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9b3-d35e-a1bf-fdf35a3f0000</link>
      <description>Hairston missed the Bills’ Wild Card victory with an ankle injury he suffered in Week 18. There are several defensive players listed as limited on the Bills’ practice report as well, though it is merely an estimation as the team held a walkthrough practice, so reports from later in the week will tell a more concrete story. Hairston will need to get some practice time in before the end of the week in order to have a chance at playing in the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9b3-d35e-a1bf-fdf35a3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos DL John Franklin-Myers (hip) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9be-d968-a19b-f9ff3f670000</link>
      <description>The first-round bye gave Franklin-Myers an additional week to get healthy after he missed the Broncos’ Week 18 game. His full practice Tuesday is a good indication he will play in the Divisional Round against the Bills. LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) was also limited and could be nearing a return in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9be-d968-a19b-f9ff3f670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9c0-d56e-afff-ffe87f6f0000</link>
      <description>Arroyo was placed on injured reserve after suffering a knee injury in Week 14 but is nearing a return after a full practice on Tuesday. He was designated to return last week and looks to be in good shape to return to his rotational tight end role for the Divisional Round against the 49ers. With AJ Barner (hip) also fully practicing, the Seahawks tight end room is in good shape for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9c0-d56e-afff-ffe87f6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9c7-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b3190000</link>
      <description>Cross (hamstring) was a key injury to keep an eye on heading into the playoffs, having not played since Week 15. The good news is he is practicing in full after the Seahawks’ first-round bye and is likely to go for the Divisional Round against the 49ers. Sam Darnold will have a better time in the pocket with Cross protecting his blind side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9c7-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b3190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon TE Kenyon Sadiq has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9cb-d35e-a1bf-fdcbf1ce0000</link>
      <description>Sadiq is declaring for the draft early and immediately becomes one of the top tight end prospects in the 2026 NFL Draft. The 20-year-old tallied 24 receptions for 308 yards and two touchdowns as a sophomore for an Oregon team that won the Big Ten Championship. He followed that up with a 51/560/8 line as a junior, leading all college tight ends in touchdown catches. Sadiq will get buzz as potentially the first tight end off the board and is a candidate to be selected in the top half of the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b9cb-d35e-a1bf-fdcbf1ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Cardinals have requested to interview Texans defensive coordinator Matt Burke for their open head coaching role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ba2e-d35e-a1bf-ffee76800000</link>
      <description>At the helm of the Texans defense with head coach DeMeco Ryans for the past three seasons, Burke has helped craft a hard-hitting, powerful defensive line and secondary. He took over defensive play-calling from Ryans towards the start of a season that saw the Texans allow the least yards and second-least points of any team in the NFL, while ranking top-seven in both sacks and interceptions. The Cardinals just moved off a defensive head coach and are now looking to interview another one, requesting an interview with Burke fresh off a two-touchdown defensive performance in the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ba2e-d35e-a1bf-ffee76800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
