<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed WR Mecole Hardman on injured reserve with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a348-db57-afda-f77a74350000</link>
      <description>Hardman will now miss at least four games. He does not need to be rostered in any format. The Bills also elevated WR Gabe Davis from the practice squad to the active roster for tonight’s game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a348-db57-afda-f77a74350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-db57-afda-f772106c0000</link>
      <description>Jurgens is making progress in the NFL’s concussion protocol, but he has a ways to go before he can be viewed as more than questionable. Having their reliable center on the field would be great for a struggling Eagles offense as they take on the division-rival Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-db57-afda-f772106c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys QB Dak Prescott (hip) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-d413-ad9f-b7df18c70000</link>
      <description>Prescott was surprisingly limited on Wednesday after head coach Brian Schottenheimer told reporters that the Cowboys’ quarterback would handle a “normal workload” at Wednesday’s walkthrough. Regardless, Prescott is now practicing fully and can be treated as a QB1 entering a Week 12 showdown with the division-rival Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-d413-ad9f-b7df18c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Brian Branch (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a36b-db57-afda-f77b95430000</link>
      <description>The Lions’ banged-up secondary does not need to lose another player. Branch’s return was needed. Hopefully, the impactful safety can resume practicing fully on Friday. The Lions face the Giants in Week 12. Lions CB Terrion Arnold (concussion) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a36b-db57-afda-f77b95430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a38c-d82c-a79a-b39c83870000</link>
      <description>Crosby typically plays through injuries, famously having dealt with a bursa injury in one of his knees during the 2023 season. His Friday participation level is worth monitoring, with the Raiders D/ST unit profiling as a high-upside bunch against the Browns this weekend. Rookie QB Shedeur Sanders will make his first NFL start. If Crosby is unable to play, it would somewhat hurt the Raiders D/ST’s outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a38c-d82c-a79a-b39c83870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Keon Coleman is expected to be inactive for Week 12 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a390-db57-afda-f7b2e31e0000</link>
      <description>The Bills declared Coleman inactive last week for disciplinary reasons, marking “the third time Coleman has missed game time in his two-year career due to disciplinary issues.” He was held out in the first quarter of a game against the Jaguars last year and was again held out for the Bills’ first offensive series against the Patriots in Week 5. The Bills are employing a heavy wide receiver rotation on the perimeter with Coleman sitting on the bench.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a390-db57-afda-f7b2e31e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Keon Coleman, TE Dalton Kincaid, WR Curtis Samuel, DT Phidarian Mathis, OL Chase Lundt and DB Ja’Marcus Ingram inactive for Week 12 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a398-d90e-a9da-bf9f695d0000</link>
      <description>This will be Coleman’s fourth occasion missing game time due to disciplinary reasons in less than two years in the NFL. Kincaid (hamstring) and Samuel (elbow/neck) are both out due to injury. With Coleman out last week, the Bills relied on a wide receiver rotation including Khalil Shakir, Tyrell Shavers, Gabe Davis, Mecole Hardman and Samuel. Hardman has since been placed on injured reserve, helpfully reducing the personnel grouping for fantasy purposes. Unfortunately, the Texans field an elite pass defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a398-d90e-a9da-bf9f695d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Braxton Berrios, QB C.J. Stroud, S Jalen Pitre, OT Jarrett Kingston, LB Jamal Hill, LB Damone Clark and LG Laken Tomlinson inactive for Week 12 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3a7-d82c-a79a-b3b7125e0000</link>
      <description>Berrios’ inactivity interestingly reduces the Texans’ slot receiver rotation to a two-player committee, including Christian Kirk and Jaylin Noel. Berrios was listed with a quad injury this week but practiced in full. Lane is worth stashing at this time. Stroud will now miss his third straight game since suffering a brain injury in Week 9 against the Broncos. He managed one limited session on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3a7-d82c-a79a-b3b7125e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
