<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:05:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars OC Grant Udinski withdrew his name from consideration for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</link>
      <description>Udinski becomes the third coach to remove his name from consideration for the Browns job, joining Mike McDaniel and Jesse Minter. Udinski was a finalist for the job, but is now eyeing the Bills as a potential landing spot for his first head coaching gig. If he doesn’t join the Bills, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Udinski and the Jaguars already have a new deal in place for him to remain with the team. Udinski, 30, has emerged as one of the hottest names on the market and would become the youngest head coach in NFL history if hired by the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans QB coach Jerrod Johnson will interview for the Eagles’ offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</link>
      <description>Johnson interviewed for the Dolphins’ offensive-coordinator vacancy earlier this month but ultimately lost out to Bobby Slowik. Johnson has served as the Texans’ quarterbacks coach since 2023, and worked with the Colts (2020-2021) and Vikings before that. Should he leave for Philly, Johnson, who has never served as an offensive coordinator, would benefit from having proven veterans like Jalen Hurts and Saquon Barkley already in the building.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears offensive coordinator has removed his name from the Eagles’ offensive-coordinator search.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb09-d56e-afff-ffe9c3680000</link>
      <description>Doyle won’t be making the lateral move to Philly. The opportunity to join the Eagles did come with play-calling duties, something Doyle doesn’t have in Chicago, but the 30-year-old coach who landed his first OC role this offseason will remain with the Bears for 2026, taking more time to learn under Ben Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb09-d56e-afff-ffe9c3680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver is having a second interview with the Cardinals for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb15-d35e-a1bf-ffd7d2850000</link>
      <description>Weaver remains one of the hottest names in the league’s head coaching searches. The 45-year-old coach recently had a second interview with the Steelers, and was also a finalist for the Ravens’ job before they opted to go with Jesse Minter. He was also a finalist for the Saints’ head coaching job last year. Weaver has spent the last two seasons as the Dolphins’ defensive coordinator and was previously with the Ravens from 2021-2023. It seems like only a matter of time before he secures his first head-coaching gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb15-d35e-a1bf-ffd7d2850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers hired former Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb2f-d968-a19b-fbffff830000</link>
      <description>McDaniel continued to entertain head coaching offers even after it was rumored he would join the Chargers. Now, after much deliberation, McDaniel is officially joining the Chargers to pair with Justin Herbert and company. McDaniel’s offense finished 11th or better in points scored in two of his four seasons with the Dolphins, but his final two seasons proved forgettable as Tua Tagovailoa’s limitations became apparent and defenses took advantage. McDaniel gets a top-flight QB and talent young playmakers in Ladd McConkey and Omarion Hampton to help guide his offense into 2026. All will make for enticing fantasy picks, and Herbert should enjoy a bounce back if his offensive line can stay healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb2f-d968-a19b-fbffff830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed DT Teair Tart to a three-year, $37.5 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb61-d56e-afff-ffe9cbdd0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Kris Rhim reports the deal has $20 million in guarantees. Tart started all 17 games for the Chargers in 2025, totaling 32 tackles and four TFLs while also forcing and recovering one fumble. The sixth-year defensive lineman had played the previous two seasons with the Chargers on one-year deals, but will now be locked in with the team through the 2028 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb61-d56e-afff-ffe9cbdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Lions assistant head coach/WR coach Scottie Montgomery for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb6c-d968-a19b-fbfdf3570000</link>
      <description>It’s Montgomery’s first interview of the cycle. The 47-year-old was interviewed for the Cowboys job last year and the Buccaneers job in 2023. He’s been with the Lions since 2023 as Dan Campbell’s assistant head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb6c-d968-a19b-fbfdf3570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports Jets OC Tanner Engstrand is not expected to call plays in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb8f-dc7a-af9b-ffbfdafe0000</link>
      <description>An offensive coordinator not calling plays for a defensive-minded head coach certainly evokes a strong whiff of “what would you say you do here?” Hughes added that former Colts and Panthers HC Frank Reich is “among the names” he’s heard linked to the Jets. This is certainly an out-of-left-field development as the Jets’ run game was mostly praised last year despite what looked to be a pretty elementary passing game. Perhaps they’re trying to find someone who can assist with the passing part.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb8f-dc7a-af9b-ffbfdafe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams OC Mike LaFleur is scheduled to have a second interview with the Cardinals for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba7-d35e-a1bf-ffe7a4920000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, LaFleur will meet in-person with the Cardinals on Monday and Tuesday. The 38-year-old has spent the last three seasons as the Rams’ offensive coordinator after a failed two-year stint with the Jets. LaFleur has not called plays with the Rams, but his time with the Jets wasn’t exactly a resumé builder. The Raiders also requested an interview with LaFleur, who is now available to speak with after the Rams loss in the Conference Championship game to the Seahawks this past weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba7-d35e-a1bf-ffe7a4920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports the price for Murray “starts with a third-round pick.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba6-d56e-afff-ffee98340000</link>
      <description>“That source compared Murray’s situation with Geno Smith’s when he was traded from Seattle to Las Vegas last March for a third-round pick. The source pointed out that Smith was more consistent during his last season with Seattle than Murray was in his five games with Arizona this season, however, the source added that Murray ‘is a more talented player,’” Weinfuss writes. He quotes another source that believes the Cardinals can get a second-round pick for Murray due to a down quarterback draft. It wouldn’t be exceptionally surprising to see Murray fetch a Day 2 pick in trade given desperation around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba6-d56e-afff-ffee98340000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
