<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:04:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns will have a second interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d664-d35e-a1bf-d7e6a9cb0000</link>
      <description>With the Rams advancing to the NFC Championship Game after Sunday’s win over the Bears, the Browns will be restricted from interviewing Scheelhaase until next Monday at the earliest. The 35-year-old coach has met with several teams this hiring cycle, but any teams seriously considering hiring Scheelhaase will have to delay all hiring decisions by a week as the postseason continues to play out. Scheelhaase first joined the Rams in 2024 and was elevated to pass game coordinator ahead of this season. The latest coveted coach off the Sean McVay coaching tree could soon land a head coaching job if he and the Rams continue their impressive postseason run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d664-d35e-a1bf-d7e6a9cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile with interview for the Ravens’ head-coaching vacancy on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d674-d968-a19b-def522310000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are on a short list of teams interested in Campanile’s services, joining the Titans and Dolphins as potential suitors. The 43-year-old excelled in his first season as an NFL defensive coordinator in 2025, as his Jaguars finished eighth in points allowed and 11th in yards allowed while also boasting a top-10 run and pass defense on a per attempt basis. Should the Ravens move to hire him, Campanile would take over a defense that is already loaded with talent, but underperformed under second-year defensive coordinator Zach Orr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d674-d968-a19b-def522310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports former Buccaneers OC Josh Grizzard will interview with the Eagles for their offensive-coordinator vacancy on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d683-dc7a-af9b-dfbf0e320000</link>
      <description>Grizzard was one-and-done with the Buccaneers after being elevated to offensive coordinator for the 2025 season. Grizzard took over an offense that ranked among the top passing units in 2024, only to see it finish 22nd in yards per attempt and 20th in total passing yards this season. The Eagles are fresh off firing a one-and-done offensive coordinator of their own in Kevin Patullo, so a move to a coach on a similar trajectory could prove risky for head coach Nick Sirianni next season. That said, the Eagles are clearly exhausting all options in hopes of finding an adequate replacement for former OC Kellen Moore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d683-dc7a-af9b-dfbf0e320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills fired HC Sean McDermott.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d69d-d56e-afff-f6fda6630000</link>
      <description>Another playoff loss to an AFC West team, this time the Broncos, was the final straw for McDermott. With the likes of Patrick Mahomes, Joe Burrow, and Lamar Jackson all watching from home. McDermott’s Bills again came up short in Saturday’s Divisional Round loss to the Broncos. McDermott heavily blamed a controversial interception on an apparent catch by Brandin Cooks for the latest shortcoming. He finishes his Bills tenure with a 98-50 record after being hired by the team in 2017 and had only one losing season in his nine years at the helm. McDermott led the Bills to five-straight division titles from 2020 to 2024, but finished second to an emerging Patriots team this season. The Bills will now become the most coveted job opening in the NFL, as they will likely line up several potential head coaching candidates in the coming days. Current offensive coordinator Joe Brady will likely receive an interview as a potential in-house candidate, but we would expect the Bills to cast a wide net in hopes of bringing in a coach who can capitalize on the remainder of Josh Allen’s prime in hopes of delivering the Bills their first ever Super Bowl. McDermott, should he wish to continue as a head coach in 2026, should also generate plenty of interest with seven other head coaching vacancies still open across the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d69d-d56e-afff-f6fda6630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Bills are retaining GM Brandon Beane for next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6ab-d35e-a1bf-d7eb7ea80000</link>
      <description>This news comes on the heels of the team’s decision to fire head coach Sean McDermott. Beane, who was hired by the Bills in 2017 and signed a contract extension during the 2023 offseason, will now be tasked with finding the next coach to lead the Bills into next season. Beane’s track record as of late is questionable at best. The Bills’ 2025 draft consisted of five-straight defensive picks before finally selecting tight end Jackson Hawes in the fifth-round, and 2024 first-round receiver Keon Coleman has failed to deliver on his high draft capital. He was also a health scratch for multiple games this season. While Beane has work to do in finding a new head coach, it’s imperative he finds star playmakers to surround Josh Allen with next season after this year’s cast of characters left much to be desired late in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6ab-d35e-a1bf-d7eb7ea80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Chiefs are requesting to interview Bears RB coach Eric Bieniemy for their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6cd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee810000</link>
      <description>Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy’s contract will expire shortly, and he continues to draw interest around the league for head coaching vacancies. Bieniemy, who last worked with the Chiefs in 2022, has bounced around jobs over the last three season, spending 2023 with the Commanders before moving on to UCLA as an assistant head coach and OC in 2024, and landing with the Bears in his current role this season. Bieniemy has a long history with the Chiefs and head coach Andy Reid, and was a part of two Super Bowl-winning teams in 2019 and 2022. The Chiefs never finished lower than sixth in total points scored since Bieniemy took over as offensive coordinator in 2018, but they’ve finished 15th or worse in scoring in every season since his departure. A reunion would make sense for both sides and could help the Chiefs recapture some of what made them one of the most prolific offenses in the league for five-straight seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6cd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons re-signed DC Jeff Ulbrich to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6db-d968-a19b-defb77100000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin Stefanski has officially locked in his defensive coordinator. The newly minted Falcons coach opted to stick with Ulbrich, whose lone season with the team under Raheem Morris yielded a defense that ranked 15th in yards allowed, 19th in points allowed, and set a franchise record with 57 sacks. The Falcons denied a request from the Cowboys’ earlier this month to interview Ulbrich for their defensive coordinator vacancy, which hinted at the team retaining him even through a regime change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6db-d968-a19b-defb77100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills promoted Brandon Bean to President of Football Operations.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6e7-d35e-a1bf-d7e7ad060000</link>
      <description>If the decision to retain Beane for next season came as a surprise, then the decision to promote him to President of Football Operations will evoke similar feelings. Beane joined the Bills in 2017, and while the team has enjoyed plenty of regular-season success with him calling the shots with roster management, his inability to surround Josh Allen with premium talent is a notable red flag. Beane’s first order of work is finding a new head coach to replace the recently fired Sean McDermott, but the Bills can’t continue with the receiving corps they rolled out in Saturday’s divisional round loss to the Broncos. While the likes of Brandin Cooks and Gabe Davis are almost certain to be let go this offseason, 2024 first-rounder Keon Coleman continues to look like a bust, and Khalil Shakir, while solid, can’t carry the passing game as a low ADOT slot receiver. Beane’s promotion will come with added pressure to get premium talent around Allen, who will be 30 at the start of next season. It goes without saying that the 2026 offseason will be one of the most important offseasons for the Bills in recent memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6e7-d35e-a1bf-d7e7ad060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mike McCarthy “has now interviewed twice in recent days for the Titans head coaching job.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6fd-d35e-a1bf-d7ff17530000</link>
      <description>It was reported over a week ago that McCarthy would interview with the Titans on January 17th, but according to Schefter, the team also spoke with McCarthy “once in late December in Green Bay,” while the season was still going on. This certainly throws a bit of a wrinkle in how we should view the Titans’ head-coaching vacancy, as the early decision to speak with McCarthy in-season could hint at him being the favorite in the clubhouse. McCarthy is also expected to speak with the Steelers in the coming days, giving him another potential suitor if things don’t work out with the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6fd-d35e-a1bf-d7ff17530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed TE Tanner Hudson to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d709-d35e-a1bf-d7cbbeaf0000</link>
      <description>Hudson, 31, was playing on an expiring deal this season but is now locked in for 2026. The veteran tight end played on 148 offensive snaps this season, per PFF, and has never been used as anything more than a backup since entering the league in 2019. He caught 19 passes for 168 yards and two touchdowns this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d709-d35e-a1bf-d7cbbeaf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
