<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) “is expected to have a chance” to play in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-726f-d6a5-adff-f6ef3cbe0000</link>
      <description>According to Schefter, Loveland’s injury “is not believed to be serious.” The rookie tight end caught one pass for 31 yards in Week 3’s win over the Cowboys before exiting Sunday’s contest, and has caught three passes for 31 yards on six targets. Loveland can’t be trusted by fantasy managers in Week 4 even if he is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-726f-d6a5-adff-f6ef3cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on 105.3 the Fan, Cowboys executive vice president Stephen Jones declined to commit to CeeDee Lamb (ankle) playing in Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-727a-d1b3-a5dd-737b59470000</link>
      <description>Lamb is dealing with a high-ankle sprain. He expressed optimism after Sunday’s loss to the Bears, saying he “absolutely” feels like he can play in Week 4 against the Packers, but Jones is opting to take a more measured approach. Jones said the Cowboys will wait and see how the week goes for Lamb before deciding whether or not he’ll have a chance to suit up on Sunday night. This will be something to watch throughout the week. Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports the Cowboys are thinking that Lamb will miss “2-4 weeks.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-727a-d1b3-a5dd-737b59470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed S Darnell Savage.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7286-dfde-a1bd-7e8fff940000</link>
      <description>He’ll take Will Harris’ place in the rotation. Savage had an underwhelming couple of years in Jacksonville but should be a potential starter for the Commanders. The 28-year-old had one tackle in two games with the Jaguars before being released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7286-dfde-a1bd-7e8fff940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said “everything is under evaluation and consideration” when asked if he could give up offensive play-calling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7284-d93f-ad9d-7ac7e37a0000</link>
      <description>The 0-3 Titans are open to anything to secure that much-needed first win of the season. Currently ranking 31st in both EPA per play and offensive success rate (36.8 percent), Callahan’s offense is in need of a spark, which could come from a change in play-calling. The former OC, who was once praised for the elite offenses he oversaw during his time in Cincinnati, has struggled to live up to the hype in his brief tenure as head coach of the Titans. The Titans are riding a nine-game losing streak that dates back to last season and were a bottom-tier offense in 2024, which ultimately led them to the No. 1 overall pick and QB Cam Ward this offseason. Offensive coordinator Nick Holz, who last served as OC in 2022 while at UNLV, would presumably take over at play-calling if a change were to be made. He joined Callahan’s staff during the 2024 offseason and has never held a play-calling role in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7284-d93f-ad9d-7ac7e37a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Samaje Perine (thumb) is not ruled out for Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7288-dfde-a1bd-7e8da3de0000</link>
      <description>He had an MRI after leaving Week 3’s game that did not reveal significant damage, per a source. Perine is not startable, even with Chase Brown’s abysmal stat line in front of him, but it sounds like he’s got a chance to provide more league-average third-down back work in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7288-dfde-a1bd-7e8da3de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports CeeDee Lamb (ankle) is “unlikely to play” in Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7292-d93f-ad9d-7ad738b10000</link>
      <description>This report comes about an hour after Cowboys EVP Stephen Jones declined to commit to Lamb’s Week 4 availability. It goes without saying that Lamb is trending toward missing at least one week of action, but Schefter also points out that “the Cowboys want to see how Lamb is doing in the next 10-14 days before making further determinations about his status.” Lamb undoubtedly wants to beat whatever projected return date the Cowboys will have set for him, but it’s hard to imagine him not missing at least one game with the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7292-d93f-ad9d-7ad738b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Nick Bosa (knee) suffered a season-ending torn ACL in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ac-d1b3-a5dd-73fdbd8a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers had optimism last night, but this is a devastating blow. It is the same knee he initially tore the ACL in during the 2020 season. San Francisco was getting by with Bosa and some blitz packages, but now has no obvious source of pressure on the roster. Bryce Huff could be elevated beyond his situational role as the 49ers try to pick up the pieces on defense. It’s a major downgrade for their D/ST and will make their playoff climb a little steeper, even at 3-0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ac-d1b3-a5dd-73fdbd8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said they’re “evaluating everything” when asked about who will be the starting quarterback on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72b4-dfde-a1bd-7ebd6d840000</link>
      <description>It is the second time in three weeks that Daboll hasn’t really offered much of an endorsement for Russell Wilson, although he did manage a 400-yard effort against the Cowboys in Week 2. It seems like Jaxson Dart will get his chance sooner rather than later regardless of what happens this week, with the team clearly spiraling at 0-3 and Daboll needing some way to manufacture some job security. Whenever he’s elevated, Dart will need to blow the NFL away for Daboll and Joe Schoen to have any shot of keeping their jobs. The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes that “after listening to Daboll’s entire presser, they have to be making a QB change and he’s just not ready to announce it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72b4-dfde-a1bd-7ebd6d840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce has entered concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72bd-d1b3-a5dd-73fdc0000000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Pierce left Week 3’s win over the Titans with a concussion. The veteran receiver will now need to clear protocol if he hopes to play in Week 4 against the Rams, but his recent concussion history suggests he’ll miss at least one game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72bd-d1b3-a5dd-73fdc0000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports CeeDee Lamb “could miss 3-4 weeks with a high left ankle sprain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72c5-d6a5-adff-f6c5cb910000</link>
      <description>Numerous reports continue to come in on Lamb’s ankle. In less than 24 hours, we have gone from Lamb saying he could “absolutely” play in Week 4 to the team now expecting him to miss 3-4 weeks, which always felt like the most likely outcome regardless of Lamb’s optimism. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport later reported that the Cowboys don’t plan to place Lamb on injured reserve in case he can return inside the four games players on IR are required to miss, but it sounds like this is trending toward being a multi-week absence. George Pickens and Jake Ferguson stand to benefit the most from Lamb’s absence, with Pickens profiling as a WR2 and Ferguson a fringe TE1 in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72c5-d6a5-adff-f6c5cb910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
