<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Cross (foot) is not on Seattle’s final injury report for the NFC Championship game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefa88430000</link>
      <description>Despite not practicing either of the first two sessions of the week, Cross will start against the Rams. Backup T Josh Jones (knee/ankle) is questionable, and third-string left tackle Amari Kight (knee) is doubtful. Cross would appear to be on the spot to play through the pain if neither of his backups were cleared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefa88430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) is not on Seattle’s injury report for the NFC Championship Game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefab41b0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks cleared Darnold for action just as their Friday practice session was beginning, so we do not yet know his participation level. He was limited on Wednesday and Thursday after playing through the injury last weekend. Promisingly, no setbacks have been reported. He will also have LT Charles Cross (foot) active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefab41b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with former defensive coordinator Zach Orr for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecdc-d56e-afff-eefc4fc70000</link>
      <description>Orr had been interviewed by the Cowboys earlier this offseason before they settled on Christian Parker as their defensive coordinator. There’s been some smoke linking him to the Giants with former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh, but that has yet to be realized. Thus, this is Orr’s only live lead for a defensive coordinator role. He had a somewhat disappointing season in 2025, but the 2024 Ravens defense finished highly in several categories, including first in yards per rush attempt allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecdc-d56e-afff-eefc4fc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams S Quentin Lake (illness) is not on Los Angeles’ injury report for the NFC Championship Game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ece5-d56e-afff-eeedfc1a0001</link>
      <description>The Rams will have their lynchpin defensive back on the field this weekend. He sat out Wednesday’s practice before practicing fully on Thursday and Friday. Lake is up to eight pass breakups, one interception, one forced fumble, 54 tackles and one sack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ece5-d56e-afff-eeedfc1a0001</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) is not on Denver’s injury report for the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecf1-d35e-a1bf-edf389e50000</link>
      <description>Bryant opened the week with a limited session on Wednesday and closed it by practicing fully two days in a row. Before suffering a concussion, the Broncos’ third-round rookie was a featured player on the team’s opening drive last week, catching three passes for 32 yards. He could operate similarly this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecf1-d35e-a1bf-edf389e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) for the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec5a-d968-a19b-fcfb14090000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is not yet ready to resume playing. He remained limited throughout all three practices this week after the Broncos opened his 21-day practice window on Monday. With Dobbins out, rookie RB RJ Harvey will again lead the backfield. He totaled 11 touches last week. Broncos RB Jaleel McLaughlin handled four and RB Tyler Badie had one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec5a-d968-a19b-fcfb14090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Troy Franklin (hamstring) is questionable to play in the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecf1-d968-a19b-fcf1554d0000</link>
      <description>Franklin logged three straight limited sessions this week. It is tough to say whether he will be active against the Patriots. He departed early last week. Over his last two games, he has earned just one target. Even if he is active, he is unlikely to operate as a featured player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecf1-d968-a19b-fcf1554d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) is questionable to play in the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfc-d56e-afff-eefc79700000</link>
      <description>Wattenberg practiced fully all week, so he is seemingly on track to face the Patriots in the AFC Championship Game. Getting their stud center back on the field would be great news for the Broncos’ offense, particularly fill-in QB Jarrett Stidham.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfc-d56e-afff-eefc79700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed an interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfe-dc7a-af9b-effff0a50000</link>
      <description>This is Weaver’s second interview with the Steelers, and the first in-person. Dolphins is also a candidate for the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy and has been linked to the Giants’ defensive coordinator vacancy. He previously interviewed for the now-filled Ravens’ head-coaching role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfe-dc7a-af9b-effff0a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested and interview with Chiefs DL coach Joe Cullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed03-d35e-a1bf-edc398f10000</link>
      <description>Cullen interviewed for the Commanders’ defensive coordinator vacancy earlier this month. The Chiefs’ defensive line generated pressure at a top-10 rate during the regular season (38.9 percent) and totaled 87 TFLs, tying for 15th.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed03-d35e-a1bf-edc398f10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
