<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:03:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers DL Nick Bosa (knee) and DL Mykel Williams (knee) are expected to return sometime “around” training camp this summer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26f-dc7a-af9b-effff7c60000</link>
      <description>The news comes straight from 49ers general manager John Lynch, though the 49ers’ injury updates have been less than reliable this season. Bosa, 28, tore an ACL on September21st. Williams, a 21-year-old first-round rookie, tore his on November 2nd. Williams also notably injured his knee on August 7th, suffering what was believed to be a hyperextension. Follow-up reports did not specify whether this was accurate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e26f-dc7a-af9b-effff7c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e28b-d968-a19b-fafb44450000</link>
      <description>Prior reporting on Wattenberg’s injury has been proven accurate. He missed the first two weeks of the playoffs, as expected, and will now attempt to make his return in time for Denver’s AFC Championship Game against the Patriots. Wattenberg is an all-around talented blocker. His potential return is great for the Broncos’ offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e28b-d968-a19b-fafb44450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e290-d56e-afff-e6f86cd70000</link>
      <description>We expect this to be a limited session for Bryant, who left the Broncos’ Divisional Round game against the Bills with his second recorded concussion this season. He was hospitalized after suffering a concussion in Week 16 against the Jaguars and was unable to play in Week 17 against the Chiefs. His swift turnaround is a good sign regarding his overall health and puts him on track to play in the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e290-d56e-afff-e6f86cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) resumed practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e295-d35e-a1bf-e7d76b420000</link>
      <description>The Broncos designated Dobbins to return from injured reserve on Monday. He suffered a Lisfranc injury after being hip-drop tackled by a Raiders defender in Week 10. He has a real chance to play in the Broncos’ AFC Championship Game against the Patriots, though we do not yet know whether he will unseat rookie RB RJ Harvey as the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e295-d35e-a1bf-e7d76b420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Troy Franklin (hamstring) practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e296-dc7a-af9b-efbf49470000</link>
      <description>Franklin’s early-week participation is somewhat surprising. He was forced from the Broncos’ Divisional Round game against the Bills on Saturday. We expect to see him listed as a limited participant, but he has a chance to play in the Broncos’ AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e296-dc7a-af9b-efbf49470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said QB Bo Nix’s ankle surgery “went well.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2a6-d56e-afff-e6ee84c40000</link>
      <description>Nix reportedly broke a bone in his ankle on the second-to-last play of regulation in the Broncos’ Divisional Round game against the Bills. Nix can now begin the rehabilitation process as backup QB Jarrett Stidham takes the reins for Denver’s AFC Championship Game against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2a6-d56e-afff-e6ee84c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills completed an interview with OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ab-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2a90000</link>
      <description>Hiring Brady would certainly make for a smooth transition. The Bills’ offensive coordinator has served in his current role for the past two seasons. He was the Bills’ quarterbacks coach in 2022 and 2023, and was promoted to interim offensive coordinator in the latter year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ab-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed an interview with former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2b1-dc7a-af9b-efbff3b10000</link>
      <description>McCarthy took the year after being relieved of his duties with the Cowboys following the 2024 season. McCarthy also interviewed with the Giants and Titans, though both organizations chose to go with other candidates. McCarthy’s 2024 Cowboys squad averaged just 5.0 yards per play during the regular season, ranking 27th among NFL offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2b1-dc7a-af9b-efbff3b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed TE Jaheim Bell to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e279-d56e-afff-e6f912390000</link>
      <description>Bell was drafted by the Patriots in 2024. He did not make the roster this year and joined the Eagles’ practice squad. That didn’t last long and he spent the end of the year on the Steelers’ practice squad. Back in Philly, Bell could crack the team’s roster if Dallas Goedert walks in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e279-d56e-afff-e6f912390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills scheduled an interview with Commanders run game coordinator and RB coach Anthony Lynn for their head-coaching vacancy on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2c2-d968-a19b-faf3dffd0000</link>
      <description>Lynn, 57, has served in his current roles over the last two seasons. In the two seasons before that, he served as the 49ers’ assistant head coach and running backs coach. He spent the 2021 season as the Lions’ offensive coordinator following a four-year run as the Chargers’ head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2c2-d968-a19b-faf3dffd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
