<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) will not play in Philadelphia’s Week 18 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80ae-d35e-a1bf-c5ee3dd70000</link>
      <description>Grant Calcaterra! Tanner McKee! It’s not quite the UFL, but you wouldn’t know it! We expect Goedert to be healthy for Philadelphia’s first Wild Card round injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80ae-d35e-a1bf-c5ee3dd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll declined to say whether Kenny Pickett or Aidan O’Connell will start against the Chiefs in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7ac10000</link>
      <description>Has anyone tried asking the Raiders to be normal? We’re just asking questions here. Carroll said both players would play. Neither player is worth rostering in superflex leagues in Week 18. O’Connell has probably performed like a better quarterback but spent all season buried on the depth chart for reasons that defy rational explanation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7ac10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d35e-a1bf-c5e36fce0000</link>
      <description>The Broncos will have their rookie wide receiver on the field as they attempt to retain the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed this week. Bryant has finished exactly as the half-PPR WR45 in each of his last three games and can be treated as a WR4 accordingly this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d35e-a1bf-c5e36fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (illness) is doubtful to play in Week 18 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e6-d968-a19b-d8f7aa530000</link>
      <description>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid initially said Worthy would be listed as questionable to play. Instead, the team lists him as doubtful. We do not expect him to play. The Chiefs will likely attempt to run out the clock in a lost season against the lowly Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e6-d968-a19b-d8f7aa530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (illness) is not on the injury report for Week 18 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80eb-d56e-afff-e6ebf3b70000</link>
      <description>Carter returned to practice on Friday, logging a limited session. Giants DL Dexter Lawrence (illness) was also removed from the injury report, though he did not resume practicing. We tentatively expect both players to be on the field for Week 18, but projecting their snap counts is tough. The Giants and Cowboys have both been eliminated from playoff contention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80eb-d56e-afff-e6ebf3b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Jordan Mason (ankle) is not on the injury report for Week 18 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e5-dc7a-af9b-cfffa1f80000</link>
      <description>Mason is in line to start this week with RB Aaron Jones (hip) having been ruled out. The Packers have already locked up a playoff spot. The Vikings are simply trying to get a better read on QB J.J. McCarthy. Mason is on the RB3/FLEX radar this week. He will likely cede passing down snaps to No. 3 RB Zavier Scott.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e5-dc7a-af9b-cfffa1f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes Packers vice president of player personnel Jon-Eric Sullivan and 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams are candidates for the Dolphins’ general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8101-d968-a19b-d9f16b280000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are apparently restructuring certain roles in their front office and are expected to “have three guys atop the football side—the head coach, the new GM and [senior vice president of football and business administration Brandon] Shore.” Shore is reportedly being “transitioned into an elevated role.” Breer believes the Dolphins are searching for a general manager “with a strong player-evaluation background” to complete the trio. Sullivan fits the bill, having come up “on the scouting side under the late Ted Thompson.” Breer also names the 49ers’ Williams as an option, if team owner Stephen Ross chooses to keep head coach Mike McDaniel, due to Williams and McDaniel’s “standing relationship.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8101-d968-a19b-d9f16b280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Conor Orr said reports that Broncos DC Vance Joseph could begin interviewing for head coaching vacancies next week, if the Broncos clinch the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8112-dc7a-af9b-cfbf42ff0000</link>
      <description>Orr tells readers to “expect to see” Joseph begin interviews as early as Wednesday, “in alignment with the league’s rules for coaches in the playoffs.” Joseph previously served as the Broncos’ head coach in 2017-2018 and now fields one of the NFL’s best defenses. NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe also recently reported that Joseph could be a head coaching candidate this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8112-dc7a-af9b-cfbf42ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak “could be of interest” if the Buccaneers were to move on from head coach Todd Bowles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80f5-d968-a19b-d8f525f50000</link>
      <description>Breer notes that the Buccaneers “just signed Todd Bowles to an extension through 2028 in June,” so moving on from him is an unlikely outcome. That said, the team suddenly finds itself “in the midst of a 1–7 slide, with a chance to miss the playoffs even with a win over the Panthers this weekend.” Ironically, Breer adds that “if a change comes,” he expects the Buccaneers to “look at young offensive coaches, like the ones they lost (Liam Coen, Dave Canales)” in recent seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80f5-d968-a19b-d8f525f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed OL Cole Van Lanen to a three-year, $51 million extension through 2028.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8110-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb0c10000</link>
      <description>Van Lanen, a fifth-year NFL veteran, is having a career year in his fourth season with the Jaguars. The versatile blocker has played all over the offensive line this season, taking snaps at left tackle (300), left guard (72), right guard (46) and right tackle (133). His 75.9 PFF pass-blocking grade and 78.9 PFF run-blocking grade both lead the team. The deal includes $32.5 million in guarantees and keeps Van Lanen in Jacksonville through his age-30 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8110-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb0c10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
