<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 04:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Bech caught 2-of-3 targets for 22 yards in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a8-d90e-a9da-dfaf22d50000</link>
      <description>Bech missed time with a chest injury in this one, though that hardly impacted his box score relevance. The Raiders scored a touchdown on their fourth drive, and Bech at least helped them get there with a 16-yard pickup. He should not be on fantasy rosters. The Raiders face the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a8-d90e-a9da-dfaf22d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 4-of-4 targets for 63 yards and two touchdowns in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b2-d82c-a79a-f7b6e5c90000</link>
      <description>The talented tight end helped bring the ball down to the Chargers’ five-yard line on the Raiders’ fourth drive by ripping off a 24-yard gain on a corner route via play action. Two plays later, QB Geno Smith found him wide open in the back of the end zone for his first touchdown of the day. His second punctuated an unbelievable red zone sequence on the Raiders’ ninth drive. Smith initially connected with Bowers on a four-yard touchdown, but the play was questionably overturned by the refs, seemingly post-snap, who accommodated a last-second timeout call from Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh. Smith targeted Bowers in tight, physical coverage on the next play, and although it resulted in an incompletion, one of Bowers’ coverage defenders was called for defensive pass interference, bringing a fresh set of downs. On the next play, Raiders C Alex Cappa stepped on Smith’s right foot during the dropback. Smith hit the deck, clung to the ball and waited for the sack. Smith went right back to Bowers after that, who somehow secured a one-handed catch by falling backward, to the left, with his left hand outstretched, saving the ball from hitting the ground by inches. Bowers remains an elite TE1 against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b2-d82c-a79a-f7b6e5c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 2-of-6 targets for four yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7aa-d90e-a9da-dfafcec30000</link>
      <description>It was as bleak as ever for Jefferson in a lost season in the prime of his NFL career. The Vikings designed some easy looks for Jefferson in the first quarter, but Max Brosmer —a n undrafted rookie making his first-ever NFL start — quickly looked elsewhere. Jordan Addison led the Vikings with ten targets and TJ Hockenson saw six looks from Brosmer, who averaged 4.2 yards per throw. It doesn’t really matter whether Brosmer or JJ McCarthy (concussion) is under center for the Vikings in Week 14 against Atlanta: Jefferson is nothing more than a top-24 fantasy option with limited upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7aa-d90e-a9da-dfafcec30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 15 times for 31 yards in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers, adding six receptions for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b5-d82c-a79a-f7b5898f0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty simply had nowhere to run against the Chargers’ defensive front. The unit had an excellent showing. Jeanty deserves credit for consistently getting open as a short-area route runner. His six receptions and eight targets both led the team, and his 30 receiving yards, unfortunately, trailed only TE Brock Bowers’ 63. Jeanty will have a tough time next week against the Broncos’ elite defense. Treat him as an RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b5-d82c-a79a-f7b5898f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught all six of his targets for 59 yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ba-d82c-a79a-f7be38d00000</link>
      <description>It was Hockenson’s best game of the 2025 season, and it came with undrafted rookie QB Max Brosmer under center while JJ McCarthy deals with a head injury he sustained in Week 12. Hockenson was second on the team in targets and led all Minnesota pass catchers with 59 yards. He had more than 30 receiving yards just five times in 2025 headed into Week 13. Perhaps Brosmer’s check-down tendencies can make Hockenson fantasy relevant again if the rookie gets another start in Week 14 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ba-d82c-a79a-f7be38d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 3-of-3 targets for 23 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7c0-d82c-a79a-f7d4c5740000</link>
      <description>Johnston salvages the day with a hard-fought touchdown on the Chargers’ first drive. The big-bodied wide receiver got open on a crossing route from the Raiders’ 10-yard line, secured the pass from QB Justin Herbert, turned upfield and bounced through simultaneous contact from two Raiders defenders before entering the end zone. Johnston remains a FLEX option against the Eagles in Week 14 on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7c0-d82c-a79a-f7d4c5740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 5-of-10 targets for 36 yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7bd-d82c-a79a-f7bda1e20000</link>
      <description>Addison easily led the team in targets. Justin Jefferson was held to two catches on six targets for four yards while T.J. Hockenson caught all six of his targets for a team-leading 59 yards. Undrafted QB Max Brosmer, making his first NFL start, peppered Addison in the second half with the Seattle secondary shading toward Jefferson. Addison’s fantasy floor will remain low no matter which quarterback starts for Minnesota next week against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7bd-d82c-a79a-f7bda1e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Nailor did not catch his only target in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7dc-d90e-a9da-dfdf92e40000</link>
      <description>Nailor ran a route on 21 of the Vikings’ 38 drop backs and failed to record a reception for the third time this season. Nailor appeared set to see an increased role in the Minnesota offense with Adam Thielen listed as a healthy scratch for this game. There’s just not that many attempts or air yards to go around this Vikings offense for a tertiary option like Nailor to gold any fantasy value. He should remain on waiver wires ahead of Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7dc-d90e-a9da-dfdf92e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zavier Scott had three rushes for 17 yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks, adding one catch for four yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7e1-db57-afda-d7f36c8d0000</link>
      <description>Scott could see an increased role in Week 14 if Aaron Jones misses time with the shoulder injury he sustained in the second half of the team’s loss against Seattle. Jones has a history of shoulder ailments and was quickly pulled from the game. Jordan Mason would likely take over as the Vikings’ lead back, but it could be Scott who takes on the pass-catching tole with Jones sidelined. Scott had a six-catch game in Week 3 with Jones out. He should be picked up in deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7e1-db57-afda-d7f36c8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 3-of-4 targets for 24 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 13 win against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7e5-d90e-a9da-dfef225d0000</link>
      <description>Kupp, who hasn’t had more than three catches in a game since early October, is no longer a fantasy-viable player in the run-first Seattle offense. Jaxon Smith Njigba’s domination of targets and air yards leaves precious little opportunity for everyone else in the Seattle passing game, including Kupp. He’ll only be playable in deep leagues next week against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7e5-d90e-a9da-dfef225d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
