<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Michael Silver reports Bills offensive line coach Aaron Kromer is expected to retire.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</link>
      <description>Kromer has been with the Bills for four seasons. He has been in the NFL for over 20 years, primarily as an offensive line coach, no matter the team. Pro Football Focus graded the Bills’ line as a top-10 unit in both run and pass protection this year. With Kromer hanging up the clipboard and multiple starters on expiring contracts, Buffalo’s line could look drastically different in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports former Titans offensive line coach Bill Callahan is “likely” to join new Falcons head coach Kevin Stefanski in Atlanta.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d221-d968-a19b-daf1a2c80000</link>
      <description>Callahan previously held the same role in Cleveland under Stefanski. The team let him go to coach under his son, Brian Callahan, with the Titans. That lasted less than two years and Bill ultimately resigned after the team fired Brian. Callahan is still considered one of the league’s best line coaches, even though the Titans stint didn’t work out. We fully expect him to reunite with Stefanski in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d221-d968-a19b-daf1a2c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns have requested a second interview with Jaguars offensive coordinator Grant Udinski for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d22a-d968-a19b-dafbf9270000</link>
      <description>Udinski previously discussed the opening with Cleveland via a virtual interview. He will not meet with the Browns’ bigwigs in-person, meaning he is one of the leading candidates for the job. Browns DC Jim Schwartz and Ravens OC Todd Monken are also scheduled for in-person interviews. Udinski is undoubtedly the highest-ceiling hire Cleveland could make. The 30-year-old offensive mind just helped Trevor Lawrence post career-high numbers across the board, including 38 total touchdowns. Udinski is also the least proven of the finalists, having only held his current role for one season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d22a-d968-a19b-dafbf9270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Nico Collins, T Trent Brown, RB Jawhar Jordan, QB Graham Mertz, and WR Justin Watson inactive for the Divisional Round against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d261-d968-a19b-daf1ce040000</link>
      <description>Collins, who sustained a head injury in the Wild Card round against the Chargers, did not practice this week and was ruled out on Friday. It’s a massive blow to the Houston offense. Christian Kirk, who had 144 yards and a score last week against LA, and Jayden Higgins will profile as the team’s top two receivers with Collins out. Brown tried to play but was unable to fight through an injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d261-d968-a19b-daf1ce040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is active for the Divisional Round against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d267-d968-a19b-daf7e6950000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez was removed from the Patriots’ injury report on Friday following his Wild Card Round concussion and subsequent placement in the league’s concussion protocol. He’ll join a solid New England secondary going against a Texans offense that will be without Nico Collins (concussion). Patriots declared CB ﻿Kobee Minor,﻿ LB ﻿Bradyn Swinson,﻿ OT ﻿Marcus Bryant﻿, DT ﻿Eric Gregory,﻿ G ﻿Caedan Wallace,﻿ TE ﻿CJ Dippre, and﻿ QB ﻿Tommy DeVito﻿ inactive against Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d267-d968-a19b-daf7e6950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Steelers are “open” to Aaron Rodgers’ return in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d298-d56e-afff-f6f82ceb0000</link>
      <description>Schefter said Rodgers coming back to the Steelers for another season remains “unlikely” after head coach Mike Tomlin stepped down last week, but “Steelers players are more than open to Rodgers returning to Pittsburgh; they want the four-time league MVP back and conveyed as much to various members of the Steelers organization during their exit meetings last week.” Rodgers, 42, seemed considerably less miserable during his 2025 season in Pittsburgh after two difficult years with the Jets. Schefter said Rodgers, as usual, “wants to take time away before deciding his future.” Rodgers ranked 23rd out of 36 qualifying QBs in EPA per drop back in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d298-d56e-afff-f6f82ceb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will hold a second interview with Chargers defensive coordinator Jesse Minter for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2a0-d968-a19b-daf1cc8b0000</link>
      <description>The Browns seem to be homing in on Minter and former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel after talking to Jim Schwartz, Todd Monken, and Grant Udinski about the team’s head coaching gig. Rams passing game coordinator Nathan Scheelhaase will also get a second interview with the Browns, according to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. Minter, 42, recently completed head coaching interviews with the Dolphins, Falcons, Raiders, and Ravens. His Chargers defense in 2025 allowed the league’s fifth lowest EPA per play and sixth lowest offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2a0-d968-a19b-daf1cc8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton praised QB Jarrett Stidham’s arm strength and accuracy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2a8-d968-a19b-daf9b9130000</link>
      <description>Payton on Sunday said Stidham — who will start the AFC title game with Bo Nix (ankle) sidelined — has “a lot to his ball” and has consistently demonstrated a strong arm in practice. Stidham on 197 regular season attempts over six seasons has completed 59.5 percent of his throws and averaged a decent 7.2 yards per attempt. It’s possible Stidham can manage the Denver offense well enough to make the Broncos competitive against whoever they play in the AFC title game in Denver. He likely won’t be asked to do much, however. Stidham hasn’t thrown a regular season pass since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2a8-d968-a19b-daf9b9130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will host a second interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2af-d35e-a1bf-d7ef6eb70000</link>
      <description>McDaniel is one of three head coaching canddiates to land a second interview with the Browns, along with Chargers DC Jesse Minter and Rams passing game coordinator Nathan Scheelhaase. McDaniel has interviewed for a number of jobs since the Dolphins fired him in early January after three seasons at the helm in Miami. He could have his choice of jobs in the coming days, including the Eagles’ offensive coordinator position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2af-d35e-a1bf-d7ef6eb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz was forced from Houston’s Divisional Round game against the Patriots with a left calf injury and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2d2-d968-a19b-daf3ee6d0000</link>
      <description>Schultz pulled up running a first quarter route in the Patriots’ end zone and walked off the field very gingerly. He then made his way to the locker room without assistance, but at a slow pace. He was ruled out in the second quarter. The Texans’ de facto No. 1 pass catcher with Nico Collins sidelined, Schultz’s loss is a potentially enormous blow. C.J. Stroud ended the drive following Schultz’s departure with a horrid pick, and has been struggling with turnovers ever since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d2d2-d968-a19b-daf3ee6d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
