<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jauan Jennings (shoulder/ankle) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9046-d6e9-af9d-9ad60a930000</link>
      <description>Ricky Pearsall is also expected to suit up. Both receivers were listed as questionable for Week 4. Per Schefter, Jennings is “likely to be limited.” Jennings led the 49ers in targets when he was last active in Week 2. He saw 10 looks and posted a 5/89/1 receiving line. A potential pitch count, however, is a big blow to his fantasy outlook. Jennings will sit on the WR3/4 border for a week but could be even higher than Pearsall for Week 5 if his date with the Jags does well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9046-d6e9-af9d-9ad60a930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Davante Adams (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-904d-d95b-addb-f84f40ca0000</link>
      <description>Adams missed the first two practices of the week with the hamstring injury but was back for a limited session to close the week. Head coach Sean McVay told reporters that he felt good about Adams being able to play on. The team only targets those two players, meaning both can be treated as WR1s for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-904d-d95b-addb-f84f40ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jacory Croskey-Merritt (ankle) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9052-d95b-addb-f85677c10000</link>
      <description>Bill was upgraded to a full practice on Friday after being held out of the first two practices of the week entirely. Commanders coach Dan Quinn also seemed to indicate on Friday that JCM would be good to go. Chris Rodriguez led the Commanders with 11 carries last week. Bill saw just eight. The ankle issue makes it even less likely that he sees a role change in Week 4. As nothing more than a change-of-pace back, JCM is an RB4 for heading into his date with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9052-d95b-addb-f85677c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Vikings “at least considered” signing Aaron Rodgers in the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9059-dca3-a9fb-bdd959140000</link>
      <description>Pelissero added, “But they pretty quickly decided and informed Rodgers that they were rolling with J.J. McCarthy.” Rodgers was likely interested in playing for Minnesota as the starter while the Vikings could only commit to a camp battle between him and their No. 10 overall pick from 2024. The team ultimately signed Carson Wentz to be McCarthy’s backup. Wentz is now the team’s starter with McCarthy sidelined because of an ankle injury. It’s a long season, but Pelissero’s report is a reminder that the Vikings were doing their due diligence on other quarterbacks even with McCarthy penciled in as the starter. If Wentz plays well during his interim gig, it’s not outlandish to think he could remain the starter even once McCarthy is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9059-dca3-a9fb-bdd959140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Isaiah Likely (foot) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9057-dca3-a9fb-bddfc2410000</link>
      <description>Likely is officially listed as questionable, but all signs point toward him making his 2025 debut. He was a full participant in Friday’s practice to close the week. Likely suffered a foot injury at the start of training camp and has been working his way back from the injury for roughly two months. His role in his first game back could be small at first, but the Ravens talked him up all summer and will likely make him an even bigger part of the offense this year once he is up to speed. For Week 4, Likely is a high-risk TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9057-dca3-a9fb-bddfc2410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports D’Andre Swift (hip) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9060-d95b-addb-f866c5400000</link>
      <description>Swift was limited in all three practices this week before being listed as questionable. He saw the same practice routine last week and suited up without any issues. We expect the same today. Swift has at least 15 touches in every game this year. Even with his efficiency in the basement, Swift’s volume makes him a must-start RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9060-d95b-addb-f866c5400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports teams are monitoring Seahawks CB Riq Woolen “as a possible trade target by the deadline.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9075-deb6-a7fd-d3ff63570000</link>
      <description>Woolen broke out as a rookie with 16 pass breakups and six interceptions. He defended double-digit passes in each of the next two years, though Pro Football Focus has charted him with declining coverage grades over the past two seasons. Woolen is on the final year of his current deal and is a candidate to walk in free agency. The Seahawks will likely field offers for the young corner if they can get something for him via trade during the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9075-deb6-a7fd-d3ff63570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Falcons OC Zac Robinson “is expected to be on the very short list” of names for Oklahoma State’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9086-dca3-a9fb-bd9f05e50000</link>
      <description>OSU just fired Mike Gundy in the middle of his 21st season as the team’s head coach. Robinson spent five years at Oklahoma State and was the team’s starting quarterback for three seasons. The connection between Robinson and OSU could also offer a mutual parting of ways for him and the Falcons. Atlanta is currently 1-2 with an offense that ranks 31st in points per game. Robinson will have plenty of time to prepare for his head coaching interviews if Michael Penix and the offense don’t turn things around soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9086-dca3-a9fb-bd9f05e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RT Brian O’Neil (knee) is questionable to return in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9090-dca3-a9fb-bd9906790000</link>
      <description>O’Neill went down in the first quarter while on field goal protection duties. He was helped off the field by trainers and immediately left for the locker room. O’Neill looks unlikely to return, putting the Vikings down two starting offensive linemen for Week 4. Justin Skule has taken his place in the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9090-dca3-a9fb-bd9906790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Derek Stingley Jr. (oblique) is “set to play” in Week 4 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90b9-d95b-addb-f8ff211b0000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Stingley is “pushing to play.” He will go through warmups before the team makes a final decision on his status, but it sounds like he is at least on the right side of questionable. Stingley will be tasked with covering Calvin Ridley for much of today’s game. Already struggling to put together usable box scores, Ridley will fall into the WR3 ranks for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90b9-d95b-addb-f8ff211b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
