<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Commanders and offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury mutually parted ways.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-943e-d56e-afff-f6fee1750000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury didn’t have much chance of making it to a third season at the head of Washington’s offense after the team collapsed in 2025 with Jayden Daniels missing much of the regular season with multiple injuries. Pelissero claims Kingsbury, the former Cardinals head coach, “has head coaching interest and otherwise will have multiple OC options.” Washington’s offense in 2025 was somehow 16th in EPA per play despite Daniels’ injuries (and his poor play when healthy). They were ninth in offensive success rate and 12th in yards per play, ahead of postseason teams like the Broncos, Panthers, Eagles, Chargers, Jaguars, and Steelers. The Commanders will likely hire an OC with experience getting the most out of duel-threat quarterbacks like Daniels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-943e-d56e-afff-f6fee1750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders fired defensive coordinator Joe Whitt, Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9447-d56e-afff-f6efeff50000</link>
      <description>The Commanders also parted ways with offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury after a disastrous 2025 season. Whitt, coaching one of the least talented defenses in the NFL, saw his unit get run over on the ground and through the air. Only three defenses gave up more yards per play, and only the Cardinals allowed more first downs in 2025. Washington allowed the second highest EPA per play under Whitt in 2025, and a mere three teams gave up a higher passing success rate. A first-time defensive coordinator in Washington, Whitt is not a sure thing to land another DC job in the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9447-d56e-afff-f6efeff50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Giants and Titans are expected to interview former Commanders offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-944d-d968-a19b-dcfdbf020000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury’s work with young quarterbacks is certainly a selling point for both the Giants and Titans after Kingsbury’s success with Jayden Daniels in 2024. Kingsbury’s Washington offense was surprisingly efficient in 2025 despite the team missing Daniels for much of the regular season. Washington’s offense in 2025 was somehow 16th in EPA per play. They were ninth in offensive success rate and 12th in yards per play, ahead of postseason teams like the Broncos, Panthers, Eagles, Chargers, Jaguars, and Steelers. Kingsbury would be a boon for either Jaxson Dart or Cam Ward in 2026 and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-944d-d968-a19b-dcfdbf020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Field Yates reports the Falcons and QB Kirk Cousins agreed to a “modified” final two years of Cousins’ contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-945e-dc7a-af9b-dfff39e30000</link>
      <description>The adjustments mean Cousins could stick around Atlanta for another year or two depending on what the Falcons want to do at the QB position in 2026 and beyond. Cousins, 37, showed signs of life in the season’s final month after Michael Penix was placed on injured reserve with a knee injury. He had multiple touchdowns in three of his final four games and had two games of more than 230 passing yards in the run-first Falcons offense. The contract modification could also make Cousins a trade candidate if the Falcons choose to stick with Penix as the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-945e-dc7a-af9b-dfff39e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos defensive coordinator Vance Joseph is expected to interview with the Giants, Raiders, Titans, and Cardinals for those teams’ head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9470-d56e-afff-f6f8f2570000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter confirmed these teams’ interest in Joseph after he coached one of the NFL’s most dominant defenses in recent memory. Over the past two seasons the Broncos have allowed the league’s lowest offensive success rate and the third lowest EPA per play. Joseph would look to revamp the defenses of any one of these teams; all of them rank among the NFL’s worst units.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9470-d56e-afff-f6f8f2570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals CB Cam Taylor-Britt was sentenced to five days in jail after pleading guilty to traffic charges.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9475-d56e-afff-f6fdf3540000</link>
      <description>Taylor-Britt, who in late November was placed on injured reserve with a foot injury, pleaded guilty to reckless driving and an unclassified no-license charge stemming from an incident in September, according to media reports. His sentence is expected to start immediately. Taylor-Britt, 26, selected by the Bengals in the second round of the 2022 NFL draft, has seven interceptions over 47 games in the NFL. It’s unclear if the team or the league will take action against him for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9475-d56e-afff-f6fdf3540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested permission to interview 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams for their “president of football” position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9483-d56e-afff-f6ebe1cb0000</link>
      <description>“President of football” being a very silly term aside, reporters have made it clear that the Falcons want to check the box on this job before they get to their GM and head-coaching vacancies. Williams has already been requested for the Dolphins GM position and was a finalist for the Jaguars GM position last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9483-d56e-afff-f6ebe1cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets coach Aaron Glenn, asked if Justin Fields would be back in 2026, said “he’s under contract.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9488-d35e-a1bf-d5ca02c50000</link>
      <description>So, probably not then. Fields enters year two of a two-year contract as either a trade possibility or a candidate for release. The trade would save more cap space for the Jets, so we’d expect them to pursue that avenue. Fields would still be a fairly good backup quarterback option for most teams even if he hasn’t delivered great results as a starter. The 2021 first-rounder turns 27 in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9488-d35e-a1bf-d5ca02c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said he doesn’t anticipate any changes to his coaching staff in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-948c-d968-a19b-dcfd73510000</link>
      <description>In other words, embattled DC Al Golden has survived. This seemed impossible in November, when the Bengals were putting up numbers that generated WOAT discussion in the field of defensive performance. Things did turn around a bit towards the end of the season. We can’t say we’re surprised that the Bengals retained Golden, because they are reluctant to make major changes to a fault, but it is definitely a bold move by Taylor to attach his coaching future to what happened to this defense in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-948c-d968-a19b-dcfd73510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs waived QB Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9493-d968-a19b-dcf37d230000</link>
      <description>Buechele was signed off the Bills practice squad ahead of Week 18 and completed 7-of-14 passes for 88 yards against the Raiders in a game that neither team seemed to want to win. His reward was being waived. The Chiefs also signed LB Kam Arnold, DT Marcus Harris, WR Jimmy Holiday and T Matt Waletzko to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9493-d968-a19b-dcf37d230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
