<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 2-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Vikings Week 10 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6acc-d45b-affe-7fde3e8f0000</link>
      <description>In a game that saw J.J. McCarthy drop back 47 times, Hockenson somehow still only managed to see two targets. It’s been a disappointing season for the veteran tight end, who entered the day sporting a 31-241-2 line on 39 targets. The volume hasn’t been there for Hockenson all season, and the poor quarterback play only amplifies that issue. Fantasy managers shouldn’t view him as anything more than a TE2 in Week 11 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6acc-d45b-affe-7fde3e8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed nine times for 53 yards in the Bucs’ Week 10 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ace-d673-a39e-eedf759c0000</link>
      <description>Tucker “added” a -2 yard reception. Tucker out-gained Rachaad White on the ground for the second consecutive week, though White narrowly got him in the yards from scrimmage department. White also handled 71 percent of the Bucs’ snaps to just 33 for Tucker. 24-year-old Tucker has taken on a greater “real life” role as the Bucs wait out Bucky Irving’s endless absence, but he is not coming particularly close to translating it to priority FLEX value. Even if Irving remains sidelined for next week’s potential Bills shootout, we will likely rank Tucker outside the top 36 backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ace-d673-a39e-eedf759c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad0-d673-a39e-eed118fb0000</link>
      <description>Bateman’s first target of the day came in the third quarter when Lamar Jackson tried to connect with him in the end zone. Jackson came back to Bateman on the following play, which resulted in a 10-yard gain that fell just inches short of the end zone. It continues to be a forgettable season for Bateman, who has gone for 13 or fewer yards in four of his last five games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad0-d673-a39e-eed118fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 15-of-21 passes for 173 yards, two touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Dolphins’ 30-13, Week 10 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ac8-d673-a39e-eed98a500000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa locked in on Jaylen Waddle in this game, peppering him with high-value targets. One of those attempts resulted in a 38-yard score over the top of the Buffalo defense. Two of his deep shots to Waddle, however, were easily intercepted by the Bills. Tua didn’t seem to care how many defenders were draped over Waddle. As long as his favorite target was downfield, Tua was comfortable giving him a shot at the big play. With Miami’s defense shutting down Josh Allen, the risky throws didn’t cost Tagovailoa in the long-run. They did allow him to reclaim the league lead in interceptions. Tua is up to 13 picks on the year. He will need to cut back on the mistakes if the Dolphins want to stay hot against the Commanders next week. Tagovailoa will be a low-end QB2 for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ac8-d673-a39e-eed98a500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington caught 3-of-7 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 10 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad0-d1e7-a1fa-7afa236f0000</link>
      <description>He added a punt return touchdown to help you out, staking the Jaguars to a 17-0 lead. Washington led the Jacksonville receivers in snaps with 54, as well as targets, and the toe-tap touchdown in the back of the end zone was incredibly impressive as he had to drag his foot back into the end zone. Washington is probably no more than a WR4 next week against the Chargers with Jakobi Meyers getting more than a few days to learn the offense. But he is one of the few that Trevor Lawrence actually trusts right now, and that is worth something.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad0-d1e7-a1fa-7afa236f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy had 14 rushes for 71 yards in the Giants’ Week 10 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad2-d713-ad9e-6ed6dbc50000</link>
      <description>Devin Singletary, after leading the New York backfield in Week 9 against the 49ers, saw eight carries and ran fewer routes from Tracy, though he managed three catches to zero grabs for Tracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad2-d713-ad9e-6ed6dbc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Mundt caught 1-of-2 targets for 21 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 10 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad3-d713-ad9e-6ed7911a0000</link>
      <description>He broke a tackle from Myles Bryant on his lone reception and found a first down. Neither Hunter Long nor Brenton Strange should feel very threatened when they return from injury. Obviously, don’t use Mundt in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad3-d713-ad9e-6ed7911a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 9-of-12 targets for 82 yards in the Bucs’ Week 10 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad4-d673-a39e-eed59c780000</link>
      <description>Otton’s nine receptions matched a career high and give him 35 on the season. That includes 25 over the past four weeks. It’s put Otton on the low-end TE1 radar, a ranking he can probably live up to in Week 11 as the Bucs will be tasked with matching points with the Bills on the road.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad4-d673-a39e-eed59c780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown failed to catch his only target in the Jaguars’ Week 10 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ac2-d45b-affe-7fd63f5d0000</link>
      <description>Weird one. Brown managed just 23 targets as Tim Patrick (not targeted) was the clear No. 2 receiver. We haven’t seen anything that suggested it was injury-related — perhaps the Jaguars eased him in after his concussion — but there’s no need to hold someone playing behind Tim Patrick in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ac2-d45b-affe-7fd63f5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely caught 2-of-5 targets for 17 yards in the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad2-d713-ad9e-6ed652610000</link>
      <description>The 27 points the Ravens scored in this one don’t tell the full story of how the offense struggled in the first half. The Vikings defense bottled up the Ravens for much of the afternoon, holding them to just 4.9 yards per play while keeping every pass-catcher not named Zay Flowers in check. Likely’s longest game came on an 11-yard pass that helped set up a Tyler Loop field goal in the third quarter, but there was nothing to get excited about here. The five targets he saw were a new season-high, but fantasy managers shouldn’t bank on this in Week 11 against the Browns. Likely profiles as a boom-or-bust TE2 next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ad2-d713-ad9e-6ed652610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
