<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed WR Mecole Hardman to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee58-dbe3-a9bb-fe5be04e0000</link>
      <description>Hardman was waived at last cuts but decided that staying with the Packers made sense. The 27-year-old will likely be elevated in Week 1 if Jayden Reed’s injury is as serious as it seems. Also joining the Packers practice squad are: QB Clayton Tune, RB Israel Abanikanda, DL Deslin Alexandre, DB Johnathan Baldwin, T Brant Banks, DL James Ester, LB Jamon Johnson, K Mark McNamee, DL Arron Mosby, WR Isaiah Neyor, WR Will Sheppard, DB Jaylin Simpson, and LB Kristian Welch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee58-dbe3-a9bb-fe5be04e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed RB Jeff Wilson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee5f-dbe3-a9bb-fe5fbc2f0000</link>
      <description>With Brian Robinson now in San Francisco, Wilson probably felt better about his chances of being elevated off Miami’s practice squad. The Dolphins also signed TE Greg Dulcich, CB BJ Adams, CB Cornell Armstrong, LB Quinton Bell, OL Braeden Daniels, WR AJ Henning, DT Alex Huntley, LB Derrick McLendon, K Riley Patterson, OL Josh Priebe, TE Hayden Rucci, S John Saunders Jr., TE Theo Wease Jr., S Jordan Colbert to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee5f-dbe3-a9bb-fe5fbc2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed QB Will Grier to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee69-d332-a1fd-fe7f7a580000</link>
      <description>The usual. Grier spent all of 2022 and most of 2024 with the Cowboys practice squad. He’s back to ride again. Joining him on the Dallas practice squad are: LB Justin Barron, WR Jalen Brooks, DT Earnest Brown, G Saahdiq Charles, T Geron Christian, S Alijah Clark, WR Jalen Cropper, RB Malik Davis, TE Rivaldo Fairweather, TE Princeton Fant, CB Kemon Hall, WR Traeshon Holden, LB Buddy Johnson and CB Robert Rochell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee69-d332-a1fd-fe7f7a580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed WR Tyler Scott to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0ae-dbe3-a9bb-f0ff3e660000</link>
      <description>The former Bears fourth-rounder will look to re-establish himself in what is a stacked Colts receiver room. Also joining the Colts practice squad are: LB Austin Ajiake, RB Ulysses Bentley IV, RB Khalil Herbert, T Marcellus Johnson, WR Tyler Kahmann, CB Chris Lammons, TE Maximilian Mang, DL Earnest Brown, TE Sean McKeon, DE Durrell Nchami, WR Coleman Owen, G Josh Sills, DT Josh Tupou, C Mose Vavao and S Trey Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0ae-dbe3-a9bb-f0ff3e660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said the “plan is to split those up a little bit and distribute” when asked about Kyren Williams’ workload on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0b6-d332-a1fd-f6b625b00000</link>
      <description>“He’s made of all the right stuff. He’s done everything we’ve asked of him, not that we even have to ask too much of him because he’s wired the right way. I thought he had a good preseason. Obviously, we left him out of that third game right there. He’s had a really good training camp. He’ll get his opportunities come Week 1,” LaFleur said about the second-year back from Michigan. Corum probably doesn’t have standalone value at the start of the season, and coaches talk about splitting reps more evenly all the time. But it’s worth monitoring Corum’s workload early in the season to see if he can make a real dent in Kyren Williams’ fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0b6-d332-a1fd-f6b625b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Tyreek Hill (oblique) “looks great” for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f12b-dbe3-a9bb-f17bba950000</link>
      <description>Hill has missed quite a bit of training camp and, obviously, didn’t play in the preseason. The team has been cautious with him after he suffered an oblique injury and will “do some stuff” today. It sounds like he’ll be on the injury report ahead of Week 1, but that we shouldn’t expect him to have problems playing barring a setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f12b-dbe3-a9bb-f17bba950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Jaylen Wright (leg) had surgery and could be back “Septemberish.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f13a-de13-afdc-f7fbd8450000</link>
      <description>Sounds like Ollie Gordon will get the backup work behind Devon Achane — assuming Achane is able to play in Week 1 — for most of the first month of the season. Jeff Wilson was signed to the practice squad. McDaniel noted that Wright is not out for the season, but given the timeline, it wouldn’t be surprising if Wright was placed on injured reserve before the start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f13a-de13-afdc-f7fbd8450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed WR Eric Ezukanma to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f13d-de13-afdc-f7ff96050000</link>
      <description>After three years with the Dolphins that yielded just five total games on the active roster, Ezukanma has taken his talents to Atlantic Beach. Joining Ezukanma on Jacksonville’s practice squad are: WR Chandler Brayboy, OL Jerome Carvin, LB Branson Combs, QB Seth Henigan, TE Patrick Herbert, RB Ja’Quinden Jackson, OL Ricky Lee, CB Keni-H Lovely, TE Quintin Morris, DB Jabbar Muhammad, DL Keivie Rose, DB Cam’Ron Silmon-Craig, WR Dorian Singer, OL Sal Wormley and DL Matt Dickerson. It’s a strong collection of names and we definitely didn’t do this blurb just to point out that Keni-H Lovely is a great manga.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f13d-de13-afdc-f7ff96050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent LB Kyrir White visited the Colts on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f144-de13-afdc-f7cf9b960000</link>
      <description>White, who started all 17 games for the Cardinals last year and finished with 137 combined tackles, is one of the more surprising names still on the free-agent market. With the Colts clearly looking for outside help at linebacker, it makes a lot of sense for them to sniff around the veteran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f144-de13-afdc-f7cf9b960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f154-de13-afdc-f7dfa1130000</link>
      <description>It’s his first practice since July 24. That’s not a guarantee that he suits up in Week 1 and he’s likely to be on the injury report next week, but it’s certainly optimistic news about his availability going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f154-de13-afdc-f7dfa1130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
