<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) is questionable for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b96-deb6-a7fd-dbdf1d570000</link>
      <description>Pearsall exited Sunday’s game against the Jaguars with a knee injury and did not return. He was estimated to have missed practice this week ahead of the Niners’ Thursday night clash with the Rams. Fantasy managers should prepare for be without Pearsall, who’s leading the 49ers in both targets and air yards. His absence would be a major hit to Brock Purdy if he’s able to play through a nagging toe injury that he aggravated on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b96-deb6-a7fd-dbdf1d570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OC Nick Holz said he expects TE Gunnar Helm’s “opportunities to increase.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b98-dca3-a9fb-bf99e2490000</link>
      <description>This isn’t going to do a major number on most of your fantasy squads, but an increase in Helm’s reps would likely render Chig Okonkwo unplayable in the TE2 sphere. Helm has 92 snaps in four weeks and Okonkwo is coming off a season-low 35 snaps against the Texans in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b98-dca3-a9fb-bf99e2490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed OL Jarrett Kingston off the Panthers practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba1-d95b-addb-fbe7f12e0000</link>
      <description>Kingston will replace Cam Robinson on the active roster. The 2024 sixth-rounder was active for seven games with the Panthers last year, but had just one offensive snap. It means he has less negative NFL tape in 2024-2025 than most Texans offensive linemen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba1-d95b-addb-fbe7f12e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said LB Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) and Brian O’Neill (knee) won’t practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba8-d95b-addb-fbeee1a70000</link>
      <description>It would appear to be implicit in that statement that will neither will play in Week 5 against the Browns, though it wasn’t explicitly said. O’Connell said IR is not a consideration for O’Neill and that the team is “evaluating every avenue and all options to get” Van Ginkel “100%.” Reading between the lines, it seems like an IR stint is still in play for Van Ginkel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba8-d95b-addb-fbeee1a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Baltimore Sun’s Brian Wacker reports Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is “likely” to miss Week 5’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bb5-d95b-addb-fbf726db0000</link>
      <description>He adds per one of his sources that given “the nature of the injury, he also could be out for up to 2-3 weeks.” The Ravens have a Week 7 bye, but it sounds like Jackson-reliant fantasy managers should be going ahead with waiver claims on the idea that Jackson won’t play in Week 5 and perhaps Week 6 as well. We’re sure this will be one of several Lamar updates this week unless John Harbaugh rules him out early on Wednesday. Cooper Rush would take over as the starter at quarterback if Jackson were to be sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bb5-d95b-addb-fbf726db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jets RB Braelon Allen (knee) suffered and MCL sprain and will likely land on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bc2-d95b-addb-fbc6c4270000</link>
      <description>Isaiah Davis will likely absorb some snaps, but this should be great news for Breece Hall-reliant managers as Allen’s goal-line/early-down role would seem to fit Hall much better than Davis. Allen is still looking at different opinions on the injury, meaning we’ll probably get an update with a firm timetable when he’s actually placed on injured reserve. For the next few weeks at least, though, Hall is likely to get an uptick in usage that should put him in a good place to showcase his skills ahead of the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bc2-d95b-addb-fbc6c4270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (undisclosed) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bd2-d95b-addb-fbd64c160000</link>
      <description>Not normally a noteworthy bit of information, Benson’s status is interesting because the Cardinals signed Michael Carter to their active roster on Monday. Theo Mackie of the Arizona Republic speculates that the Cardinals could turn to Carter as their lead back if Benson is hurt, and coach Jonathan Gannon would give only a vague “taking it day by day” update on Benson. This is a bit of an odd injury update timing since Arizona played on Thursday Night, but it’s certainly possible that Benson pops up on the injury report ahead of Week 5. Carter would seem to be the back to roster in what is shaping up to be a dream matchup against a beleagured Titans unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bd2-d95b-addb-fbd64c160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Detroit will designate Alim McNeill (PUP/knee) to return this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bdd-deb6-a7fd-dbdf07820000</link>
      <description>McNeill’s Week 15 ACL tear is healing well and the Lions are reportedly targeting a Week 7 or Week 8 return for their star interior player. McNeill had 8.5 sacks over the past two seasons and carried PFF grades of 86.8 and 79.6. He’ll be a big help for Detroit when he comes off the PUP list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bdd-deb6-a7fd-dbdf07820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR DeMario Douglas played just eight snaps in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9be4-d95b-addb-fbe616f80000</link>
      <description>We didn’t blurb it over the weekend, but with Stefon Diggs being unchained early in the game, Douglas’ role in New England’s offense was all but kaput. This may be rock bottom and we’d anticipate Douglas being out there more in a game script where the Patriots are actually trying to pass, but Douglas is very droppable in most leagues if Diggs is going to be New England’s main slot receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9be4-d95b-addb-fbe616f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed WR Cedrick Wilson off the Saints practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bf9-d6e9-af9d-9bf96d750000</link>
      <description>Wilson is no target threat at this stage of his career, which is good news for Jaylen Waddle, Malik Washington, and Nick Westbrook-Ikhine. Those three appear to be a the top of the pecking order in a post-Tyreek Hill Dolphins offense. Westbrook-Ikhine played the majority of the outside snaps in Hill’s absence in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bf9-d6e9-af9d-9bf96d750000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
