<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins QB Tua Tagovailoa said he is open to a “fresh start” elsewhere in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f8b-d56e-afff-efeb2f870000</link>
      <description>“That would be dope. I would be good with it,” Tagovailoa continued, and even confirmed to reporters that he understood that meant a fresh start with a different team. Tagovailoa’s contract appears all but unmovable, and the best-case scenario for him to escape would probably be a post-June 1 release ala Russell Wilson’s exit with the Broncos. This probably isn’t something that will resolve in a hurry, but you rarely hear quarterbacks so eager to leave their current organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f8b-d56e-afff-efeb2f870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested permission to interview Chiefs OC Matt Nagy for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f95-d56e-afff-effdaab20000</link>
      <description>Nagy has obvious connections to the job as Titans GM Mike Borgonzi had been with Nagy in Kansas City before taking over in the Titans’ GM role. It’s hard for us to find good things to say about Nagy given how the Chiefs offense appeared to meaningfully regress as soon as he took over for Eric Bieniemy as offensive coordinator — that doesn’t necessarily mean it’s Nagy’s fault, as Tyreek Hill also left around the same time, but it’s also hard to point to Nagy’s work the last two years as something that should guarantee him interviews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f95-d56e-afff-effdaab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested to interview Broncos DC Vance Joseph for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f99-d56e-afff-eff9d8a30000</link>
      <description>Joseph interviewed with the Jets and was also requested by the Bears last offseason. Denver’s defense slipped a bit in 2025, though it also missed Pat Surtain for several games and dealt with other normal attrition issues. He appears to be one of the hottest candidates of the 2025 offseason and we expect him to get plenty of interviews this cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f99-d56e-afff-eff9d8a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f9c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd6590000</link>
      <description>Expected to draw plenty of interest this cycle after a breakout 2025 season while leading Seattle’s offense to a 10th place finish in DVOA with Sam Darnold at quarterback, Kubiak gets his first interview request from the Falcons. Kubiak, the son of former NFL head coach Gary Kubiak, had previously worked as Saints OC in 2024 and 49ers passing game coordinator in 2023. He’d establish a return to the Shanaclan ways in Atlanta if he were to accept this job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f9c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd6590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested to interview Chiefs DC Steve Spagnuolo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fb7-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe32a0000</link>
      <description>The former Rams head coach went a ghastly 10-38 in his three years at the helm from 2009-2011, but is one of the most-respected defensive coordinators in the league. It’s certainly possible that he could draw multiple interviews this cycle as he was connected to the Giants gig — the place that launched his original HC gig — in November. Spagnuolo’s defense suffered a down year as they just couldn’t muster enough pass rush in 2025, but the Chiefs have finished in the top 10 in points allowed in six of the last seven seasons. He also has an easy link to Titans GM Mike Borgonzi, who used to work in the Chiefs front office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fb7-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe32a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested permission to interview Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fbc-d968-a19b-dffd80b40000</link>
      <description>One of four requests on the day for the Titans, Anarumo was a finalist for the Cardinals job in 2023 when it went to Jonathan Gannon, but saw only defensive coordinator requests last offseason after he was fired. The Colts defense was more scrappy than terrific in 2025 — though they dealt with plenty of injuries at the cornerback position that helps explain some of that — but NFL decision-makers continue to be enamored with Anarumo anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fbc-d968-a19b-dffd80b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said LB Tatum Bethune (groin) is out for the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fc7-dc7a-af9b-cfff2fb00000</link>
      <description>Bethune, a 2024 seventh-rounder, had 94 tackles and four passes defensed in eight starts for the 49ers after taking over for Fred Warner in the middle of Week 6’s loss to the Buccaneers. He figures to be in line for a real defensive role with the 49ers again next season. Eric Kendricks will man the middle for the 49ers in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fc7-dc7a-af9b-cfff2fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested to interview Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fcb-d35e-a1bf-cfcb234f0000</link>
      <description>A finalist for the Saints job last year, as well as both the Falcons and Commanders the year before, Weaver is apparently a great interview. The Dolphins defense arguably overperformed its talent level the last few years, but wasn’t exactly regarded as a top-of-the-league force. His only other experience as a defensive play-caller came with the disastrous 2020 Texans, though he oversaw the development of some great players as defensive line coach for the Texans and Ravens over the past decade. Weaver figures to get plenty of interview requests again this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fcb-d35e-a1bf-cfcb234f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Mattison (neck) revealed he needed emergency surgery for a fractured neck.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fdc-d968-a19b-dffd41c80000</link>
      <description>Mattison hopes to play again but is “still recovering.” The 28-year-old, an impending free agent, likely won’t be on radars for the first wave of free agency. Once he’s cleared to play, it’s possible he finds work ahead of training camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fdc-d968-a19b-dffd41c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested permission to interview Eagles Assistant GM Alec Halaby for their GM vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff2-dc7a-af9b-cfff8ba40000</link>
      <description>They also requested permission to talk to Packers vice president of player personnel Jon-Eric Sullivan, 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams, 49ers vice president of player personnel Tariq Ahmad, and Rams assistant GM John McKay. The fact that there are two 49ers-linked candidates on that list is probably good news for Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel on Black Monday. Halaby had interview requests from the Panthers and Jets the past two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff2-dc7a-af9b-cfff8ba40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
