<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:02:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers will interview Eagles defensive backs coach Christian Parker for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d8fc-d35e-a1bf-ddfee65b0000</link>
      <description>Parker will interview with the Cowboys on Wednesday before heading straight to Green Bay to interview for the same defensive coordinator position. Viewed as a “rising star” in many inner circles, Parker appears to have a good chance at his first defensive coordinator gig at the NFL level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d8fc-d35e-a1bf-ddfee65b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired former 49ers DC and Jets HC Robert Saleh as head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d9cc-d56e-afff-ffec3be00000</link>
      <description>Another domino falls in the 2026 coaching carousel as Saleh gets his second crack at head coaching duties, this time with the Titans. Long heralded for his aggressive and unrelenting defensive tendencies, Saleh will look to improve upon his .357 career win rate as a head coach after a tumultuous tenure in New York after peaking at a 7-10 record in 2022 and 2023. He steps into a near full rebuild after the Titans unloaded numerous key pieces at the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d9cc-d56e-afff-ffec3be00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Steelers on Wednesday will interview former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-db79-d56e-afff-fff97cee0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy had interviewed with the Titans, who filled their head coaching vacancy on Tuesday by hiring former 49ers defensive coordinator Robert Saleh. McCarthy, who was raised in the Pittsburgh area, would seem to be a natural fit for the Steelers as they look to keep their postseason streak alive even if they are not Super Bowl contenders. McCarthy has shown he can do just that during his stints in Green Bay and Dallas. McCarthy has won 61 percent of his games over 18 years as an NFL head coach. The Steelers are reportedly open to McCarthy’s former QB Aaron Rodgers returning in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-db79-d56e-afff-fff97cee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers requested an interview with Vikings defensive backs coach Daronte Jones for the team’s defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbb4-d35e-a1bf-dff6eb1f0000</link>
      <description>Jones is a popular name on the coaching circuit this month. After coaching a Minnesota secondary that allowed the fewest pass yards per game in 2025 (159) along with the NFL’s third lowest drop back success rate, Jones has landed interviews with the Giants and Jets for their defensive coordinator openings. The Packers are widely expected to interview many candidates to fill their DC vacancy after the Dolphins hired Jeff Hafley as their head coach this week. Jones, 47, would take over a Green Bay defense that gave up the league’s tenth highest EPA per play in 2025 if he’s hired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbb4-d35e-a1bf-dff6eb1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe believes Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley will prioritize physicality and toughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said the Dolphins under Hafley will transition from a roster predicated on speed to one based on size and toughness. The team will also look to emulate the Packers in drafting and developing players instead of making splash signings in free agency, Wolfe said. Hafley, 46, who served as Green Bay’s defensive coordinator over the past two seasons, will look to revamp a Miami defense that last year allowed the NFL’s second highest drop back success rate and the ninth highest rushing success rate. Look for the Dolphins to invest heavily in defensive players in the 2026 NFL Draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens will interview Broncos special teams coordinator Darren Rizzi for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbea-dc7a-af9b-dfffdf650000</link>
      <description>Rizzi, a longtime in special teams coordinator in New Orleans before coming to the Broncos in 2025, reportedly impressed during interviews for the Giants head coaching vacancy and could be a dark horse to take over as Baltimore’s head coach after the Ravens parted ways with longtime coach John Harbaugh, who, like Rizzi, was a special teams coordinator before getting the top job in Baltimore. Rizzi’s Denver special teams unit has been among the league’s best this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbea-dc7a-af9b-dfffdf650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC WGRZ’s Vic Carruci reports the firing of Bills head coach Sean McDermott is “being met with skepticism by players who held McDermott in high regard.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc03-d56e-afff-feeb85270000</link>
      <description>McDermott reportedly lost out in a massive power struggle with general manager Brandon Beane, who not only kept his job after assembling a mediocre roster, but was promoted to president of football operations. Beane will oversee the evaluation and hiring of McDermott’s replacement after nine successful years at the helm. Carruci said that during a meeting held five weeks ago between McDermott, Beane and Bills owner Terry Pegula, “the coach pointed out what the roster lacked to win a Super Bowl. I don’t know the specifics McDermott mentioned, but I’m told neither Beane nor Pegula was pleased with McDermott’s assessment.” Having won the power struggle, Beane will now have the chance to shape the franchise in his image as Josh Allen turns 30 in May.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc03-d56e-afff-feeb85270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connor Hughes reports Giants head coach John Harbaugh is expected “to be aggressive in targeting ex-Ravens in free agency.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc35-d35e-a1bf-ddf7af2a0000</link>
      <description>After coaching the Ravens for 18 years, it’s no surprise Harbaugh would try to get the band back together in New York. That could include C Tyler Linderbaum, who played under Harbaugh in Baltimore from 2022 to 2025. Linderbaum, 26, is an unrestricted free agent this offseason and a potential upgrade for a Giants offensive line that struggled throughout 2025. Harbaugh could also pursue Patrick Ricard and Isaiah Likely in free agency. Harbaugh could also bring in coaches he had during his time in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc35-d35e-a1bf-ddf7af2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud said he’s “still getting adjusted to” the team’s offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</link>
      <description>Stroud said after the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots that “there are no excuses” for throwing four interceptions on 47 attempts against New England, but that he was still getting comfortable in an offensive scheme installed by first-year offensive coordinator Nick Caley. Stroud in 2025 completed 64.5 percent of his passes for 3,041 yards and 19 touchdowns with eight interceptions, improving in most categories after a letdown of a 2024 season following his outstanding 2023 rookie campaign. The Texans will have to make a decision on Stroud’s fifth-year contract option by May 1, and head coach DeMeco Ryans said after the team’s postseason loss that he would not discuss the team’s plans for Stroud, who turns 25 in October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the probable cause trespassing charges against Vikings WR Jordan Addison won’t be filed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</link>
      <description>Addison, who was arrested last week, “will prepare for the filing of a civil claim arising from the alleged wrongful arrest,” according to Garafolo. “As Mr. Addison’s agent has advised, from the very outset of this incident and arrest, Mr. Addison committed no legal wrong doing,” Addison’s attorney said in a statement. “We are thrilled that the truth was finally revealed and this poor man’s name was not besmirched any longer. I am thankful we were able to bring this to light as quickly as possible.” Addison has had other run-ins with the law, including a DUI, which led to a suspension. The Vikings will have to decide this offseason on extending a fifth-year option or beginning contract talks with Addison, entering his fourth season in the league in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
