<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:02:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Flournoy caught 9-of-13 targets for 115 yards and one touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 14 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed10-d77b-adfa-ef9396dc0000</link>
      <description>Flournoy now has two 100-yard performances on his resumé this season. The second-year receiver saw nine of his 13 targets come in the second half with CeeDee Lamb (concussion) sidelined, and was on the receiving end of the only passing touchdown by Cowboys. Flournoy was the beneficiary of a broken coverage by the Lions when safety Brian Branch failed to provide help in the secondary for corner Amik Robertson. The end result was an uncontested 42-yard touchdown to give Flournoy his third receiving touchdown of the season. Flournoy could have some upside as a WR3/WR4 in Week 15 if Lamb were to miss next week’s game, but he can be left on fantasy benches if Lamb is able to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed10-d77b-adfa-ef9396dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 5-of-9 targets for 37 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 14 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed1a-da9b-a9bf-ff1f3c020000</link>
      <description>Pickens’ nine targets were second only to Ryan Flournoy, who surprised with a team-high 13 targets. The Lions kept the clamps on Pickens for most of the evening, but he had multiple chances at hauling in a long score, with one of those chances being ruined by a defensive pass interference. CeeDee Lamb exited with a concussion in the first half of Thursday’s game. If he is unable to go, Pickens would be firmly in the WR1 conversation for Week 15 against the Vikings. Even if Lamb does play, Pickens would still be a must-start in the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed1a-da9b-a9bf-ff1f3c020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-7 targets for 58 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 14 loss to Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed1f-da9b-a9bf-ff1ff2720000</link>
      <description>It was a rough night for Ferguson, who was flagged for multiple penalties on the day and also lost a fumble in the second quarter. Ferguson did come up with a key two-point conversion in the fourth quarter to cut the Lions’ lead to a field goal, but the Lions would counter with a touchdown of their own five plays later. Ferguson has seen five or more targets in each of his last five games but has just one touchdown over that span. He’ll be a fringe TE1/TE2 in Week 15 when the Cowboys face the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed1f-da9b-a9bf-ff1ff2720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Aubrey made all five of his field goals and one extra point in the Cowboys’ Week 14 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed27-d005-a9bf-fd378d280000</link>
      <description>The only constants in life are death, taxes, and Aubrey knocked down field goals from 50-plus yards. The Cowboys’ kicker will have single-handedly propelled multiple fantasy teams to victory this week when all is said and done thanks in part to his five field goal, which included three makes from 50 or more yards. Aubrey’s longest kick came on a 63-yard try late in the third quarter, which marked his third field goal from 60-plus this season. He remains a weekly must-start for fantasy managers heading into Week 15 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ed27-d005-a9bf-fd378d280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Lions S Brian Branch is believed to have suffered an Achilles injury in Week 14’s win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eeb7-d77b-adfa-eeb7c4a60000</link>
      <description>Pelissero didn’t speculate on the severity of Branch’s Achilles injury, but said the star safety “will have further tests this morning.” We tend to know where things go from here, but we’ll let them play out and hope for the best. Branch was injured in the fourth quarter on a play that took place in the end zone and remained down for several minutes while being tended to by the training staff. He eventually made his way to the sideline with help and was later carted to the locker room. Branch has started all 12 games he’s appeared in this season for the Lions, totaling 75 tackles. 2.5 sacks, and nine pass breakups. Veteran Avonte Maddox is in line to replace Branch while for however long he is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eeb7-d77b-adfa-eeb7c4a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports tests confirmed Lions S Brian Branch suffered a torn Achilles in Week 14’s win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef21-d005-a9bf-ff35e5810000</link>
      <description>The worst was confirmed on Friday, just hours after earlier reports said that the Lions feared an Achilles injury for Branch. The third-year safety will now miss the remainder of the season as he looks to undergo surgery and rehab to be ready in time for the start of next season. Branch appeared in 12 games for the Lions this season, totaling 75 tackles, 2.5 sacks, and nine pass breakups. He will enter 2026 in the final year of his rookie contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef21-d005-a9bf-ff35e5810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports CeeDee Lamb is in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef47-d77b-adfa-efc7c8c80000</link>
      <description>This was expected after Lamb exited Week 14’s game against the Lions with a concussion. Lamb came down hard on his head in the second quarter of Thursday’s game and was ruled out shortly after being evaluated on the sideline. With the injury occurring on a Thursday, Lamb will have some additional time to clear protocol before playing next Sunday night against the Vikings. If he’s unable to go, Ryan Flournoy, who went for 9-115-1 against the Lions, would have some viability as a FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef47-d77b-adfa-efc7c8c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dion Dawkins cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef4d-d77b-adfa-efcf015e0000</link>
      <description>Dawkins was out of the non-contact jersey on Thursday and is now on track to play on Sunday against the Bengals. While Dawkins will be back in action after one game away, head coach Sean McDermott said EDGE Joey Bosa and LB Terrel Bernard would be out in Week 14, while WR Joshua Palmer will be listed as doubtful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef4d-d77b-adfa-efcf015e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Dalton Kincaid (knee/hamstring) will be questionable for Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6a-d8cf-affb-ff6a08430000</link>
      <description>McDermott said he would need to see Kincaid look “functional” to play. It’s hard to know what that means, given Kincaid’s limited status in practice over the last two weeks, but it sounds like the third-year tight end will be truly questionable ahead of Week 14’s game against the Bengals. If he’s not ruled out before Sunday, fantasy managers will want to check Kincaid’s status when inactives are released 90 minutes before kickoff. Dawson Knox would again see the majority of snaps if Kincaid is unable to go, but he shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a boom-or-bust TE2. In addition to Kincaid, McDermott also said RT Spencer Brown (shoulder) would be listed as questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6a-d8cf-affb-ff6a08430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Justin Fields (knee) will be out for Week 14 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6e-d005-a9bf-ff7ef4bb0000</link>
      <description>According to Glenn, the Jets’ backup QB reported knee soreness on Wednesday and will now be ruled out. Rookie UDFA Brady Cook will be elevated from the practice squad this weekend and serve as Tyrod Taylor’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6e-d005-a9bf-ff7ef4bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
