<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed said he “would love to come back” to the Seahawks next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7309-d629-a1bc-f31d28540000</link>
      <description>Shaheed is set to enter free agency this offseason after spending a half-season with the Seahawks. The 27-year-old was traded from the Saints to Seattle at the trade deadline and tallied 15 receptions for 188 yards in nine games for the Seahawks, adding three receptions for 78 yards in the playoffs. He most notably was a return specialist for the team, returning a kick for a touchdown to open the Seahawks’ Divisional Round win over the 49ers. When asked if he would consider a return, Shaheed said, “I kind of want to run it back. We just won the Super Bowl, so, you know, why not?” Though his offensive role was minimalized in Seattle’s offense, Shaheed has value as deep threat and return specialist. Expect him to generate much interest during free agency in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7309-d629-a1bc-f31d28540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Broncos are expected to hire Bills quarterbacks coach Ronald Curry as their wide receivers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7377-d629-a1bc-f37f6a370000</link>
      <description>Curry also interviewed for the Broncos’ offensive coordinator vacancy and now lands in Denver as the wide receivers coach. He spent the past two seasons as the Bills’ quarterbacks coach, working with Josh Allen and company under Joe Brady. Curry previously worked as an offensive assistant under Sean Payton with the Saints earlier in his career, now returning to Payton’s staff to work with Courtland Sutton, Pat Bryant, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7377-d629-a1bc-f37f6a370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson announced he will return for a 14th NFL season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72e5-d042-afbc-7ff714a20000</link>
      <description>Johnson told The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane the news on Thursday morning. The potential Hall of Famer missed the second half of the 2025 season with a Lisfranc injury, though it shouldn’t affect him for the upcoming season. The 2026 season will mark his first without offensive line coach Jeff Stoutland, who stepped down from the role at the end of the year. With Philly’s 2025 season going down as a bit of a dud, 2026 might be a one last ride situation for the veteran tackle. The hope is that a change at offensive coordinator revives the team’s explosive plays on the ground and through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72e5-d042-afbc-7ff714a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Barrows believes the “stars could be aligning” for the 49ers to trade QB Mac Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7738-d89c-a1be-fffff4a60000</link>
      <description>Jones “didn’t just look like a starter in 2025 but someone who could lead an imperfect team.” Per Barrows, Quarterback-needy teams could be hoping that Jones becomes the next “Shanahan reclamation project” after watching Sam Darnold lead the Vikings to a 14-3 record in 2024 and the Seahawks to a Super Bowl victory in 2025. Darnold spent the 2023 season as a 49ers backup. The incoming rookie quarterback class is currently viewed as a thin group, which could spur teams to pursue Jones via a trade rather than rolling the dice on a questionable prospect. Barrows notes that the Dolphins, Cardinals and Vikings “are running Shanahan’s offense or something similar,” and views all three as potentially interested parties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7738-d89c-a1be-fffff4a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears promoted senior director of player personnel Jeff King to assistant general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-776e-d042-afbc-7ffe66920000</link>
      <description>King replaces former Bears assistant general manager and new Falcons general manager Ian Cunningham. Cunningham held his prior role for four seasons. King joined the NFL’s administrative ranks as a Bears scouting intern in 2015, following an eight-year playing career. He served as a pro scout from 2016-2018 before becoming the assistant director of pro scouting in 2019. He became the director of pro scouting in 2021, the co-director of player personnel in 2022 and was promoted to his prior role in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-776e-d042-afbc-7ffe66920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Brian Fleury said Seattle’s “offense will have continuity from 2025,” while implementing a dynamic run game and keeping things quarterback-friendly in the red zone.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7777-d042-afbc-7ff7f1390000</link>
      <description>Fleury’s theoretical ability to run a similar offensive system is ostensibly one reason that the Seahawks hired him. Fleury served as the 49ers’ run game coordinator and tight ends coach last season. Former Seahawks OC and new Raiders head coach Klint Kubiak served as the 49ers’ pass game coordinator in 2023. We can expect to see the Seahawks again feature shifts, motion and play action. Although Fleury has called plays defensively and for special teams, he has never done so offensively. He will do so this season, and he told reporters that he has already begun preparing to execute that assignment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7777-d042-afbc-7ff7f1390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Marquice Williams as their new senior special teams coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-77ac-d89c-a1be-ffff11270000</link>
      <description>Williams served as the Falcons’ special teams coordinator from 2021-2025. He has been coaching in the NFL since 2013, spending time with the Lions (two stints), Bears and Chargers before signing on with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-77ac-d89c-a1be-ffff11270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos re-signed WR Michael Bandy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-77fc-d042-afbc-7ffe8ffa0000</link>
      <description>Bandy, 28, scored his first career touchdown in 2025. Good for him. Bandy typically turns in an explosive play or two in the preseason, but rarely contributes once the calendar shifts from August to September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-77fc-d042-afbc-7ffe8ffa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released LB Amen Ogbongbemiga.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-780e-d990-a1de-7c4ef04e0000</link>
      <description>Ogbongbemiga, 27, spent the last two seasons with the Bears after spending his first three in the NFL with the Chargers. He recorded the most tackles since his 2021 rookie season in 2025 (10) and broke up a pass for the first time in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-780e-d990-a1de-7c4ef04e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns promoted Brandon Lynch to cornerbacks coach and pass game specialist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7815-d629-a1bc-f81d4fce0000</link>
      <description>Lynch has served as the Browns’ cornerbacks coach for the past three seasons. He now adds pass game specialist to his title. Lynch notably interviewed for the Titans’ defensive coordinator vacancy back in 2024, then serving as a member of former Browns DC Jim Schwartz’s staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7815-d629-a1bc-f81d4fce0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
