<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks rule out WR Jake Bobo (concussion) for Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</link>
      <description>Both Bobo and LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) kicked the week off with promising limited practice participation statuses, but they were ultimately unable to get cleared for action. With Bobo out, rookie speedster WR Tory Horton (ankle) should operate as the clear-cut No. 3 wide receiver. Backup WR Dareke Young (hamstring) is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) is questionable to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1baf-dbe3-a9bb-3bff30100000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero implicitly confirms the concern that McCaffrey did indeed suffer a new injury, saying the 49ers’ “opener against Seattle is on Sunday, just three days after the injury” occurred, removing the possibility that this was a precautionary measure due to some sort of muscle irritation. Pelissero previously reported that “alarm bells” are not going off within the 49ers’ facility, but the new injury-related phrasing is hardly comforting. For now, fantasy managers must prepare to be without McCaffrey, while hoping for the best. No. 2 RB Brian Robinson will be a top-18 option if McCaffrey is sidelined for Week 1. No. 3 RB Isaac Guerendo is worth adding in 12-team leagues, where available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1baf-dbe3-a9bb-3bff30100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bc3-de13-afdd-5fcb841c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings will likely operate as the No. 1 wide receiver and No. 2 pass catcher behind George Kittle when the 49ers take on the Seahawks this weekend. With Christian McCaffrey questionable to play due to his calf injury, the 49ers could shift toward a more balanced offensive approach, which would benefit 49ers pass catchers in the stat sheet. Jennings is a WR4 with upside for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bc3-de13-afdd-5fcb841c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Jordan James (finger) is doubtful to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bcf-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf032d0000</link>
      <description>James and WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) were seemingly headed in the right direction, but head coach Kyle Shanahan is often reticent to trust rookies, so maybe the team is just playing it safe with two players who are unlikely to take the field anyway. With Christian McCaffrey (calf) questionable, it’s possible the team chooses to keep James active if McCaffrey is unable to go. James could be stashed on deep-league benches, if need be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bcf-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf032d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) said he is feeling “great,” and that his absence at Friday’s practice has been “blown out of proportion” due to his injury history.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bd1-d332-a1fd-9ff730d40000</link>
      <description>This is somewhat encouraging. When asked about the injury, McCaffrey assured media members that it’s “nothing serious.” If that’s the case, there’s a chance he handles something close to a normal workload against the division rival Seahawks on Sunday. Regardless, fantasy managers should prepare their backup plans in case McCaffrey needs more time to heal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bd1-d332-a1fd-9ff730d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims Jr. (thigh) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bee-d332-a1fd-9ffeb3020000</link>
      <description>Mims is expected to make his debut, operating as the Broncos’ No. 2 wide receiver behind Courtland Sutton. If he can maintain anything close to the elite efficiency and explosiveness he produced in a part-time role last year, he could fit into fantasy lineups as a WR3. The Titans’ secondary is a beatable unit. Consider him an upside FLEX play for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bee-d332-a1fd-9ffeb3020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) for Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bec-dbe3-a9bb-3bff52910000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw suffered two quad injuries this summer and the second one is apparently still an issue. He was sidelined through all three Week 1 practices. The complete lack of participation is concerning, even for his Week 2 availability. Broncos backup DT Malcolm Roach (calf) is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bec-dbe3-a9bb-3bff52910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WRs Hollywood Brown and Tyquan Thornton are expected “to fill the void” left by Rashee Rice (suspension) in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bf6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7c8b00000</link>
      <description>Brown successfully rehabbed a sprained ankle that he injured during training camp while Thornton made a few splash plays in the preseason. Both players are difficult to trust as more than dart throw FLEX options but for those in need of a risk-reward wide receiver, deploying one of Patrick Mahomes’ pass catchers is not a bad idea. Brown is listed as a starter on the Chiefs’ depth chart and should get the opportunity to produce before Thornton, who currently sits among the third-stringers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bf6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7c8b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OG Mekhi Becton (illness) is active for Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c0b-de13-afdd-5ecbb86c0000</link>
      <description>Becton was listed as questionable earlier today, after coming down with a last-minute illness. That Chargers’ right guard will be on the field for Week 1, though. The Chargers declared S RJ Mickens, TE Tucker Fisk, CB Nikko Reed, OLB Kyle Kennard, T Foster Sarell, TE Oronde Gadsden II and DL Naquan Jones inactive for Week 1. Gadsden impressed coaches in training camp but the rookie tight end needs a little more time before he is ready for live action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c0b-de13-afdd-5ecbb86c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Elijah Mitchell is inactive for Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</link>
      <description>Mitchell’s deactivation suggests the Chiefs will roll with Isiah Pacheco, Kareem Hunt and rookie Brashard Smith, who notably took a few first-team reps in preseason play last month. He might be worth stashing on benches before kickoff. The Chiefs also declared WR Jalen Royals (knee), TE Jared Wiley, DT Omarr Norman-Lott, OL Hunter Nourzad and DE Malik Herring inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
