<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers elevated OLB Jason Pierre-Paul ahead of Week 16 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</link>
      <description>The appearance will be the first regular season game for the soon-to-be 37-year-old veteran in a over two years. It’ll come in a must-win, divisional showdown with the Panthers. The two teams play twice in the final three weeks of the regular season to decide who will represent the NFC South in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d91-d35e-a1bf-7dd3b1460000</link>
      <description>The Bears get back one of their defensive leaders after Edmunds missed the previous four contests while on injured reserve. His return comes at the perfect time, ahead of a divisional clash with the Packers on Saturday evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d91-d35e-a1bf-7dd3b1460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) for Week 16 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d93-d35e-a1bf-7dd331a70000</link>
      <description>Pearsall picked up two injuries in Week 15 and will now miss the team’s Monday Night Football game against the Colts. His absence could thrust Kendrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson into more prominent roles, although it would likely be wide receiver Jauan Jennings and tight end George Kittle that stand to benefit the most against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d93-d35e-a1bf-7dd331a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger off the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dc8-da28-afbb-fdfda71d0000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger will not be active for Week 16 against the Jaguars, but the quarterback will get a nicer paycheck will operating as the emergency signal-caller going forward. The 27-year-old was offered a chance to join the Colts’ active roster after the Daniel Jones’ injury, but he declined and chose to stick with Denver. One can’t help but think this is a reward for his loyalty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dc8-da28-afbb-fdfda71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Watson (Achilles) was not activated off injured reserve prior to the Texans’ Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dcc-da28-afbb-fdfd69bc0000</link>
      <description>Watson has been out of action since the middle of September with his Achilles injury. The 29-year-old could be an option in the final weeks, but in a role that provides zero fantasy upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dcc-da28-afbb-fdfd69bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce is off the injury report for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dd1-da28-afbb-fdfd5efc0000</link>
      <description>Pierce was able to get in a couple of full practices, and barring a setback, the 25-year-old should be ready to roll for the Monday Night Football tilt against the 49ers. Pierce’s skill set does not pair well with Philip Rivers, so he should be consider as a WR4 at best for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dd1-da28-afbb-fdfd5efc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Pelissero of NFL Network reports that Josh Jacobs (knee) will be active for Week 16 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e08-dc7a-af9b-ffbfecae0000</link>
      <description>Even with Jacobs not practicing all week, the tailback will go in a crucial game for the Packers in their chances of winning the NFC Central. The 27-year-old may not see as many touches as he would, but he’s worth RB2 consideration for the contest against Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e08-dc7a-af9b-ffbfecae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared WR Christian Watson (chest/shoulder) active for Week 16 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e0b-d35e-a1bf-7fcb560a0000</link>
      <description>Both Watson and Josh Jacobs will be active for the pivotal division showdown against the Bears. Watson should be considered a WR3 for the contest. The Packers inactives for the Saturday showdown will be S Evan Williams, RT Zach Tom, DL Quinton Bohanna, TE Josh Whyle and DL Nazir Stackhouse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e0b-d35e-a1bf-7fcb560a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared RB D’Andre Swift active for Week 16 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e2e-d087-addf-bffe7cea0000</link>
      <description>Swift was questionable for Saturday’s Week 16 contest against the Packers, but as expected, the tailback will get the nod for the crucial divisional matchup. The Bears inactives for the contest will be WR Rome Odunze WR Luther Burden, LB Amen Ogbongbemiga, LB Ruben Hyppolite, QB Case Keenum and DL Jonathan Ford.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e2e-d087-addf-bffe7cea0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
