<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills owner Terry Pegula said the team’s coaching staff pushed to draft WR Keon Coleman in 2024.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e123-d56e-afff-e7eb090b0000</link>
      <description>Pegula during a press conference Wednesday absolved general manager Brandon Beane of responsibility for the sorry state of the team’s wideout room. Referring to the drafting of Coleman in 2024, Pegula said Beane “has taken, for some reason, heat about it, and I’m here to say a word about it.” Pegula said former head coach Sean McDermott’s wide receivers coaches advocated for taking Coleman, who has been an unmitigated bust over the past two seasons. Pegula added that he fired McDermott — among the league’s most successful coaches over the past decade — based on the Bills’ Divisional Round loss to the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e123-d56e-afff-e7eb090b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals will host a second interview with Jaguars defensive coordinator Anthony Campanile for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e15d-dc7a-af9b-efffd7c00000</link>
      <description>Campanile, after coaching one of the league’s best defenses in 2025, seems to be the favorite for the Arizona head coaching job after the team parted ways with Jonathan Gannon. Campanile has interviewed with a numbers of teams, including the Ravens and Dolphins. Jacksonville in 2025 ranked second in takeaways and allowed the NFL’s third lowest rushing success rate and the 11th lowest drop back success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e15d-dc7a-af9b-efffd7c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills president of football operations Brandon Beane said Josh Allen could require offseason foot surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e177-d56e-afff-e7ffcf730000</link>
      <description>Though Beane didn’t offer a timeline for when Allen might undergo surgery to repair a foot injury he sustained in Week 16 against the Browns, he was confident would not affect Allen’s availability for organized team activities in the offseason. Allen gutted it out through the foot injury — among others — over the season’s final month, logging 23 rushing attempts over the team’s two postseason games despite the injury. Barring complications, Allen should be ready to go this spring as he prepares for his age-30 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e177-d56e-afff-e7ffcf730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said RB Ken Walker is running more decisively.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e194-d968-a19b-f9f504ff0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald praised Walker as the veteran prepares to take over as the Seahawks’ lead back with Zach Charbonnet (ACL) done for the remainder of the season. Walker ran wild against the 49ers in the Divisional Round, totaling 116 yards and three touchdowns on 19 carries. “I think you’re seeing the results in the past X amount of weeks now of ... stacking all those reps,” Macdonald said. “I thought this was the most decisive he’s ran up to this point, and as expected, you just keep getting better and keep finding ways to improve, especially in the run game. He’s done a great job.” Walker has long had issues with looking for the big play and losing yardage instead of taking what the defense gives him. He’ll need to continue being decisive in the NFC title game against a Rams defense allowing the league’s tenth lowest rush EPA since Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e194-d968-a19b-f9f504ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks activated RB George Holani (hamstring) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1b3-d968-a19b-f9f346290000</link>
      <description>Holani has been on IR since he injured his hamstring in Week 12 against the Titans. He could see an uptick in snaps and usage this week against the Rams in the NFC title game with Zach Charbonnet (ACL) done for the season. Holani could rotate with Cam Akers behind lead back Ken Walker, fresh off a three-touchdown outing against the 49ers. A bigger back, Holani could potentially take goal line touches over Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1b3-d968-a19b-f9f346290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said he expects CB Carlton Davis (concussion) to be limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1ba-d56e-afff-e7fa35680000</link>
      <description>Davis exited the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans after suffering a concussion. The veteran cornerback leads his team with 12 pass breakups this season. He has also intercepted two passes. Beginning the week with a limited session is a good sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1ba-d56e-afff-e7fa35680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said WR Mack Hollins (abdomen) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1b9-dc7a-af9b-efbf0f3c0000</link>
      <description>Hollins landed on injured reserve after injuring his abdomen in late December. The speedy field-stretching wide receiver would be nice to have on the field due to his blocking ability, but his absence allows WR Kayshon Boutte to remain on the field, operating as an effective downfield pass catcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1b9-dc7a-af9b-efbf0f3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said the team hasn’t seen Joe Mixon (foot) in a while and wants to get an “examination” on his foot before determining if he can play in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1d1-d968-a19b-f9f138d40000</link>
      <description>Mixon reportedly underwent some procedures on his foot on his own and did not run it by the team’s medical staff last offseason. There were seemingly complications and he did not suit up for the 2025 season. The team never gave a clear answer as to what was going on with Mixon’s foot. Caserio saying they haven’t seen Mixon in a while might mean they know just as little as we do. Even if Mixon can play in 2026, we don’t expect that to happen in Houston. The Texans can cut him for $8 million in cap savings this offseason. We fully expect them to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1d1-d968-a19b-f9f138d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said he is “anticipating” Nick Caley to return as offensive coordinator for the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1d6-d35e-a1bf-e5d6e7ca0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ offense didn’t return to its 2023 heights under Caley, but C.J. Stroud did bounce back after a troublesome 2024 season. He averaged 7.2 yards per attempt with a 4.5 percent touchdown rate and a 1.9 percent interception rate. All three of those marks were improvements over his previous season. Caserio and head coach DeMeco Ryans will give Caley at least one more chance to get Stroud back to his Rookie of the Year form. Then the team will have some big decisions to make on Caley and Stroud, who has one year left on his rookie contract, plus the fifth-year option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1d6-d35e-a1bf-e5d6e7ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said Dalton Schultz’s calf injury isn’t believed to be “anything major.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1e8-d35e-a1bf-e5eab9e90000</link>
      <description>Schultz left the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots in the first quarter and did not return. The good news is that it doesn’t sound like the calf injury will affect his offseason routine much, if at all. Schultz quietly led the Texans with 82 receptions this year. He finished second on the team in yards at 777. Houston has several young receovers fighting to see more work in 2026, but Schultz has proven to be a reliable check-down option for C.J. Stroud over multiple years. He will remain a solid TE2 fantasy option for the upcoming season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e1e8-d35e-a1bf-e5eab9e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
