<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f154-de13-afdc-f7dfa1130000</link>
      <description>It’s his first practice since July 24. That’s not a guarantee that he suits up in Week 1 and he’s likely to be on the injury report next week, but it’s certainly optimistic news about his availability going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f154-de13-afdc-f7dfa1130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans CB L’Jarius Sneed (knee) trending toward playing in Week 1 against the the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1a4-d332-a1fd-f7b6d26c0000</link>
      <description>Sneed joined the active roster on August 20th after spending nearly one month on the active/physically unable to perform list, so one would hope he is ready to go by Week 1, given the extended absence. Back in May, Titans head coach Brian Callahan acknowledged that Sneed’s balky knee requires management “all the time,” and the veteran cornerback underwent a cleanup procedure in late July. While the Titans would presumably prefer to feature Sneed as a starter, it’s possible the knee issue limits him to a rotational role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1a4-d332-a1fd-f7b6d26c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Hunter Renfrow “has interest from several teams.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1b8-de13-afdc-f7fb128b0000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is reportedly “weighing his options” at this time. We do not expect Renfrow to land a flex-worthy role, entering his age-30 season. Renfrow was sidelined for the entirety of 2024 due to ulcerative colitis. He could help a young quarterback develop, operating in a rotational backup role, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1b8-de13-afdc-f7fb128b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints head coach Kellen Moore said LG Trevor Penning (toe) is out of his walking boot.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c1-dbe3-a9bb-f1d3b8460000</link>
      <description>Moore reportedly did not “have a substantive update on his progress” beyond that. Penning transitioned from offensive tackle to left guard this offseason, after faring well as a run-blocker but struggling as a pass-protector through three NFL seasons. The lost practice reps could hurt his development. His Week 1 status is unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c1-dbe3-a9bb-f1d3b8460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals waived DT Eric Gregory.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c7-d332-a1fd-f7f7502c0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Ben Baby notes that the Bengals have one practice squad spot remaining. Gregory could be a candidate for it. The Bengals signed OT Javon Foster and S Russ Yeast to the practice squad and released OT Devin Cochran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c7-d332-a1fd-f7f7502c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said Marvin Mims Jr. (groin) will return to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1ce-de13-afdc-f7cffd0f0000</link>
      <description>Courtland Sutton warmed hearts on Sunday, saying Mims had secured the Broncos’ No. 2 wide receiver role. On Wednesday, Mims exited practice with the groin injury. Soft tissue strains can be finicky in the rehab process but ESPN’s Adam Schefter previously reported that the team is “not overly concerned,” so we like Mims’ odds of returning to practice on Monday. He makes for a worthwhile bench stash ahead of what could be a breakout third-year campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1ce-de13-afdc-f7cffd0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown (hamstring) logged his second consecutive practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1e7-d332-a1fd-f7f76ab90000</link>
      <description>Brown is on track to assume fantasy football WR1 duties against the Cowboys next week. Eagles OG Landon Dickerson logged his second consecutive practice as well, after undergoing a “minor procedure” on his injured meniscus earlier this month. He has a chance to play in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1e7-d332-a1fd-f7f76ab90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed QB Kedon Slovis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1f7-d332-a1fd-f7f7273e0000</link>
      <description>Slovis returns to his home state of Arizona after three preseason appearances with the Texans. He completed 27-of-43 passes for 233 yards, one touchdown and one interception and rushed three times for seven yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1f7-d332-a1fd-f7f7273e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed WR Russell Gage Jr. to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1fe-dbe3-a9bb-f1ff42d40000</link>
      <description>The 49ers bolster their wide receiver depth with availability concerns swirling around Brandon Aiyuk (knee), Jauan Jennings (calf, contract) and Demarcus Robinson (suspension). Gage should not be expected to return flex value in Week 1. The 49ers also released S Richie Grant, while QB Adrian Martinez, RB Sincere McCormick and WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling were signed to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1fe-dbe3-a9bb-f1ff42d40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
