<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 5-of-8 targets for 48 yards in the Eagles’ Week 13 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd1-d82c-a79a-ffd535350000</link>
      <description>Smith and Jalen Hurts connected on a 30-yard pass early in the contest, and after that, it was all dink-and-dunk between the two. It’s been a feast or famine type year for the wideout in 2025, with this one squarely in the middle at best. Smith will remain a high-end WR3 — if there is such a thing — for Week 14 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd1-d82c-a79a-ffd535350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 2-of-4 targets for 27 yards in the Eagles’ Week 13 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd4-db57-afda-def6434b0000</link>
      <description>Goedert was held to just two catches for the third consecutive weeks as the Eagles’ offense continues to disappoint at unanticipated — before the season, anyway — levels. The 30-year-old tight end is now off the TE1 radar going forward, including a Week 14 bout against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd4-db57-afda-def6434b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cairo Santos hit his only field goal attempt and went 3-for-3 on extra points in the Bears’ Week 13 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd6-d6c4-abfb-ded7b1d80000</link>
      <description>Santos had no trouble dealing with the swirling winds in Philadelphia and connected on a 30-yard attempt to give Chicago a 10-3 lead. The veteran kicker has been solid in 2025 while making 18-of-22 of his attempts and not missing an extra point this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd6-d6c4-abfb-ded7b1d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said OC Kevin Patullo will continue calling plays.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccaf-d90e-a9da-dfafd8ad0000</link>
      <description>Sirianni adds that “if he thought Kevin Patullo was the issue, he’d make the change.” It is fair to point out that the Eagles’ offensive health has been an issue this season, which is not helping things, but the play calling clearly needs work. For now, Sirianni is sticking with his guy. Despite the offensive woes, the Eagles sit atop the NFC East at 8-4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccaf-d90e-a9da-dfafd8ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that an “MRI and other tests confirmed” Amon-Ra St. Brown suffered “a low-ankle sprain with no structural damage and a quick return” is expected.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd2-db57-afda-def28a740000</link>
      <description>Rapoport deemed it a “1-2 week injury,” yet adds that St. Brown will “push to play.” St. Brown regularly plays through injuries, so it would be unsurprising to see him out there next Thursday against the Cowboys. The team could handle it conservatively by keeping him sidelined for the recommended recovery window, though. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd2-db57-afda-def28a740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cd86-d6c4-abfb-df87cba70000</link>
      <description>Mayfield suffered a sprained AC joint in his non-throwing shoulder and left the game in the first half of Week 12’s loss to the Rams. The 30-year-old quarterback has progressed throughout the week, taking all of the first-team reps in practice on Friday. Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Mayfield was trending towards playing, which is confirmed by Fowler’s report. It’s good news for fantasy managers and the Buccaneers as Teddy Bridgewater seemed borderline disinterested in playing quarterback in relief of Mayfield last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cd86-d6c4-abfb-df87cba70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports there’s a “solid chance” Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (illness) plays in Week 13 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d014-d90e-a9da-df1f65fd0000</link>
      <description>Harrison is recovering from appendicitis. The 23-year-old wide receiver practiced in a limited capacity all week. While Harrison had seen an uptick in production with Jacoby Brissett under center, it was nothing compared to what Michael Wilson did in the last two weeks with Harrison out. Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon made no guarantees that those targets will automatically go back to Harrison this week, making him a WR2/WR3 for the Week 13 matchup against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d014-d90e-a9da-df1f65fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C Frank Ragnow failed his physical and won’t rejoin the Lions this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d060-d90e-a9da-df6fb01d0000</link>
      <description>Earlier this week, Ragnow and the Lions made it known that the 29-year-old center was coming out of retirement to rejoin the team for the stretch run of the season. Unfortunately, Friday’s physical revealed a grade three hamstring strain that will keep him out for the remainder of the season. Ragnow won’t rejoin the team this season and given his previous health issues, it’s unclear if he plans to play again in the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d060-d90e-a9da-df6fb01d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren (illness) is questionable for Week 13 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d080-db57-afda-d6b2d8c30000</link>
      <description>Warren was added to the injury report as questionable with an illness. The 23-year-old tight end’s status is up in the air for the matchup with the Texans. Fantasy managers will need to have a backup plan in place, but Warren is still a TE1 if he’s ultimately active in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d080-db57-afda-d6b2d8c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins activated TE Darren Waller (pectoral) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d0db-d82c-a79a-f3df16950000</link>
      <description>Waller will make his return to the active roster following a four-game absence while on injured reserve with a pectoral injury. The veteran managed just four appearances for the Dolphins prior to the injury, scoring four touchdowns on his 10 receptions in that span.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d0db-d82c-a79a-f3df16950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
