<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:02:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers (shoulder) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e89-d90d-a5bd-bedb1f4b0000</link>
      <description>Nabers said last week that it’s “part of the plan” for him to miss portions of Giants practice in the coming weeks as he deals with a shoulder issue. Jets beat writer Connor Hughes said Nabers’ Tuesday absence was “very noteworthy” and could be a sign that the star receiver is dealing with a significant injury. Hopefully Nabers can fully ramp up in the days before the team’s regular season opener against the Commanders. Last year, Nabers had 19 catches for 186 yards and one touchdown in two games against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e89-d90d-a5bd-bedb1f4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love will undergo surgery on his left thumb.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9eab-d45c-a7fc-9ebb2cd70000</link>
      <description>The procedure will fix a ligament injury in Love’s non-throwing hand. The team hopes Love will be able to return to practice next week. “More importantly, he’ll be ready for Week 1, and that’s the most important thing,” said Packers general manager Brian Gutenkunst. “We’ll get him back in plenty of time. I don’t foresee this affecting him long term at all.” The oft-injured Love had expressed interest in running more in 2025. With the thumb issue, perhaps that’s off the table for now. Losing Love would be a massive blow for everyone in the Green Bay offense. Malik Willis would likely start for the Packers if Love misses any regular season time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9eab-d45c-a7fc-9ebb2cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers general manager Brian Gutekunst said Christian Watson (knee) is likely to begin the regular season on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9eb5-d90d-a5bd-beff8daf0000</link>
      <description>This confirms reporting from ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler that Watson, who suffered a torn ACL last January, will begin the year on PUP. Look for the Packers to ease Watson into the wideout rotation when he’s eligible for return from PUP. He could be a strictly situational downfield option for Jordan Love — who’s undergoing thumb surgery — with Matthew Golden reportedly emerging as Green Bay’s No. 1 wideout. Jayden Reed (foot) could also be iffy for the start of the regular season. The Packers offense is a banged-up unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9eb5-d90d-a5bd-beff8daf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Brevin Jordan (knee) is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9edd-df63-a199-dfff7c860000</link>
      <description>Jordan sustained a gut-wrenching knee injury during Monday’s practice. He was seen writhing and screaming on the ground for several minutes and Texans teammates appeared shaken up and emotional. Jordan was coming back from an ACL injury he sustained last year and was slated to be a regular part of the team’s tight end rotation. Now his NFL career could be in jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9edd-df63-a199-dfff7c860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jets QB Tyrod Taylor underwent knee surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f11-d90d-a5bd-bf5b4f330000</link>
      <description>The team hopes Taylor will be ready for Week 1, Rapoport said. The veteran journeyman was slated to serve as Justin Fields’ backup. If he’s sidelined for the start of the regular season, Adrian Martinez or Brady Cook would be Fields’ backup. Whoever serves as New York’s QB2, Fields’ starting gig won’t be nearly as precarious as it was last year in Pittsburgh, when he was benched for reasons never fully explained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f11-d90d-a5bd-bf5b4f330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) is not practicing on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f3c-df63-a199-df3f76760000</link>
      <description>The Ammortal Chamber awaits Stafford for another day, apparently. With every day that passes sans Stafford practicing, we get a little more concerned that he won’t be ready for the opener. Jimmy Garoppolo is Los Angeles’ backup quarterback. We’ll continue to monitor what Sean McVay called a “flexible and fluid” situation on Stafford’s back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f3c-df63-a199-df3f76760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets coach Aaron Glenn said Allen Lazard (shoulder) will “miss a couple of weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f3f-d05a-adda-bfbf79790000</link>
      <description>Lazard was spotted in a sling after the Jets’ first preseason game and has, by most accounts, been lapped by Josh Reynolds in the Jets WR2 competition. This puts his Week 1 availability into question and an IR or PUP stint is probably not out of the question as well. Lazard does not need to be held unless you’re in a wildly deep league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f3f-d05a-adda-bfbf79790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs (back) left Tuesday’s practice with trainers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f45-df63-a199-df6fc6110000</link>
      <description>He got medical attention after coming up with a deep ball, was crouched over for a few minutes, then walked off “holding” his lower back. It’s hard to speculate on what kind of injury may have happened here based on this information, but the Packers can ill-afford to lose Doubs as they’ve already been practicing without Dontayvion Wicks and Jayden Reed. It’s all coming up Matthew Golden right now for fantasy purposes. We’ll update Doubs’ status when the Packers do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f45-df63-a199-df6fc6110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Kevin Fishbain believes that Caleb Williams “hasn’t been consistent enough” in training camp and that his accuracy “hasn’t been there like it was last summer.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f55-df63-a199-df7f8cfb0000</link>
      <description>We didn’t get to see Williams work with the 1s in Sunday’s preseason tune-up against the Dolphins, but it’s not exactly a glowing endorsement from Fishbain on the behind-the-scenes work. Fishbain also gave a “stock down” update to the entire Bears passing game, saying it “hasn’t been a smooth camp” for them. This doesn’t necessarily mean a whole lot — it’s just practice — but we’d love to be reading more positive updates on Williams and the Bears right now as we search for breakout quarterbacks at lower ADPs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f55-df63-a199-df7f8cfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes that Shedeur Sanders has “generally outplayed [Dillon] Gabriel throughout camp.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f86-d90d-a5bd-bfdfc5300000</link>
      <description>Despite this, he thinks the Browns may let Dillon Gabriel start Cleveland’s second preseason game on Saturday against the Eagles. Gabriel missed the first preseason game with a hamstring injury, but returned to 11-on-11s today. Meanwhile, Sanders is “the only one of the primary four yet to take any snaps with the No. 1 offense.” The priors have guided Cleveland so far and Gabriel remains above Sanders on the depth chart — but this looks to be a big week for Gabriel, who will have to assert himself as deserving of the No. 3 job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9f86-d90d-a5bd-bfdfc5300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
