<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Jordan Love (concussion) has been cleared for Week 18 against the Vikings, but Clayton Tune will start.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a7b-d35e-a1bf-7ffbf0a00000</link>
      <description>Love is practicing in full and out of the concussion protocol. The Packers are locked in as the No. 7 seed in the NFC, giving them nothing to play for in Week 18. Love will be one of several starters who get the week off. LaFleur told reporters the team hasn’t made a decision on Tune’s backup versus Minnesota. Malik Willis is dealing with shoulder and hamstring issues. He could be inactive as the team’s third quarterback, with Love holding the clipboard for Tune on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a7b-d35e-a1bf-7ffbf0a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur announced Clayton Tune will start in Week 18 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a83-d968-a19b-7af3e9fa0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Love is out of the league’s concussion protocol but will get the week off with nothing to play for on Sunday. Malik Willis is dealing with multiple injuries and could be the team’s third-string quarterback this week. Tune made one disastrous start for the Cardinals in 2023. He completed 11-of-20 passes for 53 yards and two interceptions. We don’t expect much offensive output from the Packers this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a83-d968-a19b-7af3e9fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LT Tristan Wirfs (toe) is questionable for Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a9e-d968-a19b-7aff18b40000</link>
      <description>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles told reporters Wirfs’ status before the official injury report is out. We suspect Wirfs was limited in practice today. He missed Tuesday’s practice but was back on the field for some light work yesterday. The Bucs need a win on Saturday and an Atlanta loss on Sunday to win the NFC South and secure a playoff berth. We suspect Wirfs will push to play in the must-win game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7a9e-d968-a19b-7aff18b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7aa7-d35e-a1bf-7fe758690000</link>
      <description>No surprises here. Dowdle was listed as a full participant yesterday and is good to go for his showdown with the Bucs. Dowdle is ceding some work to Chuba Hubbard every week but remains the Panthers’ clear lead back. He should get plenty of touches in a must-win game versus the Bucs on Saturday. The Panthers can make the playoffs with a win. They can also win the NFC South with a loss and an Atlanta win on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7aa7-d35e-a1bf-7fe758690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Kamari Lassiter (ankle/knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7711-d968-a19b-7ff1b5ef0000</link>
      <description>Lassiter got hurt in Week 17 against the Chargers, but was able to return later in the game. Thus far, he has missed both practices in Week 18. Fellow starting CB Derek Stingley (oblique) resumed practicing today, as did LB Azeez Al-Shaair (knee/shoulder). The Texans (11-5) have secured a playoff spot, yet trail the Jaguars (12-4) in the AFC South standings. If the Jaguars lose to the Titans this week, the Texans can steal the division title by beating the Colts. The outcome seems unlikely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7711-d968-a19b-7ff1b5ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ribs) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7acc-d968-a19b-7afdae0b0000</link>
      <description>This marks Robinson’s second missed practice, putting him firmly in the questionable camp for Week 18. The Giants (3-13) have been playing for pride for some time, having been eliminated from playoff contention long ago. Having Robinson active against the division-rival Cowboys (7-8-1) would certainly be ideal, as the team continues to evaluate rookie QB Jaxson Dart. We still think Robinson has a chance to play this week, but they could choose to play things safely with their reliable slot receiver. Check back tomorrow for an update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7acc-d968-a19b-7afdae0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50b60000</link>
      <description>Johnson came down with a bug last Friday and was unable to play in Week 17 against the Raiders. He must be really going through it. Fortunately, Johnson was seen observing practice from the sideline. Yesterday, he was reportedly among a group of ill players sent home by the coaching staff. He has a chance to play this week. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ad6-d968-a19b-7af722460000</link>
      <description>Carter’s absence is unsurprising. The coaching staff reportedly sent him and others home yesterday. The Athletic’s Dan Duggan noted DL Dexter Lawrence was also absent on Thursday. He believes Lawrence is “also in the illness category.” Both players have a chance to face the Cowboys this week, though the team notably kept TE Theo Johnson (illness) sidelined in Week 17, and he has not yet resumed practicing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ad6-d968-a19b-7af722460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (back) practiced on Thursday and it “appears as though” he will start in Week 18 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7add-d56e-afff-fefd62b80000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter echoed Jamison Hensley’s belief that Jackson will be under center in Week 18. The Ravens (8-8) and Steelers (9-7) are competing for the AFC North crown and a ticket to the postseason. Jackson’s mobility was reportedly impeded by the back contusion he suffered in Week 16. Hopefully, that is no longer the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7add-d56e-afff-fefd62b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d968-a19b-7af7b22a0000</link>
      <description>This is the second time this week that Wirfs’ status has changed. On Tuesday, he was reportedly set to resume practicing. Instead, he was listed as a non-participant on the official injury report. Earlier today, Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles told reporters that Wirfs would be listed as questionable for Week 18. He is now good to go after practicing twice in a limited capacity. The Buccaneers (7-9) no longer control their own destiny. In order for them to make the playoffs, they must beat the Panthers (8-8) on Saturday and they need the Falcons (7-9) to beat the Saints (6-10) on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d968-a19b-7af7b22a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
