<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 3-of-8 targets for 25 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b093-d56e-afff-f6fb370a0000</link>
      <description>Allen operated as Justin Herbert’s top target earner against the Patriots, just like he did all season long. The 33-year-old wide receiver successfully supplanted youngster, Ladd McConkey, as the team’s No. 1 wide receiver after returning from a one-off campaign with the Bears in 2024. Allen caught 81-of-118 targets for 777 yards and four touchdowns. He finished as the half-PPR WR33 on the year, but his productivity notably decreased as the season progressed. After finishing as the WR17 or better in Weeks 1-3, he finished inside the position’s top 36 just three times in Weeks 4-18. Allen is a free agent this offseason. Should the Chargers re-sign him, he would warrant FLEX treatment in 2026 drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b093-d56e-afff-f6fb370a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 3-of-4 targets for 32 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0a4-d968-a19b-f8f5e9320000</link>
      <description>McConkey briefly flashed his top-tier route running abilities by selling a Patriots’ defensive back on an in-breaking fake before cutting back outside, en route to a 20-yard gain. His low target total is inexplicable, as is his status as the No. 2 wide receiver behind a 33-year-old Keenan Allen. McConkey caught 66-of-102 targets for 789 yards and six touchdowns this season. His yardage total led the team, but still falls far short of expectations after a promising 2024 rookie campaign. We give him decent odds of bouncing back next year. The talent he flashed last season is difficult to fake. McConkey can be viewed as a fantasy football WR2 for next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0a4-d968-a19b-f8f5e9320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 3-of-6 targets for 20 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0a6-d56e-afff-f6ee53100000</link>
      <description>The Chargers attempted to get Johnston going in the second half, but were unable to do so. The lanky wide receiver led the team in receiving touchdowns this year, catching 51-of-78 targets for 735 yards and eight touchdowns. Johnston was seemingly headed toward a career year early on, banking two WR1 finishes and two WR2 finishes in Weeks 1-4. His fantasy results became more volatile as the season progressed. Johnston has established himself as a capable tackle-breaking weapon and should compete for a starting role in 2026. His FLEX viability could simply come down to WR Tre’ Harris’ offseason development. Chargers veteran WR Keenan Allen is a free agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0a6-d56e-afff-f6ee53100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 2-of-3 targets for 20 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d56e-afff-f6fa05b50000</link>
      <description>Harris picked up a 14-yard gain on the Chargers’ first play from scrimmage, but caught just one pass after that. It took a while for the second-round rookie to earn a role in the offense this season, earning just six targets in Weeks 1-5. He caught 30-of-43 targets for 324 yards and one touchdown this year. Harris will be given the chance to earn a starting role in 2026, but his outlook is tough to project. He never once hit 55 receiving yards in a game. Wide receivers frequently make strides in their second season, but his to-date productivity does not inspire confidence. Harris could run as the Chargers’ No. 2 wide receiver next year, but he has a very wide range of potential outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d56e-afff-f6fa05b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 3-of-3 targets for 30 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d968-a19b-f8fbbd0c0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden was unable to deliver a high-end performance against the Patriots, but he continued to show off his ability to get open on in-breaking routes. The talent should serve him well in his second NFL season next year. The fifth-round rookie caught 49-of-68 targets for 664 yards and three touchdowns this season, far surpassing expectations, given his draft capital. A knee injury suffered by veteran TE Tyler Conklin allowed Gadsden to remain active on game day in Week 3. He seized the opportunity, catching 5-of-6 targets for 46 yards in his first NFL game. Gadsden finished as the half-PPR TE16 this year and should be able to enter the TE1 tier in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d968-a19b-f8fbbd0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Dissly earned zero targets in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d1-d56e-afff-f6f998a80000</link>
      <description>Dissly caught 11-of-15 targets for 97 yards this season. The veteran tight end has one year remaining on his contract, but the team can save $4 million by releasing him while taking only a $1.5 million hit in dead money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d1-d56e-afff-f6f998a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeAndre Lambert-Smith did not play in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da22390000</link>
      <description>A hamstring injury suffered in Week 18 kept the situational deep threat sidelined against the Patriots. He caught 5-of-12 targets for 51 yards and one touchdown in his rookie season. Lambert-Smith will get the chance to earn a spot on the game-day roster this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da22390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed one time for minus-one yard in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da021c0000</link>
      <description>Hampton was evidently just an emergency option for the Chargers this evening. The big-bodied back, drafted 22nd overall by the Chargers, dealt with injuries in both ankles this season. He was sidelined in Weeks 6-13 after fracturing his left ankle in Week 5. He then injured his right ankle late in the season, though it is unclear when exactly it happened. The Chargers rested key starters in Week 18, Hampton among them. He rushed 124 times for 545 yards and four touchdowns, and caught 32-of-34 targets for 192 yards and one touchdown. Hampton warrants RB1 treatment entering 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da021c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal rushed 11 times for 31 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots, adding two receptions for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0e8-d35e-a1bf-f5eab9aa0000</link>
      <description>Vidal functioned as the Chargers’ clear-cut lead back against the Patriots this evening. The compact back proved his value this season, playing effectively as a featured starter with Omarion Hampton sidelined by ankle injuries for much of the year. Vidal rushed 155 times for 643 yards and three touchdowns, and caught 16-of-20 targets for 136 yards and one touchdown. It is unclear whether he will offer standalone FLEX value in 2026, but he has proven himself as a high-upside bench stash option moving forward. He banked four weekly RB1 finishes this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0e8-d35e-a1bf-f5eab9aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaret Patterson did not play in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ef-d56e-afff-f6ef96810000</link>
      <description>Patterson operated as the Chargers’ No. 3 running back this season, rushing 41 times for 159 yards and one touchdown, and catching 3-of-4 targets for eight yards. He is a free agent this offseason. Patterson is unlikely to be a late-round fantasy target in 2026, but he could fill in as a rotational player for a team hit hard by injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ef-d56e-afff-f6ef96810000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
