<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Seahawks after suffering a left shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2615-db7b-a5dd-a615e03f0000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear when the injury occurred, but Jennings unfortunately looked a bit rusty before leaving. Per the broadcast, Jennings “could barely lift his [left] arm” while working with trainers on the sideline. He and Brock Purdy had difficulty getting on the same page, which is likely due to Jennings’ extended absence in training camp, as he dealt with a calf injury and renegotiated his contract. To this point, Jennings has caught 2-of-5 targets for 16 yards. The 49ers face the Saints’ beatable defense in Week 2. If active, Jennings will be a FLEX option with big-play upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2615-db7b-a5dd-a615e03f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 4-of-8 targets for 66 yards in the Patriots’ Week 1 loss to the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2653-dbe3-a9bb-3653c17a0000</link>
      <description>Henry remained a focal point for Drake Maye, tying for the team lead in targets as Maye attempted a whopping 46 passes. This is a slightly deeper Pats skill corps than a year ago, so it’s difficult to see that continuing. But there’s no question Henry has Maye’s trust. The problem is this offense just doesn’t score many touchdowns, while coach Mike Vrabel is already pledging a more balanced attack going forward. Henry has a reasonable floor, but a close to nonexistent ceiling makes him a mediocre TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2653-dbe3-a9bb-3653c17a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans C Jake Andrews (ankle) left Houston’s Week 1 game against the Rams and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-262d-db7b-a5dd-a62d638b0000</link>
      <description>He was carted off — never a great sign — after limping to the sideline under his own power. Jarrett Patterson took over at center for the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-262d-db7b-a5dd-a62d638b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheim Sanders rushed three times for three yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 1 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2651-de13-afdd-66dbd6e00000</link>
      <description>Sanders only played a handful of snaps, but made the most of his limited work as a short-yardage specialist. He converted his first carry for a one-yard first down and plunged into the end zone from a yard out later on the drive. With Quinshon Judkins expected to return next week, Sanders will likely be made inactive versus Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2651-de13-afdd-66dbd6e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier had ten rushes for 24 yards in the Falcons’ Week 1 loss against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2656-d332-a1fd-b676c6ed0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier, along with backfield mate Bijan Robinson, was bottled up all day against a stout Tampa front seven. The Falcons’ backs averaged a meager 2.2 yards per carry, and Allgeier was stuffed on two short yardage carries in the first half. While Allgeier is the clear-cut RB2 in the Falcons backfield, he would be a must-start option in 12-team leagues should Robinson miss time this season. Allgeier did not log a pass route against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2656-d332-a1fd-b676c6ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught 6-of-8 targets for 103 yards in the Patriots’ Week 1 loss to the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-265b-dbe3-a9bb-365b143f0000</link>
      <description>The 100-yard outing was just the second of Boutte’s three-year career, though the first came last Week 18. Boutte’s second straight 100-yard effort comes after a supposed offseason transformation earned raves from New England media. So far, so good on that front. The big day was extra impressive since Boutte limped off early with injury. Coach Mike Vrabel said afterward he doesn’t want to be throwing the ball 46 times going forward, but Boutte has shown enough to crash the WR4 mix for a Week 2 date with Miami’s porous defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-265b-dbe3-a9bb-365b143f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 2-of-7 targets for -2 yards and a touchdown in New England’s Week 1 loss to the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2660-dbe3-a9bb-3673fef90000</link>
      <description>That’s certainly a statline. Douglas’ two-yard score was a first quarter red zone strike in the end zone. He then, obviously, corralled only one more look for -4 yards. In addition to being a deeply weird box score, it’s a discouraging one in light of Drake Maye attempting 46 passes. Four other Pats caught at least four passes. Douglas maintains some last-gasp WR4 appeal in PPR leagues, but it has long been obvious he’s not about to complement that modest floor with ceiling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2660-dbe3-a9bb-3673fef90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared FS Reuben Lowery, RB Keaton Mitchell, FB Patrick Ricard, OT Carson Vinson, TE Isaiah Likely, and LB David Ojabo inactive for Week 1 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2660-de13-afdd-66eb4adf0000</link>
      <description>Likely and Ricard had already been ruled out earlier in the week while Mitchell comes as somewhat of a surprise, leaving Justice Hill and Rasheen Ali as the active backs behind Derrick Henry. Expect a slight uptick in route participation for Mark Andrews as the Ravens clash with the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2660-de13-afdd-66eb4adf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams drew one target in the Patriots’ Week 1 loss to the Raiders, catching a 12-yard pass.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2664-d332-a1fd-b67693180000</link>
      <description>Williams’ lone look came in the mostly meaningless final minute. Not great considering that Drake Maye attempted 46 throws. The Pats could need their third-round rookie sooner rather than later, but he’s not looking worth a 12-team roster hold ahead of Week 2 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2664-d332-a1fd-b67693180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Curtis Samuel is inactive for Week 1 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2665-de13-afdd-66ef4b210000</link>
      <description>That means Tyrell Shavers and Elijah Moore get the call behind starters Joshua Palmer, Keon Coleman, and Khalil Shakir in the Bills’ first game of the season. All five could see meaningful snaps for a team that typically rotates wide receiver through in a package-heavy offense. Also inactive for the Bills are CB Tre’Davious White, DB Jordan Hancock, OL Sedrick Van-Pran Granger, OT Chase Lundt, and DE Landon Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2665-de13-afdd-66ef4b210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
