<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a75-dbe3-a9bb-3a77e4250000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes this is an indication that “the plan is to rehab and attempt to play with a brace -- rather than immediate surgery.” We’ll see how well Worthy plays through the obvious limitations — his practice statuses this week should be among the most-monitored — but it sounds like there’s at least a chance he’s able to be ready for the Eagles in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a75-dbe3-a9bb-3a77e4250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said James Daniels (pectoral) is “week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a90-d332-a1fd-beb6d2250000</link>
      <description>It’s not a “season-ending injury” but Daniels will for sure miss this week’s game. Daniels was only able to play three snaps in the opener before being replaced by Kion Smith. We’d be unsurprised if Daniels went on IR ahead of Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a90-d332-a1fd-beb6d2250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said “we’ll see” when asked if Quinshon Judkins would play in Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a8b-de13-afdd-6ecb53120000</link>
      <description>While there’s been some belief that Judkins could suit up as early as next week against the Ravens, Stefanski has opted not to commit to the rookie seeing the field to start the week. Stefanski said the Browns “gotta get through the week of practice” before determining how the backfield could look in Week 2, but with Judkins now under contract and practicing with the team, the expectation is he will see the field sooner rather than later. Judkins missed all of training camp after his arrest for domestic battery in July, but the rookie will not face any charges stemming from the arrest. It’s still possible he faces some kind of suspension from the league, but Judkins’ return will immediately cut into the workload that Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford saw in Week 1 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a8b-de13-afdd-6ecb53120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said CB Charvarius Ward (head) is in concussion protocol after displaying symptoms Monday morning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a96-de13-afdd-6edf2bff0000</link>
      <description>Just what the Colts needed: Another CB injury. We’ll monitor this one ahead of Week 2 but it would not be ideal for the Colts to be down their best outside coverage player against Courtland Sutton and the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a96-de13-afdd-6edf2bff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan M. Alexander reports Texans TE Cade Stover suffered a broken foot and will be out indefinitely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9a-de13-afdd-6edb1e2b0000</link>
      <description>The Texans will turn to Harrison Bryant as their TE2. Stover was surprisingly involved in Week 1, being targeted four times. The second-year tight end might be looking at a second-straight year of the injured reserve list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9a-de13-afdd-6edb1e2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Detroit plans to use WR Isaac TeSlaa “more on offense moving forward.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9d-dbe3-a9bb-3adfa56c0000</link>
      <description>Campbell explained away TeSlaa’s lack of involvement in Week 1 by noting his illness and missing practice kept them from wanting to load him up too much. TeSlaa caught a touchdown on his only target, playing just three snaps. What “more” is could be anything, but we’d start expectations for Week 2 at maybe 20-30 snaps as TeSlaa works to dislodge Kalif Raymond from the WR3 role. He’s by no means a must-start, but a worthy bench stash as waivers open this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9d-dbe3-a9bb-3adfa56c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said he hopes to have more clarity on OT JC Latham (hip) by Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aa6-de13-afdd-6eef593b0000</link>
      <description>Latham left Week 1’s game after playing 45 of 57 snaps, giving way to Olisaemeka Udoh at right tackle. It would be a huge loss for the Titans if Latham was sent to injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aa6-de13-afdd-6eef593b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Bengals RG Lucas Patrick will miss a “couple of weeks” with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ab3-de13-afdd-6efbbf220000</link>
      <description>Patrick played on 16 snaps in Week 1’s game against the Browns before going down and was replaced by Dalton Risner. Risner, who signed with the Bengals on a one-year contract this offseason, earned a PFF blocking grade of 43.6 in his debut performance with the Bengals and played on 611 snaps for the Vikings last season. A strong performance by Risner in the coming weeks may be enough to unseat Patrick, who has been on three different teams over the last four seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ab3-de13-afdd-6efbbf220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Brock Bowers (knee) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2abd-db7b-a5dd-aabda54a0000</link>
      <description>Carroll admitting that anything is wrong should be a warning sign for fantasy managers, as he’s always supremely optimistic on injuries. Bowers’ practice status will be a major news story for the week ahead. We wouldn’t be surprised if he missed Week 2, but at the very least we expect the Raiders to take it easy on him in practice ahead of their game against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2abd-db7b-a5dd-aabda54a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans restructured S C.J. Gardner-Johnson’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</link>
      <description>According to KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson, the Texans are converting $7.75 million of Gardner-Johnson’s base salary into a $6.58 million signing bonus that will free up just over $3.086 million in cap space. Gardner-Johnson is in the second year of a three-year deal he originally signed with the Eagles in 2024, but can be released with no dead cap hit if the team opts to move on from him at the end of this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
