<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Noah Fant (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828b-d95b-addb-eacfb4b10000</link>
      <description>The Bengals play on Monday night, so Fant has an extra day to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol. Beginning the practice week with a DNP designation is a bad sign though. The Bengals are likely to be without their positional target leader (14) against the Broncos this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828b-d95b-addb-eacfb4b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (toe) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828c-d6e9-af9d-8a9c9d120000</link>
      <description>Pitts was removed from the injury report ahead of Week 3 with this same toe injury and we expect that to remain the case going forward until the pattern changes. Pitts will be an interesting TE2 play against the Commanders, but until we see him featured in the red zone it’s going to be hard to trust him as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828c-d6e9-af9d-8a9c9d120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Samaje Perine (thumb) is practicing in full for Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828e-d95b-addb-eacee33a0000</link>
      <description>The team officially lists Perine with a finger injury, though prior reports specify the thumb. The Bengals’ pass-catching specialist is evidently expected to play this week, though his pass-catching efficacy is in question. The Bengals need all the help they can get if they hope to win games this season. He does not need to be rostered in fantasy though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828e-d95b-addb-eacee33a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82a5-d6e9-af9d-8ab595180000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner helpfully shared a video of Pearsall and WR Demarcus Robinson, whose three-game suspension recently came to a close, leading positional drills. Pearsall can be seen wearing a white sleeve on his left leg, perhaps to reduce swelling. His participation today puts him on track to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars. He is a low-end WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82a5-d6e9-af9d-8ab595180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82c8-d95b-addb-eace735a0000</link>
      <description>The Saints’ right tackle is now firmly on track to suit up in Week 4 against the Bills. Fuaga entered Week 2 with a knee injury and exited Week 2 with a back injury as well. The 23-year-old was unable to play in Week 3 against the Seahawks. Saints EDGE Chase Young (calf) and OG Dillon Radunz (toe) remain sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82c8-d95b-addb-eace735a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82de-deb6-a7fd-d3df1b380000</link>
      <description>Godwin was a full participant on Wednesday. Godwin either suffered a setback or this was a pre-planned day off. We think it is likely a day off, but the fact that his practice repetitions are still being so strongly managed is a good reminder of Godwin’s status. The veteran wide receiver underwent two offseason surgeries to correct the dislocated ankle he suffered in Week 7 last year. It stands to reason that the Buccaneers could keep him on a snap count in his first couple of games back. Rankings will vary strongly. He is most prudently viewed as a boom-bust WR3/FLEX in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82de-deb6-a7fd-d3df1b380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82e8-d95b-addb-eaee6a290000</link>
      <description>Wirfs is on track to play in Week 4 against the Eagles. His expected return comes at a great time. Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield has been banged up in recent weeks. Although he successfully rehabbed a toe injury, Mayfield is now on the injury report with a biceps injury in his throwing arm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82e8-d95b-addb-eaee6a290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82eb-d6e9-af9d-8afb7f000000</link>
      <description>Dissly’s injury, coupled with TE Tyler Conklin’s zero-catch showing, allowed intriguing rookie TE Oronde Gadsden II to take the field last week, catching five passes for 46 yards. Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said Gadsden will play more this week, following the solid debut. Gadsden should be stashed on benches at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82eb-d6e9-af9d-8afb7f000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RG Mekhi Becton (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82ef-dca3-a9fb-bfff7a000000</link>
      <description>The Chargers’ center-to-right tackle trio exited Week 3 in rough shape. The group’s overall health is improving, though. C Bradley Bozeman (back) returned to practice in a limited capacity on Thursday and RT Trey Pipkins III (knee) was upgraded to full participation. Becton evidently has not made progress in the NFL’s concussion protocol. He may miss the Chargers’ Week 4 game against the Giants, but the other two should be good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82ef-dca3-a9fb-bfff7a000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) is active for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-830f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fff5a0000</link>
      <description>Aside from Charbonnet, Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and S Julian Love (hamstring) are also returning to action this evening. Charbonnet can be expected to handle 10-plus touches against the division rival. The Seahawks declared S Nick Emmanwori, LB Jared Ivey, TE Nick Kallerup, LB Connor O’Toole, OT Josh Jones, OL Mason Richman and WR Cody White inactive for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-830f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fff5a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
