<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Michael Penix will start Week 4 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c71-deb6-a7fd-7fff91a10000</link>
      <description>Morris said the team wasn’t close to benching Penix following the team’s Week 3 meltdown against the Panthers. Penix against Carolina completed 18-of-36 passes for 172 yards and two interceptions. Penix was the week’s second most inaccurate quarterback, trailing only Trevor Lawrence. Kirk Cousins came in last week for fourth quarter mop-up duty, but appears far from seizing the starting gig from Penix, who has one touchdown pass over the season’s first three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c71-deb6-a7fd-7fff91a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) could return in Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c78-deb6-a7fd-7fff9ce50000</link>
      <description>Morris said there’s a chance Terrell, who’s been out since Week 1, could suit up in Week 4 against Washington. That seems like a remote possibility, however, considering the seriousness of the injury. With Terrell sidelined, Atlanta’s secondary has struggled to stop opposing passing attacks. If Terrell is out this week it would be a boon for Washington’s pass catchers and whoever starts at quarterback for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c78-deb6-a7fd-7fff9ce50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (concussion) is out for Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c83-dca3-a9fb-7d9b95860000</link>
      <description>Jones will miss Thursday night’s game against the Seahawks after sustaining a head injury in Week 3 and entering the NFL’s concussion protocol. Greg Dortch could see an increase in playing time with Jones sidelined. He won’t be fantasy viable as the team’s fourth or fifth option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c83-dca3-a9fb-7d9b95860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rob Demovsky reports Packers RT Zach Tom (oblique) is unlikely to play in Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c88-dca3-a9fb-7d99a1b70000</link>
      <description>Tom exited Week 3’s loss to the Browns after aggravating an oblique injury he had been dealing with headed into the matchup. “It was somewhat of a surprise Tom was active against the Browns, which in hindsight, coach Matt LaFleur said was a mistake,” Demovsky said of Tom, widely considered the Packers’ best offensive lineman. Green Bay could miss Tom against a Dallas defense pressuring the passer at the NFL’s sixth highest rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c88-dca3-a9fb-7d99a1b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) did not practice Wedneday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</link>
      <description>Brown exited Week 3’s win over the Texans with the shoulder injury and did not return. In his absence, Parker Washington functioned as a full-time wideout and four of 11 targets for 34 yards, leading the Jaguars in targets somehow. Brown would have to get in at least a limited practice by Friday if he has any hope to suit up in Week 5 against the 49ers. Washington would be a deep league option if Brown is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said QB Jaxson Dart will start for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</link>
      <description>Daboll said it was his decision to bench Russell Wilson and install Dart as the rest-of-season starter. He refused to explain his thinking when asked about Wilson’s benching, which came after a disastrous performance on Sunday night against the Chiefs. Dart will get his first NFL start in Week 4 against a stingy Chargers defense that last week stalled the Broncos passing attack. Dart should bring more aggressive downfield passing to the mix and will likely take off and run more than Wilson. He’ll be viable in superflex formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is expected to miss a few weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ca9-dca3-a9fb-7db903970000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported a 2-4 week timeline for Tracy earlier this week. Daboll’s comments corroborate that story. As expected, Tracy won’t practice today. It would be a surprise to see him on the field at any point this week. The New York backfield is now Cam Skattebo’s for the taking. Skattebo turned 16 touches into 121 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs. He was the lone bright spot on an otherwise dreadful offense that has since changed quarterbacks. Expect Daboll to lean on his ground game in Jaxson Dart’s first start, meaning an even larger workload for Skattebo in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ca9-dca3-a9fb-7db903970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cba-deb6-a7fd-7fff39f00000</link>
      <description>Giants head coach Brian Daboll didn’t say why Nabers is absent from today’s practice, but it likely has something to do with the hard hit he took in Week 3 against the Chiefs. Russell Wilson threw a jump ball in the end zone to Nabers, who was promptly sandwiched between two Chiefs defenders before slamming into the turf. Nabers briefly left the game but was back on the field after a once-over by the training staff. Nabers is constantly dealing with some minor injury. He almost always finds a way to play through his various ailments. We will expect the same from him this week for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cba-deb6-a7fd-7fff39f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs coach Todd Bowles said TE Ko Kieft suffered a broken leg in Week 3 and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ccf-d95b-addb-7ccf61b90000</link>
      <description>Kieft doesn’t have any targets this year but has been on the field for 14 percent of Tampa Bay’s offensive snaps, serving primarily as a blocker. He also pitches in frequently on special teams. Backup tight end Payne Durham could see a few more snaps each week with Kieft out of the picture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ccf-d95b-addb-7ccf61b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports Tetairoa McMillan does not appear to be practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cd2-deb6-a7fd-7fdf010f0000</link>
      <description>Both T-Mac and Xavier Legette were in street clothes for the open portion of practice. It’s possible their activity ramps up later in the session, but it looks like both will go down as DNPs on Wednesday. Legette missed Week 3 with a hamstring issue but was at least limited for all three practices. A DNP would suggest the issue isn’t progressing as expected. McMillan’s injury is new, though it could be a maintenance day for the high-usage wideout. We will get more info when the Panthers drop their first injury report of the week later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cd2-deb6-a7fd-7fdf010f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
