<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he will not bench Justin Fields after Week 6’s loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddb1-dd4c-afb9-fff1fbba0000</link>
      <description>Glenn, who said that Fields “did some pretty good things” in his first four games of the season, said it will take more than one bad game to bench Fields. A quick glance at Fields’ second-half splits may change Glenn’s tune on his QB1, as the majority of Fields’ production has come in garbage time for the now 0-6 Jets. He’s also now thrown for less than 50 yards in two of the games he’s appeared in this season. Among 34 qualified quarterbacks this season, Fields ranks 30th in EPA/play and 23rd in dropback success rate. There’s plenty of blame to go around for the Jets disastrous start, but Fields deserves a good chunk of it, as the offense has consistently gotten off to a slow start. It wouldn’t be surprising if Glenn eventually made the switch to veteran Tyrod Taylor, but it will again be Fields under center in Week 7 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddb1-dd4c-afb9-fff1fbba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Puka Nacua suffered a sprained ankle in Week 6’s win over the Ravens “that will likely cause him to miss time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddea-d94a-a79d-ddef38d90000</link>
      <description>The Rams get the Jaguars in Week 7 and then have a Week 8 bye. It wouldn’t be surprising to see Nacua sit out next week, giving him two weeks to recover while hopefully avoiding a stint on injured reserve. We’ll hopefully get more clarity on his Week 7 availability once Sean McVay speaks to the media, but fantasy managers should prepare to be without Nacua for at least the next two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddea-d94a-a79d-ddef38d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ankle) is day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de38-def2-abdb-df79baa20000</link>
      <description>This could be an overly optimistic take by McVay, but the real proof will be in the injury report. McVay did note that Nacua’s availability for next week is uncertain, but if he can get on the practice field in any capacity he could have a chance to suit up in Week 7 against the Jaguars. Still, it wouldn’t be surprising if he missed at least one game with the Rams having a Week 8 bye coming up. Nacua played through the injury in Sunday’s win over the Ravens, but played primarily a decoy role. Keep an eye out for Wednesday’s injury report, which will give us a better sense of where things could stand for next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de38-def2-abdb-df79baa20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles EDGE Za’Darius Smith retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de43-def2-abdb-df637c210000</link>
      <description>This one comes as a bit of a surprise after Smith signed a one-year contract with the Eagles shortly before Week 1, and played in the team’s Week 6 loss to the Giants on Thursday night. The former fourth-round pick who first entered the league with the Ravens in 2015 walks away from the game with 70.5 career sacks on his resumé to go with 87 TFLs and 10 forced fumbles. Smith’s most productive seasons came with the Packers, who he signed a four-year contract with during the 2019 offseason. He earned back-to-back Pro Bowl nods during his first two years in Green Bay, racking up 26 sacks over that span and also received Second-Team All-Pro honors in 2020. Smith’s decision to walk away leaves an already banged up Eagles defense another man short. They will likely look to bring on another veteran pass rusher in the coming days to make up for his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de43-def2-abdb-df637c210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers HC Mike Tomlin said S Miles Killebrew suffered a “significant” injury in Week 6’s win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de56-db72-a199-fe5f53730000</link>
      <description>Killebrew, a special teams ace, exited in the second quarter of Sunday’s game and did not return to the field. He was injured on a kick return play and remained down for several minutes, and Aaron Rodgers noted after the game that a “borderline unplayable” sod on the field may have been at least partly to blame for the injury. Tomlin said Killebrew would miss Week 7’s game against the Bengals, but by the look of things on Sunday and Tomlin’s quotes on Monday, this sounds like a multi-week injury that could perhaps turn into a season-ender for the 10-year vet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de56-db72-a199-fe5f53730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers HC Mike Tomlin said “we’ll see” when asked if Calvin Austin (shoulder) would return in Week 7 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de5c-def2-abdb-df7dcc3d0000</link>
      <description>Austin was a DNP all week leading up to Sunday’s contest against the Browns. With Week 7’s tilt against the Bengals coming on Thursday night, it could be too much to ask Austin to suit up in such a short window, but the Steelers’ injury report will bear out where things stand for the fourth-year receiver this week. Austin has caught 10 passes for 139 yards and two touchdowns this season, and won’t be on the Week 7 fantasy radar even if he is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de5c-def2-abdb-df7dcc3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Week 7’s game against the Lions is “not in play” for Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de69-db72-a199-fe6b494e0000</link>
      <description>Bowles isn’t wasting any time letting us know that the Buccaneers will be without their RB1 for a third-straight week. Bowles said last week that Irving would be out “at least two weeks,” but his shoulder injury, which is apparently the more severe of the two injuries, has now pushed that absence to three weeks. Rachaad White, who has totaled 157 yards from scrimmage and three touchdowns in the two games without Irving will be a fringe RB1/RB2 in next week’s game against the Lions, while Sean Tucker will serve as a lightly-used backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de69-db72-a199-fe6b494e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Chris Godwin (fibula) will not play in Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de6c-dd4c-afb9-ffed70680000</link>
      <description>Godwin will miss a second-straight game after being classified with a week-to-week injury late last week. The injury to Godwin’s fibula is reportedly in a different location from the fractured fibula Godwin suffered last season, and recently returned from in Week 5, but regardless of specifics, there’s little reason to set an expectation for when we could see Godwin again. The team doesn’t appear interested in placing him on injured reserve at this time, so it’s possible he returns inside of four weeks, which is the mandatory number of missed games for an player on IR, but anything feels possible at this point. With Godwin already ruled out for Week 7, we’ll now hope that Week 8 comes with better news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de6c-dd4c-afb9-ffed70680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said he is hopeful that Mike Evans (hamstring) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de75-def2-abdb-df754a500000</link>
      <description>Chris Godwin (fibula) has already been ruled out for Week 7, and rookie receiver Emeka Egbuka, who suffered a hamstring injury of his own in Week 6 is expected to miss some time as well. Evans’ return couldn’t come at a better time for the Buccaneers, who have managed to push their record to 5-1 to start the year despite injuries to several key players. Evans did not practice at all last week, so it’s too early to say if he’ll make his return in Week 7 against the Lions. With that said, the Monday night tilt will give him a little extra time to heal, which could make all the difference for a suddenly depleted receiving corps. The Bucs will release their first injury report of the week on Thursday, hopefully Evans is able to log snaps in some capacity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de75-def2-abdb-df754a500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) is expected to undergo further testing on Tuesday to determine how much time he could miss.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de76-db72-a199-fe7f47470000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on an official word regarding Egbuka’s absence, but it seems pretty safe to assume at this time that the rookie will miss at least one game with his injury. We’ll hopefully get a clear timeline once testing concludes on Tuesday, but his impending absence could leave the Bucs very thin at receiver in Week 7’s game against the Lions with Chris Godwin (fibula) already ruled out. There’s hope Mike Evans (hamstring) will be able to return to this week, but if he is unable to go, the duo of Kam Johnson and Tez Johnson appear poised to serve as the Bucs’ top two receivers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de76-db72-a199-fe7f47470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
