<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Dolphins “hope” Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) is able to play in Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ce3-d1b3-a5dd-5df383890000</link>
      <description>Waddle will test out his shoulder in warmups before being clear for action. He briefly left the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots to be checked out by trainers but returned to the game and wasn’t listed on Monday’s injury report. He was then added as a limited participant on Tuesday and Wednesday. It sounds like the Dolphins are just being cautious with a receiver known for laboring through injuries, but fantasy managers will want to check Miami’s inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to be sure. If Waddle can’t suit up, second-year wideout Malik Washington would be in line for No. 2 receiver duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ce3-d1b3-a5dd-5df383890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 3 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5cea-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb61a80000</link>
      <description>First-year head coach Aaron Glenn didn’t string Jets fans or the Bucs along with the idea that Justin Fields might play this week. He ruled out the young quarterback on Wednesday, giving him a week to recover from the concussion he suffered on Sunday versus Buffalo. That puts Taylor in line to make his first start as a Jet after backing up Aaron Rodgers in 2023. Taylor made five starts with the Giants in 2023. He went 2-3 with five touchdowns and three interceptions. Taylor is as conservative as you would expect a 36-year-old journeyman to be, but that should keep the fantasy stocks of Breece Hall and Garrett Wilson afloat. Taylor himself is nothing more than a 2QB dart-throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5cea-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb61a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports a Week 4 return for Chris Godwin (ankle) “feels like a real possibility.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d5d-d6a5-adff-ffddfb1a0000</link>
      <description>Bucs GM Jason Licht said at the end of training camp that Godwin was likely to play in Week 5 or later, so a Week 4 return would be a great outcome for the veteran wideout. We remain skeptical that he will actually be ready by next week, but Fowler’s reporting at least indicates that things are going smoothly in Godwin’s rehab. Emeka Egbuka and Mike Evans will hold things down until Godwin returns. If he looks anything like he did in 2024, Godwin will be a problem for both wideouts. He averaged 7.1 receptions for 82 yards in his seven appearances last year. It might take a few more weeks, but Godwin should be back in the WR2 ranks before midseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d5d-d6a5-adff-ffddfb1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said how Mac Jones plays “doesn’t really affect” whether Brock Purdy (toe) will play in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d69-dfde-a1bd-5fed04ed0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan is already getting out ahead of a potential quarterback controversy by reiterating that there isn’t anything Mac Jones can do to earn more playing time. He will stay under center until Purdy is healthy and then head back to the bench. The 49ers just signed Purdy to a contract extension this offseason, keeping him in town through the 2030 season. Purdy’s deal also includes a no-trade clause. Even if Jones outplays Purdy, there’s no viable way for the team to make the switch. Purdy is practicing this week and could return after missing one game, though we suspect he will be held out until at least Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d69-dfde-a1bd-5fed04ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed S Tony Jefferson from their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d7e-dfde-a1bd-5ffff3940000</link>
      <description>Jefferson came out of retirement to play for Jim Harbaugh in 2024. He was released by the team this year at the end of camp but immediately joined LA’s practice squad. He started for the Chargers versus the Raiders last week and broke up two passes with one interception. The strong performance was enough to earn him a permanent spot on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d7e-dfde-a1bd-5ffff3940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed EDGE Clelin Ferrell, formerly of the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d83-d1b3-a5dd-5df36fa30000</link>
      <description>Ferrell appeared in 14 games for the Commanders last year, operating as a rotational pass-rusher. He notched 3.5 sacks and a forced fumble. With Khalil Mack landing on injured reserve because of an elbow injury, the Chargers were bound to add some depth at EDGE. Ferrell will work his way into the mix as a part-time player until Mack is ready to return. The Chargers also signed DE Rashad Weaver to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d83-d1b3-a5dd-5df36fa30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury said Jayden Daniels (knee) is “preparing mentally” on Thursday, but Marcus Mariota “is taking the reps.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d91-d6a5-adff-ffd5a5b30000</link>
      <description>It’s a long-winded way of saying Daniels won’t practice on Thursday. Head coach Dan Quinn said earlier this week that Daniels won’t practice until Friday at the earliest, so his absence today doesn’t come as much of a surprise. All signs point to Mariota getting the start in Week 3, but the Commanders are at least leaving the light on for Daniels right now. Daniels will be all but guaranteed to miss Sunday’s game versus the Raiders if he doesn’t return to practice tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d91-d6a5-adff-ffd5a5b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Burrow (foot) is expected to undergo surgery on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d9c-d6a5-adff-ffdde6810000</link>
      <description>Rapoport noted that the procedure could be pushed back if the swelling in Burrow’s foot doesn’t allow him to go under the knife. Burrow is facing a three-month recovery, meaning the Bengals are going to be without their star quarterback for most of the season. It’s possible Burrow is ready right at three months and is able to return for a playoff push, but that hinges on both his health and the team staying in the hunt with Jake Browning under center. For fantasy purposes, managers can proceed under the assumption that Burrow is done for the year. Browning is a must-add in all Superflex and 2QB formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d9c-d6a5-adff-ffdde6810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed OG Shane Lemieux, formerly of the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dcf-d93f-ad9d-5fcf53ae0000</link>
      <description>Lemieux played in six games with the Saints last year, earning a 42.1 PFF pass-blocking grade and a 58.8 PFF run-blocking grade. He allowed 10 quarterback pressures in those appearances, tying for the second-most among Saints offensive linemen during that span. Lemieux is now on the Seahawks’ practice squad. It is unclear whether he will be called up to the active roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dcf-d93f-ad9d-5fcf53ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dde-dfde-a1bd-5fdffe650000</link>
      <description>This is fantastic news. Likely returned to practice last Friday, practicing in a limited capacity, but he was ultimately unable to suit up for Week 2 against the Browns. His continued participation indicates he remains setback-free. Late last week, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport speculated that Likely could play in Week 3 against the Lions on Monday night. The game’s late kickoff makes banking on Likely a bit risky, but the fact that he is participating in this week’s first practice, which is often a day of rest for injured players, is promising. The Ravens chose not to put Likely on injured reserve to begin the year, which indicates they expect him to return before Week 5. He is currently on track to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dde-dfde-a1bd-5fdffe650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
