<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Eagles are hosting free agent CB Mike Hilton for a visit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-298c-d332-a1fd-bfbe5ed20000</link>
      <description>Hilton has spent the last four seasons with the Bengals. He appeared in 16 games for them last season, totaling 73 tackles and one interception while also breaking up five passes. The Eagles’ corners struggled at times in the team’s Week 1 win over the Cowboys and could benefit from adding a veteran like Hilton to shore up a secondary that C.J. Gardner-Johnson and Darius Slay this offseason. If signed, Hilton shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a depth player who can contribute in nickel and dime packages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-298c-d332-a1fd-bfbe5ed20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Christian Darrisaw’s (knee) “status is murky” for Week 1’s game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2998-db7b-a5dd-a99c16820000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw was listed as questionable entering the weekend but may be trending toward missing Monday night’s Week 1 game against the Bears. Darrisaw suffered a season-ending knee injury in Week 8 of last season. Rapoport suggests that even if Darrisaw does play, the team may opt to take it easy on him in his return, which could lead to backup Justin Skule seeing more snaps than initially expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2998-db7b-a5dd-a99c16820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Allen Lazard was inactive for Week 1 due to the two weeks of camp he missed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29ad-db7b-a5dd-a9ad52d90000</link>
      <description>Glenn didn’t say if Lazard would be active for Week 2’s game against the Bills, but said the decision to scratch him for Week 1 was made because they want to make sure he’s up to speed with the offense. Garrett Wilson led the Jets with 7-95-1 through the air in Sunday’s loss, but fellow receivers Tyler Johnson and Josh Reynolds combined for just four receptions for 49 additional yards. Lazard won’t make for a huge upgrade at the position, but he should provide a bit more than Johnson and Reynolds did if he’s active next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29ad-db7b-a5dd-a9ad52d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin played 55 snaps in Week 1’s loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29b6-d332-a1fd-bfb66d850000</link>
      <description>The snap total comes courtesy of PFF. Fannin, who surprised with a receiving line of 7-63-0 on a team-high nine targets, saw the fourth-most snaps of any Browns offensive position player in Week 1, and found himself lining up all over the formations. In addition to playing 41.7 percent of his snaps in the slot, Fannin also lined up 29 times as an inline tight end and took three snaps out of the backfield. It’s only one week, but Fannin’s usage was no fluke. He’s a priority add in all formats for fantasy managers looking to improve at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29b6-d332-a1fd-bfb66d850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins ran 12 routes in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a0e-dbe3-a9bb-3a5ff8850000</link>
      <description>In a game that saw the Ravens’ offense produce 40 points, the route totals run by their pass-catchers were shockingly low. Zay Flowers led the group with 22 on the evening, per PFF, while Hopkins’ 12 routes ranked fifth-fewest on the team, ahead of only Derrick Henry. Hopkins was always expected to see a reduced role after signing with the Ravens this offseason, but his 12 routes in a high-scoring Week 1 affair that saw the team drop back just 22 teams is an indicator his fantasy value could be worse than we initially suspected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a0e-dbe3-a9bb-3a5ff8850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Terrion Arnold’s groin injury is not thought to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a19-d332-a1fd-be3f029f0000</link>
      <description>Whether or not Arnold misses any time is to be determined, but it sounds like the second-year corner avoided anything major after exiting in Week 1’s game against the Packers. Arnold appeared in 16 games as a rookie last season, totaling 60 tackles and 10 pass breakups while earning a PFF coverage grade of 50.2. He allowed 86 receiving yards and one touchdown in Week 1’s loss to the Packers, per PFF. We’ll likely know in the coming days if he’ll have a chance to suit up in Week 2 when the Lions take on the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a19-d332-a1fd-be3f029f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed WR Kendrick Bourne, formerly of the Patriots, to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a1f-db7b-a5dd-aa1fadb20000</link>
      <description>Bourne’s signing comes a week after he met with the Niners to discuss a possible reunion, and less than 24 hours after Jauan Jennings suffered a shoulder injury in Sunday’s win over the Seahawks. Bourne was let go by the Patriots during roster cutdowns last month and underwhelmed to the tune of 28-305-1 in 12 games after returning from a torn ACL he suffered in 2023. After spending the first four years of his career with the Niners in Kyle Shanahan’s offense, Bourne, who was dealing with a foot sprain this summer, is cleared to play and could make for an easy plug-and-play from an offensive perspective, but it’s hard to imagine him having much, if any, fantasy value at this time. He can earn up to $5 million on his one-year deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a1f-db7b-a5dd-aa1fadb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Saints fear S Julian Blackmon suffered a torn labrum in Week 1’s loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a48-d332-a1fd-be7e35da0000</link>
      <description>The Saints are still conducting more tests to confirm the severity of Blackmon’s injury, but Rapoport reports the sixth-year safety could be looking at season-ending surgery if the worst is confirmed. The Saints signed Blackmon to a one-year deal this offseason after he was let go by the Colts at the end of last season, and he made the start for the Saints on Sunday against the Cards, appearing on 66 defensive snaps while totaling seven tackles and one pass breakup. We’ll know more about the specifics of his injury soon, but it would be a tough blow to a defense that’s already expected to face its share of struggles this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a48-d332-a1fd-be7e35da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll confirmed Russell Wilson will start in Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a5c-db7b-a5dd-aa5c99260000</link>
      <description>Daboll continues to love the pain. Wilson wasn’t disastrous in Week 1 against the Commanders, but he didn’t do anything to extend what is presumably an already very short leash. After declining to commit to Russ on Sunday, Daboll will again put Mr. Unlimited under center in Week 2 against the Cowboys. The Cowboys limited the duo of A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith to a combined 4-24-0 line in Week 1, and that was with a perfectly capable QB in Jalen Hurts under center. It’s hard to imagine Wilson and Malik Nabers faring a whole lot better in Week 2, so we wouldn’t rule out a switch to Jaxson Dart if the game gets off to a rocky start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a5c-db7b-a5dd-aa5c99260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a75-dbe3-a9bb-3a77e4250000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes this is an indication that “the plan is to rehab and attempt to play with a brace -- rather than immediate surgery.” We’ll see how well Worthy plays through the obvious limitations — his practice statuses this week should be among the most-monitored — but it sounds like there’s at least a chance he’s able to be ready for the Eagles in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a75-dbe3-a9bb-3a77e4250000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
