<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer said Trevon Diggs suffered a concussion and will not play in Week 7 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2fd-da18-a39b-faffa59b0001</link>
      <description>We don’t know the specifics of this, but according to Schottenheimer, Diggs’ concussion is the result of an at home accident. The veteran corner has totaled 18 tackles and one TFL in six games this season while earning a PFF coverage grade of 62.5 Opposing QBs have targeted him just 15 times on the year, but could find a little more room to throw C.J. Godwin expected to step up in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2fd-da18-a39b-faffa59b0001</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) will play in Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f30e-df81-ab9b-ffcf5f620000</link>
      <description>The return of Hubbard likely spells the end of Rico Dowdle in a bell cow role, although that doesn’t mean we should expect Hubbard to see the 29 percent opportunity share he enjoyed through the first five weeks of the season. Dowdle totaled 473 yards from scrimmage and two touchdowns in the two games Hubbard missed, touching the ball an absurd 60 times over that span. They get a decent Week 7 matchup against the Jets, but until we see how the touches are distributed, neither back should be viewed as much more than a fringe RB2/RB3 play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f30e-df81-ab9b-ffcf5f620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said Jalen Coker (quad) will play in Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f319-d651-a9df-fb1dd9160000</link>
      <description>It’s the first taste of action Coker will get this season. The second-year receiver caught 32 passes for 478 yards and two touchdowns with the Panthers last season, and earned six or more targets in four of the 11 games he appeared in. The former UDFA is unlikely to see a significant role out of the gate, but could have some fantasy viability in deeper leagues if Xavier Legette or Tet McMillan were ever to miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f319-d651-a9df-fb1dd9160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (concussion) will not play in Indianapolis’ Week 7 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f320-df81-ab9b-ffe79b1a0000</link>
      <description>Ditto Ashton Dulin (chest) — this should push Alec Pierce into a top-three role in the pecking order for sure this week, and perhaps unearth Adonai Mitchell from the sealed space garbage can where Shane Steichen placed him following his goal-line turnover against the Rams. Pierce is a viable FLEX option against a Chargers defense that has struggled to take care of business of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f320-df81-ab9b-ffe79b1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said CB Kenny Moore (Achilles) will be active for Indianapolis’ Week 7 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f324-d651-a9df-fb3506320000</link>
      <description>Moore missed three games with the Achilles injury and should return as an immediate starter in the nickel as the Colts try to shore up their cornerback room from the inside-out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f324-d651-a9df-fb3506320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) will not play in Week 7 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f328-da18-a39b-fb3b76ba0000</link>
      <description>On one hand, the absence of Njoku means Harold Fannin will play the majority of snaps and run the majority of routes among Browns tight ends. On the other hand, the Browns and Dolphins are expected to play in extremely windy and perhaps rainy conditions, making for a tough passing game environment. Fantasy managers considering starting Fannin will need to decide whether or not the risk of severe weather is worth the gamble, but rest assured, Fannin will be on the field as Njoku now eyes a Week 8 return against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f328-da18-a39b-fb3b76ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs (chest) is questionable for New England’s Week 7 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f32d-da18-a39b-fb3fa43b0000</link>
      <description>We don’t have a full practice status yet for Diggs, but he was limited in each of his first two practices of the week. Even if he does play, we’re likely to see Pop Douglas and Kayshon Boutte be more involved than usual if the Patriots, as expected, lean over the reeling Titans in Mike Vrabel’s return to Nashville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f32d-da18-a39b-fb3fa43b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Conklin (concussion) is questionable for Week 7 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f32d-d99b-a1dd-fb2d06fb0000</link>
      <description>Conklin suffered a concussion in last week’s loss to the Steelers. Regardless of his game designation, whether or not Conklin has a chance to suit up depends primarily on whether or not he clears concussion protocol. Backup tackle KT Leveston would likely draw the start in place of Conklin if he is unable to go. In addition to Conklin, the Browns also listed DT Mason Graham (knee), DT Mike Hall (knee), WR Gage Larvadain (concussion), and LB Joe Tryon-Shoyinka (hip) as questionable for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f32d-d99b-a1dd-fb2d06fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado will not play in Arizona’s Week 7 game against Green Bay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f336-df81-ab9b-fff7ca3f0000</link>
      <description>Michael Carter figures to get the third-down back duties as he did last week, with Bam Knight picking up early-down duties. Essentially it’s what happened last week as Demercado went down super early in Arizona’s loss to the Colts. Demercado didn’t practice all week and is questionable for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f336-df81-ab9b-fff7ca3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) will not play in Week 7 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f337-d99b-a1dd-fb3f14a90000</link>
      <description>Ridley was a DNP all week in practice, so this doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Titans will be without their WR1 in a Mike Vrabel revenge game, which seems bad for a 1-5 team that is fresh off of firing its head coach. Replacing Ridley will be Van Jefferson, who ran a season-high 34 routes in last week’s game against the Raiders, should be set up for another busy day in Week 7. Jefferson caught 4-of-6 targets for 75 yards last week and will be on the WR4/WR5 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f337-d99b-a1dd-fb3f14a90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
