<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:04:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) is questionable for Week 17 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6124-d56e-afff-e7ec03670000</link>
      <description>London returned from a four-game absence in Week 16 to play 69% of the team’s offensive snaps. He logged a week of limited sessions before drawing the questionable tag for the team’s Week 17 meeting with the Rams on Monday Night Football. Fantasy managers can likely plan to start London in the Championship round as he should suit up, regardless of the fact he carries a designation through the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6124-d56e-afff-e7ec03670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is doubtful for Week 17 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6158-d968-a19b-79f93d5e0000</link>
      <description>Adams has dealt with multiple hamstring issues in his age-33 season, making it likely he is held out for Monday Night Football in Week 17. The Rams have legitimate Super Bowl aspirations and are likely to take a cautious approach with their red zone weapon. Fantasy managers counting on Adams in Championship week are better off looking elsewhere for help at wide receiver unless all other options are exhausted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6158-d968-a19b-79f93d5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared RB Kimani Vidal, WR Derius Davis, CB Benjamin St-Juste, S RJ Mickens, OLB Kyle Kennard, OL Jamaree Salyer, and TE Tyler Conklin inactive for Week 17 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6166-dc7a-af9b-efff09690000</link>
      <description>Vidal was curiously left off the team’s announcement on social media but was confirmed to be out by ESPN’s Adam Schefter a couple minutes later. That certainly shakes things up for the Chargers. Rookie Omarion Hampton should be in line for all the volume he can handle as the Chargers fight to keep pace with the Broncos in the AFC West. Hassan Haskins should continue to operate in the primary change of pace role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6166-dc7a-af9b-efff09690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared T Aireontae Ersery, WR Braxton Berrios, QB Graham Mertz, CB Alijah Huzzie, DE Solomon Byrd, LB Jamal Hill, and T Trent Brown inactive for Week 17 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6167-d968-a19b-79f71e6e0000</link>
      <description>The Texans will be without both starting tackles for a Saturday showdown against the Chargers, a game with significant playoff implications for both teams. The game profiles as a tight defensive battle, although both teams carry enough firepower on offense to drive the scoring up if forced into a more aggressive stance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6167-d968-a19b-79f71e6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints beat reporter Nick Underhill reports WR Chris Olave (back) is traveling with the team and is expected to play in Week 17 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6171-d35e-a1bf-65f393ab0000</link>
      <description>Olave popped up on the team’s injury report as a Friday addition due to a back injury. Concerns about his status were raised when the team elevated a wide receiver on Saturday, although those worries ultimately appear to have landed unfounded. Olave is coming off a season-high 16 targets on his way to a 10-148-2 line against the Jets and can be started with confidence in fantasy Championships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6171-d35e-a1bf-65f393ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers WR Christian Watson (illness) will play in Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6190-d968-a19b-79f1d99a0000</link>
      <description>How much he will play remains to be seen after the Packers locked up a playoff berth with Detroit’s loss on Christmas. That said, the Packers can still clinch the NFC North with consecutive wins and consecutive losses by the Bears, which is the difference between home and road games to kick off the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6190-d968-a19b-79f1d99a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots placed WR Mack Hollins (abdomen) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6193-d968-a19b-79f3dd160000</link>
      <description>Hollins played a large role for the Patriots due to his willingness and ability to block in the run game, something that isn’t likely to be made up for outside of a drastic shift to heavier rates of 12-personnel. Austin Hooper could see a significant role the rest of the way, starting in Week 17 against the Jets. That said, he isn’t likely to carry enough upside to be of use in fantasy circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6193-d968-a19b-79f3dd160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 17 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-61a0-d56e-afff-e7e834820000</link>
      <description>Henderson came into the weekend listed as questionable for the team’s Week 17 game against the Jets but has since been cleared by an independent neurologist. Expect no limitations as he forms a committee with established veteran Rhamondre Stevenson. Henderson’s per-touch upside keep him in the upside-RB2 discussion for fantasy Championship week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-61a0-d56e-afff-e7e834820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared QB Lamar Jackson, WR Tylan Wallace, OT Joseph Noteboom, DT Aeneas Peebles and CB Keyon Martin inactive for Week 17 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-620a-d968-a19b-7afbd1b90000</link>
      <description>The back contusion Jackson suffered last week against the Patriots will keep him sidelined in Week 17. The Ravens (7-8) trail the Steelers (9-6) in the AFC North playoff hunt. Jackson’s absence is extremely unfortunate. Backup QB Tyler Huntley is barely on the QB2 radar. He does not need to be started in single-quarterback re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-620a-d968-a19b-7afbd1b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (shoulder/illness) is active for Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-622a-dc7a-af9b-efbfdee40000</link>
      <description>Watson practiced fully on Tuesday and Wednesday before being downgraded with an illness on Friday. Fortunately, the Packers’ No. 1 wide receiver is good to go. Both the Packers (9-5-1) and Bears (11-4) have secured playoff spots, though the exact seeding has not yet been determined. The Packers declared QB Jordan Love, DL Collin Oliver, OL Zach Tom, WR Savion Williams, DL Nazir Stackhouse and DL Barryn Sorrell inactive for Week 17 against the Ravens. Packers S Evan Williams (knee) is active. As expected, QB Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) gets the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-622a-dc7a-af9b-efbfdee40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
