<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (hip/knee) is not on Indianapolis’ final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f061-da9b-a9bf-fe6d94c40000</link>
      <description>He’ll play his usual role against the Jaguars. He’s a potential FLEX play as Downs has been seeing more work over the past month, but he’s scoreless over his last three games and he’s managed just 57 yards on 15 targets over that span. Daniel Jones’ knee injury may have taken some of the wind out of Downs’ sails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f061-da9b-a9bf-fe6d94c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (knee/shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f063-da9b-a9bf-fe6f2a380000</link>
      <description>Barner totaled five and four targets, respectively, over the last two weeks. He occasionally lines up as the quarterback on the Seahawks’ tush-push attempts. He is likely to handle a similar workload this week against the Falcons, making him a touchdown-dependent TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f063-da9b-a9bf-fe6f2a380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Parker Washington (hip) is questionable for Jacksonville’s Week 14 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f064-d77b-adfa-fae7f7480000</link>
      <description>He was limited on both Thursday and Friday after missing Wednesday’s practice. We’d probably paint Washington as a true game-time decision here, but he’s faded out of the pecking order with Brenton Strange healthy and Jakobi Meyers back, so he’s not someone worth holding up your FLEX decision for if you have other options. Washington managed just a 1/26 line on three targets before leaving Week 14’s game with the hip injury, and has been held under 40 yards in three of his last four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f064-d77b-adfa-fae7f7480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars EDGE Travon Walker (knee) is questionable for Jacksonville’s Week 14 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f067-d8cf-affb-fc6f4b4b0000</link>
      <description>Walker hasn’t played since Week 11, but was able to get in two limited sessions this week and appears to be trending towards a return in a must-win AFC South top-of-division showdown with the Colts. The pass rusher has had a somewhat disappointing year to this point with just 2.5 sacks in nine games. Arik Armstead (hand) and Eric Murray (neck) are also questionable for Jacksonville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f067-d8cf-affb-fc6f4b4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Julian Love (hamstring) is expected to be activated from injured reserve in Week 14 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f066-da9b-a9bf-fe6f9b880000</link>
      <description>The same can be said for Seahawks DT Jarran Reed (wrist/thumb), who is also on injured reserve. The team must make the requisite roster moves by 1:00 pm tomorrow in order for Love and Reed to play. The Seahawks ruled out WR Dareke Young (quadriceps). He remains on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f066-da9b-a9bf-fe6f9b880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars LT Walker Little (concussion) won’t play in Jacksonville’s Week 14 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f069-d77b-adfa-faebb8060000</link>
      <description>Little did not practice all week. Cole Van Lanen would seem likely to take over at left tackle in Week 14. The Jaguars also ruled out S Andrew Wingard with a concussion of his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f069-d77b-adfa-faebb8060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RB Kyren Williams (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f06a-d005-a9bf-f87e26a50000</link>
      <description>Williams was limited for the week’s first two practices, but upgraded to full on Friday. He will likely continue to split time with No. 2 RB Blake Corum, but Williams remains a borderline RB1/2 in what should be a fantasy-friendly game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f06a-d005-a9bf-f87e26a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) will not play in Arizona’s Week 14 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f06d-da9b-a9bf-fe6d44ea0000</link>
      <description>He had gone limited-limited over the first two days of the week, but Demercado popped up with a surprise DNP on Friday and was ruled out. That’s just normal Cardinals backfield stuff these days, as the world has conspired to give Zonovan Knight RB2/FLEX assignments. Arizona also named Xavier Weaver (hamstring) as questionable after he DNP’ed, a move that had Cardinals beat Darren Urban predicting a lot of Trent Sherfield on Sunday. So, you know, there are healthier teams in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f06d-da9b-a9bf-fe6d44ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said he expects Maxx Crosby (knee) to play in Las Vegas’ Week 14 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f082-d005-a9bf-f8b6142e0000</link>
      <description>Crosby has not practiced in either of the last two sessions of the week and will likely get a questionable tag when the report drops later. As Vegas’ best (only?) good defensive player at this point, Crosby being ruled out would be big fantasy news for the Broncos’ prospects in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f082-d005-a9bf-f8b6142e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said he expects TE Michael Mayer (ankle) to miss Week 14’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f084-d77b-adfa-fa876e620000</link>
      <description>Carroll is “hopeful” that Mayer will play against the Eagles in Week 15. Fantasy managers have not been given a compelling reason to roster Mayer for the better part of the last month, and this latest rule out won’t help matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f084-d77b-adfa-fa876e620000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
