<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 6-of-8 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Titans’ Week 16 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4415-d56e-afff-e6fd1add0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo led the Titans in catches on an afternoon where Cam Ward took another modest but legitimate step forward. His score was a seven-yarder on a shovel pass. The Titans’ most consistent compiler this season, Okonkwo has now caught at least four passes three of the past four weeks, but spiked weeks have not been a thing. This is a low-ceiling offense, one where Ward is really spreading the ball around. That means Okonkwo will keep maxing out as a low-upside TE2 for the fantasy finals against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4415-d56e-afff-e6fd1add0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 4-of-9 targets for 54 yards in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4410-d35e-a1bf-45d2007a0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown nearly saved the Lions’ season on the final play. ARSB was stopped at the one-yard line with time winding down. As he was pushed back, St. Brown flipped the ball to Jared Goff, who somersaulted into the end zone for a game-winning touchdown. St. Brown was flagged for offensive pass interference amidst the chaos and the game ended, giving Pittsburgh the win. The Lions are nearly out of the playoff hunt, but they can’t be eliminated entirely before their Christmas showdown with the Vikings. St. Brown will project for low-end WR1 numbers in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4410-d35e-a1bf-45d2007a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 2-of-3 targets for nine yards in the Titans’ Week 16 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4420-d968-a19b-5cf19d460000</link>
      <description>Helm’s missed connection was a fourth down grab where he couldn’t quite get both feet in bounds. It wasn’t the best awareness from the rookie tight end, but a rare notable mistake for a player who has been looking lively down the stretch, even if it’s not always reflected in the box score. Despite that intrigue, Helm will not be a top-24 option for the fantasy finals against the Saints. The Titans don’t generate enough pass attempts, and spread the ball around too much on the targets they do disperse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4420-d968-a19b-5cf19d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 5-of-9 targets for 70 yards in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-441a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb67f0000</link>
      <description>Williams finished second on the team in targets, tied with Amon-Ra St. Brown. While he did break his 100-yard game streak at three, Williams’ floor has increased dramatically with Dan Campbell calling the shots on offense. Williams is reguarly invovled on short and intermediate crossers while still getting plenty of opportunities to hit the home run. Williams is entrenched as a WR2 heading into Week 17 against Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-441a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb67f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 3-of-5 targets for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Titans’ Week 16 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4425-dc7a-af9b-cfbf90ea0000</link>
      <description>In addition to his fourth receiving score of the season, Dike set the Titans’ single-season record for kick return yardage. The 24-year-old has been a legitimate all-purpose weapon, even if it hasn’t quite translated to weekly WR4 value. Maybe that will be on tap for 2026, but Dike still lacks either the floor ceiling to be a trusted fantasy option for finals week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4425-dc7a-af9b-cfbf90ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught 4-of-7 targets for 52 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4422-d35e-a1bf-45e2799d0000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa’s touchdown grab this week was relatively routine for his lofty standards. He climbed that ladder on a hole shot into the end zone and was spun around by a collision with multiple defenders. For most players, it would have been an incredible addition to the highlight reel. It was just another Sunday for TeSlaa. The rookie is up to five touchdown grabs on the year. He will be a boom/bust WR6 for his Week 17 date with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4422-d35e-a1bf-45e2799d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 3-of-4 targets for 58 yards in the Titans’ Week 16 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4429-d56e-afff-e6e9f10b0000</link>
      <description>Today was the first time since Nov. 2 Ayomanor caught more than two passes, while those receiving yards were actually a new season high. Not bad, if not terribly notable. Chimere Dike remained the more impressive young wideout against the Chiefs. Ayomanor is a young player who has shown something in an offense displaying subtle signs of progress, but he’s not on the radar for fantasy finals week, while his 2026 rank remains very much to be determined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4429-d56e-afff-e6e9f10b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalif Raymond caught 4-of-5 targets for 62 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-442a-d35e-a1bf-45ea227c0000</link>
      <description>Raymond and Isaac TeSlaa split the No. 3 role this week. Both players topped 50 yards and scored. TeSlaa did so on seven targets compared to five for Raymond. Jared Goff compiled 364 yards in a failed comeback bid, allowing multiple ancillary pieces to get home this week. That shouldn’t be the case next week. We don’t recommend starting Raymond or TeSlaa in the fantasy football finals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-442a-d35e-a1bf-45ea227c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Firkser caught all four of his targets for 40 yards in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-442f-dc7a-af9b-cfbf441e0000</link>
      <description>With Sam LaPorta and Brock Wright on IR, Firkser and Shane Zylstra continued to split the TE1 duties in Detroit. Firkser led the way in all receiving categories. Zylstra still managed three grabs for 20 yards. Firkser could be worth a look in DFS tournaments when the Lions take on Minnesota on Christmas, but he isn’t on the redraft radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-442f-dc7a-af9b-cfbf441e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeQuint Allen had four rushes for ten yards in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-443c-d968-a19b-5cfd46cb0000</link>
      <description>Allen, with Bhayshul Tuten (finger) done for the season, is the Jags’ No. 2 back behind Travis Etienne, who had 16 carries for 50 yards against the Broncos. Allen had an inside-the-five carry against Denver, suggesting he could be the goal line back over Etienne. He should remain on waiver wires ahead of Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-443c-d968-a19b-5cfd46cb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
