<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports, “The Colts and quarterback Anthony Richardson have mutually agreed to explore a trade.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9aed-d89c-a1be-bfff2f3d0000</link>
      <description>This is in everyone’s best interest. The Colts will likely bring back Daniel Jones in free agency. Even though they will need a solid backup because of Jones’s Achilles injury, Richardson is a lottery ticket that might become a starter, not a steady QB2 option. It’s time for someone else to take a crack at unlocking Richardson’s potential. With Richardson clearly out of the team’s long-term plans, it shouldn’t take much in the way of draft picks to acquire him. Teams embarking on a rebuild would be wise to make an offer, even if Richardson is now a high-risk bet at his position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9aed-d89c-a1be-bfff2f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s James Boyd reports Anthony Richardson “has regained full vision in his right eye.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b22-d042-afbc-fff2667f0000</link>
      <description>This news comes shortly after it was announced that the Colts and Richardson would explore trade options for the former No. 4 overall pick. Richardson suffered a fractured orbital bone last season that landed him on injured reserve. Colts GM Chris Ballard said on Tuesday at the combine that Richardson was “cleared to play,” but the third-year quarterback dealt with impaired vision for an extended period of time while recovering. Richardson has one year left on his rookie contract, which will likely be a prove-it year, as the Colts or any acquiring team is unlikely to exercise his fifth-year option. Richardson is an intriguing reclamation project for any team interested in taking a shot at the versatile signal-caller, but he will have a short time to prove himself as a player worth keeping beyond the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b22-d042-afbc-fff2667f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said he wants to see Bryce Young “affect the game at the line of scrimmage” more in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b2c-d042-afbc-fffed2790000</link>
      <description>Canales has already turned over play-calling duties to offensive coordinator Brad Idzik. Now, he hopes Young will also have more opportunities in 2026 to make adjustments at the line of scrimmage and take advantage of mismatches he sees. Canales said he loves “the strides (Young has) taken in terms of the operation” but wants him to take more “ownership” next season. Young had his best season as a pro in 2025, throwing for 3,011-23-11 while completing 63.6 percent of his passes. Young made clear strides in his second season under Canales, but may need to show more growth this season if he hopes to earn a long-term extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b2c-d042-afbc-fffed2790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders HC Klint Kubiak said they “definitely want to have a two-man show (at RB),” this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b83-dbf6-abdd-ff934f380000</link>
      <description>It’s not the news dynasty managers who spent valuable draft capital last season want to hear, but it isn’t all that surprising to hear from Kubiak, who deployed both Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet at high rates last season. Jeanty will almost certainly operate as the lead back, but it is a bit alarming when you consider how Walker and Charbonnet were utilized last season, and the fact that both running backs finished as the RB28 in PPR points per game (11.3). It’s far too early to panic, but fantasy managers already participating in early best ball drafts may want to consider this latest piece of news before selecting Jeanty in the last first/early second round of drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b83-dbf6-abdd-ff934f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on the Pat McAfee Show, Panthers GM Dan Morgan said “I haven’t talked to any teams about a trade (for Andy Dalton).”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bcc-d042-afbc-ffde0fef0000</link>
      <description>This comes a day after ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported the Panthers had been receiving calls about Dalton for a potential trade. Morgan said he “would talk to Andy” about any requests for a trade that may come through, but it’s hard to imagine the 38-year-old signal-caller being in high demand with free agency and the draft still to go. Dalton has one more year remaining on his current deal with the Panthers, and could make for a nice bridge for a team bringing in a younger quarterback, but wouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a one-year option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bcc-d042-afbc-ffde0fef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PennLive’s Nick Farabaugh reports the Steelers met with Penn State QB Drew Allar at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bf9-dbf6-abdd-fff977160000</link>
      <description>A true wild card in this year’s draft, Allar saw his 2025 season cut short due to a season-ending ankle injury. The former Nittany Lion started each of his last three years with the team and put together a mixed bag of performances while throwing for 7401-61-13 and adding another 732 yards and 12 touchdowns on the ground. Allar has a chance to improve his draft stock with a solid combine, where he is expected to throw, and should meet with plenty of teams who are interested in finding out what he could offer as a Day 2 or Day 3 selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bf9-dbf6-abdd-fff977160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released C Tyler Biadasz.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c63-d89c-a1be-bfffe2e40000</link>
      <description>Biadasz joined the Commanders in 2024 and started all 31 games he played. The veteran center’s release comes with one year still left on his deal, but it can net the team savings just north of $8.285 million if he’s designated as a post-June 1 release. A one-time Pro Bowler, Biadasz will be 28 at the start of next season and earned a PFF grade of 71.5 while playing on 954 snaps, per PFF. He should have plenty of suitors on the open market in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c63-d89c-a1be-bfffe2e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports extending Will Anderson “is a priority” for the Texans this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c98-d629-a1bc-bc9df1ba0000</link>
      <description>Anderson has totaled 23 sacks over the last two seasons and has wasted little time establishing himself as a premier pass-rusher in the league. The former No. 3 overall pick is entering the fourth-year of his contract and will have his fifth-year option picked at some point in the coming weeks. When he signs his deal, Anderson, 24, could reset the market for pass rushers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c98-d629-a1bc-bc9df1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills re-signed S Sam Franklin Jr. to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f49-d629-a1bc-bf5db7f80000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler, Franklin can earn up to $7.5 million on his new deal, with $5 million coming in the first two years. Franklin is a career special-teams player who appeared on 329 special-teams snaps for the Bills last season, totaling 13 tackles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f49-d629-a1bc-bf5db7f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate said he is only planning to run the 40-yard dash at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</link>
      <description>Tate is widely believed to be the top receiver in this year’s class and has confirmed he will run on Saturday when the receivers, quarterbacks, and running backs get their chance to shine. Tate caught 51 passes for 875 yards and nine touchdowns last season while averaging 17.2 YPR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
