<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said the team would have to change the offense for QB Teddy Bridgewater.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb0f-d82c-a79a-bb9fa4500000</link>
      <description>Bridgewater played the entire second half in the team’s Week 12 blowout loss to the Rams after Baker Mayfield went down with a shoulder injury that was deemed a “low-grade” shoulder sprain — one that could cost him at least one week. Bridgewater on Sunday completed eight of 15 attempts for 62 scoreless yards, with an average depth of target of 6.4, well short of Mayfield’s aDOT of 8.5. “He’s a different quarterback, so schematically, we’ll have to do some different things for him to make him feel comfortable within the offense and do a lot of things he likes to do,” Bowles said of Bridgewater. “There are some similar things, but there are also some differences that way to make him more comfortable. He’s been here long enough to where if he had to go, we can tweak it the right way for him to be successful.” Short-area Bucs pass catchers like Cade Otton and Rachaad White might benefit if Bridgewater draws the start in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb0f-d82c-a79a-bb9fa4500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed EDGE Shaq Lawson, formerly of the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb6f-d413-ad9f-bfffc8ed0000</link>
      <description>This will be Lawson’s third stint with the Bills. He was drafted by Buffalo and played for the Bills from 2016 to 2019, and again from 2022 to 2023. He last played for the Panthers in 2024. Lawson will start on the Bills’ practice squad but could see game action shortly as the Bills defense struggles to stop opposing rushing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb6f-d413-ad9f-bfffc8ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports up to three NFL teams are interested in pursuing North Carolina head coach Bill Belichick this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb8e-d90e-a9da-bf8f7e900000</link>
      <description>Anderson’s somewhat vague report suggests the 73-year-old Belichick could be in the running for another NFL job even after failing as UNC’s head coach in 2025. The Tarheels are 4-7 after losing two straight games; they have just two wins in the ACC. “There’s more to the story of why Belichick did not end up head coaching another NFL team a couple seasons ago--with his own desires and preferences regarding workplace dynamics playing more into a part of it, than I think has been discussed, publicly known, or given real credence,” Anderson said. Belichick has said he won’t pursue another NFL head coaching job after being passed over by the Falcons two years ago. The presence of Belichick’s social media influencer girlfriend, Jordon Hudson, could complicate things for Belichick if he goes after an NFL gig in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb8e-d90e-a9da-bf8f7e900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports Colts defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo “is expected to receive strong consideration” for the Giants head coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb95-d82c-a79a-bb9504b20000</link>
      <description>Anarumo’s role in improving the Colts defense this season could leave him with his choice of head coaching jobs in the offseason, assuming a handful of head coaches will get the axe in January and February. The Colts are allowing the tenth lowest EPA per play this season. They’ve been particularly tough against opposing passing offenses. The Giants, meanwhile, sport one of the league’s most putrid defenses in need of a total overhaul. Anarumo, 59, served as the Giants’ defensive backs coach in 2018 before landing the Bengals’ defensive coordinator job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb95-d82c-a79a-bb9504b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans interim head coach Mike McCoy said Cam Ward’s rushing in Week 12 was “the next part of his growth” as an NFL quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bba3-d82c-a79a-bbb758aa0000</link>
      <description>“I think yesterday he took that next step and made plays with his feet,” McCoy said Monday, a day after Ward logged six rushes for 37 yards and a touchdown on a broken play near the goal line. “He was not only taking what they gave him, but he was taking off and running. That was the next part of his growth.” Coming into Week 12 against the Seahawks, Ward had just 79 rushing yards on the season. His 37-yard rushing effort against Seattle came after a 33-yard rushing total against Houston in Week 11. McCoy said Ward’s running was part of a renewed effort for the QB to be more decisive in the pocket. A little more rushing could make Ward a superflex-viable fantasy option in the final month of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bba3-d82c-a79a-bbb758aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals QB Joe Burrow (toe) will return in Week 13 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bbd3-db57-afda-fff3120c0000</link>
      <description>Burrow practiced on Monday and is fully expected to start for the Bengals on Thursday night against the Ravens. He missed two and a half months with a toe injury he sustained in Week 2 against the Jaguars. Burrow’s return could give the Bengals an outside shot to sneak into the playoffs, though that would likely require a Thanksgiving night win over the heavily-favored Ravens. Burrow struggled before this toe injury. He ranked 29th out of 33 qualifying QBs in drop back success rate in the first couple weeks of the season. Ja’Marr Chase’s fantasy prospects don’t change all that much with Burrow back under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bbd3-db57-afda-fff3120c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said he hasn’t considered changing the team’s offensive play-calling duties.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc02-d90e-a9da-bf0f97a80000</link>
      <description>Offensive coordinator Kevin Patullo, increasingly reviled among Eagles faithful, will retain play calling duties headed into the team’s Week 13 game against the Bears. Sirianni’s blessing comes after the Eagles blew a 21-point lead against the Cowboys in Week 12, failing to score a single point in the second half. “Yesterday, I felt Kevin did a good job of calling it,” Sirianni said after the loss. “Obviously, he’s going to want plays back.” The Eagles rank 18th in pass rate over expected, well above where they were in 2024 as the NFL’s most run-heavy unit. Saquon Barkley’s lack of explosiveness this season has left the Eagles with little choice but to lean on Jalen Hurts and the passing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc02-d90e-a9da-bf0f97a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley said he’s “in a little funk right now” after the Eagles’ Week 12 loss against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc0f-d413-ad9f-bddfcd0e0000</link>
      <description>Barkley’s immense struggles continued in Week 12 against one of the league’s most generous rush defenses. He had 22 yards on 10 rushes while catching seven passes for 52 yards as the Eagles blew a 21-0 lead. “I’m a big believer that the run game starts with me and ends with me,” Barkley said. “I’m in a little funk right now. I’ve had funks before. Just got to break it. Only way I know how is by flushing this, working my butt off, and get ready for the next opportunity.” Barkley has averaged 1.9 yards per carry in the fourth quarter this season, well below his 6.6 YPC in the fourth quarter of 2024 games. Barkley ranks 20th in running back breakaway rate in 2025; last year he was first.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc0f-d413-ad9f-bddfcd0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints released K Blake Grupe.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc15-d413-ad9f-bddda8310000</link>
      <description>Grupe, the team’s kicker since 2023, missed two field goals in Week 12 against the Falcons. It was part of a larger trend, as Grupe has now missed eight of his 26 field goal tries after making 85 percent of his attempts during his first two years with the Saints. Former Browns and 49ers kicker Cade York is likely to kick for the Saints in Week 13 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc15-d413-ad9f-bddda8310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed K Cade York, formerly of the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc1a-db57-afda-fe3a1c710000</link>
      <description>York will likely kick for the Saints this week against the Dolphins after the team released Blake Grupe following his two missed field goal tries against the Falcons in Week 12. York, who has bounced around the NFL since entering the league in 2022 with the Browns, converted nine of his 11 field goal attempts in 2024 with the Bengals. York has a career conversion rate of 73 percent. He should remain on waiver wires for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc1a-db57-afda-fe3a1c710000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
