<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:04:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said he thinks “there will be competition for our starting quarterback.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9008-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd9b90000</link>
      <description>“Who that is and what that looks like remains to be seen,” McDaniel elaborated. McDaniel, who also added that his understanding is that he is the Dolphins head coach until he is told otherwise, seems to believe there are options both inside and outside of the building that the Dolphins could turn to in 2026. The Dolphins finished out the year letting Quinn Ewers have the reins with Tua Tagovailoa a healthy scratch. Zach Wilson also received some run in Week 18 against the Patriots, though Wilson is an impending free agent. Without much in the way of cap space, the Dolphins might have to get creative at quarterback in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9008-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd9b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX’s Peter Schrager reports the Titans will interview former Falcons HC Raheem Morris for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-900d-d56e-afff-f6ed51d10000</link>
      <description>The Titans have already been linked to six head coaches and we’re not even out of Black Monday yet. Morris was a respectable 16-18 in two years in Atlanta, even if a significant number of those wins came after the Falcons were mathematically eliminated from the playoffs this past month. He had improved the Falcons defense by leaps and bounds in his second year — though it required quite a lot of draft capital to get there. The Titans are clearly casting a wide net in their head-coaching search.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-900d-d56e-afff-f6ed51d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed WR Xavier Restrepo to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9012-dc7a-af9b-dfbf345f0000</link>
      <description>Restrepo had finally gotten elevated just before Thanksgiving before an ankle injury knocked him out for the season. He finished with three catches for 41 yards in two games. The Titans also signed DE David Ebuka Agoha, DB Keydrain Calligan, DT Timmy Horne, LB Nate Lynn, WR Hal Presley III, NT Isaiah Raikes, LB Cam Riley, RB Blake Watson, G Clay Webb and TE Joel Wilson to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9012-dc7a-af9b-dfbf345f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed WR Chris Blair, P Trenton Gill, DB Tysheem Johnson, DT Ben Stille, OT Andrew Stueber, RB Carlos Washington and DB A.J. Woods to reserve/future deals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</link>
      <description>Blair, mostly a special teamer, has played eight games and 48 offensive snaps for the Falcons over the past three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Phillip Dorsett to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</link>
      <description>We don’t know how much future there is to reserve for the 33-year-old (happy birthday!), but the Raiders are here for it. The Raiders also signed RB Chris Collier, G McClendon Curtis, LB Jamin Davis, DT Treven Ma’ae, T Joshua Miles, TE Albert Okwuegbunam (remember him?), WR Brenden Rice, G Layden Robinson, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, and T Dalton Wagner to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed TE Sal Cannella, G Jack Conley, WR Luke Floriea, RB Ahmani Marshall, T Tyre Phillips and TE Caden Prieskorn to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</link>
      <description>Cannella had a four-target game against the Steelers in Week 17 after Harold Fannin left early due to a groin injury, catching two balls for 11 yards. The 29-year-old UFL star is merely a depth piece.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed WR Malik Cunningham to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</link>
      <description>The former Louisville quarterback made his first career appearance in an NFL game in 2025. He ran the ball against the Cowboys in Week 14 one time and gained one yard. OL Devin Cochran, DE Ahmed Hassanein, TE Zach Horton, WR Jackson Meeks, OL Mason Miller (not the Padres reliever), RB Jabari Small, DL Chris Smith and S Loren Strickland were also all signed to reserve/future deals by the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed LB Josh Ross, WR Dontae Fleming, S Kahlef Hailassie, G Vershon Lee, T Caleb Etienne, WR Joaquin Davis, WR Jeshaun Jones and TE Bryson Nesbit to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-902c-d56e-afff-f6ecf3f90000</link>
      <description>Ross has appeared in 22 NFL games and has 11 tackles, all of them as a special teamer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-902c-d56e-afff-f6ecf3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed CB Dalys Beanum, CB Beanie Bishop Jr, WR Elijah Cooks, S Elliott Davison, DT Coziah Izzard, OT Easton Kilty, CB Jayden Price, and OT Barry Wesley to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-908c-d56e-afff-f6ec1f3d0000</link>
      <description>Cooks appeared in 11 games for the Jaguars during the 2023 and 2024 season, catching a combined 3-of-4 targets for 38 yards. He’ll look to break out in camp and preseason after change of scenery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-908c-d56e-afff-f6ec1f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger to the 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9090-dc7a-af9b-dfbfda090000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger was not elevated for Week 18 while still having one standard elevation remaining, but will now head into the postseason a member of the 53-man, game-day roster. It’ll give the Broncos additional maneuverability during what they hope is a long playoff run as the No. 1 seed in the AFC. The veteran backup chose not to sign with the Colts following the injury to Daniel Jones and was reported to have had discussions with the Broncos regarding their plans moving forward. “We’ve talked about some things for the playoffs,” Ehlinger said ahead of Week 18, hinting at the move made official Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9090-dc7a-af9b-dfbfda090000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
