<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:01:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts claimed LB Chad Muma off waivers from the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec99-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbbdf00000</link>
      <description>Muma started just seven games in three years in Jacksonville, never really establishing himself as one of their best two inside linebackers. The Colts have a gaping hole at the position next to Zaire Franklin, though, and Muma could get a chance to secure that role in the final year of his rookie contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec99-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbbdf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles claimed C Willie Lampkin off waivers from the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9b-de13-afdc-eedbc6370000</link>
      <description>Lampkin, who went undrafted, had terrific tape in Week 1’s preseason game against the Cowboys and went Reddit-viral for pancaking three different Cowboys en route to a 94.1 PFF grade with the backups. He’s a particularly short center at a list 5-foot-11, 290 pounds, which explains why he went undrafted despite an 85.6 PFF grade at North Carolina in his senior season. The Eagles seem to think the Rams were on to something here — perhaps Lampkin can crack their interior line at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9b-de13-afdc-eedbc6370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns claimed RB Raheim Sanders off waivers from the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9e-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf5e4c0000</link>
      <description>He’ll slot in as the third back behind Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford for the time being. The rookie 23-year-old had a 79.2 PFF pass block grade in 59 total snaps in the preseason and could eventually replace Ford as the third-down back — he was a strong possibility for the Chargers practice squad had he made it unclaimed. The Browns also claimed CB Jarrick Bernard-Converse off waivers from the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9e-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf5e4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints claimed WR Trey Palmer off waivers from the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca1-db7b-a5dd-eca5c2840000</link>
      <description>Palmer isn’t an immediate threat for a big role in New Orleans, but given how banged up Rashid Shaheed and Chris Olave have been in recent years, it’s not impossible that he eventually becomes fantasy-interesting. For the time being, Palmer likely won’t make the three-wide behind those two and Devaughn Vele. The Saints also claimed OL Xavier Truss off waivers from the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca1-db7b-a5dd-eca5c2840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed QB Hendon Hooker to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca9-de13-afdc-eeeb49d10000</link>
      <description>Hooker, the Lions third-rounder from 2023, couldn’t find a taker for his services on a 53-man roster so he’ll hop aboard the Panthers practice squad. Joining him there will be RB DeeJay Dallas, CB Kevin King, LB Krys Barnes, CB Shemar Bartholomew, OLB Boogie Basham, DE Jared Harrison-Hunte, OL Jarrett Kingston, LB Maz Mwansa, TE Bryce Pierre, WR Ja’seem Reed, CB Mike Reid, DT Sam Roberts, OT Mike Tarquin, S Trevian Thomas and OL Brandon Walton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca9-de13-afdc-eeeb49d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills GM Brandon Beane said Tre’Davious White (leg) will play again this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eccf-de13-afdc-eecf034b0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t rule him out of Week 1, though that seems aggressive. Buffalo will be relying on pieces like Dorian Strong or Ja’Marcus Ingram to fill out the Week 1 depth chart at outside corner next to Christian Benford while White heals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eccf-de13-afdc-eecf034b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed RB Clyde Edwards-Helaire to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ecdb-db7b-a5dd-ecdfea7e0000</link>
      <description>It’s been done. He’ll be joined by QB Chris Oladokun, FB Carson Steele, WR Hal Presley, OT Chu Godrick, OL C.J. Hanson, DT Coziah Izzard, DT Brodric Martin, CB Melvin Smith Jr, CB Kevin Knowles and FS Mike Edwards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ecdb-db7b-a5dd-ecdfea7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said there’s a “possibility” Najee Harris (eye) plays in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ece5-d332-a1fd-fef7a8c50000</link>
      <description>That stops short of guaranteeing Harris will be available. We’re likely going to have to monitor practice reports for Harris next week, but there’s a chance he’ll step in and split carries with Omarion Hampton in Week 1. We’ve yet to see any reports of Harris practicing in full, though Harbaugh says Harris will practice this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ece5-d332-a1fd-fef7a8c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed G Dalton Risner.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed13-de13-afdc-efdb92530000</link>
      <description>He’ll probably step in as an instant starter at right guard, with the Lucas Patrick and Cody Ford tandem struggling in the preseason. Risner had a 67.0 PFF blocking grade in 2024 and has been roughly an adequate guard over his six NFL seasons. That makes him a huge upgrade on what the Bengals had in-house. Risner took visits with the Bengals and Seahawks before picking Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed13-de13-afdc-efdb92530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed LB Junior Colson (shoulder) on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</link>
      <description>Colson started just one game in his rookie season as a 2024 third-round pick, posting a PFF coverage grade of 34.0. He was a possibility to challenge Denzel Perryman for playing time in 2025, but that will go by the wayside now that he’s missing the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
