<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:02:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 4-of-5 targets for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 11 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9547-d1e7-a1fa-dfef94640000</link>
      <description>Ferguson’s five looks paled in comparison to the combined 18 targets between CeeDee Lamb and George Pickens, although the veteran tight end found paint for the seventh time this season after failing to score in 2024. His weekly target volume is likely to remain modest for as long as both Lamb and Pickens are healthy, but Ferguson’s established red zone role continues to keep him in TE1 territory ahead of a Week 12 showdown with the division rival Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9547-d1e7-a1fa-dfef94640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 27-of-42 passes for 238 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Raiders’ 33-16, Week 11 loss to the Cowboys, adding 14 yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-954b-d1e7-a1fa-dfebe38e0000</link>
      <description>The fact that the headline for Smith in this one is a tongue-in-cheek comment on the team’s inability to run the football tells the tale of how the game played out for the Raiders at home. The defense kept the team in the game in the first quarter but the wheels came off as they allowed four consecutive touchdown drives to fall into a 31-9 hole they would not come near clawing out of. Smith’s lone touchdown toss came in the fourth quarter and a screen to Tre Tucker, capping off the only drive of the night over 50 yards. Smith remains under team control through the 2027 season after signing a two-year extension this offseason, something that could come under siege after a rocky start to his 2025 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-954b-d1e7-a1fa-dfebe38e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed six times for seven yards in the Raiders’ Week 11 loss to the Cowboys, adding 27 yards on six receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9552-d713-ad9e-fd56ff760000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Geno Smith was asked to throw the football 42 times versus just 12 team rush attempts as the Raiders struggled to move the football consistently throughout, initially playing the Cowboys to a tightly contested field goal battle before allowing four straight touchdowns to fall into a 31-9 deficit. The game flow significantly impeded Jeanty’s workload as the team struggled to stay afloat. Jeanty’s otherworldly talent seems to be going to waste in his rookie season considering the team’s poor run-blocking offensive line and consistently negative game script. Things don’t get any better ahead of a Week 12 meeting with the stout defensive front of the Browns, where Jeanty will be a low-end RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9552-d713-ad9e-fd56ff760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 7-of-12 targets for 72 yards in the Raiders’ Week 11 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9556-d673-a39e-b5d7d6390000</link>
      <description>The 12 looks handily led the team, but it was two drops and routine plays that left a sour taste in fantasy managers’ mouths in this one. Neither instance would have taken significant points off the board considering the Raiders really only threatened paint on one drive, but it remains noteworthy that Bowers has now struggled in back-to-back games following his three-touchdown eruption in his first game back from injury in Week 9. Bowers has all the runway in the world for fantasy liftoff after the team traded wide receiver Jakobi Meyers at the deadline, but he has yet to make good on the upside case. Even so, fantasy managers can likely count on top tier production from their second round pick the rest of the way as the team has little competition for targets in its current state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9556-d673-a39e-b5d7d6390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 4-of-8 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown in the Raiders’ Week 11 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-955b-d1e7-a1fa-dffba8880000</link>
      <description>Tucker has been forced into an unnatural role in the Las Vegas offense following the trade of Jakobi Meyers to the Jaguars, and he now has just 113 yards receiving in the three games since Meyers’ departure. It is clear he is not ready to fulfill primary duties and his counting stats are likely to continue to suffer the rest of the way while playing the X-type role. Up next is a difficult matchup with the man-heavy Browns in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-955b-d1e7-a1fa-dffba8880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Jonathan Jones reports Ja’Marr Chase will appeal his one-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-973b-d1e7-a1fa-dffb720a0000</link>
      <description>The league handed down a suspension after Chase was seen spitting at Steelers S Jalen Ramsey during the Bengals’ Week 11 loss to the Steelers. Chase will reportedly argue that if he meant to spit at Ramsey, he would have aimed for his face and not his jersey or the ground. It’s an interesting argument, one that likely won’t change the NFL’s calculus in suspending the star wideout. Tee Higgins and Andrei Iosivas would operate as the Bengals’ top two receivers if Chase misses Week 12 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-973b-d1e7-a1fa-dffb720a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said QB Dillon Gabriel will start Week 12 if he clears the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9747-d673-a39e-b7d7c8720000</link>
      <description>Gabriel suffered a head injury in the Browns’ Week 11 loss to the Ravens. Shedeur Sanders came in for his first regular season game action and struggled mightily, averaging 2.9 yards per attempt and throwing an interception on 16 throws in relief of Gabriel. Sanders said Sunday was the first time he’s ever thrown a ball to the Browns’ starting pass catchers. While Stefanski said he “trusts” Sanders, Gabriel is the locked-in starter for the time being. Neither Browns quarterback holds any fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9747-d673-a39e-b7d7c8720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Emari Demercado suffered a high-ankle sprain and is “unlikely” to play in Week 12 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9782-d45b-affe-d7961fd90000</link>
      <description>Demercado went down in the second quarter against the 49ers. He was listed as questionable to return but never did so. Bam Knight went on to lead the way with five carries for 24 yards and a score. Michael Carter, however, led the backfield in snaps. He operated as the primary back on passing downs and racked up five catches for 22 yards. Expect a similar allocation of reps when the Cardinals take on the Jags this week. Knight will be a low-end RB3 while Carter could have some RB4 value in PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9782-d45b-affe-d7961fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed EDGE Jesse Luketa, formerly of the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97a9-d45b-affe-d7bf25050000</link>
      <description>The news comes from NFL Insider Jordan Schultz. Schultz didn’t specify whether Luketa is joining the team’s practice squad or active roster, but we will assume it’s a practice squad addition for now. Luketa appeared in 10 games for the Cardinals last year and recorded three sacks before suffering a season-ending thigh injury. he also contributed heavily on special teams. Luketa gives them Rams’ some extra depth as they eye a playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97a9-d45b-affe-d7bf25050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Giants EDGE Abdul Carter “vehemently denied Tuesday that he slept through a walk-through practice last week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97ae-d673-a39e-b7bfc8440000</link>
      <description>The No. 3 overall pick was benched for a series on Sunday after reports surfaced that he slept through practice last week. Carter says the Giants changed their practice schedule and he was getting treatment while he was supposed to be at the walk-through. The young defender still owned up to his mistake but wanted to clear the air on exactly what happened. Between the Carter benching and a loss to the Packers in Week 11, it has been a rocky start for interim head coach Mike Kafka. Things won’t be getting any better in Week 12 when the Giants travel to Detroit to take on the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97ae-d673-a39e-b7bfc8440000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
