<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 5-of-9 targets for 72 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-434a-d087-addf-f3faabc90000</link>
      <description>The catches were tied for Waddle’s most since the calendar flipped to November, while the yards were his most in five games. In other words, his production didn’t disappear with Quinn Ewers under center, though Waddle was the intended target on one of the rookie’s two picks. This was also a game with a largely non-competitive second half. Ewers could still end up a downgrade on Tua Tagovailoa, but you didn’t see enough red flags this afternoon to bench Waddle for Week 17 against the Bucs. The ‘Fins want to see what Ewers has, and he will be called on to throw vs. Tampa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-434a-d087-addf-f3faabc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 15 times for 81 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals, adding three receptions for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-434d-d35e-a1bf-47cf90d40000</link>
      <description>Not the spiked week fantasy managers were hoping for against one of the league’s worst defenses, but also not a matchup-killer. Achane’s score was a 48-yarder in the first quarter where he took a toss and found the edge perfectly set. He, predictably, was then off to the races. We shudder to think what his day would have been like without the big play, but big plays are what Achane does. He has a decent-enough setup for Week 17 against the Bucs, though rookie QB Quinn Ewers’ play has much further that it could fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-434d-d35e-a1bf-47cf90d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Tipton caught 4-of-5 targets for 29 yards in the Saints’ Week 16 win against the Jets, adding one rush for 12 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4347-d35e-a1bf-47c7f2260000</link>
      <description>Tipton was an every-down wideout for the Saints alongside Chris Olave, who led the team with 16 targets and ten grabs on the day. Week 16 marked the first time in 2025 Tipton had more than three receptions in a game. He can safely be left on waiver wires ahead of Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4347-d35e-a1bf-47c7f2260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller caught 3-of-5 targets for 40 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4350-dc7a-af9b-cfff46f80000</link>
      <description>Waller had a quiet day in a dream matchup where rookie QB Quinn Ewers couldn’t find the space up the seam. Waller’s longest grab was a 22-yarder where Ewers got hit and delivered a wobbler. With Ewers an uncertain commodity and the Bucs a matchup downgrade for Week 17 — every team is better vs. tight ends than Cincinnati — Waller will be more of a touchdown-dependent TE2 than legitimate TE1 for the fantasy finals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4350-dc7a-af9b-cfff46f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals C Hjalte Froholdt (elbow) returned to Week 16 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ea-da28-afbb-c6ff690b0000</link>
      <description>Froholdt injured his left elbow in the first half and was taken to the locker room for examination. He required a moment to collect himself after the play, seemingly in a lot of pain. The team concerningly labeled him as questionable to return. At this point, he was “the only healthy offensive line starter.” Froholdt successfully returned partway through the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ea-da28-afbb-c6ff690b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught a 23-yard pass and scored a nine-yard rushing touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4352-d35e-a1bf-47d2c13c0000</link>
      <description>Washington’s fourth quarter catch was his only target, and it came with the ‘Fins trailing 45-14. His rushing score came on a second quarter sweep. It was the second of his career. Washington has tacked 15 rushes onto a consistent receptions floor this season, but he wasn’t spiking any weeks with Tua Tagovailoa, and there is no reason to expect that to change with Quinn Ewers. He will not be a top-50 option for the fantasy finals vs. Tampa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4352-d35e-a1bf-47d2c13c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared QB Tommy DeVito, LB Robert Spillane, OT Marcus Bryant, TE CJ Dippre, and WR Efton Chism inactive for Week 16 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4353-d35e-a1bf-47d33e250000</link>
      <description>All of Carlton Davis, Marcus Jones, Harold Landry, and Christian Barmore are active for the Patriots after coming into the weekend listed as questionable. Tommy DeVito will continue to serve as the emergency quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4353-d35e-a1bf-47d33e250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared QB Cooper Rush, WR Tylan Wallace, OT Joseph Noteboom, DT C.J. Okoye, DT Aeneas Peebles, and CB Chidobe Awuzie inactive for Week 16 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4354-dc7a-af9b-cfff93de0000</link>
      <description>Awuzie has seen his snaps reduced of late with both Nate Wiggins and Marlon Humphrey healthy, with his absence going down as a loss of depth more than losing an established starter. The same can be said of defensive tackle C.J. Okoye, with the Ravens largely healthy as they continue a late-season push towards the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4354-dc7a-af9b-cfff93de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dulcich caught 3-of-3 targets for 46 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4358-d35e-a1bf-47daf1ce0000</link>
      <description>This was the second straight week Dulcich posted 46 yards, tying for his second most of the season. Good enough, but bad was Dulcich’s soft third quarter fumble that helped lead to a 21-0 frame for the Bengals. Still an afterthought behind Darren Waller in an offense trying out a seventh-round rookie quarterback, Dulcich is out of sight, out of mind for the fantasy finals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4358-d35e-a1bf-47daf1ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Wright rushed nine times for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 16 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-435b-d087-addf-f3fb28150000</link>
      <description>Wright added an 18-yard catch. Nearly all of Wright’s work, including his three-yard score, came with the Dolphins down 3-4 touchdowns in the fourth quarter. Maybe the Dolphins will try to lighten De’Von Achane’s load a bit for the final two weeks of the season, but Wright will only be a FLEX factor if Achane misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-435b-d087-addf-f3fb28150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
