<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed RB Jase McClellan, formerly of the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a8a-d05a-adda-ba8ab28e0000</link>
      <description>McClellan was a fourth-round pick of the Falcons last season and was let go by the team in June. His signing comes just days after Rachaad White suffered a groin injury, but White was mentioned as being day-to-day by head coach Todd Bowles. There could be nothing to this signing, but the timing of it is interesting. McClellan rushed 13 times for 32 scoreless yards last season and should be considered a long shot to make the final 53-man roster if White is healthy by roster cut down day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a8a-d05a-adda-ba8ab28e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Ja’Lynn Polk (shoulder) won’t play against the Vikings in preseason Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a93-df63-a199-dbbb072d0000</link>
      <description>Polk appeared to suffer an injury during Friday night’s game against the Commanders. He’s been sidelined with a shoulder injury for most of the offseason, though it’s unknown if this is the same shoulder. It’s certainly possible that the Patriots waive/injured Polk or place him on injured reserve in the coming weeks, as the second-rounder never seemed to make a real push in what has become a stacked New England receiving room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a93-df63-a199-dbbb072d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes Joe Flacco is “probably” the team’s opening-day starter at quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a9f-d45c-a7fc-9a9f053d0000</link>
      <description>Kenny Pickett, the only serious contender to Flacco, has been dealing with a hamstring injury that has kept him as a 7-on-7 participant for most of the last week. Whoever wins this job will be one of the lowest-regarded fantasy options in the league, but Flacco’s success in Kevin Stefanski’s offense in 2023 at least throws some optimistic scenarios on the table for Jerry Jeudy and David Njoku.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a9f-d45c-a7fc-9a9f053d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans re-signed QB Trevor Siemian.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a98-df63-a199-dbbbc67d0000</link>
      <description>Siemian spent part of last season with the Titans but never attempted a pass. The veteran quarterback last threw a pass in Week 18 of the 2023 season and will now compete for backup duties with Brandon Allen. Siemian’s signing comes just days after the Titans watched Tim Boyle complete 4-of-13 passes for 24 yards and two interceptions in a preseason game against the Buccaneers. He has since been released. Siemian has a good chance to stick on the Titans’ 53-man roster if the team opts to keep three quarterbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a98-df63-a199-dbbbc67d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans activated C Lloyd Cushenberry from the active/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aab-d90d-a5bd-bafb103b0000</link>
      <description>We’ll see just how close Cushenberry is to competing this week. Titans coach Brian Callahan said: “Timeline-wise, I’ll probably refrain from giving a timeline, but it’s encouraging that, hopefully, we’ll get him on the practice field with the group this week for the return to play process.’ Cushenberry still has a chance to start the season as Tennessee’s center, but he’ll need to get healthy in a hurry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aab-d90d-a5bd-bafb103b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Tashan Reed believes Jamal Adams may challenge for a starting spot at linebacker for the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac6-df63-a199-dbef0c130000</link>
      <description>The Raiders signed Adams on the condition that he’d move to linebacker. Adams relayed that conversation with Pete Carroll to the media on Saturday like so: “He told me, ‘You’re going to be in the linebacker room so get over it ... I said, ‘Alright, s—, let’s do it.’” Okay then! Adams has played just 15 games since 2022 and will try to unseat Germaine Pratt for a spot at Will linebacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac6-df63-a199-dbef0c130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Eagles LG Landon Dickerson will have “a minor procedure on his knee” and hopes to be ready for the start of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac9-d45c-a7fc-9adb8fd00000</link>
      <description>Dickerson suffered a meniscus injury on Sunday and has been undergoing tests and seeking multiple opinions to figure out the best course of action. Now, according to Garafolo, Dickerson will be considered week-to-week after a minor surgery to correct the issue and is eyeing a Week 1 return if all goes according to plan. It’s about the best news the three-time Pro Bowler could have hoped for after the initial diagnosis sounded far worse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ac9-d45c-a7fc-9adb8fd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is “on track to be back around Week 6.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ad7-d90d-a5bd-badf0ad60000</link>
      <description>That “around” is doing a lot of lifting, but this is the first gesture towards a real timetable we’ve had about Aiyuk’s potential return. He’ll almost certainly open the season on the PUP list with this estimate. Aiyuk’s ADP has fluctuated outside of the top 40 among wideouts at this point and he’s probably best-regarded as a dart throw at the moment. The fifth-year receiver will be at the top of the 49ers receiver pecking order when he’s healthy — we just don’t know when he will be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ad7-d90d-a5bd-badf0ad60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jordan Watkins is expected to miss about a month with a high ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9add-df63-a199-dbffb9010000</link>
      <description>The hits keep on coming for the Niners, who are expected to be without Brandon Aiyuk (knee) for at least the first month of the season, and are at risk of being without Jauan Jennings (calf) as well. Jacob Cowing is also battling a hamstring injury, although Kyle Shanahan said he could return to practice on Tuesday. Still, it goes without saying that the Niners’ receiver room is banged up, and Watkins had a chance to see some work early in the season with the injuries piling up. It was reported earlier this month that Watkins was ‘in the mix’ for WR3/WR4 duties. A month-long absence means Watkins could be at risk of missing the first month of the season, but we’ll likely get more clarity on that as Week 1 draws closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9add-df63-a199-dbffb9010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Marquez Callaway.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</link>
      <description>Cut after the draft by the Buccaneers and by the 49ers in training camp, Callaway continues his quest to be rostered for the 2025 season. He has five targets and no catches since 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
