<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 03:20:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 14 times for 58 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys, adding 22 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c803-d90e-a9da-df0f27260000</link>
      <description>Hunt remained the clear lead back with the return of Isiah Pacheco to the game-day roster, out-touching the younger back 15-to-5 in the loss. That said, he remains one of the more touchdown-dependent backs in the league considering the the pass-first nature of the Kansas City offense. He might also be forced to overcome fewer opportunities in the coming games as Pacheco works his way back into game shape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c803-d90e-a9da-df0f27260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 8-of-12 targets for 92 yards and two touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c805-d82c-a79a-fb95369d0000</link>
      <description>Rice got the party started with a 29-yard grab on the team’s opening possession, tacking on an additional score on fourth-and-three at the start of the fourth quarter on a beautiful catch over a defender in the middle of the end zone. His 12 targets were double the next closest Kansas City skill position player as he continues to operate as the key cog of the offense. Rice will look to keep his torrid stretch going against a much stiffer opponent when the Chiefs take on the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c805-d82c-a79a-fb95369d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 5-of-6 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c808-d82c-a79a-fb9cf8270000</link>
      <description>Kelce found paint on the final play of the third quarter to send the Chiefs to a 14-7 lead, but things would stall out in the second quarter as they were held off the scoreboard on their final two possessions of the first half. He extended his franchise record for total touchdowns scored that he set two weeks ago, something he’ll look to replicate in a difficult matchup against the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c808-d82c-a79a-fb9cf8270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 4-of-6 targets for 61 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80b-d90e-a9da-df0fe9310000</link>
      <description>Worthy’s six targets tied for second on the team with Travis Kelce but were half of Rashee Rice’s team-leading 12 on the evening, something fantasy managers have grown to accept since the talented third-year receiver’s return from a six-game suspension to start the season. He’ll likely have to overcome modest volume again when the Chiefs take on the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80b-d90e-a9da-df0fe9310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught both targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80e-d82c-a79a-fb9e3e410000</link>
      <description>Brown’s fourth quarter touchdown was his first road score since the 2022 season while with the Cardinals. He continued to play well behind the top trio of Rashee Rice, Travis Kelce, and Xavier Worthy, keeping him heavily reliant on touchdowns to return usable fantasy weeks. That is unlikely to change ahead of a difficult matchup with the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80e-d82c-a79a-fb9e3e410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 27-of-39 passes for 320 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Cowboys’ 31-28, Week 13 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c811-db57-afda-de33263b0000</link>
      <description>His lone mistake on the evening came on the team’s first possession when he was picked by Jaylen Watson on a pass intended for George Pickens near midfield, otherwise notching points on six of seven drives outside of their final possessions of each half. The highlight of his evening came in the fourth quarter as they attempted to ice the game, hitting alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb for a 51-yard strike against a two-high alignment, leading to a field goal to extend their lead to 10 points with just over five minutes to play in the final frame. The Cowboys have now beaten last year’s Super Bowl participants in back-to-back games after downing the Eagles a week ago. The win takes them to 6-5-1 and on the fringes of the playoff discussion in the NFC with another difficult matchup on deck when they travel to Detroit to take on the Lions in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c811-db57-afda-de33263b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams rushed 17 times for 59 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 13 win over the Chiefs, adding 21 yards and a touchdown on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c817-d6c4-abfb-de177cbf0000</link>
      <description>Williams again operated as a borderline workhorse back for a Cowboys team that is surging late in the season. His fourth quarter receiving touchdown came on a broken play from the three while trailing by a point, with a successful two-point conversion giving the Cowboys a lead they would not relinquish. Backup running back Malik Davis surged to 47 yards and a touchdown on only three carries and could begin to earn more work in the backfield after consecutive strong performances on limited touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c817-d6c4-abfb-de177cbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 7-of-9 targets for 112 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 13 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c81b-d82c-a79a-fb9f233d0000</link>
      <description>Lamb got the Cowboys on the board in the first quarter with a 15-yard touchdown on the team’s second possession, seeing ample production throughout the first half before the Chiefs adjusted to account for his exploits. He was then rather quiet after the break as the team relied more heavily on George Pickens before a 51-yard catch in the fourth quarter shot him over the 100-yard mark in a hurry. He would add one more catch before all was said and done to finish with his best fantasy output in six weeks. He gets a pristine matchup on paper in Week 14 against the injury-riddled secondary of the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c81b-d82c-a79a-fb9f233d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 6-of-13 targets for 88 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 13 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c81e-d90e-a9da-df1fd4660000</link>
      <description>Pickens started slow as he managed to coral only three of his first nine targets, but he got the better of secondary corner Jaylen Watson in the fourth quarter, notching 55 yards in the final frame. This was the first game in six weeks in which Pickens was outperformed by CeeDee Lamb, with the latter going over 100 yards for the first time in the same timeframe. Pickens should continue to demand WR1 treatment in fantasy circles ahead of a solid on-paper matchup against the Lions in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c81e-d90e-a9da-df1fd4660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 5-of-6 targets for 36 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 13 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c825-db57-afda-de3749900000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Dak Prescott’s only incompletion when targeting his veteran tight end was a touchdown grab in the third quarter that was called back as Ferguson was unable to get his second foot inbounds after further review. It has now been eight games since Ferguson saw more than seven targets, keeping him heavily reliant on touchdowns for fantasy production with CeeDee Lamb healthy. He should be counted on for another five to seven looks when the Cowboys take on the Lions in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c825-db57-afda-de3749900000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
