<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Williams caught 6-of-7 targets for 53 yards in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</link>
      <description>It was a career day for Williams, who ranked second among Jets receivers in routes (30) and third in snaps with 41. Williams has played primarily on special teams this season and currently leads the league in punt return yards (396) and has two punt return touchdowns. He seemed to show good chemistry with Brady Cook, who he has presumably spent a lot of time with in practice, but his strong performance in Week 15 could warrant a stronger look over the final three weeks of the season. Williams has played 30-plus snaps and run 20-plus routes in back-to-back weeks. He’s worth a stash in deeper leagues ahead of next week’s game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (ankle) left Chicago’s Week 15 game against the Browns and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-225a-d8cf-affb-be7af1cc0000</link>
      <description>He was officially questionable to return after leaving in the third quarter. Bears coach Ben Johnson said after the game that they’d look at it tomorrow. It’s possible that the Bears will lose their ascending receiver ahead of Week 16’s date against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-225a-d8cf-affb-be7af1cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Christian Watson’s injury is not believed to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2248-d77b-adfb-eacb982c0000</link>
      <description>Watson appeared to have suffered a shoulder injury but was later listed with a chest injury. The Packers’ top deep threat was taken to the hospital for further evaluation, but was able to fly home with the team after the game. According to Packers beat writer Rob Demovsky, Watson had a CT scan as aprecaution on his lungs, but “no issue with his lungs” was found. Whether or not he’s able to play in Week 16 against the may not be known until later in the week, but it sounds like this will be a short-term absence for Watson at the worst. With the Packers playing on Saturday, we should have our first injury report on Tuesday, which will give us a better sense of where Watson’s availability could stand for next week. If he’s unable to go, Romeo Doubs and Matthew Golden would be the favorites to see expanded roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2248-d77b-adfb-eacb982c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said “I would expect [Ricky Pearsall] to be alright” after Week 15’s win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-228e-d77b-adfb-ea8f28550000</link>
      <description>Pearsall battled through an ankle injury early in Sunday’s win and later went down with a knee injury. Shanahan said he believes Pearsall’s knee injury resulted from “irritating his PCL from the past,” and noted that such injuries tend to linger. Pearsall said after the game that he will have some imaging done, so we’ll likely know within the next 24 hours if there’s anything to be concerned about heading into Week 16. We’re well into the part of the season when every player is dealing with some injury or another. Hopefully, Pearsall will be available for Week 16’s game against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-228e-d77b-adfb-ea8f28550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets fired DC Steve Wilks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22a3-d005-a9bf-fab7d25b0000</link>
      <description>A 48-20 loss to the Jaguars was the final straw for Wilks, whose defense entered the day ranked in the bottom five in EPA per play entering the day and had allowed six 30-plus point performances on the year. Another indictment of Wilks is the fact that his defense has yet to force an interception through the first 15 weeks of the season. Life got harder following this year’s trade deadline, when the Jets dealt stars Sauce Gardner and Quinnen Williams away for future draft picks, but Sunday’s loss to the Jaguars set a new low for the season. Wilks hasn’t spent more than one season with a team since his first stint with the Panthers, which lasted from 2012 to 2017. The long-time defensive coordinator who helped lead a top-five 49ers defense in 2023 could find a new home next offseason, but this latest stop left much to be desired. Defensive backs coach/passing game coordinator Chris Harris will takeover as interim DC for the final three weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22a3-d005-a9bf-fab7d25b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) is believed to have suffered “a bad sprain” in Week 15’s loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22be-d8cf-affb-bebe23b30000</link>
      <description>Knight is expected to undergo an MRI on Monday to confirm the diagnosis, but the belief is that he did not break anything. Knight is highly unlikely to play in Week 16’s game against the Falcons, and depending on the severity of his injury, it wouldn’t be surprising if this proved to be season-ending. We’ll check back in with an update when the team provides one, but an already thin Cardinals backfield could be looking at Emari Demercado and Michael Carter as it’s top two options down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22be-d8cf-affb-bebe23b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers added RB Jaylen Warren (illness, questionable) to the injury report for Week 15 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22c3-d005-a9bf-faf760f70000</link>
      <description>Players typically play through any illness-related issues, but Warren’s addition to the injury report just hours before kickoff is concerning. NFL Network’sTom Pelissero reportsWarren “woke up sick and is getting fluids” and that he is “optimistic” about playing on Monday night. His status will be one to watch for when inactives are announced 90 minutes before kickoff, but if he is unable to go, Kenneth Gainwell would be primed for a large role on Monday night against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22c3-d005-a9bf-faf760f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans DT Mario Edwards (pectoral) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-230f-d005-a9bf-fb3f68570000</link>
      <description>Edwards has appeared in 14 games for the Texans this season, tallying 13 tackles, 1.5 sacks, and two TFLs in a supporting role. Naquan Jones, who the Texans recently claimed off waivers, took over in Edwards’ absence on Sunday and will presumably be tasked with filling his role for the remainder of the season. Edwards signed a two-year deal with the Texans this offseason and should be back in time for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-230f-d005-a9bf-fb3f68570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryans HC DeMeco Ryans said Woody Marks (ankle) should be fine after being injured in Week 15’s win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2314-d8cf-affb-bf3e6a070000</link>
      <description>Ryans said the team will monitor Marks’ injury this week, but this doesn’t appear to be too big of an issue. Ryans said after Sunday’s game that Marks could have returned against the Cardinals if needed, so his comments on Monday aren’t too surprising. Fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on his practice status throughout the week, but Marks has a nice Week 16 matchup against the Raiders on tap if he is able to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2314-d8cf-affb-bf3e6a070000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
