<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 01:29:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 2-of-6 targets for 30 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 7 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff15-d651-a9df-ff15480e0000</link>
      <description>Johnston had a rough outing in this one, dropping a pass that would have gone for more than 30 yards, and another on third down during the Chargers’ eighth drive. He was also the intended receiver on an end zone interception thrown by QB Justin Herbert, and failed to put up a preventative effort when Colts S Nick Cross made a play on the ball. Johnston is a WR4/FLEX option against the Vikings on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff15-d651-a9df-ff15480e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Carter rushed 7 times for 11 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers, adding two receptions for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff14-df81-ab9b-ffd7ea880000</link>
      <description>Carter was the definitive No. 2 in the Cardinals’ backfield, ceding most early down work to Bam Knight. He did mix in on passing downs, but D’Ernest Johnson was also involved on third downs and passing downs. Knight tallied 34 snaps, Carter had 28, and Johnson had 14 in a frustrating committee. Carter was inefficient against the Packers and is no more than a low-upside RB4 after the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff14-df81-ab9b-ffd7ea880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 2-of-2 targets for 23 yards in the Chargers’ Week 7 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff15-d651-a9df-ff159f110000</link>
      <description>Harris was largely quiet in this one but nearly ripped off a long gain on the Chargers’ sixth drive. The Chargers’ rookie was taken down by a shoestring tackle by Colts S Nick Cross. Harris will likely be required to unseat WR Quentin Johnston in order to be fantasy-relevant. He is not on the FLEX radar against the Vikings next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff15-d651-a9df-ff159f110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal rushed nine times for 20 yards in the Chargers’ Week 7 loss to the Colts, adding four receptions for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1c-df81-ab9b-ffdff2a30000</link>
      <description>The Chargers’ running game was an afterthought in this one. The Colts got up 6-3 in the first quarter before tacking on 17 unanswered points in the second quarter. On the plus side, Vidal out-touched RB Hassan Haskins 13-3 and continued to take snaps in scoring position. Vidal will again be RB2-viable against the Vikings with six teams on bye next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1c-df81-ab9b-ffdff2a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 10-of-13 targets for 74 yards and two touchdowns in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1b-d99b-a1dd-ff1fd50e0000</link>
      <description>McBride continues to hit season-highs with Jacoby Brissett at quarterback. The tight end was the Cardinals’ definitive top pass-catcher and saw 13 total targets, converting those into 10 receptions for 74 yards. He nearly high-pointed a ball for an early touchdown, but the pass was broken up by Edgerrin Cooper. McBride found redemption later, scoring twice the rest of the game. His fantasy value has been elevated from good to elite with Brissett throwing him the ball. Kyler Murray is expected to return after the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye, decreasing McBride’s touchdown opportunities moving forward. McBride is still an elite fantasy TE1 the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1b-d99b-a1dd-ff1fd50e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hassan Haskins rushed once for three yards in the Chargers’ Week 7 loss to the Colts, adding two receptions for two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1f-d651-a9df-ff1f5b670000</link>
      <description>Haskins spelled RB Kimani Vidal from time to time in this one, but he is nothing more than a bench stash right now. The big-bodied plodder technically completed a hurdle against the Colts when he left his feet on a short two-legged hop as a would-be tackler barreled into his shins before faceplanting. It was an uneventful outing for Haskins beyond that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff1f-d651-a9df-ff1f5b670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 2-of-5 targets for 58 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff20-d651-a9df-ff350cbf0000</link>
      <description>Harrison cleared concussion protocol to return to the Cardinals’ offense this week. He was second on the team in targets behind Trey McBride, but only converted a pair of two long receptions. Harrison’s first target was punched out by the Packers, initially ruled a fumble but overturned to an incomplete pass. He made an excellent 35-yard sideline catch in the third quarter and drew a pass interference call, but was mostly held in check by the Packers defense. Harrison is in the high-end WR3 range coming out of the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff20-d651-a9df-ff350cbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports Titans president of football operations Chad Brinker and GM Bike Borgonzi will lead the team’s search for a new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2a-d99b-a1dd-ff2ec8a30000</link>
      <description>According to Florio, the Titans’ search for a new head coach is in the “beginning stages,” but the team does not plan to use an outside firm to conduct its search. Florio reports that the Titans plan to use an “extremely calculated process” to find their third head coach in four seasons, but we’ll see what truly comes of the search before passing judgment. The Titans have been an organizational disaster for the last several seasons and are on track to finish 2025 with their fourth-straight losing campaign. They’ll have plenty of time between now and the end of the season to say and do all of the right things as they work toward hiring a new coach, but whoever is hired will have their work cut out for them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2a-d99b-a1dd-ff2ec8a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 3-of-7 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2f-d651-a9df-ff3f82e60000</link>
      <description>Johnson and Daniel Bellinger combined for 11 targets and two touchdowns on the day. Most of Johnson’s production came on a 44-yard catch and run score in the fourth quarter in which he shed several tackles and barreled into the end zone. It was Johnson’s fourth touchdown of the 2025 season. He logged 36 routes to 21 routes for Bellinger. Though he’s not targeted at a high rate, Johnson will be a usable streaming option in Week 8 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2f-d651-a9df-ff3f82e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 6-of-12 targets for 95 yards in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff37-df81-ab9b-fff7f0c40000</link>
      <description>No other New York pass catcher saw more than seven targets. Robinson had a couple crucial fourth quarter receptions, and seemed to be Jaxson Dart’s primary target in high leverage situations. The back-and-forth game script led to a season high in targets for Robinson, who had 84 yards and a score last week against the Eagles. He’ll face off against the Eagles once again in Week 8 and should be considered a top-30 fantasy play as Dart’s top option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff37-df81-ab9b-fff7f0c40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
