<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:53:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Mike McCoy as their new assistant head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-536a-d629-a1bc-f37fdac30000</link>
      <description>This hiring makes sense for all involved. McCoy, 53, concluded his 2013-2016 run as the Chargers’ head coach with a 27-37 record. He then served as the Broncos’ (2017) and Cardinals’ (2018) offensive coordinators in one-off campaigns before spending three seasons as the Jaguars’ quarterbacks coach. The Titans hired him as a senior offensive assistant last year and promoted him to interim head coach in-season. The Raiders’ first-time head coach, Klint Kubiak, will call plays offensively while learning how to handle his other, newfound responsibilities. McCoy can help teach Kubiak team management basics, among other things.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-536a-d629-a1bc-f37fdac30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that there is still “a lot to repair” between the Raiders and EDGE Maxx Crosby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5396-d89c-a1be-ffdf55070000</link>
      <description>Raiders head coach Klint Kubiak recently said he wants Crosby “to be a part of our success going forward,” though Pelissero believes that the team is still determining whether it makes sense to keep Crosby or trade him. From Crosby’s side of things, he remains undecided as to whether he will ask to be traded. Crosby, 28, has regularly played through injuries in lost seasons with the Raiders since entering the NFL in 2019. The team’s decision to shut him down with two games to go in 2025 remains a sore spot for him. For now, the veteran pass rusher will continue dutifully rehabbing at the Raiders’ team facility after undergoing a meniscus repair in early January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5396-d89c-a1be-ffdf55070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers hired Robert Kugler as their new tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5364-d042-afbc-7ff678f20000</link>
      <description>Kugler spent the last two seasons serving as an assistant offensive line coach with the Patriots. He held the same role with the Panthers in the two prior seasons. The Pat McAfee Show’s Steelers correspondent, Mark Kaboly, notes that Krugler is a former Steelers training camp “ball boy” and son of former Steelers OL coach Sean Kugler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5364-d042-afbc-7ff678f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired Ken Zampese as their new senior offensive assistant and pass game specialist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers also hired T.J. Yates as pass game coordinator, Andrew Mitchell as assistant offensive line coach and Todd Bowles Jr. as a defensive assistant. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport previously reported both Zampese and Yates’s expected hirings. Bowles joins his father’s coaching staff after playing most recently at Long Island University in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Patriots ILB coach Zak Kuhr could replace former DC Terrell Williams, who now occupies a “high-ranking role on the staff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ca-d629-a1bc-f3dfe9480000</link>
      <description>Kuhr took over defensive play-calling duties while Williams underwent treatment for prostate cancer this season. Williams is reportedly cancer-free, and will occupy a new role next season. Rapoport labels Kuhr “a top candidate” for the Patriots’ new defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ca-d629-a1bc-f3dfe9480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals completed an interview with Seahawks DB coach and pass game coordinator Karl Scott for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53cd-d629-a1bc-f3dd72070000</link>
      <description>Scott has served in his current roles with the Seahawks for the past four seasons. He coached Vikings defensive backs in 2021 after working his way up the college coaching ranks with six different schools from 2007-2020. He served as a defensive coordinator once before, at Southeastern Louisiana in 2014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53cd-d629-a1bc-f3dd72070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Dave Borgonzi as their new linebackers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5436-d355-a5bd-df761dc30000</link>
      <description>Titans general manager Mike Borgonzi is Dave’s brother. The latter Borgonzi previously coached linebackers with the Cowboys (2025), Bears (2022-2024) and Colts (2018-2021). He held offensive and defensive assistant roles with the Cowboys and served as a defensive quality control coach with the Buccaneers before that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5436-d355-a5bd-df761dc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derek Carr said he is willing to unretire if given the opportunity to join a team that has a “chance to win a Super Bowl.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5448-d042-afbc-7ddaf4500000</link>
      <description>Carr’s comments, made during a podcast with his older brother, David, confirm a recent report from NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. David notably stated that Derek is currently healthy, and suggested a team whose colors are “purple and gold,” like the Vikings, would make for an ideal fit. The younger Carr declined to respond, but he certainly seems interested in returning to the NFL in the right situation. The Saints currently retain his contract rights. Whether they would ask for significant trade compensation to acquire him is unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5448-d042-afbc-7ddaf4500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said that the Seahawks could use the franchise tag or the transition tag to keep RB Kenneth Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54a0-d042-afbc-7df2b49b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that “it does sound like Seattle would like to keep him.” In a three-player segment, Rapoport only mentioned the transition tag in relation to Walker. The transition tag is worth less than the franchise tag, but it allows the player to go “shop” his contract offer from the his current team to see if another team will beat it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54a0-d042-afbc-7df2b49b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said the Cowboys “are going to” franchise tag WR George Pickens and could be willing to trade him away for a second-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54aa-d355-a5bd-dffef7f90000</link>
      <description>Rapoport previously suggested a tag-and-trade scenario is possible. This time, he notes that the Cowboys acquired him for a third-round pick, so sending him away for a second would be a nice value increase. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo also believes the Cowboys will franchise tag Pickens, but made it a point to express consternation over the idea of then trading him away if the Cowboys’ goal is to one day win a Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54aa-d355-a5bd-dffef7f90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
