<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:02:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 31-of-43 passes for 337 yards and three touchdowns in the Packers’ 40-40, Week 4 tie against the Cowboys, adding 28 yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9341-d95b-addb-fb477f890000</link>
      <description>Love also lost a critical fumble late in the first half that contributed to a wild change in momentum after the Packers led 13-0, eventually going into the break down 16-13. Green Bay completely controlled the game through the first 20 minutes before Dallas blocked the point after try on the team’s second touchdown and returned it for two points, sparking an abrupt turnaround in the game environment which was exacerbated by Love’s fumble two possessions later. The game then went off the rails in the second half with the two teams trading touchdowns on six consecutive possessions before a Brandon McManus field goal tied the game at 37 as time expired. The new overtime rules came into play as each team was granted a possession, both of which ended in field goals to send the teams to the first tie of the 2025 season. The tie sends the Packers into their bye ranked second in the NFC North behind the Lions, before a home meeting with the Bengals in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9341-d95b-addb-fb477f890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 22 times for 86 yards and two touchdowns in the Packers’ Week 4 tie against the Cowboys, adding 71 yards on four receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93b1-deb6-a7fd-d3ff59b10000</link>
      <description>The 157 yards from scrimmage were the most for Jacobs as a member of the Packers. It also marked his highest yardage output since the 2022 season while with the Raiders. And it wasn’t simply a function of the game going to overtime as he did not receive a touch after regulation. Jacobs’ fantasy day got off to a slow start before the veteran back punched in two second half touchdowns, rewarding fantasy managers that drafted him in the top three rounds this offseason. He briefly left the contest in the fourth quarter before not seeing the field in overtime, something the team’s Week 5 bye should remedy. Next up for Jacobs and the Packers is a home meeting with the Bengals in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93b1-deb6-a7fd-d3ff59b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 6-of-8 targets for 58 yards and three touchdowns in the Packers’ Week 4 tie against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93b7-dca3-a9fb-bfbf1ce00000</link>
      <description>Doubs scored his first two touchdowns from two and one yards out, the first on a fade to the back corner of the end zone and the second on an inside release slant where he beat his defender to the interior. He would tack on a career-high third score with 1:45 remaining in the fourth quarter to put the Packers up by four, but a quick Cowboys touchdown forced the team to march the field with under a minute to play to give kicker Brandon McManus a chance to send the game to overtime, which he would convert. Doubs remains unlikely to see elite volume on a consistent basis in a rather spread Green Bay offense but his 19 touchdowns since the 2022 season leads his rookie class, keeping him in the weekly WR3 discussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93b7-dca3-a9fb-bfbf1ce00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught 5-of-6 targets for 58 yards in the Packers’ Week 4 tie against the Cowboys, adding five yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93bc-d95b-addb-fbfe50700000</link>
      <description>Golden got off to a blazing start by catching a 46-yard dime down the sideline on the team’s first possession but would gain only 12 more yards through the air the rest of the game. His next major contribution came in overtime when he caught a 14-yard pass over the middle of the field on fourth down to keep Green Bay’s only extra time possession alive, eventually leading to a field goal as time expired to send both teams to the showers with a tie. Fantasy managers are still waiting for the unquestioned breakout from the talented rookie but should take solace in the downfield connection with Jordan Love. Golden and the Packers head to their bye in Week 5 before a Week 6 home matchup against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93bc-d95b-addb-fbfe50700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft caught all five targets for 56 yards in the Packers’ Week 4 tie against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93c1-dca3-a9fb-bfd93f980000</link>
      <description>Kraft was targeted on only five of Jordan Love’s 43 pass attempts on a night 10 Packers drew a target, making the most of his opportunities by returning a tidy 11.2 yards per reception mark. He was utilized early in the screen game before the Cowboys started dropping linebackers to clog the middle of the field, clearly fighting through an emphasis of the opposing defense throughout the night. Kraft’s elite yards per target and yards per route run values keep him squarely as a TE1 in fantasy circles as the team heads to their Week 5 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93c1-dca3-a9fb-bfd93f980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 31-of-40 passes for 319 yards and three touchdowns in the Cowboys’ 40-40, Week 4 tie against the Packers, adding two yards and a touchdown on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93c4-d6e9-af9d-9bd4cdef0000</link>
      <description>The Packers jumped out to an early 13-0 lead before Dallas special teams sparked a change in the game environment with a blocked PAT returned for two points. Dak led five touchdown drives versus just two punts following that point in the game before being held to three points in overtime, which goes down as a missed opportunity after the team had the football inside the five on first down. The most impressive touchdown drive by Prescott came after the team went down by four points with under two minutes to play, scoring to retake the lead on just four plays that took just over a minute off the clock. That score sent the Cowboys up by three, a lead they would see erased on a Green Bay field goal as time expired to send the game to extra time. The offensive eruption was made that much more impressive considering the team was playing without CeeDee Lamb after the alpha wide receiver injured his ankle in Week 3. Next up for Prescott and the Cowboys are the Jets on the road in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93c4-d6e9-af9d-9bd4cdef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams rushed 20 times for 85 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 4 tie against the Packers, adding 15 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93ca-deb6-a7fd-d3dfa1f30000</link>
      <description>Williams has now reached 100 yards from scrimmage in two of four games to start the 2025 season, narrowly missing the century mark a third time in Week 3. His early-season returns highlight a massive career turnaround following a down year in 2024 with the Broncos, rewarding fantasy managers that took the gamble in the middle rounds of drafts this offseason. He is now averaging 4.9 yards per carry through the first month of play and could see an even heavier workload after backfield mate Miles Sanders departed with an ankle injury before the half. Up next for Williams and the Cowboys are the Jets in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93ca-deb6-a7fd-d3dfa1f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 8-of-11 targets for 134 yards and two touchdowns in the Cowboys’ Week 4 tie against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93cf-dca3-a9fb-bfdf7f520000</link>
      <description>Pickens and the rest of the Dallas offense got off to a slow start before turning the tables on the Packers in the second quarter, punctuating both halves with touchdowns grabs inside of two minutes to play. He also added a highlight reel catch over two defenders with just under a minute to play in the first half to set up Dallas’ first touchdown of the game, a two-yard Dak Prescott carry on a draw. In all, it was both a fantastic real-world performance and a stellar fantasy outing in the absence of alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb. He’ll look to carry the momentum into Week 5 when the Cowboys face off against the Jets on the road.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93cf-dca3-a9fb-bfdf7f520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught all seven targets for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 4 tie against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93d3-d95b-addb-fbd7c29a0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson ranked second on the team in targets behind only George Pickens but managed to gain only 40 yards in a low-aDOT role. Even so, his third quarter touchdown was his first score since Week 13 of the 2023 season, returning yet another usable fantasy score in the absence of alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb. His next opportunity to put up meaningful counting stats comes in Week 5 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93d3-d95b-addb-fbd7c29a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Tolbert caught 4-of-6 targets for 61 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 4 tie against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93d7-dca3-a9fb-bfdf33060000</link>
      <description>Tolbert and KaVontae Turpin were both asked to step into increased roles in the absence of alpha wide receiver CeeDee Lamb, who missed the first of a projected 3-4 games with an ankle sprain in Week 4. It was Tolbert, and not Turpin, who returned usable fantasy stats in a PPR format, with the latter catching just 3-of-4 targets for 30 yards while adding four yards on his lone carry. Neither are recommended streaming options when the Cowboys take on the Jets on the road in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-93d7-dca3-a9fb-bfdf33060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
