<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d59-d95b-addb-7d5f52740000</link>
      <description>On the plus side, NBC Sports Bay Area’s Matt Maiocco does not list Jennings with a shoulder injury. It’s possible the issue is behind him now. The big-bodied wide receiver injured his shoulder in Week 1, played through it, and picked up an ankle injury in Week 2. He was unable to face the Cardinals in Week 3. As long as Jennings can at least log a limited session by the end of the week, he should be good to go for Week 4. He plays through injury whenever possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d59-d95b-addb-7d5f52740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf3-d6e9-af9d-fef38b420000</link>
      <description>Great news. Wednesday’s practice marks Purdy’s fourth consecutive session. NBC Sports Bay Area’s Matt Maiocco promisingly lists Purdy only with the toe ailment, indicating his left shoulder injury could be behind him. Purdy’s backup, QB Mac Jones (knee), aggravated a PCL sprain that he initially suffered over the summer, in the 49ers’ Week 3 win over the Cardinals. He was limited today as well. Both players’ participation is a good sign for the Week 4 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf3-d6e9-af9d-fef38b420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts (toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d61-d6e9-af9d-fff12c610000</link>
      <description>Pitts dealt with a foot issue in the offseason and popped up on the injury report with a toe injury in the middle of last week. He was limited for Thursday’s practice and returned for a full session on Friday. The toe issue will be something to monitor as the season progresses, but Pitts doesn’t appear at risk of missing Week 4. Assuming he participates in all three practices this week, Pitts will be a high-end TE2 versus the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d61-d6e9-af9d-fff12c610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d5f-d6e9-af9d-ffdf555e0000</link>
      <description>Jones sprained his PCL in training camp and reportedly aggravated the sprain in Week 3, but remained in the game to help his team secure the victory. Starting QB Brock Purdy (toe) was also limited on Wednesday. Both players are on track to be available for the 49ers’ Week 4 game against the Jaguars at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d5f-d6e9-af9d-ffdf555e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Ward (ankle/calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d67-dca3-a9fb-7dff8ecf0000</link>
      <description>Ward has been through the ringer already, taking 15 sacks through three games. He has two fumbles and threw his first interception, a pick-six, in Week 3. The sacks are clearly taking their toll on the rookie, even if the ankle and calf injuries aren’t expected to sideline him on Sunday. Ward was already off the fantasy radar, even in 2QB leagues. The injuries should give fantasy managers a good enough excuse to pull the plug on Ward for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d67-dca3-a9fb-7dff8ecf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts DT DeForest Buckner (back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d6c-dca3-a9fb-7dfddb320000</link>
      <description>A DNP to open the week isn’t ideal, but Buckner is no stranger to playing through injuries. He should be able to suit up as long as he gets in some practice reps later this week. Buckner had 6.5 sacks in 12 games last year. He is still searching for his first sack of the season in 2025 and will look to get it versus Matthew Stafford and the Rams in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d6c-dca3-a9fb-7dfddb320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks placed FB Robbie Ouzts on injured reserve with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d6b-d6e9-af9d-fffbb1af0000</link>
      <description>The fan-favorite rookie will be eligible to return after missing four games. Though not all teams utilize the fullback position, the Seahawks certainly do, and Ouzts has made a solid impression to begin his career. He boasts a 67.3 PFF run-blocking grade, ranking top three among running backs and fullbacks with at least 25 qualifying snaps. The Seahawks are on bye in Week 8. Seahawks FB Brady Russell will take over in Ouzts’ stead. The Seahawks signed S D’Anthony Bell to the active roster and S Jerrick Reed II to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d6b-d6e9-af9d-fffbb1af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d7a-d95b-addb-7d7e38770000</link>
      <description>Fuaga missed Week 3 with the pair of injuries. Trevor Penning was active but did not play. Penning was upgraded to a full participant in Wednesday’s practice and could be ready to make his first start by Sunday. Getting both linemen back in the trenches would be a notable boost for Spencer Rattler as he searches for his first NFL win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d7a-d95b-addb-7d7e38770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec reports that the Ravens’ “entire starting IDL” group did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d7b-dca3-a9fb-7dfb3cd60000</link>
      <description>The sidelined interior defenders include DT Nnamdi Madubuike (neck), DT Broderick Washington and NT Travis Jones. Injury statuses for the latter two players are currently unknown. Ravens OLB Kyle Van Noy (hamstring) also remains sidelined. Madubuike still leads the team with 10 quarterback pressures and two sacks despite sitting out in Week 3. The Ravens need the players to get healthy quickly. They face the Chiefs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d7b-dca3-a9fb-7dfb3cd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d83-d95b-addb-7dc7445a0000</link>
      <description>Collins has a lengthy injury history, but this is likely just a maintenance day for the veteran wideout. He is coming off his best game of the season with eight catches for 104 yards and a score in the Texans’ Week 3 loss to the Jags. Per usual, Collins was one of the few bright spots on an otherwise disappointing offense. Collins remains a low-end WR1 based on his elite role, even if the offense is limiting his ceiling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d83-d95b-addb-7dc7445a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
