<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright is active for Week 7 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-da18-a39b-ff3336990000</link>
      <description>Healthy scratched in recent weeks, Wright is up for a game expected to feature awful weather on the shores of Lake Erie. It is worth noting that rookie Ollie Gordon II hasn’t exactly been lighting it up as De’Von Achane’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-da18-a39b-ff3336990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker (quad) is active for Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-d651-a9df-fd3531f00000</link>
      <description>With Coker activated, WR Hunter Renfrow — who had taken on the full-time slot role in Carolina — is a healthy scratch. Coker could see a significant role in the run-heavy Panthers offense, operating as the team’s No. 2 wideout behind Tetairoa McMillan. Coker is a workable fantasy option in 14-team leagues. Other Carolina inactives for Week 7: RB DeeJay Dallas, G Damien Lewis, TE James Mitchell, DT Cam Jackson, and DT Jaden Crumedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-d651-a9df-fd3531f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (groin) is officially active for Week 7 against the New Orleans Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd23-da18-a39b-ff335b890000</link>
      <description>A report had come out on Saturday that Swift was trending towards playing, and he said himself that he was going to, but now we have the official word. While the rain should stop before kickoff on Sunday, the wind gusts could be up to 30 mph, which means both the Bears and Saints could look to use their running and short passing game more than normal. Swift should be fired up as an RB2, especially after the Bears seemed to fix their running game during the bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd23-da18-a39b-ff335b890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) will not play in Week 7.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd21-d651-a9df-fd35ff0e0000</link>
      <description>This was expected all along after Bowers entered the weekend listed as doubtful. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported early Sunday that the team is hopeful Bowers will be able to return after its Week 8 bye, meaning Michael Mayer will again draw the start for a depleted Raiders pass-catching corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd21-d651-a9df-fd35ff0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared DT Grady Jarrett, K Cairo Santos, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, G Luke Newman, LB Noah Sewell, WR Jahdae Walker, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 7 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd25-d651-a9df-fd358f7f0000</link>
      <description>Jarrett, who has been battling a knee injury, was said to be likely to suit up on Sunday, but that will not be the case. With the weather making this likely to be a run-heavy game, Jarrett being out is a slight bump for Alvin Kamara and Kendre Miller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd25-d651-a9df-fd358f7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared S Ugo Amadi, CB Rejzohn Wright, CB Isaac Yiadom, DT Jonah Williams, OL Torricelli Simpkins III, and OL Xavier Truss inactive for Week 7 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd27-df81-ab9b-ffe780010000</link>
      <description>No surprises here. The Saints will be relatively healthy heading into the Week 7 showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd27-df81-ab9b-ffe780010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Patrick (groin) will not return in Week 7 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd24-da18-a39b-ff377c3b0000</link>
      <description>The Jags also ruled out safety Eric Murray (neck) for the remainder of the game. Patrick’s day ends with one catch for 22 yards. His absence will free up some routes for Dyami Brown and Parker Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd24-da18-a39b-ff377c3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports EDGE Brandon Graham is “strongly considering coming out of retirement to sign with Philadelphia.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd3b-da18-a39b-ff3bb82f0000</link>
      <description>Graham hung up the cleats after bringing home his second Lombardi Trophy last season. The 37-year-old played a part-time role in 2024 and missed two months with a torn tricep. He returned for a minor role in the Super Bowl, giving him a fairytale ending to a storied career. The Eagles are dealing with multiple injuries along their defensive line and the pass-rush has suffered as a result. Graham’s return, even for a rotational role, would bolster the defense as Philly eyes another postseason run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd3b-da18-a39b-ff3bb82f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports Chuba Hubbard took the first reps when the Panthers first lined up their starters for warmups.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd4c-df81-ab9b-ffcf477c0000</link>
      <description>Rico Dowdle was second in the order. This isn’t definitive proof that Hubbard is the starter, but it’s the best intel fantasy managers are going to get before kickoff. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler previously reported that the Carolina backs will trade series early in the game, with things potentially changing as the contest goes on. At this point, fantasy managers should treat both runners as high-risk RB3s in a good matchup with a putrid Jets defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd4c-df81-ab9b-ffcf477c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught 3-of-7 targets for 31 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 7 loss to the Rams before exiting with an apparent shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd56-df81-ab9b-ffd7da4f0000</link>
      <description>Thomas was laboring through an injury or two throughout this game and finally went down on a light push from a Rams defender with less than five minutes to play. He appeared to be in tremendous pain and was assisted off the field by trainers. Down by four touchdowns, BTJ had no chance of returning. It’s a nightmare end to a frustrating day for the young wideout. The Jags failed to get much going on offense and Thomas Jr. committed multiple drops. He gave one up early while trying to avoid contact on a middle-of-the-field strike from Trevor Lawrence. Another came on a much-needed deep shot later in the game. If Thomas misses any time, Travis Hunter is set to take over the No. 1 role in Jacksonville, putting him in the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd56-df81-ab9b-ffd7da4f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
