<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith (hamstring) won’t play in Los Angeles’ Wild Card game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a42d-d968-a19b-fcfd9ac70000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week. The rookie would enter next week with a questionable tag if the Chargers survive in New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a42d-d968-a19b-fcfd9ac70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OT Jamaree Salyer (hamstring) is not on Los Angeles’ final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a42f-d56e-afff-e6ef0a330000</link>
      <description>It’s great news for Herbert as Salyer is the best option the Chargers currently have at left tackle. He’ll be an incremental upgrade for Herbert after leaving Week 17’s loss to the Texans, likely sending Austin Deculus back to the bench. CB Donte Jackson (ankle) will also play in this one and was removed from the injury report as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a42f-d56e-afff-e6ef0a330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys completed an interview with Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a432-d56e-afff-e6fafa7a0000</link>
      <description>The process for moving past fired DC Matt Eberflus is in its opening stages. Jones, 47, hasn’t called plays for a defense since his brief stint as LSU defensive coordinator in 2021. He does have plenty of high-level defensive experience and specializes in defensive back play, which makes him a good thought for a Cowboys back seven that figures to have a lot of turnover this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a432-d56e-afff-e6fafa7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) told reporters “training camp is the goal” when asked when he would return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a43f-d56e-afff-e6ff3d5a0000</link>
      <description>Skattebo dislocated his ankle in late October and was given a 4-6 month recovery timetable at the time. “Getting my dorsiflexion in the foot is the main thing obviously,” Skattebo said. “I was stuck in a boot for eight weeks. Just strengthening it up. I broke my bone and dislocated my ankle. So anything you can imagine to get the ankle moving again is what I have to get up.” Given that this timetable would bump up against most May team activities, it’s possible the Giants play it slow and that we don’t see much of Skattebo at early offseason activities. Still, this is an encouraging update overall and Skattebo figures to have control of the backfield if healthy after staging an early-season takeover from Tyrone Tracy in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a43f-d56e-afff-e6ff3d5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (right quad) is questionable for Buffalo’s Wild Card game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a446-d56e-afff-e6ee4cba0000</link>
      <description>With a practice report of DNP-Full-DNP, we’re not entirely sure what to believe here. What we know is that if the Bills trust Prater to kick through this, they’ll roll with him on Sunday. If not, Matthew Wright will get the #RevengeGame honors against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a446-d56e-afff-e6ee4cba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed their interview with Seahawks DC Aden Durde for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a440-d35e-a1bf-e5c2fecb0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks’ defense allowed the fewest yards per pass play (6.03) and run play (3.7) in Durde’s second season serving as the team’s defensive coordinator. He served as the Cowboys’ defensive line coach (2021-2023) and Falcons’ linebackers coach (2020) in his two prior stops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a440-d35e-a1bf-e5c2fecb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) is not on Buffalo’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a448-d56e-afff-e6e87b790000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday after two limited sessions and figures to be a key figure in the Sunday Wild Card showdown with Jacksonville. The Bills will likely need him to pop a few big plays against the Jaguars split-safety coverages to spring a road win. This knee has kept Kincaid on the report often in the second half of the season and figures to be an issue again next week if the Bills advance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a448-d56e-afff-e6e87b790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) is questionable for Buffalo’s Wild Card game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44a-dc7a-af9b-efffc4ce0000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited Friday practice to hit the questionable line after a pair of missed sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. Even if Johnson is active, the Bills could lean a little more on Ray Davis if they don’t trust what the saw on Friday. Johnson’s hard to trust in DFS and Playoff Best Ball lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44a-dc7a-af9b-efffc4ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Terrel Bernard (calf) won’t play in Buffalo’s Wild Card game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44c-d56e-afff-e6ec669e0000</link>
      <description>Bernard injured the calf in Week 17 and has not practiced yet while earning a pair of rule-outs. Dorian Williams and Joe Andreessen saw all the linebacker snaps against the Jets in a meaningless Week 18, while we’d expect to see Shaq Thompson and Matt Milano out there for the Bills on Sunday against the Jaguars. Buffalo also ruled out 2025 first-round CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle), who injured himself late in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44c-d56e-afff-e6ec669e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
