<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 7-of-11 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 5 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a857-d95b-addb-e857667f0000</link>
      <description>Aside from the yards, it was an evening of new career highs across the board, while the touchdown was Tonges’ third in five 2025 appearances. This, after he entered the season with one career target and zero catches. Tonges has exceeded the wildest expectations for his George Kittle caretaking, but Kittle is eligible to return from his hamstring injury in Week 6, and the early reports are that he just may do so. Tonges’ time in the fantasy TE2 sun could be at an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a857-d95b-addb-e857667f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chuba Hubbard (calf) “is expected to miss” Week 5’s game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa03-dca3-a9fb-bf9b80ba0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard’s calf injury will require at least a one-game absence. The Panthers’ RB1, while not officially ruled out by the team, is expected to miss Week 5 against the Dolphins, per Rapoport, which would put Rico Dowdle in line for lead duties. Hopefully, this is only a one-week thing for Hubbard, who has struggled out of the gate. After breaking out for 250-1,195-10 on the ground last season, Hubbard has totaled just 217 scoreless yards on 53 carries this season, but has found the end zone twice through the air. Fantasy managers who add Dowdle can view him as a fringe RB2/RB3 against a Miami defense that’s allowed the third-most rushing yards per game and fourth-highest YPC (5.1) to its opponents this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa03-dca3-a9fb-bf9b80ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent DE Drake Jackson is scheduled to meet with the Jets, Commanders, and Ravens in the coming days.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</link>
      <description>Jackson was waived with a failed injury designation earlier this offseason after a knee injury prematurely ended his 2023 campaign and kept him out for all of 2024. Now cleared for a return, the former second-round pick has totaled six sacks in 23 career games, but could provide help to a team in need of bolstering its pass rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (ankle) will play in Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</link>
      <description>Garrett was a DNP to open the week and was upgraded to a limited participant in Thursday’s practice. Garrett’s injury doesn’t appear too severe at this point. We would expect him to see his normal assortment of snaps as he looks to get after Carson Wentz in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Newsome (hamstring) is questionable for Week 5’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</link>
      <description>Newsome popped up on Thursday’s injury report with a hamstring and will officially be questionable entering the week. It’s never a good sign when a player is a late addition to the injury report, and the Browns will need all hands on deck if they hope to slow the receiving duo of Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison. If he’s unable to go, backup Myles Harden appears next in line to receive snaps. In addition to Newsome, RT Jack Conklin (elbow), who hasn’t played since Week 1, is also questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out J.J. McCarthy (ankle) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa27-dca3-a9fb-bfbf8d000000</link>
      <description>It was reported shortly after McCarthy suffered his ankle injury that the Vikings were hoping McCarthy could return for Week 7, so a Week 5 absence has long been expected. McCarthy was a DNP in practice all week, despite hopes he would be able to suit up at some point. McCarthy will have a bye in Week 6 to get right before trying to take the field in Week 7. Carson Wentz will again start for the Vikings in Sunday’s game in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa27-dca3-a9fb-bfbf8d000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out C Ryan Kelly (concussion) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa30-d95b-addb-ea7652f10000</link>
      <description>In addition to Kelly, backup center Michael Jurgens (hamstring) has also been ruled out. The Vikings will also be out RT Brian O’Neill (knee) and LG Donovan Jackson (wrist), leaving the offensive line particularly thin against a physical Browns defensive front that’s led by Myles Garrett. With a Week 6 bye on the horizon, the Vikings will hope a week away will give their team plenty of time to heal up once they return stateside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa30-d95b-addb-ea7652f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa35-deb6-a7fd-fbff3c4d0000</link>
      <description>Van Ginkel suffered his neck injury in Week 2 and hasn’t been heard from since. The veteran linebacker has yet to return to the practice field, but will have a Week 6 bye before setting his sights on Week 7 against the Eagles. The Vikings’ decision not to place him on injured reserve suggests they believe he could return after the bye, but the proof will be in his practice status ahead of Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa35-deb6-a7fd-fbff3c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers DT Kalia Davis will undergo surgery to repair a broken hand.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa3a-dca3-a9fb-bfbb8b940000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport was first to report the surgery. According to Rap, Davis “could miss as few as two games,” and the fourth-year lineman is expected to return to play with a club on his hand. Davis has totaled seven tackles and two TFLs in five starts for the 49ers this season, and is quietly stepping into a key role for Kyle Shanahan’s defense after spending the previous two seasons as a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa3a-dca3-a9fb-bfbb8b940000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
