<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Davante Adams (oblique) will be ready to play in Week 11 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a12-d1e7-a1fa-7afa785c0000</link>
      <description>Adams did not practice Wednesday. The veteran wideout left Week 10 late in the game while holding his back in pain. McVay later told reporters that he could have returned if needed. Adams is up to nine receiving touchdowns this year after scoring another last week. Even as the clear WR2 in LA’s offense, he is pushing for a WR1 ranking heading into a must-win game versus the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a12-d1e7-a1fa-7afa785c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder/toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a1b-d1e7-a1fa-7afbfdd70000</link>
      <description>Jones was held out of last Wednesday’s practice entirely and still suited up. He should have no issues playing in Week 11. In Week 10, Jones led the Vikings with nine carries, which he turned into 47 scoreless yards. Jordan Mason only saw four attempts. As the lead back of the team, Jones could work his way into the RB2 ranks for a Week 11 date with the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a1b-d1e7-a1fa-7afbfdd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a26-d45b-affe-7fb61fdb0000</link>
      <description>Schultz has been dealing with the shoulder issue for a few weeks and it hasn’t cost him any playing time yet. He should be able to return to practice later this week, though fantasy managers may want to keep an eye on the situation. Schultz caught 7-of-11 targets in Week 10 against the Jags. He will push for a low-end TE1 ranking if there aren’t any surprises with the shoulder issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a26-d45b-affe-7fb61fdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a2f-d1e7-a1fa-7aef31320000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez played ahead of rookie Jacory Croskey-Merritt in the first half of the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions. He then hurt his shoulder in the third quarter and JCM took over. Rodriguez did not return after playing just one snap in the second half. A limited practice suggests he should be good to go for Week 11 versus Miami. In a game that could be close, Rodriguez will have some RB3 potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a2f-d1e7-a1fa-7aef31320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a33-d45b-affe-7fb72e240000</link>
      <description>Gordon was active last week but only saw one carry. Jaylen Wright operated as the backup to De’Von Achane, seeing five rush attempts. With the backup role now undecided, neither Gordon nor Wright should be cracking any fantasy lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a33-d45b-affe-7fb72e240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 11 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a36-d1e7-a1fa-7afe8d2e0000</link>
      <description>Mims returned to practice last week, but a short turnaround to Thursday Night Football made it impossible for him to clear the league’s concussion protocol in time. A full practice today puts him on track to be cleared well ahead of Sunday’s game against the Chiefs. Mims has been stuck in a part-time role this year but is still capable of breaking long plays. He will be a WR5 for his first game in three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a36-d1e7-a1fa-7afe8d2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions CB Terrion Arnold (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a64-d1e7-a1fa-7aee834d0000</link>
      <description>Arnold is in concussion protocol after exiting the Lions’ Week 10 win over the Commanders. He did not practice on Wednesday, putting his Week 11 status in jeopardy. If Arnold cannot go, veteran Rock Ya-Sin will take his place starting on the perimeter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a64-d1e7-a1fa-7aee834d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a74-d713-ad9e-7e74b6a30000</link>
      <description>Knight is dealing with an ankle issue to begin Week 11. The 24-year-old touched the ball 11 times for an inefficient 33 yards in Week 10 with Emari Demercado posting a more efficient game. If Knight cannot go this week against the 49ers, Michael Carter enters the fray again while Demercado is in the RB3 range. Knight is a touchdown-dependent RB3 play when healthy while Trey Benson remains on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a74-d713-ad9e-7e74b6a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a7c-d673-a39e-fefd10b70000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed Week 10 with back/hip issues and is trending to miss Week 11 as well. Also not practicing on the defense were LB Baron Browning (concussion), LB Mack Wilson (ribs), or S Dadrion Taylor-Demerson (ankle). The Cardinals defense is hurting heading into a Week 11 matchup against the 49ers and each of these players will need to log a practice to have a chance to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a7c-d673-a39e-fefd10b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden (quad) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a83-d45b-affe-7f97d37a0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden gets the best possible start to the week as the Chargers list him as a full participant for Wednesday’s practice. Despite not returning in Week 10 against the Steelers, Gadsden’s MRI did not show any major issues and is now participating fully in practice. He is now on track to play Week 11 against the Jaguars, where he should be in the low-end TE1 range for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a83-d45b-affe-7f97d37a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
