<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports “financial hurdles remain before any potential Adam Thielen-Vikings reunion can occur.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d293-dbe3-a9bb-f2d3ad980000</link>
      <description>Russini points out that in March, the Panthers bumped up Thielen’s 2025 salary. The 35-year-old receiver comes with a cap hit just north of $10.108 million this season, per Over the Cap, and the Vikings have already been working to increase their cap flexibility with the trade of Harrison Phillips earlier in the week. Thielen would be a natural fit in the Vikings’ offense if a trade is able to get done, but there’s still plenty to work out here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d293-dbe3-a9bb-f2d3ad980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released WR Zach Pascal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d2e0-d332-a1fd-d6f6ffee0000</link>
      <description>Pascal is again looking for work after being a part of the Giants’ initial cutdown to 53 players. The 30-year-old receiver has bounced between three different teams since 2022 and didn’t catch a pass in 17 games with the Cardinals last season. In addition to Pascal, the Giants also cut WR Jordan Bly, LB K.J. Cloyd, CB O’Donnell Fortune, LB Dyontae Johnson, C Jimmy Morrissey, WR Montrell Washington, and OL Jaison Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d2e0-d332-a1fd-d6f6ffee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers released QB Logan Woodside.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d30a-dbe3-a9bb-f35b5fe80000</link>
      <description>The Steelers also released LB Kenny Willekes and LS Jake McQuaide and waived RB Evan Hull, CB Kam Alexander, S Quindell Johnson, DB Kyler McMichael, DB Mikey Victor, OG Doug Nester, OT Julian Pearl and TE Kevin Foelsch. The two biggest names here are Woodside and Hull. Both players will likely be offered tryouts and/or practice squad spots at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d30a-dbe3-a9bb-f35b5fe80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler said the Cowboys would need a “Herculean” offer to consider trading EDGE Micah Parsons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d306-d332-a1fd-d7361ea30000</link>
      <description>Fowler uses the Cowboys’ 1989 Herschel Walker trade with the Vikings as an example. The Vikings gave the Cowboys five players attached to conditional draft picks, plus six more future draft picks, to acquire the star running back. Fowler adds that the Cowboys have received “multiple trade inquiries” for Parsons, but the team is currently “not entertaining” them. Fowler’s Cowboys sources “remain optimistic” about signing Parsons to an extension, but “on the players’ side, not so much optimism.” Fowler also said that the Packers, Cardinals, Ravens and “even some teams in Dallas’ own division,” make sense as potential trade partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d306-d332-a1fd-d7361ea30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed CB Tre Avery, formerly of the Patriots, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d358-dbe3-a9bb-f35be8f70000</link>
      <description>Avery forced one incompletion on eight targets, playing for the Patriots in the 2025 preseason. He played for both the Titans and 49ers in 2024. The Buccaneers waived WR Jaden Smith in a corresponding move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d358-dbe3-a9bb-f35be8f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots waived TE Jaheim Bell.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d364-d332-a1fd-d776eae60000</link>
      <description>Bell was an intriguing receiving tight end in the 2024 NFL Draft. The Patriots also waived RB Micah Bernard, DT Philip Blidi, DB Isaiah Bolden, TE Cole Fotheringham, WR Phil Lutz, LB R.J. Moten, CB Jordan Polk, OG Tyrese Robinson, OG Sidy Sow, RB Shane Watts and QB Ben Wooldridge and released DT Kyle Peko, LB Monty Rice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d364-d332-a1fd-d776eae60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) expected to miss “about a month” and is a candidate to begin the year on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d373-d332-a1fd-d77721620000</link>
      <description>Harmon was diagnosed with an MCL sprain. No word yet on the specific severity. Being placed on injured reserve would require him to miss at least four games, and the Steelers notably have a Week 5 bye. The good news is that the Steelers will get their first-round rookie back this year. The bad news is that they face four capable rushing offenses to begin the year (Jets, Seahawks, Patriots and Vikings).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d373-d332-a1fd-d77721620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OT Charles Cross (finger) participated in team drills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d31b-dbe3-a9bb-f35bdf930000</link>
      <description>The occasion marks Cross’ first full-contact practice participation since late July. ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports that this “puts him ahead of [head coach Mike] Macdonald’s initial timeline and serves as an obvious indication he’ll be play[ing] in the opener.” It’s great news for Sam Darnold, who has the 49ers’ pass rush on tap in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d31b-dbe3-a9bb-f35bdf930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released TE Dalton Keene.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3af-de13-afdc-d7ef6b7f0000</link>
      <description>The Texans released Keene (hamstring) and waived WR Xavier Johnson (hand) from injured reserve with injury settlements. Both moves are in relation to cutdown day, coming up next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3af-de13-afdc-d7ef6b7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exhibit’s Josina Anderson reports the Vikings are “not likely” to trade for Panthers WR Adam Thielen “at this point.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3cc-de13-afdc-d7cf7ccc0000</link>
      <description>That makes two national reporters who have pumped the brakes on a potential Thielen-Vikings reunion. Both Anderson and The Athletic’s Dianna Russini highlighted the potential deal’s financial speed bumps while also stopping short of fully ruling out the trade between the two teams at some point. If the Panthers are willing to take on some of Thielen’s contract to facilitate the trade, the Vikings might be willing to make the move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3cc-de13-afdc-d7cf7ccc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
