<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:25:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) was listed as a DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9778-d95b-addb-ff7ea8910000</link>
      <description>Here we go again. Just over 24 hours after making his return from a toe injury that sidelined him for two weeks, Purdy is now dealing with a flare up of the same injury that could cost him another game this week. To amplify matters, the 49ers play on Thursday against the Rams, making for a short turnaround time for the Niners’ QB1 to get right and suit up. It’s early, but fantasy managers hoping to have Purdy this week should prepare for another Mac Jones start if his absence extends further into the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9778-d95b-addb-ff7ea8910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports an MRI revealed a high-ankle sprain for Chargers LT Joe Alt.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-977b-dca3-a9fb-bffb89570000</link>
      <description>Alt was already looking at a multi-week absence, but Rapoport reports that Alt will “seek various opinions to determine how long he’s out.” Hopefully, this isn’t a sign of an absence that’s longer than already expected. The Chargers now find themselves down both tackle spots, a harsh reality that was felt on Sunday by Justin Herbert, who was pressured 20 times in Sunday’s loss to the Giants, per PFF. Backup Austin Deculus took over for Alt and played 53 snaps in Week 4. He’s the favorite to handle the starting left tackle spot going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-977b-dca3-a9fb-bffb89570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) was listed as a “DNP” on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9777-d95b-addb-ff7715c10000</link>
      <description>The 49ers did not hold practice on Monday as they prepare for a Thursday Night Football divisional matchup against the Rams, but it is nonetheless notable that Pearsall was estimated as a non-participant after he felt “a little bit of instability” in the team’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars. The 49ers remain one of the most injured teams in the league, which has seemingly been a yearly occurrence for Shanahan’s squad. Fantasy managers will want to monitor his practice status Tuesday to see if alternate plans will need to be made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9777-d95b-addb-ff7715c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers listed WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder, ankle) as a “DNP” on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-978e-d95b-addb-ffceebcc0000</link>
      <description>Jennings has been fighting through injuries for over two months now, something that continues after he gutted through shoulder and ankle injuries in Week 4. He was unable to return usable counting stats against the Jaguars and now has a quick turnaround with a Week 5 matchup against the Rams on Thursday Night Football on tap. Jennings has proven to be an integral part of the passing offense in the absences of George Kittle and Brandon Aiyuk, but his health will have to cooperate to return WR3 numbers for fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-978e-d95b-addb-ffceebcc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings OT Brian O’Neill (knee) suffered a sprained MCL in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9792-deb6-a7fd-d7dfe10e0000</link>
      <description>The injury is likely to sideline the veteran tackle for multiple weeks after injuring his knee in the first quarter of the team’s Week 4 game against the Steelers in Dublin, Ireland. Three of five starting offensive linemen are currently sidelined in Minnesota, something highly likely to influence their offensive efficiency while playing with backup Carson Wentz under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9792-deb6-a7fd-d7dfe10e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared RB Jaleel McLaughlin, QB Sam Ehlinger, LB Que Robinson, OT Frank Crum, TE Lucas Krull, and DL Jordan Jackson inactive for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97a7-dca3-a9fb-bfbfcee40000</link>
      <description>McLaughlin has been a healthy scratch throughout the season while Krull continues to deal with a toe injury sustained in preseason. The Broncos are looking to bounce back from consecutive close losses after dropping Week 2 by a point to the Colts and Week 3 by three points to the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97a7-dca3-a9fb-bfbfcee40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared TE Noah Fant, WR Jermaine Burton, DT McKinnley Jackson, DT Howard Cross III, and DE Shemar Stewart inactive for Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97aa-d95b-addb-ffee48db0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals continue to hurt along the defensive line but have played above their talent level with new defensive coordinator Al Golden, but have been victimized on the ground due to mounting injuries through three games. They face a difficult test against the Broncos Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97aa-d95b-addb-ffee48db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (hip) is active for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97ae-dca3-a9fb-bfbfe12b0000</link>
      <description>Mims was a late-week addition to the team’s injury report with a hip injury Saturday, ultimately doing enough in pre-game workouts to be active against the Bengals. His presence is more of a boost to the offense than boon to his individual fantasy value considering his downfield, yet limited, role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97ae-dca3-a9fb-bfbfe12b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Braelon Allen (knee) headed to locker room Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97b1-d95b-addb-fff794170000</link>
      <description>Allen was hit hard in the knee during a kickoff return in the second quarter, eventually taken to the locker room ahead of the half. There has yet to be an update passed by the team but it certainly appears as if his night is done. Allen gained 26 yards on four carries and lost a fumble at the goal line prior to departing. Expect both Breece Hall and Isaiah Davis to see a slight uptick in usage in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97b1-d95b-addb-fff794170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Tyreek Hill (leg) was carted to the locker room in the third quarter of Week 4 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97fa-d6e9-af9d-9ffa30890000</link>
      <description>Hill is almost certainly done for the season with what looked like a gruesome lower leg injury. Team training staffs were both on the scene after the injury happened, cutting his cleat off to stabilize his leg. He was seen with a smile as he was carted to the locker room. Jaylen Waddle and Malik Washington will be tasked with stepping up through the air in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97fa-d6e9-af9d-9ffa30890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
