<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea4e-d94a-a79d-eb4f6c5e0000</link>
      <description>It is becoming increasingly likely that Bowers sits until after the Raiders’ Week 8 bye. Fantasy managers have not gotten the expected production out of an injured Bowers and will now have to pivot as he continues to miss time. Michael Mayer is now the sole No. 1 tight end for the Raiders and will be a low-end TE1 in Week 7 should Bowers remain out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea4e-d94a-a79d-eb4f6c5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea5c-db72-a199-fa5fcda10000</link>
      <description>Watson is nearing a return from the PUP list after tearing his ACL late last season. He was limited in last week’s practices and not activated for Week 6, but starts out Week 7 logging another limited session. Watson will likely need a full practice before he is officially activated and certainly could get there for this week’s matchup against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea5c-db72-a199-fa5fcda10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Jordy Nelson upheld Lions S Brian Branch’s one-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea62-dd4c-afb9-efe39e980000</link>
      <description>Branch was given a one-game suspension by the NFL for starting an on-field fight between the Chiefs and Lions on Sunday night. Nelson, best known for his career as a wide receiver with the Packers, was jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA to hear Branch’s appeal. He upholds the suspension, keeping Branch out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ea62-dd4c-afb9-efe39e980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) is “considered a long shot” to play in Week 7 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ecfc-d651-a9df-edfd4ba20000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson was absent from all three practices this week before being listed as questionable. Players rarely play without a single practice on the books and the short turnaround to a Thursday game makes it even more unlikely Hendrickson is out there tonight. Hendrickson has four sacks on 23 pressures this season. Losing him will be a big blow to a defense that was already struggling to keep opponents in check this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ecfc-d651-a9df-edfd4ba20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Mike Evans (hamstring) is expected to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ed17-da18-a39b-ff17d7930000</link>
      <description>It will likely be a limited session for Evans, but it’s still a big step in the right direction. Evans has been out since Week 3 with the hamstring issue. This will be his first practice post-injury. With Chris Godwin out for Week 7 and Emeka Egbuka likely out as well, Evans’ return will be crucial for the Bucs’ receiving room. Assuming he does play, Evans will dominate targets in a potential shootout with the Lions. He will immediately return to a high-end WR2 ranking this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ed17-da18-a39b-ff17d7930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ed40-d99b-a1dd-ff4cc0c30000</link>
      <description>Egbuka went down with the hamstring issue in Week 6 and is likely going to miss at least one game. The Bucs get their bye in Week 9, so it wouldn’t be surprising for them to hold the rookie out two games, allowing him to return in Week 10 after a lengthy recovery period. With Chris Godwin also out for Week 7, a returning Mike Evans will be the focal point of the Bucs’ passing attack, putting him in the WR2 ranks for his first game in a month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ed40-d99b-a1dd-ff4cc0c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) will not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edec-d651-a9df-edfd28190000</link>
      <description>Campbell did note that Decker could return to practice later this week. The Lions play on Monday, giving them one extra day of prep. Decker labored through this shoulder injury early in the year but was eventually put on the bench to heal. He has been out since Week 4. Dan Skipper will start at left tackle if Decker remains out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edec-d651-a9df-edfd28190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (concussion) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b1-dd4c-afb9-eff1cd6f0000</link>
      <description>Both Downs and WR Ashton Dulin (chest) were absent during the portion of practice that is open to the media. We expect both players to be listed as non-participants. This is bad news. Players must pass through all five phases of the NFL’s concussion protocol, while remaining setback-free, before they can return from a concussion. Even if a concussed player resumes practicing late in the week, the protocol adds a unique hurdle to the return-to-play process. Should Downs practice in full on Friday, he must then successfully meet post-practice observation standards. The Colts’ slot receiver has not yet been ruled out, and he does still have a chance to play, but he is trending toward a Week 7 absence. Colts WR Adonai Mitchell will seemingly get a shot at redemption against the Chargers with Dulin also ailing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b1-dd4c-afb9-eff1cd6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Ashton Dulin (chest) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edfe-d99b-a1dd-fffe53f80000</link>
      <description>Both Dulin and slot receiver Josh Downs (concussion) were not present during the portion of practice that is open to the media. Dulin could still get on the field this weekend by returning to practice on Friday, but both players appear to be heading toward a Week 7 absence. Embattled second-year WR Adonai Mitchell could get a chance to rebound from his costly Week 4 fumble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edfe-d99b-a1dd-fffe53f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pauline reports that the Seahawks would be willing to trade CB Riq Woolen for Dolphins RB De’Von Achane “if the opportunity existed.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee02-da18-a39b-fe13d3470000</link>
      <description>Per Pauline, “even if no such deal [involving Woolen] is available, Seattle could make a move for the ball carrier if Miami continues to lose games and chooses to sell off pieces.” The Seahawks are apparently very interested in Achane’s “speed and home run-hitting ability not presently found at running back for the Seahawks.” Speed and home-run hitting ability sound an awful lot like RB Kenneth Walker III’s skillset. Walker is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. The 4-2 Seahawks are currently fifth in the NFC, and GM John Schneider spent the offseason harping on the importance of locker room harmony. Pauline does not address whether a follow-up trade involving one of the incumbent running backs could occur, and the Dolphins must first be willing to part ways with a talented, young running back under contract through 2026, for a second trade to even be considered. No reporter is perfect, but Pauline has reported accurately on Seahawks happenings during the Schneider era. Whether the Seahawks successfully acquire Achane remains to be seen, but it sounds like they could be in play for a speedy running back before the November 4th trade deadline, regardless. Achane’s fantasy-scoring ceiling would likely take a hit if he is thrust into a split backfield in Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee02-da18-a39b-fe13d3470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
