<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Falcons could be “conservative” with playing Drake London (knee) in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d82c-a79a-b3be66fc0000</link>
      <description>It’s potentially bad new for London drafters who expected him back in Week 13 and beyond after head coach Raheem Morris said on Wednesday that he was hopeful the star wideout could come back after a one-week absence. Pelissero said London’s knee issue is considered “tricky” to manage. The Falcons could drop out of postseason contention if they lose to the Saints in Week 12, making it more likely the team would rest London and not rush him back into game action. Until his return, Darnell Mooney will function as the de facto WR1 for Atlanta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d82c-a79a-b3be66fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports “there is a good chance” that Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) is good to go for Week 13 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1c9-db57-afda-f7fb62ff0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is missing his third straight game because of the ankle injury today. He has been back at practice for two weeks but has never progressed beyond a limited session. It seems like he may need to get in a full practice before the team clears him for action. If that happens next week, BTJ will return for a WR2 fantasy outlook against a weak Tennessee defense. Jakobi Meyers will hold down the fort as the team’s top wideout for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1c9-db57-afda-f7fb62ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LG Jared Wilson was carted to the locker room in Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1ed-d90e-a9da-bfefb3760000</link>
      <description>Wilson was injured on the first drive of the game. He was able to hobble off the field and into the blue medical tent, but the cart was brought out to take him into the locker room. Ben Brown will come in to replace him, but this is a situation to monitor for Rhamondre Stevenson and TreVeyon Henderson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1ed-d90e-a9da-bfefb3760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals CB Marco Wilson has been ruled out for the rest of Week 12 against the Patriots with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b20b-d413-ad9f-b7df36440000</link>
      <description>The Bengals’ defense has struggled enough this year, so losing a starting cornerback is not ideal. We’ll see if Drake Maye and the Patriots are able to take advantage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b20b-d413-ad9f-b7df36440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RT Morgan Moses is questionable to return to Week 12 against the Bengals with an illness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b218-db57-afda-f63a43790000</link>
      <description>The Patriots already lost starting left guard Jared Wilson to an injury on the first drive, so this would be a big blow to their offensive line. The Bengals have been able to get pressure on Drake Maye often to start this game, and that could continue if Moses can’t come back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b218-db57-afda-f63a43790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers CB Keisean Nixon (neck) left Green Bay’s Week 12 game with the Vikings and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b237-d90e-a9da-bf3f45db0000</link>
      <description>He suffered a stinger. Kamal Hadden took over at outside corner for the Packers. Luckily for them, Minnesota doesn’t seem to have any interesting in throwing the football today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b237-d90e-a9da-bf3f45db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (knee) is active for Week 12 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b239-d413-ad9f-b7fd44a30000</link>
      <description>Conklin was the only member of the Browns listed as questionable for this game. Inactive for the Browns are QB Dillon Gabriel, RB Raheim Sanders, OG Zak Zinter, OT Cornelius Lucas, WR Jamari Thrash, and DE Alex Wright.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b239-d413-ad9f-b7fd44a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared QB Aidan O’Connell, RB Zamir White, LB Jamin Davis, DL Leki Fotu, and DT Tonka Hemingway inactive for Week 12 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b23c-d413-ad9f-b7fdde1e0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell was activated from injured reserve earlier this week. He is currently behind Kenny Pickett on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b23c-d413-ad9f-b7fdde1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) is active for Week 12 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b237-d90e-a9da-bf3f0fb60000</link>
      <description>Strange makes his return from injured reserve against a Cardinals defense that enters Week 12 having allowed the 12th-most receiving yards (617) to opposing tight ends. Players returning from lengthy, injury-induced absences make for risky starts. Strange could be a tad rusty, and the Jaguars’ pass-catching corps looks quite a bit different than it did when he last played, in Week 5. Strange must be viewed as a highly volatile fantasy option this week. The Jaguars declared WR Brian Thomas Jr., CB Jourdan Lewis, RB Cody Schrader, EDGE Travon Walker, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Anton Harrison and TE Hunter Long inactive for Week 12 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b237-d90e-a9da-bf3f0fb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RG Trey Smith suffered an ankle injury in Week 12 against the Colts and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b249-d82c-a79a-b3ddd4fa0000</link>
      <description>Smith had his ankle rolled on in the first half and immediately went down. He was ruled out shortly after halftime. The Chiefs will now attempt to pull off a comeback over the Colts without one of the best guards in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b249-d82c-a79a-b3ddd4fa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
