<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bucky Irving’s foot sprain is not expected to be a long-term injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</link>
      <description>The sprain, per Schefter, is a “week to week” injury. It could keep Irving sidelined in Week 5 against Seattle after Tampa’s lead back was seen in a walking boot on Wednesday. Irving is reportedly seeking medical opinions this week. If he sits in Week 5, Rachaad White would serve as Tampa’s RB1 with Sean Tucker possibly taking a solid RB2 role behind White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed RB Myles Gaskin, formerly of the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a084-d95b-addb-e8c661aa0000</link>
      <description>Gaskin, who was released by the Ravens in August, will join the Seahawks’ practice squad for now. It’s unclear whether he was signed due to an injury to Ken Walker or Zach Charbonnet, but he’s a good distance from any kind of fantasy relevance at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a084-d95b-addb-e8c661aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said RB Braelon Allen’s knee injury is “pretty serious.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a092-d6e9-af9d-aa92b92d0000</link>
      <description>Allen picked up the knee injury on a kick return in Week 4 against the Dolphins. Glenn said Allen is seeking secondary medical opinions on the injury before the team makes a decision on how much time he’ll miss. If it’s a season ending injury, Breece Hall should see a bump in weekly touches and perhaps goal line usage. Isaiah Davis, meanwhile, would likely operate as the Jets’ No. 2 back and should be rostered in 12-team leagues. Davis had five touches for 28 yards in Week 4 with Allen sidelined for much of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a092-d6e9-af9d-aa92b92d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) was medically cleared to return to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a0-dca3-a9fb-bdb9aa0c0000</link>
      <description>Daniels is expected to log a full practice Wednesday after missing the past two weeks with a knee injury he picked up in Week 2. Barring any practice setbacks, Daniels should be under center for the Commanders in Week 5 against a tough Chargers defense. His return to the lineup will be welcome news for Deebo Samuel and Zach Ertz, who should remain in fantasy lineups in a potential back-and-forth affair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a0-dca3-a9fb-bdb9aa0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans opened the three-week practice window for Tyjae Spears (ankle).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a3-dca3-a9fb-bdbb47260000</link>
      <description>Spears could return to game action as early as this week against the Cardinals if he’s able to practice in the coming days. His presence in the Titans backfield could be a hit to Tony Pollard’s weekly fantasy prospects. Pollard through four games has accounted for 68 of the Titans’ 73 running backs rushes while catching six of nine targets. It’s hard to get excited about anyone in a dumpster fire of a Tennessee offense, but Spears is a decent pick up in deeper leagues in case Pollard misses any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a3-dca3-a9fb-bdbb47260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed RB Trey Benson (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0b5-deb6-a7fd-f3ffd67f0000</link>
      <description>Benson is reportedly expected to be back at some point this season. He banged up his knee in the fourth quarter of Arizona’s Week 4 loss to the Seahawks and will now miss at least four weeks. That means Emari Demercado will take over as the team’s lead back for now, though Michael Carter should mix in to the Cardinals backfield while Benson is sidelined. Demercado should be considered a top-20 fantasy play this week against a bad Titans defense. Carter, meanwhile, should be rostered in most 12-team formats as the next guy up in the injury-ravaged Cardinals backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0b5-deb6-a7fd-f3ffd67f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Trey Benson (knee, IR) “underwent arthroscopic surgery on his meniscus and now is expected to be sidelined 4-to-6 weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0bb-d95b-addb-e8ff9fce0000</link>
      <description>Benson was placed on injured reserve today after suffering an injury late in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks. The injury quickly went from making him questionable for Week 5 to sidelining him for over a month. Emari Demercado and Michael Carter will be the Cardinals’ top two backs for now. Demercado will get the first crack at the starting job with Carter likely mixing in every few drives. Both running backs will be priority waiver wire adds this week with injuries mounting and bye weeks rolling in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0bb-d95b-addb-e8ff9fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s John Keim reports Terry McLaurin (quad) was on the field for the start of Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0ca-d95b-addb-e8cef2940000</link>
      <description>McLaurin could make a surprise appearance later in the session, but things are trending toward a DNP for his first practice of Week 5. McLaurin missed Week 4 with the quad issue and was considered week to week as of the end of last week. Dan Quinn said on Monday that he was trending in the right direction, though he didn’t say if he expected McLaurin to return for Week 5. Deebo Samuel will operate as the team’s top wideout if McLaurin remains out, putting him in the WR2 ranks for a date with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0ca-d95b-addb-e8cef2940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0d5-d95b-addb-e8d7052a0000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Doug McDermott, linebacker Matt Milano is also expected to be limited in practice. The Bills lost both defenders after Week 1. Neither player has practiced since, so even a limited session to open the week is a step in the right direction. At 4-0, the Bills don’t need to rush either player back. Drake Maye and the Patriots will be hoping both players take their time while recovering ahead of their Week 5 date on Sunday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0d5-d95b-addb-e8d7052a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0dd-d95b-addb-e8df04780000</link>
      <description>This was the expectation after NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported Jackson’s status as “week to week” earlier today. Previous reports have also indicated that Jackson will not suit up for Week 5 against the Texans. All signs point to Cooper Rush making his first start as a Raven. Rush was a competent passer in Dallas last year, going 4-4 as a starter while Dak Prescott nursed a hamstring injury late in the year. Losing Jackson is a devastating blow to the Baltimore offense, but Rush is at least one of the league’s more capable backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0dd-d95b-addb-e8df04780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
