<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed an interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfe-dc7a-af9b-effff0a50000</link>
      <description>This is Weaver’s second interview with the Steelers, and the first in-person. Dolphins is also a candidate for the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy and has been linked to the Giants’ defensive coordinator vacancy. He previously interviewed for the now-filled Ravens’ head-coaching role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecfe-dc7a-af9b-effff0a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested and interview with Chiefs DL coach Joe Cullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed03-d35e-a1bf-edc398f10000</link>
      <description>Cullen interviewed for the Commanders’ defensive coordinator vacancy earlier this month. The Chiefs’ defensive line generated pressure at a top-10 rate during the regular season (38.9 percent) and totaled 87 TFLs, tying for 15th.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed03-d35e-a1bf-edc398f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Kyle Smith as their new assistant general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed19-d56e-afff-eff954050000</link>
      <description>Smith signed on with the Falcons in 2021 as their vice president of player personnel. He was promoted to the assistant general manager role in 2023 and remained in that role until now. He opts for a lateral move to a new organization as the Falcons rework their front office under new president of football, Matt Ryan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed19-d56e-afff-eff954050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Chris Tabor as their new special teams coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed1e-d35e-a1bf-edde89f60000</link>
      <description>Tabor held the same role with the division-rival Bills in 2025. Before that, he served as the Panthers’ special teams coordinator from 2022-2023 and was promoted to interim head coach briefly during the latter season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed1e-d35e-a1bf-edde89f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested an interview with Vikings DL coach Marcus Dixon for their potential defensive line coach vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed62-d968-a19b-fdf3da520000</link>
      <description>Cowboys DL coach Aaron Whitecotton is “drawing interest” from the Titans as they search for a defensive coordinator under new head coach Robert Saleh. Rather than waiting to find out if Whitecotton leaves, the Cowboys are proactively starting their own search for his potential replacement. ESPN’s Todd Archer notes that Dixon coached the Broncos’ defensive line from 2022-2023, while new Cowboys DC Christian Parker coached Broncos defensive backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed62-d968-a19b-fdf3da520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets fired senior assistant and pass game coordinator Scott Turner.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed1c-d56e-afff-effc6d970000</link>
      <description>Turner’s time with the Jets comes to a close after just one season. The Jets also fired QB coach Charles London, DL coach Eric Washington, LB coach Aaron Curry, defensive assistant Roosevelt Williams and defensive assistant Alonso Escalante.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed1c-d56e-afff-effc6d970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed an interview with Jaguars OC Grant Udinski for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed71-d56e-afff-eff98f090000</link>
      <description>Udinski, 30, completed his second interview with the Browns today. The young candidate piloted an offense that ranked top-12 in yards per pass play (7.15) during the regular season. He is also expected to interview for the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed71-d56e-afff-eff98f090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Eagles senior personnel director and advisor to the general manager Joe Douglas for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed83-d968-a19b-fdf30cc10000</link>
      <description>Douglas is currently in his second stint with the Eagles’ front office. He previously served as the Eagles’ vice president of player personnel from 2016-2019 before taking the Jets’ vacant general manager position. He has been in his current role for one year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed83-d968-a19b-fdf30cc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (concussion) is not on New England’s injury report for the AFC Championship Game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed83-d968-a19b-fdf347670000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Davis would be listed as questionable, but Davis ended up clearing the NFL’s concussion protocol this afternoon. Davis leads the team with 12 pass breakups this year. His return is good news for the Patriots’ defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ed83-d968-a19b-fdf347670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports former Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel canceled his interview with the Bills to discuss the team’s head coaching position on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f025-d56e-afff-f6ed96ef0000</link>
      <description>While the Bills are just beginning their search for a new head coach after dismissing Sean McDermott earlier this week, McDaniel has already withdrawn his name from the Browns head coaching search and interviewed for multiple offensive coordinator positions before agreeing to sign on with the Chargers. Schultz says McDaniel and the Bills remain in contact for a potential interview, but there’s a “strong possibility” he moves forward with the Chargers. McDaniel’s presence in Los Angeles would be massive as fantasy managers could expect the 42-year-old coach to get the most out of Justin Herbert and the rest of the Chargers’ offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f025-d56e-afff-f6ed96ef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
