<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The D.C. City Council approved the Commanders to build a stadium at the old RFK Stadium site with a vote of 11-to-2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59d6-dfde-a1bd-5fdf9ba00000</link>
      <description>The Commanders and owner Josh Harris finally got their last leg of approval and will officially be opening a new stadium in Washington, D.C., set to open in 2030. The D.C. City Council gave their second and final approval for a $3.8 billion project to develop in and around the old RFK Stadium site. This will bring the Commanders back to Washington, D.C. for the first time in three decades. A 65,000-seat stadium and more development around the site is in store as the Commanders begin the process of making a monumental move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59d6-dfde-a1bd-5fdf9ba00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59e4-dfde-a1bd-5fedc4a40000</link>
      <description>Dissly popped up on the injury report with a knee issue on Wednesday. The 29-year-old has just two catches for 25 yards the first two weeks of the season. He has, however, been the Chargers’ starting tight end. Should he miss any time, Tyler Conklin and rookie Oronde Gadsden should see an increase in opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59e4-dfde-a1bd-5fedc4a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Daiyan Henley (illness) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59eb-dfde-a1bd-5fef21010000</link>
      <description>Henley was added to the Chargers’ injury report prior to their Monday night game with an illness. He played in the team’s win over the Raiders, so a missed practice two days later is a surprise, but not concerning yet. Henley is still on track to play in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59eb-dfde-a1bd-5fef21010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59ef-d93f-ad9d-5bef30ba0000</link>
      <description>Carter popped up on the injury report with a shoulder injury, getting in limited reps on Wednesday. It does not seem to be a major issue for the Eagles’ defensive centerpiece, just enough to limit him to begin the week. Barring setbacks, expect Carter to play in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59ef-d93f-ad9d-5bef30ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59f1-d93f-ad9d-5bf79c220000</link>
      <description>Bowers played through his knee injury in the Raiders’ Monday night loss to the Chargers, though he was clearly not at full health. The fact that he is practicing in any capacity is a good sign, but the Raiders will be managing his workload throughout the week. Barring setbacks, Bowers is still on track to play Week 3 against the Commanders. Despite playing through injury, the weak fantasy tight end landscape means Bowers is still a top-five play when active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59f1-d93f-ad9d-5bf79c220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OG Trevor Penning (toe) was limited in practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59f5-d1b3-a5dd-59f5f11c0000</link>
      <description>Penning returned to practice after being sidelined for turf toe heading into the season. Returning to play in Week 3 against the Seahawks may be optimistic, but this is good news for the Saints’ offensive line. Penning received a 70.1 run blocking grade from PFF last season and his addition to the line should open up more lanes for Alvin Kamara. The incumbent starting left guard, Dillon Radunz, was sidelined in practice Wednesday with a toe injury. Penning and Radunz’s practice statuses will be ones to monitor for the Saints heading into the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59f5-d1b3-a5dd-59f5f11c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a01-dfde-a1bd-5e8d41fd0000</link>
      <description>Also out was EDGE Chase Young (knee). Both Fuaga and Young did not practice last Wednesday, either. However, Fuaga did practice later in the week and went on to play in Week 2 while Young was sidelined again while still not practicing. Between the two, Fuaga is more likely to work his way back to play Week 3 against the Seahawks while it seems Young will still need more time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a01-dfde-a1bd-5e8d41fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a05-d93f-ad9d-5ac7305a0000</link>
      <description>An ineffective showing in Week 2 is now followed up by a foot injury for Charbonnet. He has led Kenneth Walker in touches the first two weeks of the season off the strength of his pass-blocking, but that could change quickly if his foot injury is major. Fantasy managers should stay tuned as we find out more information about the severity of Charbonnet’s foot while Kenneth Walker fantasy managers are on track to get a boost in Week 3 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a05-d93f-ad9d-5ac7305a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a14-dfde-a1bd-5e9d68550000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon missed Week 2 against the Steelers with a knee injury and now starts out Week 3 not practicing. Also out on Wednesday were S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) and S Julian Love (hamstring). Emmanwori has an ankle sprain that seems like a multi-week issue stemming from Week 1, while Love played through a groin injury last week and is now dealing with a hamstring. Needless to say, the Seahawks secondary is banged-up heading into Week 3 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a14-dfde-a1bd-5e9d68550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a18-d1b3-a5dd-5b794ca50000</link>
      <description>Horton caught his first career touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 2 win over the Steelers and has operated as the No. 3 wide receiver for the first two weeks of the season. He pops up on the injury report with a groin issue, though he did get in limited work on Wednesday. Horton is still tracking to play in Week 3, though he is not on fantasy radars yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a18-d1b3-a5dd-5b794ca50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
