<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 04:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins EDGE Chop Robinson suffered a concussion in Miami’s Week 9 game against the Ravens and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3250-d48c-ad9f-fe5d9d280000</link>
      <description>The second-year first-rounder went down at the midway point of the first half and was ruled out just before the break. He should be considered week to week, though he has 10 days to get cleared for Week 10 against the Bills. The 22-year-old is in the midst of a disappointing sophomore campaign, registering only one sack and eight hurries thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3250-d48c-ad9f-fe5d9d280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson completed 18-of-23 passes for 204 yards and four touchdowns in the Ravens’ 28-6, Week 9 win over the Dolphins, adding five rushes for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3842-d45b-affe-7dd6eebf0000</link>
      <description>Active for the first time since Week 4 following last weekend’s curious false start, Jackson waltzed to a QB1 effort with typical passing efficiency. It was another curiously low key game on the ground, but Jackson appeared no worse for the wear after missing more than a month. Carving up one of the league’s worst defenses, he found role player Charlie Kolar for a touchdown in addition to Mark Andrews (twice) and Rashod Bateman. The even better news is that Jackson avoided further injury and now has 10 days rest and recover for a matchup with the Vikings’ intense but burnable defense. Jackson should be back just in time to save fantasy seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3842-d45b-affe-7dd6eebf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 25-of-40 passes for 261 yards and an interception in the Dolphins’ 28-6, Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3846-d1e7-a1fa-7aee6dc60000</link>
      <description>Four days after beclowning a Falcons team starting Kirk Cousins without Drake London, the Dolphins went right back to embarrassing themselves and their fans, mustering two field goals amidst a blizzard of miscues and ill-timed penalties. Tua’s pick was a fourth quarter sail job in garbage time, but he was lucky it was his only giveaway. It was not Dolphins’ only giveaway, as Malik Washington and someone named Tahj Washington both lost fumbles. Along the way, multiple long gains were wiped out by penalties, some of them legitimate. Others, not so much. That was a bad break, but bad breaks only ruin your night if you are bad. The Dolphins are, and Tagovailoa is going to struggle for top-24 status when Miami hosts the Bills for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3846-d1e7-a1fa-7aee6dc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 19 times for 119 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-384a-d673-a39e-bcdbc9dd0000</link>
      <description>This was the inverse of Henry’s Week 8, where he was inefficient but found the end zone twice. Tonight he got stood up at the one-yard line but was consistently ripping nice gains. Coach John Harbaugh acknowledged the effort by leaving Henry in the game with the Ravens up big in the fourth quarter. The result was his second 100-yard effort in three weeks and third of the season. A fourth could be on tap for Week 10 against a decent Vikings defense, but one that coughs up a ton of rushing yardage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-384a-d673-a39e-bcdbc9dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 6-of-9 targets for 82 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3852-d713-ad9e-7c567a590000</link>
      <description>It was another solid effort for Waddle as he operated as something of a “rare bright spot” for a team that immediately found itself back in crisis following last Sunday’s outlier win over the Falcons. Waddle was unlucky to be held below 100 yards, as he took a mammoth hit on a second quarter 36-yard reception only for the grab to be called back by a bogus tripping penalty. Waddle has been absolutely cooking since Tyreek Hill’s season-ending injury, but there are limits to what any wideout can accomplish with Tua Tagovailoa under center. That makes him a volatile but high-upside WR2 heading into Week 10 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3852-d713-ad9e-7c567a590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 14 times for 67 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens, adding six receptions for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3856-d45b-affe-7dd689e20000</link>
      <description>Continuing to operate with efficiency on the ground and volume through the air, Achane lost a seventh catch to a questionable second half review overturn. Achane looked smooth and explosive vs. the Ravens’ shaky defense, but Tua Tagovailoa couldn’t sustain drives long enough for Achane to get enough handles on the ground. Fantasy managers will still take the 100-plus yards and six receptions. Operating as a high-floor RB1, Achane gets the Bills’ awful run defense in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3856-d45b-affe-7dd689e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 5-of-5 targets for 64 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385a-d713-ad9e-7c5ebd4a0000</link>
      <description>5/64 meant it was not a disastrous night in PPR leagues, but fantasy managers will lament that Lamar Jackson threw for four scores and none of them went his No. 1 wideout’s way. Then again, Jackson’s overdue return to the lineup means Flowers will have an enhanced floor and elevated ceiling going forward. That includes for Week 10 against a swarming Vikings defense that is nevertheless prone to surrendering big plays. Flowers is a strong WR2 who will mix in WR1 statlines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385a-d713-ad9e-7c5ebd4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 2-of-3 targets for 22 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385e-d1e7-a1fa-7afe890f0000</link>
      <description>It was the second time in five days Andrews commanded only three targets. The difference this time, as you can see, is that he scored two touchdowns. The first was a two-yarder on a first quarter fourth down where Andrews got lost in the back of the end zone. The second was a 20-yarder where two Dolphins defenders freed Andrews by running into each other. Sometimes it’s better to be lucky than good. Elsewhere, Andrews converted a tush push as a runner and watched Isaiah Likely turn his four targets into 3/30. With Likely and Lamar Jackson finally both healthy at the same time, Andrews’ already perilously low floor could be sinking even lower. He will be more of a TE2 than TE1 for Week 10 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385e-d1e7-a1fa-7afe890f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely caught 3-of-4 targets for 60 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3863-d713-ad9e-7c77de1c0000</link>
      <description>Finally healthy at the same time as Lamar Jackson, Likely more than doubled his previous season production and was just four yards off Zay Flowers for the team lead. Likely’s biggest gain was a 35-yard catch-and-run as time expired in the first quarter. Always capable of long gainers down the seam, Likely could be something of a second half X-factor for the Ravens, though he’s probably still a lower-end TE2 as he fights Mark Andrews for seam looks in a run-based offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3863-d713-ad9e-7c77de1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 3-of-3 targets for 48 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3866-d673-a39e-bcf7edca0000</link>
      <description>Washington also lost a fourth quarter fumble in a red zone pileup at the Ravens’ 14-yard line. Not ideal. His 48 yards receiving were at least a new season high after he reached that number twice as a rookie. Decent enough, but Washington is still stuck on 3-6 weekly targets even after Tyreek Hill was lost for the season. WR4 value is not materializing. Maybe that will change for Week 10 for a Bills contest where the Dolphins will undoubtedly have to throw more than they would like.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3866-d673-a39e-bcf7edca0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
