<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f0-d6a5-adff-f6f5a7020000</link>
      <description>Legette has target volume working in his favor if he does play as a game-script underdog and with eight attempts in his direction last week. He made -2 yards of them, of course, but if we’re just going to play this out in theory and say he’s definitely not a good receiver, a healthy Legette could get 30-40 yards. He doesn’t belong near fantasy lineups until we see better actual production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f0-d6a5-adff-f6f5a7020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out Chris Godwin (ankle) for Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62ed-dfde-a1bd-7eed25970000</link>
      <description>Tristan Wirfs (knee) was also ruled out for Week 3’s contest. Both Godwin and Wirfs were limited in practice all week, but neither was ever expected to play this week. While there’s some hope Godwin could return in Week 4 against the Eagles, we’ll reserve our optimism until next week’s practices start up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62ed-dfde-a1bd-7eed25970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns K Andre Szmyt (calf) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f4-d1b3-a5dd-63f5e6d10000</link>
      <description>He popped up on the injury report for the first time this week and will undergo an MRI per head coach Kevin Stefanski. It’s possible the Browns replace Szmyt ahead of kickoff if the injury is serious. Please do not start either Browns kicker against the Packers defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f4-d1b3-a5dd-63f5e6d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LG Joel Bitonio (back) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62fc-d93f-ad9d-7aff40960000</link>
      <description>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Bitonio only has a chance to play “because of experience” after missing all three practices this week with a back injury. Cleveland would likely shuttle Teven Jenkins into a starting role if Bitonio missed Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62fc-d93f-ad9d-7aff40960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) will be questionable for Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f5-d6a5-adff-f6f553ee0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka only logged one practice this week, but his limited action on Friday was enough for him to draw the questionable tag heading into the weekend. It’s an encouraging sign for his Week 3 availability, but fantasy managers will still want to check his availability 90 minutes before kickoff when inactives are announced. Egbuka has caught 8-of-13 targets for 96 yards and three touchdowns through the first two games of this season and would be firmly on the WR2 radar if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62f5-d6a5-adff-f6f553ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6300-d1b3-a5dd-63718e410000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez has worked all three days this week and would seem to have a decent chance of being active for Week 3. The third-year star suffered a hamstring injury in training camp that has kept him out up until this week. His return would do wonders for a Pats secondary that could badly use a ceiling-raiser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6300-d1b3-a5dd-63718e410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak said the team has to “keep finding ways to get” both Zach Charbonnet and Kenneth Walker III involved, adding “I see two starters.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6308-d93f-ad9d-7bcf00230000</link>
      <description>This is in addition to Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald saying that the plan is for each back to have “ample opportunity” on a weekly basis. Walker will make for a nice fantasy play in Week 3 if Charbonnet is ruled out after missing the first two practices of the week, but it seems like this will be a weekly guessing game for fantasy managers going forward when both are healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6308-d93f-ad9d-7bcf00230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) will not play in Week 3’s game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-630b-d6a5-adff-f7cf69ca0000</link>
      <description>Latham has now not practiced at all in either of the last two weeks after leaving Week 1’s game against the Broncos with the injury. It’s possible he winds up on injured reserve over the weekend. The Titans started John Ojukwu last week, but have also used Oli Udoh at right tackle in Week 1. Either way, it’s good news for Colts D/ST streamers this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-630b-d6a5-adff-f7cf69ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSOCTV reports Cowboys DE Jadeveon Clowney was arrested last week for trespassing.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-630c-d93f-ad9d-7bcf03470000</link>
      <description>According to the report, Clowney was arrested for trespassing and failure to identify in his hometown of Rock Hill, South Carolina, on September 12th. Both charges are misdemeanors. Clowney reportedly tried to park his car in a closed parking lot where parking was not permitted. The veteran pass rusher signed with the Cowboys last Sunday and participated in practice this week. It would be surprising if he faced any kind of suspension for this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-630c-d93f-ad9d-7bcf03470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas (wrist) said he is good to go for Week 3 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6317-d1b3-a5dd-637752480000</link>
      <description>Thomas apparently played through the same wrist injury last week — something we found out after the loss to the Week 2 loss to the Bengals. He was listed as a limited participant in Thursday’s practice, but that may have been out of precaution. Thomas has struggled out of the gate, catching five passes for 60 scoreless yards through the first two weeks of the season. Despite the struggles, he remains a must-start for fantasy managers against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6317-d1b3-a5dd-637752480000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
