<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:02:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall caught 5-of-8 targets for 85 yards in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall showed no wear after missing Week 16, immediately returning to lead the team in receiving on a night the two offenses combined for more than 940 yards of total offense and 80 points. The only thing he didn’t do for fantasy managers was find the end zone. He could have more target competition after it was reported that tight end George Kittle is likely to make a return to the game-day lineup when the 49ers host the Seahawks in Week 18 for a battle for the No. 1 seed out of the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 7-of-9 targets for 60 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</link>
      <description>Tonges was active throughout as a primary outlet for quarterback Brock Purdy over the middle of the field, also seeing numerous designed targets in the flat. His target total was bolstered by a game in which the two teams combined for over 940 yards of total offense and 80 points. Although the outburst in production was a welcome sight to fantasy mangers that scooped Tonges as a plan B option to Kittle, his role appears likely to take a significant hit with Kittle expected back for Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 2-of-4 targets for 42 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ four targets ranked behind fill-in tight end Jake Tonges, Ricky Pearsall, and Christian McCaffrey, but he saved his fantasy outing with a 38-yard touchdown in the fourth quarter to give the 49ers their final lead of the game. It was the first NFL regular season game in NFL history that was tied at seven, 14, 21, 28, and 35 points, with the 49ers eventually emerging victorious following an incomplete pass in the end zone as time expired. Jennings is unlikely to see his target volume surge significantly considering tight end George Kittle is expected to return to the game-day roster in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Juszczyk caught 2-of-2 targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</link>
      <description>Juice scored on an unreal play from quarterback Brock Purdy in which the former Mr. Irrelevant evaded two would-be sacks to deliver the football to the left corner of the end zone and into the waiting hands of Juszczyk. The veteran fullback remains unlikely to see meaningful volume on a weekly basis but his moderate snap rates keep a sporadic touchdown within his range of outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bears WR Luther Burden suffered a quad injury that’s not thought to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6a5a-d56e-afff-eefa9b740000</link>
      <description>Burden was one of two Bears receivers in the area of Caleb Williams’ target on the final play of the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers. The 22-year-old receiver remained down following the play and was subsequently carted to the locker room. It’s certainly encouraging news that Schefter reports the injury isn’t serious, though he also passes along that Burden will undergo additional testing. Following a breakout game with eight catches, 138 yards and a touchdown, Burden could be the Bears’ leading receiver in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6a5a-d56e-afff-eefa9b740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers T Trent Williams (hamstring) left San Francisco’s Week 17 game against the Bears and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab7-d968-a19b-7af753060000</link>
      <description>He played just one snap. Austen Pleasants replaced him. Williams being ruled out and seen hobbling on the sideline with what The Athletic’s Matt Barrows called a hamstring strain does not bode well for his availability for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab7-d968-a19b-7af753060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interim head coach Mike Kafka told reporters he has no doubts that QB Jaxson Dart has proven he’s a franchise quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab6-dc7a-af9b-efbfc5a40000</link>
      <description>Dart bounced back from a 33-yard performance in the Week 16 loss to the Vikings to throw for 207 yards in the win over the Raiders Sunday. The 22-year-old signal caller’s future with the organization is a topic for discussion with the Giants currently in control of the No. 2 overall pick in the 2026 NFL Draft and the team’s coaching situation in flux. While Kafka could remain the head coach next year, the Giants are said to be interested in speaking with a list of candidates that could include Notre Dame’s Marcus Freeman. In a sense, an endorsement from Kafka is relatively meaningless as he doesn’t currently have much of a say in the future direction of the franchise. Dart will have one more chance to make an impression against the Cowboys in Week 18 before what’s likely to be an offseason full of changes in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab6-dc7a-af9b-efbfc5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LT Will Campbell (knee) will return to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6aca-dc7a-af9b-efff79fa0000</link>
      <description>Campbell was placed on injured reserve after suffering a torn MCL in Week 12 against the Bengals. The 21-year-old left tackle will have his 21-day practice window opened this week. He’s eligible to return from injured reserve for Week 18’s matchup with the Dolphins, though the Patriots will have to see him practice first. If all goes well, it looks like the Patriots will be getting a big piece of their offensive line back ahead of a potentially deep playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6aca-dc7a-af9b-efff79fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bears LB Noah Sewell suffered a torn Achilles and is out for the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b0c-d968-a19b-7bfd0cdc0000</link>
      <description>Sewell had appeared in 13 games this year, starting nine of them. The 23-year-old linebacker had 59 tackles including three tackles for loss and one forced fumble. His 41.5 overall PFF grade ranked 81st out of 86 linebackers. Sewell was carted off the field after suffering an injury in the third quarter of the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers. He’ll miss the rest of the season with a torn Achilles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b0c-d968-a19b-7bfd0cdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals head coach Zac Taylor told reporters Joe Burrow will play in Week 18 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b12-d35e-a1bf-6fd2d18b0000</link>
      <description>Taylor said that Burrow gives them the best chance to win, which is both true and not really the point anymore given the Bengals were officially eliminated from playoff contention weeks ago. Burrow is wrapping up his second season in the last three years in which he appeared in 10 games or less due to injury. A significant injury against the Browns in Week 18 would be absolutely devastating for the Bengals and Burrow, who carries a nearly $48 million cap hit in 2026. Maybe Taylor comes to his senses before game-time or he lets Joe Flacco at least play the second half, but he’s remained consistent in recent weeks about Burrow playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b12-d35e-a1bf-6fd2d18b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
