<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:11:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Josh Paschal (undisclosed) will be out “longer” than expected.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccf5-dbe3-a9bb-fcf7b4ed0000</link>
      <description>Campbell thought that Paschal, who was placed on the non-football injury list to open camp, would be back practicing in September. Instead, it seems like Paschal will be out through at least the first month of the season. The Lions have not disclosed what Paschal is dealing with. It looks like we’ll be getting a big dose of Al-Quadin Muhammad and Marcus Davenport on the other side of Aidan Hutchinson to open the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccf5-dbe3-a9bb-fcf7b4ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Tristan Wirfs (knee) will open the season on the 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccf9-de13-afdc-cefb15f50000</link>
      <description>That does not mean that Wirfs will be healthy enough to play right away, but as they’re doing with Chris Godwin, the Bucs are opting to leave Wirfs on the roster so that he can practice with the team if ready. It sounds like Wirfs is on a similar timeline as Godwin is. Perhaps they’ll both be ready by Week 4 or so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ccf9-de13-afdc-cefb15f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Saints, Browns, and Chiefs are among the teams “making calls” in search of running backs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd34-de13-afdc-cfff99160000</link>
      <description>The Browns have the most unsettled room among the three, with Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson seemingly in the driver’s seat for carries with Quinshon Judkins still unsigned. The Chiefs and Saints each appear to have a true lead back (Isiah Pacheco, Alvin Kamara) but a need for a more established back behind them with late-round rookies Devin Neal and Brashard Smith apparently not solidifying roles in camp. Ford and Sampson are, accordingly, the backs with the most to potentially lose as cuts approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd34-de13-afdc-cfff99160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kris Rhim reports Najee Harris (eye) continues to work out on side fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd3a-dbe3-a9bb-fd7b42f60000</link>
      <description>We haven’t gotten an update on Harris in a week or so, but it doesn’t seem like much has changed since he made it back to practice. Jim Harbaugh’s last update on Harris was that there’s a chance he’d be ready for Week 1, but with only a few weeks before the start of the season, we’d need to see a drastic ramp-up to believe that is in the cards. Harris may avoid being placed on the IR or the PUP list based on how often he’s been working to the side, but it’s hard to recommend him in fantasy until he gets back on the actual practice field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd3a-dbe3-a9bb-fd7b42f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson is not practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd63-de13-afdc-cfeb93350000</link>
      <description>He left Wednesday’s practice early after having his foot stepped on — the Ravens released a statement saying that he was fine. Ravens reporters saw him flexing his hand and wrist on the sideline. We don’t have an official injury diagnosis and don’t believe Jackson is seriously hurt, but any time Jackson isn’t practicing it’s newsworthy. Further updates from the Ravens should be coming at some point in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd63-de13-afdc-cfeb93350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Kaleb McGary (leg) will “miss time” at the start of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd72-db7b-a5dd-ed76d8ef0000</link>
      <description>The severity of his leg injury is not yet known, but McGary went down in practice and required an MRI yesterday. With Storm Norton also hurt, the Falcons will be on RT3 at the start of the season at the very least. It’s possible that this is an injury that sends McGary to IR-return, and we wouldn’t rule out that it was a season-ender based on the descriptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd72-db7b-a5dd-ed76d8ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (undisclosed) is close to returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</link>
      <description>Quinn added that the “arrow is pointing up for him.” The oft-injured wideout hasn’t participated much in training camp to this point. This paints a picture of a return for Week 1, but Quinn did not exactly promise that with words. Brown should probably be the Commanders’ No. 3 receiver when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR Johnny Wilson (knee/ankle) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</link>
      <description>Wilson suffered the injury at Tuesday’s practice and was carted off. While Wilson’s a fun player at 6-foot-6 and shaped like a tight end, he wasn’t expected to have a major role in the Eagles offense this year. The 2024 sixth-rounder will instead look to get ready for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn says he “see[s] the ascension taking place” with Jaylin Lane.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders fourth-round pick this year, Lane reportedly can “apply it very quickly” when given coaching points. Lane has a chance to eventually take over for Noah Brown in three-wideout sets at some point this season, and should make for an intriguing stash in dynasty at the very least given his youth relative to the rest of the Commanders wideout room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions C Graham Glasgow (leg) left Friday’s joint practice against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</link>
      <description>No word yet on the severity of the injury, but it would be yet another blow to the Lions’ interior line if Glasgow missed real time. We’d expect an update from Detroit sometime in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
