<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 9 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4624-d45b-affe-57b65c080000</link>
      <description>Golden walked to the locker room in the middle of the third quarter before being listed as questionable. The rookie had two catches for nine yards before exiting. With Tucker Kraft also injured, the Packers will lean on Romeo Doubs and Christian Watson in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4624-d45b-affe-57b65c080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud (concussion protocol) left Houston’s Week 9 game against the Broncos and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4626-d673-a39e-e6b7ca5e0000</link>
      <description>Stroud was 6-for-10 for 79 yards before leaving, his helmet hit the turf when he slid late and was hit by Kris Abrams-Draine. Davis Mills took over and will presumably be in the superflex conversation in Week 10 if Stroud can’t clear protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4626-d673-a39e-e6b7ca5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RT Tytus Howard (concussion protocol) left Houston’s Week 9 game against the Broncos and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4628-d713-ad9e-6e7c9c300000</link>
      <description>He was concussed shortly before halftime and wasn’t in on Houston’s final two drives. Howard, Houston’s best remaining offensive lineman, leaves a big void for second-rounder Blake Fisher to fill. Ed Ingram (ankle) is also questionable to return, with Juice Scruggs stepping into his role at right guard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4628-d713-ad9e-6e7c9c300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Locket is active for Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-462c-d673-a39e-e6bd1c8b0000</link>
      <description>Lockett, who signed with the Raiders last week after being released by the Titans, will likely take on a rotational role at wideout against the Jags. Tre Tucker will remain the team’s primary downfield target for now. The Raiders declared RB Zamir White, WR Dont’e Thornton Jr., CB Darnay Holmes, Guard Caleb Rogers, DT JJ Pegues, and DT Tonka Hemingway inactive against Jacksonville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-462c-d673-a39e-e6bd1c8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared NCB Taron Johnson, WR Joshua Palmer, OT Chase Lundt, DE Landon Jackson, DT DaQuan Jones, LB Shaq Thompson, and KR/PR Brandon Codrington inactive for Week 9 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-463e-d713-ad9e-6e7e2ee70000</link>
      <description>More bad news for a Bills defense that just lost defensive tackle Ed Oliver for the season. Johnson picked up a groin injury in practice this week, which means the Bills will be without one of the league’s best slot cornerbacks and also without Shaq Thompson, who has been perhaps their best linebacker this season. It’s an overall upgrade to the Chiefs’ passing game over the middle of the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-463e-d713-ad9e-6e7e2ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) is active for Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4632-d713-ad9e-6e76460e0000</link>
      <description>Brown could see an increased role in the coming weeks with Travis Hunter sidelined with a knee injury. Brown and Parker Washington will see regular snaps and routes as the WR2 and WR3 behind Brian Thomas, who remains the team’s clear No. 1 wideout. Jaguars declared LB Devin Lloyd, WR Tim Patrick, RB Cody Schrader, OL Wyatt Milum, TE Quintin Morris, and DT Khalen Saunders Sr. inactive against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4632-d713-ad9e-6e76460e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared CB Kristian Fulton, RB Isiah Pacheco, WR Jalen Royals, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, OT Josh Simmons, and OL CJ Hanson inactive for Week 9 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4641-d45b-affe-57d7a5450000</link>
      <description>Even with Isiah Pacheco (knee) out, the Chiefs are not going to have Mitchell active, which means Clyde Edwards-Helaire has surpassed him on the depth chart. Simmons remains out due to unclear personal reasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4641-d45b-affe-57d7a5450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones was forced from Minnesota’s Week 9 game against the Lions with a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4647-d713-ad9e-6e57fa240000</link>
      <description>In just his second game back from his early-season hamstring injury, Jones was announced as “questionable” midway through the third quarter but does not appear to be returning. Ineffective in Week 8, Jones had been much better so far today, turning nine carries into 78 yards. He also tacked on two receptions for 20 yards as Jordan Mason remained ineffective. Regressing to his career injury mean after 2024’s healthy campaign, Jones should be considered on the wrong side of questionable for Week 10 against the Ravens’ soft run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4647-d713-ad9e-6e57fa240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (head) is questionable to return Week 9 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4648-d673-a39e-e6d9f1c70000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez hit his head on the field after Drake London beat him to a 40-yard jump ball in the second half of the Pats’ Week 9 game against the Falcons. He is likely being evaluated for a concussion and is questionable to return to the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4648-d673-a39e-e6d9f1c70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
