<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed WR Chris Blair, P Trenton Gill, DB Tysheem Johnson, DT Ben Stille, OT Andrew Stueber, RB Carlos Washington and DB A.J. Woods to reserve/future deals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</link>
      <description>Blair, mostly a special teamer, has played eight games and 48 offensive snaps for the Falcons over the past three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Phillip Dorsett to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</link>
      <description>We don’t know how much future there is to reserve for the 33-year-old (happy birthday!), but the Raiders are here for it. The Raiders also signed RB Chris Collier, G McClendon Curtis, LB Jamin Davis, DT Treven Ma’ae, T Joshua Miles, TE Albert Okwuegbunam (remember him?), WR Brenden Rice, G Layden Robinson, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, and T Dalton Wagner to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed TE Sal Cannella, G Jack Conley, WR Luke Floriea, RB Ahmani Marshall, T Tyre Phillips and TE Caden Prieskorn to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</link>
      <description>Cannella had a four-target game against the Steelers in Week 17 after Harold Fannin left early due to a groin injury, catching two balls for 11 yards. The 29-year-old UFL star is merely a depth piece.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed WR Malik Cunningham to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</link>
      <description>The former Louisville quarterback made his first career appearance in an NFL game in 2025. He ran the ball against the Cowboys in Week 14 one time and gained one yard. OL Devin Cochran, DE Ahmed Hassanein, TE Zach Horton, WR Jackson Meeks, OL Mason Miller (not the Padres reliever), RB Jabari Small, DL Chris Smith and S Loren Strickland were also all signed to reserve/future deals by the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed LB Josh Ross, WR Dontae Fleming, S Kahlef Hailassie, G Vershon Lee, T Caleb Etienne, WR Joaquin Davis, WR Jeshaun Jones and TE Bryson Nesbit to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-902c-d56e-afff-f6ecf3f90000</link>
      <description>Ross has appeared in 22 NFL games and has 11 tackles, all of them as a special teamer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-902c-d56e-afff-f6ecf3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed CB Dalys Beanum, CB Beanie Bishop Jr, WR Elijah Cooks, S Elliott Davison, DT Coziah Izzard, OT Easton Kilty, CB Jayden Price, and OT Barry Wesley to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-908c-d56e-afff-f6ec1f3d0000</link>
      <description>Cooks appeared in 11 games for the Jaguars during the 2023 and 2024 season, catching a combined 3-of-4 targets for 38 yards. He’ll look to break out in camp and preseason after change of scenery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-908c-d56e-afff-f6ec1f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger to the 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9090-dc7a-af9b-dfbfda090000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger was not elevated for Week 18 while still having one standard elevation remaining, but will now head into the postseason a member of the 53-man, game-day roster. It’ll give the Broncos additional maneuverability during what they hope is a long playoff run as the No. 1 seed in the AFC. The veteran backup chose not to sign with the Colts following the injury to Daniel Jones and was reported to have had discussions with the Broncos regarding their plans moving forward. “We’ve talked about some things for the playoffs,” Ehlinger said ahead of Week 18, hinting at the move made official Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9090-dc7a-af9b-dfbfda090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL reinstated suspended Steelers WR DK Metcalf and suspended Chargers LB Denzel Perryman.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9096-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe4960000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was suspended for two games for throwing a punch at a fan in Week 16 while Perryman was suspended for the same timeframe for repeated player safety violations following a helmet-to-helmet hit on Cowboys WR Ryan Flournoy. Both players were reinstated as their respective teams prepare for the postseason, meaning they are cleared to practice ahead of the Wildcard Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9096-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe4960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed LB Swayze Bozeman, TE Tanner Conner, OLB Trace Ford, OL Reid Holskey, CB Patrick McMorris, and CB Myles Purchase to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a0-dc7a-af9b-dfbf30660000</link>
      <description>GM Joe Schoen’s first act after being retained by the team was to sign six practice squad players to reserve/futures contracts. We’re sure this is the right move for the team’s future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a0-dc7a-af9b-dfbf30660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LB Von Miller said he wants to play another year and remain with the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a4-d56e-afff-f6ece7f40000</link>
      <description>Miller will be 37 in March but said he wants to return for a 17th professional season, also stating that he hopes to remain in Washington. “Whoever wants me, that’s where I’ll be,” the veteran continued, stating that he understand he is no position to be making demands considering his age. Either way, Miller seems intent on playing again in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-90a4-d56e-afff-f6ece7f40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
