<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce (back) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 14 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f002-d8cf-affb-fc2ad60e0000</link>
      <description>He was fine all week, but picked up a DNP on Friday and was added to the injury report. Pearce’s absence would be good news for Sam Darnold’s time in the pocket against a Falcons defense that has mostly been good against non-Bryce Young pass offenses this year. The rookie, acquired for the Falcons first-round pick in 2026, has five sacks in 12 games this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f002-d8cf-affb-fc2ad60e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-effe-d8cf-affb-fffefd370000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler breaks the positive news, saying, barring a “surprise” Adams will be good to go. Adams’ 14 scrimmage touchdowns are the third-most in the NFL, following Week 14’s Thursday Night Football game. Even in the unlikely event that the Rams were to limit Adams’ snap, he is as good a bet as any to return WR1 value as a non-stop touchdown-scorer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-effe-d8cf-affb-fffefd370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Ty Chandler (knee) is questionable for Minnesota’s Week 14 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f005-da9b-a9bf-fe0d8d280000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full all week, so he’d seem likely to be activated from injured reserve and play against the Commanders on Sunday. With both Aaron Jones and Jordan Mason healthy, it doesn’t feel like Chandler is going to find a fantasy-friendly role this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f005-da9b-a9bf-fe0d8d280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is questionable for Minnesota’s Week 14 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f007-d005-a9bf-f83721e60000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw practiced in full on Wednesday as he continues to rest on Thursdays, but he did not play off a questionable tag in Week 13 and it should not be assumed he’ll be ready for this week’s game. Donovan Jackson (ankle) is also questionable after missing last week’s game and returning to practice on Thursday in a limited session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f007-d005-a9bf-f83721e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder) is not on Minnesota’s final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f009-da9b-a9bf-fe0d41710000</link>
      <description>Jones has been limited in practice all week, but will likely remain the lead back for the Vikings against the Commanders. He deserves a low-end RB2 ranking in most leagues. Jones spoke to the media Thursday and agreed with their suggestion that this offense has been “dumbed down” for J.J. McCarthy’s sake, so perhaps there’s some chance of a Vikings rebound in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f009-da9b-a9bf-fe0d41710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RT Taliese Fuaga (ankle) will not play in New Orleans’ Week 14 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00b-d005-a9bf-f83fffef0000</link>
      <description>Fuaga played in Week 13, but appears to have injured his other ankle — this is not the same ankle he was on the report for earlier in the year — somewhere along the way despite playing 100 percent of the snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00b-d005-a9bf-f83fffef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00d-d77b-adfa-fa8fd3380000</link>
      <description>Godwin practiced fully on Thursday before logging a limited session on Friday. We suspect this was just rest. Godwin and rookie WR Emeka Egbuka will again operate as the team’s top-two wide receivers, with WR Mike Evans (collarbone) and WR Jalen McMillan (neck) having been ruled out. Godwin with a FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00d-d77b-adfa-fa8fd3380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints S Justin Reid (knee) won’t play in New Orleans’ Week 14 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f010-d77b-adfa-fa933b460000</link>
      <description>He suffered a knee injury in Week 13, one that Kellen Moore said will “not send him to injured reserve.” But it doesn’t appear that Reid will be back any time soon. Terrell Burgess will likely be called upon for most of the snaps at safety on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f010-d77b-adfa-fa933b460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00c-d77b-adfa-fa8fe2660000</link>
      <description>Just one week ago, Mayfield’s availability was in question. He played through the AC joint in his non-throwing shoulder last week, albeit in pain, but he is once again ready to roll for game day. The Buccaneers’ quarterback practiced fully on consecutive days to close the week. He can be treated as a borderline QB1/2. Unfortunately, WR Mike Evans (collarbone) and WR Jalen McMillan (neck) will not play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f00c-d77b-adfa-fa8fe2660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f011-d8cf-affb-fc3b873b0000</link>
      <description>Irving totaled 19 touches in his first game back from a lengthy injury, finishing as the half-PPR RB14. It was a promising showing. Irving can be treated as a trusted RB1 against the Saints this weekend, once again operating as the Buccaneers’ clear-cut lead back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f011-d8cf-affb-fc3b873b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
