<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:05:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Cardinals have scheduled a second interview on Tuesday with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d867-dc7a-af9b-dfff00470000</link>
      <description>Saleh is currently interviewing with the Titans for their head coaching vacancy. If he lives without a deal, he will be on his way to Arizona for a second meeting with the Cardinals on Tuesday. Saleh has made the rounds this coaching cycle, meeting with four different teams to discuss their head-coaching vacancies, with the Cardinals being the first team to put in a second request. The former Jets head coach returned to the Bay Area in 2025 to lead the Niners defense to a 13th-ranked finish in points allowed, and is clearly a valued candidate on the coaching market despite going 20-36 in his first try as a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d867-dc7a-af9b-dfff00470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed a virtual interview with Panthers DC Ejiro Evero, amongst others.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d888-d35e-a1bf-ddca3a580000</link>
      <description>The Steelers reportedly completed virtual interviews with seven coaches during the previous week, to include, Evero, Packers DC Jeff Hafley, 49ers OC Klay Kubiak, Chargers DC Jesse Minter, Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase, Rams DC Chris Schula, and Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver. The team will also reportedly conduct in-person interviews this week for the select few that made it through their first round of questioning. More to come following the unexpected departure of Mike Tomlin, who had been the league’s longest tenured coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d888-d35e-a1bf-ddca3a580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Vikings pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones for their vacant defensive coordinator position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d891-d968-a19b-d8f181380000</link>
      <description>Jones has drawn a lot of interest this coaching cycle after contributing to a defense that allowed the fewest pass yards per game in 2025 at only 158.5. That was also part of the reason the Vikings faced one of the highest rush rates over expectation during the regular season. All of the interest in Jones has come for defensive coordinator vacancies, which makes sense considering the highest position he has held at the NFL level came in 2025 when he added defensive pass game coordinator to his resume.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d891-d968-a19b-d8f181380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers interviewed Cardinals passing game coordinator and wide receivers coach Drew Terrell for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d896-dc7a-af9b-dfbffdad0000</link>
      <description>Former Cardinals offensive coordinator Drew Petzing landed on his feet after less than two weeks on the open market following his termination in Arizona, hired by the Lions for the same position. Terrell, who worked under Petzing with the Cardinals, has also been a hot commodity this coaching cycle after picking up interviews with the Commanders and Chargers. Terrell has coached at the NFL level for eight season as he attempts to land an offensive coordinator gig for the first time in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d896-dc7a-af9b-dfbffdad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers will interview Eagles defensive backs coach Christian Parker for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d8fc-d35e-a1bf-ddfee65b0000</link>
      <description>Parker will interview with the Cowboys on Wednesday before heading straight to Green Bay to interview for the same defensive coordinator position. Viewed as a “rising star” in many inner circles, Parker appears to have a good chance at his first defensive coordinator gig at the NFL level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d8fc-d35e-a1bf-ddfee65b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired former 49ers DC and Jets HC Robert Saleh as head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d9cc-d56e-afff-ffec3be00000</link>
      <description>Another domino falls in the 2026 coaching carousel as Saleh gets his second crack at head coaching duties, this time with the Titans. Long heralded for his aggressive and unrelenting defensive tendencies, Saleh will look to improve upon his .357 career win rate as a head coach after a tumultuous tenure in New York after peaking at a 7-10 record in 2022 and 2023. He steps into a near full rebuild after the Titans unloaded numerous key pieces at the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d9cc-d56e-afff-ffec3be00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Steelers on Wednesday will interview former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-db79-d56e-afff-fff97cee0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy had interviewed with the Titans, who filled their head coaching vacancy on Tuesday by hiring former 49ers defensive coordinator Robert Saleh. McCarthy, who was raised in the Pittsburgh area, would seem to be a natural fit for the Steelers as they look to keep their postseason streak alive even if they are not Super Bowl contenders. McCarthy has shown he can do just that during his stints in Green Bay and Dallas. McCarthy has won 61 percent of his games over 18 years as an NFL head coach. The Steelers are reportedly open to McCarthy’s former QB Aaron Rodgers returning in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-db79-d56e-afff-fff97cee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers requested an interview with Vikings defensive backs coach Daronte Jones for the team’s defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbb4-d35e-a1bf-dff6eb1f0000</link>
      <description>Jones is a popular name on the coaching circuit this month. After coaching a Minnesota secondary that allowed the fewest pass yards per game in 2025 (159) along with the NFL’s third lowest drop back success rate, Jones has landed interviews with the Giants and Jets for their defensive coordinator openings. The Packers are widely expected to interview many candidates to fill their DC vacancy after the Dolphins hired Jeff Hafley as their head coach this week. Jones, 47, would take over a Green Bay defense that gave up the league’s tenth highest EPA per play in 2025 if he’s hired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbb4-d35e-a1bf-dff6eb1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe believes Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley will prioritize physicality and toughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said the Dolphins under Hafley will transition from a roster predicated on speed to one based on size and toughness. The team will also look to emulate the Packers in drafting and developing players instead of making splash signings in free agency, Wolfe said. Hafley, 46, who served as Green Bay’s defensive coordinator over the past two seasons, will look to revamp a Miami defense that last year allowed the NFL’s second highest drop back success rate and the ninth highest rushing success rate. Look for the Dolphins to invest heavily in defensive players in the 2026 NFL Draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
