<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson is inactive for Week 18 against the Cowboys, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a3c-d56e-afff-eefc133f0000</link>
      <description>Wilson will end his first, and likely only, season in New York with just six games played (three starts). He completed 69-of-119 passes (58 percent completion rate) for 831 yards, three touchdowns, and three interceptions. He also took 10 sacks and had his worst QBR and overall quarterback rating of his career. Wilson will be a free agent this offseason and is unlikely to be signed into a clear starting job. He will almost certainly need to compete for, and win, a job if the 37-year-old wants to continue his playing career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a3c-d56e-afff-eefc133f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 7-of-11 passes for 70 yards in Week 18 against the Giants before being benched in the second half.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a54-d56e-afff-eefc6dcb0000</link>
      <description>Prescott was not hurt, but the Cowboys simply decided that, with nothing to play for, they’d rather let Joe Milton play the second half. It was a bit of a surprising move considering Prescott is battling with Matthew Stafford to lead the NFL in passing yards and would be the first Cowboys player ever to accomplish the feat. Prescott will now finish the season by going 404-for-589 for 4,552 yards with 30 touchdowns and 10 interceptions. He is only 104 passing yards ahead of Stafford for the lead, heading into the 4 pm slate. It was a strong year for Dak, who had his most passing yards per game since 2020 and also added 178 rushing yards and two touchdowns on the ground. A big season for that production was the addition of George Pickens, who will be a free agent at the end of the season. How the Cowboys handle the second wide receiver spot will be a huge part of determining Dak’s fantasy value in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a54-d56e-afff-eefc6dcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy exited the Vikings’ Week 18 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a57-d56e-afff-eeff694b0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy appeared to be in severe pain after his first pass attempt of the second half, shaking his injured right hand and getting it checked out by the Vikings’ training staff. McCarthy appears to be done for the day after throwing for 182 scoreless yards against Green Bay’s backup defenders. McCarthy’s first full NFL season went about as badly as anyone could have predicted. He was woefully unprepared to take over as the Vikings’ starter after missing his rookie season with a knee injury, making baffling decisions and throwing inaccurately throughout his 11 games as the team’s starter. McCarthy was soft-benched in September for veteran journeyman Carson Wentz and missed Week 17 with the hand injury that flared up in Week 18 against the Packers. McCarthy will finish 11 touchdowns to 12 interceptions, completing 57 percent of his passes. The Vikings will have no choice but to bring in a veteran to compete for starting duties in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a57-d56e-afff-eeff694b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donovan Ezeiruaku was ejected from Week 18 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a95-d968-a19b-daf58e3e0000</link>
      <description>After the Giants scored a touchdown, there was a lot of pushing and shoving between the two teams, and Ezeiruaku ripped off the helmet of a Giants player and held it above his head in celebration. He was immediately penalized and removed from the game, ending his season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a95-d968-a19b-daf58e3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders declared QB Jayden Daniels, QB Marcus Mariota, QB Sam Hartman, RB Chase Edmonds, LT Laremy Tunsil, DE Jalyn Holmes, and DT Sheldon Day inactive for Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a95-d968-a19b-daf538210000</link>
      <description>The Commanders already ruled out Daniels and Mariota at the quarterback spot, leaving Josh Johnson to start for the final game of the regular season. Sam Hartman is inactive, but will be the emergency third quarterback. Left tackle Laremy Tunsil was also ruled out for an eliminated Commanders team looking ahead to next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a95-d968-a19b-daf538210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
