<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Malik Willis (shoulder/hamstring) is questionable for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f65-d56e-afff-ffed7cc00000</link>
      <description>He never progressed past a limited session this week, just as it was ahead of Week 18’s game where he was ultimately the inactive emergency quarterback. If Willis can’t go this week, Desmond Ridder will be Green Bay’s backup against the Bears. The fact that Ridder was signed to the active roster early in the week seems to forecast that there’s a real chance of Willis sitting again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f65-d56e-afff-ffed7cc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers OL Zach Tom (back/knee) is questionable for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f67-d968-a19b-dff7fd3c0000</link>
      <description>Tom did not play at all after leaving Week 15’s game against the Broncos and was given Friday off. At this point it seems likely that they are managing his injuries to try to get whatever they can out of him here. He’s a re-injury risk on Saturday, but the Packers have to let Tom play through it if he can. He’s simply too much of an upgrade for them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f67-d968-a19b-dff7fd3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales is “very optimistic” that Robert Hunt (questionable/biceps) will play on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f6b-d968-a19b-dffbe58a0000</link>
      <description>Hunt has been designated to return and looks likely to be active against the Rams, perhaps swinging the run game matchup. The 29-year-old power guard has been on IR since Week 2’s torn bicep. Chandler Zavala (IR/calf) is also questionable for Saturday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f6b-d968-a19b-dffbe58a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f71-dc7a-af9b-dfff2b240000</link>
      <description>Warren was spotted with a mask and gloves on in the locker room. Most of the time, players play through illness in playoff games. We’d expect at worst Warren winds up with a questionable tag on Saturday and plays, so we’re not overly concerned about the illness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f71-dc7a-af9b-dfff2b240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is not on Los Angeles’ final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f78-d968-a19b-dff964080000</link>
      <description>Adams looks likely to be full-go from the jump after three full sessions of practice this week. He probably could have played at any point after the Rams’ unfortunate Week 16 loss to Seattle, but there wasn’t much reason for him to risk it. He’ll be one of the top playoff best ball picks and DFS plays for this week with a solid matchup against the Panthers pass defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f78-d968-a19b-dff964080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens and Titans requested to interview former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f7a-d56e-afff-fffa634f0000</link>
      <description>Both teams have been linked to Kingsbury in prior reports, as have the Giants. The former Commanders offensive coordinator continues to get head-coaching buzz. Another interview or two seems likely. Kingsbury’s offense delivered up-and-down results over the last two seasons, though injuries played a large role in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f7a-d56e-afff-fffa634f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions general manager Brad Holmes said the team will have an “in-depth” discussion about RB David Montgomery’s future in Detroit this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f8d-d56e-afff-ffed12aa0000</link>
      <description>Montgomery is under contract through 2027. The Lions can save $11.26 million by cutting him this offseason, while taking on $8.6 million in dead money. Holmes adds that the Lions “love” Montgomery and believe “he deserves to be in a situation where his skill set can be utilized.” Montgomery operated as the team’s No. 2 running back this season, totaling 182 touches—far fewer than the 221 and 235 he logged in 2024 and 2023, respectively. The Lions could choose to look for a complementary power back to partner with RB Jahmyr Gibbs in the draft this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f8d-d56e-afff-ffed12aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State LB Arvell Reese declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f57-d56e-afff-ffff5c510000</link>
      <description>Reese was a member of Ohio State’s national championship squad in 2024, typically lining up as a linebacker in the box. Reese then split snaps defensively in 2025, lining up frequently as both a linebacker and pass rusher on the edge, notching 31 tackles, nine TFLs, 20 quarterback pressures and seven sacks. He was named the Big Ten Linebacker of the Year for his final season efforts, while also earning Consensus All-America and first-team All-Big Ten honors. ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes Reese “certainly has to be in the conversation for the Jets” with the second overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f57-d56e-afff-ffff5c510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fba-d968-a19b-dffb8b080000</link>
      <description>Goedert, 31, is now up to two limited sessions in the lead-up to the Eagles’ Wild Card Round game against the 49ers. We expect Goedert to suit up. Although we would like to see him practicing fully, the team could just be limiting the veteran player’s reps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fba-d968-a19b-dffb8b080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed their interview with Broncos passing game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fc5-d35e-a1bf-dfc76cde0000</link>
      <description>Webb has just three years of coaching experience under his belt, having been hired as the Broncos’ quarterbacks coach in 2023. He managed to add the passing game coordinator title last offseason. Interviewing for the Ravens’ head-coaching vacancy this quickly is quite an accomplishment. Thus far, Webb has also been linked to the Raiders, who reportedly requested to interview him earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fc5-d35e-a1bf-dfc76cde0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
