<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jalen Nailor (hand) is practicing in full for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ba-de13-afdd-56fb939d0000</link>
      <description>Nailor is firmly on track to suit up in Week 1 against the Bears. Unfortunately, he could be fourth in the passing game pecking order, playing behind Justin Jefferson, Adam Thielen and T.J. Hockenson. Nailor cannot be relied on to return FLEX value in 12-team leagues, instead profiling as a low-floor WR6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ba-de13-afdd-56fb939d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16c0-d332-a1fd-96f67a3e0000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw still has a chance to suit up for Week 1 against the Bears. J.J. McCarthy’s blindside protector tore both his ACL and MCL in Week 8 last year and has spent the offseason rehabbing the injuries. He was able to participate in team drills in late July, which was a positive sign for his early-season availability. Hopefully, he returns to practice by Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16c0-d332-a1fd-96f67a3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16bc-dbe3-a9bb-36fffb3b0000</link>
      <description>It’s a curious development for Smith, who was said to be dealing with a “health issue” in late August. NFL players generally play through illnesses, but this could be something to monitor. The Vikings’ defense is talented and well-coached, so they might be okay without him. It’s a story worth following, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16bc-dbe3-a9bb-36fffb3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) practice in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d3ffdd0000</link>
      <description>Taylor was limited yesterday so today’s upgrade is great news. In a perfect world, Taylor will kick back on the sideline and let Justin Fields lead the Jets to a decent record. Fields briefly dealt with a toe injury in training camp, though, so it’s good to have a reliable backup at the ready. Taylor does not need to be rostered in re-draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d3ffdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d9-d332-a1fd-96ff834d0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw is trending toward missing Week 1 at this point, as he rehabs his second significant quad injury of the offseason. If he is active, it’s unlikely he plays a full complement of snaps. Broncos backup DT Malcolm Roach exited practice after suffering a calf injury today, which jeopardizes his availability for this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d9-d332-a1fd-96ff834d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Jaydon Blue is inactive for Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ee-db7b-a5dd-b6ee00bb0000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal (seemingly) healthy scratch for Blue, who was an early summer hype merchant who slowly faded from fantasy consciousness after suffering a bruised heel and a low-ankle sprain in training camp. He was not listed on the injury report, but perhaps he needs more time. The Cowboys will instead roll with Javonte Williams and Miles Sanders as their two active backs. Williams will likely handle passing down duties while Sanders rotates in for change-of-pace rushes. The Cowboys also declared LB Shemar James, DT Mazi Smith, OT Ajani Cornelius, OL Hakeem Adeniji, OL Trevor Keegan and DT Perrion Winfrey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ee-db7b-a5dd-b6ee00bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) “is expected to play” in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16f6-d332-a1fd-96f630720000</link>
      <description>Rapoport relayed his source’s info, saying, Parsons’ facet sprain is something he “needs to take some medicine for” and that an “epidural could potentially await him if he keeps having problems with it.” Shot or not, Parsons is all but guaranteed to be on the field when the Packers host the Lions on Sunday. The Packers face Parsons’ former Cowboys squad in Week 4, and play the Browns in Week 3. The Packers’ D/ST could be a high-scoring unit, racking up sacks aplenty both weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16f6-d332-a1fd-96f630720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Tanner McKee, EDGE Azeez Ojulari, EDGE Ogbo Okoronkwo, OL Drew Kendall, OT Cameron Williams, OL Kenyon Green and DT Ty Robinson inactive for Week 1 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fcae-d332-a1fd-febec9da0000</link>
      <description>McKee had been set to be Jalen Hurts’ backup before breaking his throwing thumb late in training camp. No. 2 duties now belong to Sam Howell. Beyond that, this is a mercifully quiet early-season injury list for the defending-champion Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fcae-d332-a1fd-febec9da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16fe-dbe3-a9bb-36ffdebe0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez is highly unlikely to play at this point, having rehabbed this hamstring injury for more than a month. Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers’ day would be considerably easier if Gonzalez were unable to go. Patriots OT Will Campbell was also added to the injury report with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16fe-dbe3-a9bb-36ffdebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1717-db7b-a5dd-b71728c50000</link>
      <description>Teams often give veteran players, particularly older running backs, days off at the first sign of irritation or discomfort, so it is entirely possible this is simply the 49ers acting out of an abundance of caution. McCaffrey does have a history of calf and Achilles tendon issues dating back to Week 17, 2023, so managing his practice load is prudent. Tomorrow’s injury report should help clarify his Week 1 status. In the meantime, fantasy managers are advised to pickup Brian Robinson if he available in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1717-db7b-a5dd-b71728c50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
