<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll said Geno Smith (ankle) will not play Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c6-dc7a-af9b-ffffce3f0000</link>
      <description>It appears as though Smith’s season is over. Earlier today, Vegas Nation’s Vincent Bonsignore reported that the Raiders will use “a combination of Kenny Pickett and Aidan O’Connell” this week. Neither player should be in starting lineups, in what sounds like some sort of game-day platoon. In his first season with the Raiders, Smith completed 302-of-448 passes for 3,025 yards, 19 touchdowns and 17 interceptions, while rushing 41 times for 109 yards. He is under contract through 2027, though he is owed no money that season. If the Raiders were to cut him this offseason, it would cost them $18.5 million in dead money while saving them $8 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c6-dc7a-af9b-ffffce3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jack Bech (back) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d9-d56e-afff-f6f944b30000</link>
      <description>Bech is back. Whether that means much for the Raiders’ Week 18 outlook remains to be seen. The underwhelming rookie will at least have a chance to put a good game on film for whichever coaching staff is there to review it in 2026, though. Bech is a low-floor FLEX this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d9-d56e-afff-f6f944b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Kareem Hunt (illness) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c7-d56e-afff-f6ef86b70000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs rotated three running backs last week, rendering all low-floor options. If Hunt’s illness were to sideline him on game day, both RB Isiah Pacheco and RB Brashard Smith would get a projections boost against the Raiders’ porous defense in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76c7-d56e-afff-f6ef86b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (illness) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d8-dc7a-af9b-fffff7480000</link>
      <description>Worthy has performed underwhelmingly for quite some time. Illnesses rarely keep players sidelined on game day, so we expect him out there against the Raiders this week, though he will likely be stuck running cardio for much of it. Worthy is a touchdown-dependent FLEX option in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76d8-dc7a-af9b-fffff7480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76e3-d968-a19b-7ef312380000</link>
      <description>Hampton is a candidate to sit out in Week 18 against the Broncos. Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh has already ruled out QB Justin Herbert (hand), and told reporters earlier this week that getting his players healthy is a priority this week. Chargers backup RB Jaret Patterson could handle a decent workload, with Nos. 2 and 3 RBs, Kimani Vidal (neck) and Hassan Haskins (concussion), limited on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76e3-d968-a19b-7ef312380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76e0-d56e-afff-f6e875dc0000</link>
      <description>Chargers starting RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday. Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh has only ruled out QB Justin Herbert (hand) thus far, though other starters could also be ruled out as the week progresses. Chargers No. 3 RB Hassan Haskins (concussion) was limited as well. Backup RB Jaret Patterson can be stashed by running back-needy fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76e0-d56e-afff-f6e875dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) said he is feeling “fabulous” and “absolutely” expects to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ed-d968-a19b-7efd284e0000</link>
      <description>Kittle resumed practicing in a limited capacity on Tuesday. We do not yet know his participation level today, but he is certainly on the right side of questionable for Saturday’s game. The Seahawks field an elite defense, but Kittle should be started as a high-end TE1 all the same.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ed-d968-a19b-7efd284e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philip Rivers said he intends to retire after 18 seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ed-dc7a-af9b-ffff369c0000</link>
      <description>Rivers could still suit up as a backup one last time, but it appears as though his time in the NFL has finally come to a close. Kay Adams spoke with Rivers on Wednesday, pressing him on the matter. The 44-year-old quarterback reiterated that it is, indeed, time to hang up his cleats. In three games with the Colts, Rivers completed 58-of-92 passes for four touchdowns and three interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-76ed-dc7a-af9b-ffff369c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed (concussion) was seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7703-dc7a-af9b-ffbf84920000</link>
      <description>Shaheed was seen practicing without a red non-contact jersey today. That is a good sign regarding his availability for the Seahawks’ Week 18 game against the 49ers on Saturday. If he is indeed cleared to play, Shaheed warrants WR3/FLEX treatment against the 49ers’ fantasy-friendly defense. The game’s outcome determines both the NFC West champion and the NFC’s No. 1 playoff seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7703-dc7a-af9b-ffbf84920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewOrleans.Football’s Nick Underhill reports Chris Olave will miss Week 18 against the Falcons after a blood clot was detected in his lung.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-79d0-d35e-a1bf-7dd247940000</link>
      <description>Per Underhill, the blood clot was “caught early before anything bad could happen and will be fine.” That is a major relief. The hope will be that this issue doesn’t affect his offseason routine, but the worst-case scenario is already off the table. Olave’s fourth season comes to an end with 100 receptions for 1,163 yards and nine touchdowns. All three of those marks are career-highs. He finished the fantasy football season as the WR6. Olave has always been a good target-earner, but he hit a new level in 2025, logging a 30 percent target share despite needing to develop chemistry with two quarterbacks throughout the year. Both Spencer Rattler and Tyler Shough, who can be penciled in as the team’s starter for 2026, locked in on Olave and never looked back. Assuming this health scare passes, Olave will enter his fifth season as a low-end WR1 in early fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-79d0-d35e-a1bf-7dd247940000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
