<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-6 targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 13 win against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b2-db57-afda-d6b226bc0000</link>
      <description>Jennings cashed in on a short touchdown grab from Brock Purdy, his fourth touchdown reception of his past five games as the de facto WR1 in the run-heavy 49ers offense. Jennings on Sunday against the Browns led the Niners in targets. He now has at least six targets in each of his past four games. Jennings and the Niners will have their bye next week before returning to face the Titans in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b2-db57-afda-d6b226bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 16-of-27 passes for 229 yards and two touchdowns in the Jaguars’ 25-3, Week 13 win over the Titans, adding three carries for 25 yards and a two-point conversion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6a8-db57-afda-d6ba25a40000</link>
      <description>Lawrence and the Jaguars offense hit a groove in the first quarter and hardly had to do much the rest of the game. He completed long throws to Parker Washington and Jakobi Meyers in the first quarter, capping off the drive with a short touchdown pass to Meyers. On the next possession, Lawrence found Brenton Strange over the middle of the field for his second score of the game, adding two more points a two-point conversion sneak. Lawrence was sacked three times and struggled a bit in the pocket after LT Walker Little (concussion) left the game. However, his second half did not need much nuance as the Jaguars defense locked up the offense in a blowout victory. Lawrence will certainly face more resistance against the Colts in Week 14 and will rank as a fantasy QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6a8-db57-afda-d6ba25a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 16-of-29 attempts for 168 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 13 win against the Browns, adding two rushes for five yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ba-db57-afda-d6ba18870000</link>
      <description>Purdy, who has struggled in cold conditions in the past, managed the offense well and made a number of strong throws on Sunday in windy Cleveland. Purdy connected with Jauan Jennings for a short touchdown and ran one in for three yards out, saving his fantasy day against the elite Browns defense. It was a nice bounce back effort for Purdy after last week’s three-interception performance against Carolina. Purdy will be a solid fantasy option in Week 15 against the Titans when the 49ers return from their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ba-db57-afda-d6ba18870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacoby Brissett completed 29-of-40 passes for 301 yards, two touchdowns and an interception in the Cardinals’ 20-17, Week 13 loss to the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6bb-d82c-a79a-f7bf4b410000</link>
      <description>The gunslinging journeyman added three rushes for 16 yards. Making his seventh start in place of Kyler Murray, Brissett reached 300 yards for the third straight game and fourth time overall. He spread the ball around, targeting a returning Marvin Harrison Jr. seven times. Michael Wilson also saw seven looks, with Trey McBride leading the team with nine. Brissett’s INT was a costly early mistake that in his defense came on a tipped pass. His scores were a 15-yard strike to Bam Knight in stride and late 15-yarder to McBride. Simply dropping back and letting it rip, Brissett’s Flacco-ian fantasy production is showing no signs of abating, though the Rams are a difficult Week 14 matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6bb-d82c-a79a-f7bf4b410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 1-of-2 targets for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 13 win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b9-d82c-a79a-f7bdd08e0000</link>
      <description>The Rams did their part to keep McMillan under wraps for most of the game, but the rookie receiver came up big in the fourth quarter. With the Panthers down 28-24 in the fourth quarter and facing a fourth and two, McMillan broke free behind Emmanuel Forbes to haul in a 43-yard pass for the go-ahead touchdown, which proved to be the game-winning score for the now 7-6 Panthers. The two targets he saw in this one were the fewest McMillan has seen in any game this season, but the rookie did just enough to satisfy fantasy managers for the week. He’ll be on the WR2 radar when the Panthers return in Week 15 to face the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b9-d82c-a79a-f7bdd08e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 12 times for 28 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 13 win over the Titans, adding one reception for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b9-db57-afda-d6bb24670000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars went up two scores by halftime and never looked back. Though Etienne still operated as the Jaguars’ lead back, this led to less opportunities in the passing game for him. Bhayshul Tuten got the red zone opportunities, so Etienne’s role was reduced to an inefficient 2.3 yards per carry. Without a score, this ends up as a bad fantasy day for him, though the manner of usage indicates he is still the top back in the backfield. Tuten will take some red zone usage while LeQuint Allen takes passing-down usage, but Etienne remains an explosive option as both a runner and pass-catcher. He is in the RB2 range for Week 14 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6b9-db57-afda-d6bb24670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 19 times for 64 yards in the Texans’ Week 13 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6c0-d82c-a79a-f7d457740000</link>
      <description>He added a three-yard catch on his only target. Despite missing time to an injured foot in the first half, Marks out-snapped Nick Chubb 41-25. He had a number of big gains, none bigger than a nine-yarder to help run out the clock as the Colts ran out of timeouts. He also could have done a little more with a breakaway alley in the third quarter, but couldn’t quite cross up Nick Cross. Marks will be a low-end RB2 candidate against a Chiefs defense that has been fairly good against the run this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6c0-d82c-a79a-f7d457740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker caught 4-of-6 passes for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 13 win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6be-d82c-a79a-f7be80630000</link>
      <description>Coker led all Panthers’ pass-catchers in receptions, yards, and targets in this one. The second-year receiver caught his first touchdown of the season in the third quarter when he broke free past Emmanuel Forbes on a fourth and three to haul in a 33-yard score. He later came up with a 10-yard reception on the game’s final drive to covert a first down and officially put the game on ice. The six targets Coker saw in this one sets a new season-high, but fantasy managers shouldn’t rush to chase this performance in Week 15 against the Saints when the Panthers return from their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6be-d82c-a79a-f7be80630000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
