<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:25:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons claimed WR Malik Heath off waivers from the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old receiver has a career 31/308/3 slash line in 37 games with the Packers and can be involved on special teams. The Falcons are at a point where they’re relying on David Sills every weekend. The waiver claim makes some sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers listed QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield continues to be listed with the same left shoulder injury he has played through each of the last two weeks. We’ll assume he’s good to go for Thursday night’s game against the Falcons unless we hear otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL flexed the Patriots’ Week 16 game against the Ravens to Sunday Night Football.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffef-d005-a9bf-ffffb6770000</link>
      <description>The Bengals and Dolphins were initially slated to play on Sunday night in Week 16. They will now move to a standard 1:00 PM EST slot, while the Ravens and Patriots will prepare to play under the lights in a game that could still carry major playoff implications for both teams. As is the case with every Sunday night game on NBC, we will be waiting all day for this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffef-d005-a9bf-ffffb6770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs OT Wanya Morris suffered a season-ending knee injury in Week 14’s loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-000e-d005-a9bf-d83e7fb00000</link>
      <description>Morris suffered a gruesome knee injury early in the first quarter of Sunday’s game against the Texans and was ruled out shortly after. The third-year tackle was replaced by rookie UDFA Esa Pole, who allowed three pressures on 42 pass-blocking snaps against one of the top pass-rushing defenses in the league. It’s yet another massive blow to a Chiefs offensive line that was already missing its two starting tackles prior to Morris going down. Pole will likely draw the start in Week 15’s game against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-000e-d005-a9bf-d83e7fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed LB Jason Pierre-Paul.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0021-d005-a9bf-d83504410000</link>
      <description>JPP hasn’t played an NFL snap since 2023. The 36-year-old pass rusher spent four seasons with the Buccaneers from 2018 to 2021 and split time with the Saints and Dolphins in his last season. If he’s elevated to the active roster, JPP wouldn’t serve as anything more than a situational pass rusher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0021-d005-a9bf-d83504410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LG Ben Bredeson (knee) will not play in Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0027-d77b-adfb-caa7693e0000</link>
      <description>Beat writer Greg Auman reports that the Buccaneers may be without Bredeson “for multiple weeks” after the sixth-year tackle suffered a knee injury in Week 14’s loss to the Saints. Auman said the absence could be long enough to warrant Bredson landing on injured reserve, which would end his season. Bredeson has started all 11 games he’s appeared in this season, earning a PFF grade of 53.7 while allowing 20 pressures and one sack. Elijah Klein is listed behind Bredeson on the depth chart and will presumably draw the start on Thursday night against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0027-d77b-adfb-caa7693e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Omar Ruiz reports Chargers QB Justin Herbert (left hand) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-003a-d8cf-affb-bc3a81b00000</link>
      <description>Per Ruiz, Herbert is expected to play while wearing a padded glove on his surgically repaired left hand. The veteran quarterback was seen warming up with the glove about two hours prior to kickoff for Monday Night Football. Herbert will remarkably play after breaking his non-throwing hand in Week 13, having undergone surgery to address the issue Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-003a-d8cf-affb-bc3a81b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers QB Justin Herbert (left hand) is active for Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0054-da9b-a9bf-de5d375e0000</link>
      <description>Confirming previous reports, Herbert will suit up against the Eagles just seven days after having surgery on his non-throwing hand to repair a broken bone. Expect the veteran quarterback to operate almost exclusively from shotgun, something that influence play calling tendencies. Inactive for the Chargers are CB Nikko Reed, LB Kyle Kennard, T Austin Deculus, WR Dalevon Campbell, TE Tyler Conklin, and WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0054-da9b-a9bf-de5d375e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared OLB Josh Uche, QB Sam Howell, CB Mac McWilliams, RB A.J. Dillon, RT Lane Johnson, and DT Jalen Carter inactive for Week 14 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-005e-da9b-a9bf-de5f5f520000</link>
      <description>Johnson had already been ruled out earlier in the week, targeting Week 15 against the Raiders as his potential return date. Philadelphia’s offensive struggles have been exacerbated with the veteran’s absence, something that could come to a head against the league’s third-ranked defense on Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-005e-da9b-a9bf-de5f5f520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts will bring in QB Philip Rivers for a workout Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0060-da9b-a9bf-de6defa50000</link>
      <description>The 44-year-old quarterback last played in 2020 as a member of the Colts. The now-quarterback-needy team are seriously considering bringing him back as veteran depth behind Riley Leonard, a notion that appears as outlandish as it does potentially brilliant. That said, Leonard is currently dealing with a knee ligament injury that could hold him out of the team’s Week 15 game against the Seahawks. Rivers, a surefire Hall of Fame candidate, would be first eligible in the next induction class but could see his clock reset should he gain eligibility in 2025. Stay tuned as this outrageous story develops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0060-da9b-a9bf-de6defa50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
