<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports Rico Dowdle will “start and get the bulk of the carries” against the Packers in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d673-a39e-bf9b963c0000</link>
      <description>Slot your running back rankings accordingly, folks. This is not a surprise after what Canales said on Monday about the situation, but it does look like the Panthers will divvy up carries favoring Dowdle while Hubbard will be “part of the offense” as well. We’re tentatively expecting something in the area of 60/40 or 70/30 Dowdle carries. Hubbard will be a rough desperation FLEX based on that, with the Packers favored by nearly two touchdowns on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d673-a39e-bf9b963c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d713-ad9e-7fde54c10000</link>
      <description>London was limited on Wednesday and Thursday. We do not yet know his Friday participation level, but he has ostensibly rehabbed the injury he suffered last Friday to the point where he can play effectively on game day. London will face stiff coverage from Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez on the perimeter. Playing through injury against a talented opponent is certainly less than ideal, but London can still be treated as a WR1 thanks to his top-tier talent and target-earning ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d713-ad9e-7fde54c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants CB Paulson Adebo (knee) won’t play in New York’s Week 9 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8d-d673-a39e-bf9d7d930000</link>
      <description>Neither will Cor’Dale Flott (concussion) — this is good news for Jauan Jennings, who figures to be the only 49ers wideout playable in most fantasy leagues while other targets flow to Christian McCaffrey and George Kittle. Disappointment Deonte Banks played all 59 snaps last week and the Giants also heavily employed Korie Black and Andru Phillips.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8d-d673-a39e-bf9d7d930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Daniel Bellinger (neck) is doubtful for New York’s Week 9 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8f-d713-ad9e-7fdf8b310000</link>
      <description>They haven’t dropped the full injury report yet, but we’d be surprised if Bellinger did more than a limited session. Theo Johnson should consolidate more tight end targets, perhaps enough to be a low-end TE1 play against San Francisco’s banged-up linebacker corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8f-d713-ad9e-7fdf8b310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) will not play in Chicago’s Week 9 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b92-d673-a39e-bf930be20000</link>
      <description>We’re a little surprised that Swift didn’t at least get a questionable tag, but this officially makes it Kyle Monangai szn for Week 9 against the woeful Bengals run defense. You could talk us into as high as a low-end RB2 tag for Monangai. Swift has played through this groin listing in recent weeks, but usually practices on Thursday when given time off on Wednesday. That was not the case this week. Ben Johnson called the groin injury a “week-to-week deal” and said he thinks the time off is “gonna pay dividends for us down the stretch here.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b92-d673-a39e-bf930be20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d45b-affe-7f9e9f7f0000</link>
      <description>Mooney was upgraded to full participation on Thursday, though his Friday participation has not yet been released. Assuming he remains a full go, his Week 9 game against the Patriots serves as somewhat of a prove-it week. The Falcons’ field-stretching wide receiver has finished in the WR3-WR4 range just twice this season. Now, in reasonably good health, Mooney enters no-excuses territory. He can be treated as a volatile FLEX option against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b8a-d45b-affe-7f9e9f7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (concussion) will not play in Chicago’s Week 9 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b95-d713-ad9e-7fd51c680000</link>
      <description>He will look to escape concussion protocol next week. Olamide Zaccheaus (knee) was cleared off the final injury report and figures to take most of the third-receiver snaps for the Bears this week, but he’s mostly an unexciting low-floor FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b95-d713-ad9e-7fd51c680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip/groin) is not on Chicago’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b97-d713-ad9e-7fd739ab0000</link>
      <description>As has become the norm since winding up in the hospital after a Monday night game a few weeks ago, Moore has been an injury report fixture that gets cleared to play on Friday. He’s an unexciting FLEX play against the Bengals in Week 9 — but he is coming off his best game of the season in both targets (7) and yards (73) against the Ravens in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b97-d713-ad9e-7fd739ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (back) is not on Chicago’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b99-d673-a39e-bf99511c0000</link>
      <description>Kmet got in a full session on Friday to officially clear a back injury that had him miss one game. He figures to steal some of the potential upside away from Colston Loveland in a game against the Bengals, who have allowed the most fantasy points to tight ends per game this year. Loveland is slightly less appealing with this news, but still meets the standard of TE1 flier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b99-d673-a39e-bf99511c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (heel) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b95-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb4b00000</link>
      <description>Odunze sat out on Wednesday, was limited on Thursday and practiced in full on Friday. The Bears did not list Odunze on the injury report in prior weeks, but he told reporters yesterday that he has been dealing with the ailment for some time. Perhaps this explains his poor showings in Weeks 6-7. No matter. He bounced back in Week 8 and can be expected to produce high-end fantasy results once again in Week 9 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b95-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb4b00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
