<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs EDGE Haason Reddick (ankle/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dbf-dab4-a3fb-9fff51e00000</link>
      <description>Several Tampa Bay defenders did not practice on Wednesday. Lavonte David and Antoine Winfield are among the most notable names on the list. David is dealing with knee and rib issues while Winfield has a toe injury. Coming off a Monday night game, the Bucs might be giving their veterans some maintenance days because of the short week. Still, it’s notable just how many big names they have on the injury report. A banged-up Bucs defense could help Spencer Rattler get back on track after throwing three interceptions in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dbf-dab4-a3fb-9fff51e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dc4-deb1-a39b-2dcefd210000</link>
      <description>Mayfield is known for playing through injuries. A limited practice to open the week means this knee issue should be a non-story by Friday. Mayfield lost Mike Evans to a multi-month shoulder injury on Monday and Chris Godwin has already been ruled out for Week 8. Emeka Egbuka managed to play through his hamstring issue, giving Mayfield one top-flight weapon to work with. Even with injuries piling up for the Bucs, Mayfield is entrenched in the QB1 ranks heading into his matchup with the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dc4-deb1-a39b-2dcefd210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewOrleans.Football’s Nick Underhill reports Chris Olave (ankle) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dc9-d5d8-a3ff-fde954d90000</link>
      <description>Per Underhill, Olave suffered the ankle injury in the Saints’ Week 7 loss to the Bears. You wouldn’t know that by his box score, which shows 98 yards and two touchdowns. Olave didn’t practice today, but that appears to be a precautionary measure to get him ready for Week 8. He will remain in the WR2 ranks versus the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dc9-d5d8-a3ff-fde954d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dcc-d5d8-a3ff-fded25090000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been dealing with the ankle injury for a few weeks. It has yet to cost him any playing time. With Kendre Miller out for the year because of a torn ACL, Kamara could actually see more work versus the Bucs on Sunday. Rookie running back Devin Neal should be in line for more work as well, making him worth a stash in deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dcc-d5d8-a3ff-fded25090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (neck) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dce-dab4-a3fb-9ffe56b20000</link>
      <description>The neck injury is new for Johnson, but it doesn’t look like something that will force him to miss Week 8’s game. A limited session to open the week is standard fare for veterans midway through the season. Coming off a 79-yard return to form versus the Bears, Johnson will flirt with a TE1 ranking ahead of his date with the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dce-dab4-a3fb-9ffe56b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd0-deb1-a39b-2dde354e0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall attempted to play through the knee issue in Week 4 but quickly re-aggravated the injury. He has been out ever since. A DNP to open the week suggests Pearsall will miss another game because of the lingering injury. Jauan Jennings and Kendrick Bourne will again operate as the team’s top wideouts. Jennings turned four catches into 31 yards while Bourne was held to 14 yards on two grabs. Fantasy managers can treat Jennings as a WR3 while Bourne is falling into the WR5 ranks ahead of San Francisco’s matchup with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd0-deb1-a39b-2dde354e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd5-dab4-a3fb-9ff51db20000</link>
      <description>Purdy returned to practice last week for some limited work. The team still chose to sit him for their matchup with the Falcons. Head coach Kyle Shanahan said on Monday it would be “a reach” for him to play this week, though he didn’t rule Purdy out entirely. We are fully expecting to see Mac Jones under center this week. Jones has been a competent QB2 for fantasy purposes across his four starts. He will stay in that range for a tough road game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd5-dab4-a3fb-9ff51db20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (ankle) is questionable for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ddb-deb1-a39b-2ddf02c50000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin O’Connell has already announced Carson Wentz as the starter, so McCarthy would only be available for backup duties if he is active. We expect the QB2 role to go to Max Brosmer versus the Chargers. McCarthy will continue to rehab his ankle injury for now, getting the mini-bye from Thursday to next Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ddb-deb1-a39b-2ddf02c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Darrisaw (knee) is questionable for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dde-d5d8-a3ff-fdffd9d70000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw was a surprise addition to the injury report on Wednesday. He was listed as a DNP and hit with the questionable tag. A late-week DNP, especially on a short week, is an ominous sign for a player. Justin Skule would likely take his place in the lineup if Darrisaw can’t suit up versus LA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dde-d5d8-a3ff-fdffd9d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (calf) was limited in practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0deb-d5d8-a3ff-fdeb1e5c0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs played through the calf issue and an illness in Week 7. He ceded six carries to Emanuel Wilson and logged just 13 rushes of his own but saved the day for fantasy managers with a pair of touchdowns. His workload should increase as he puts the calf issue behind him. Per usual, Jacobs is an RB1 heading into his Week 8 matchup with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0deb-d5d8-a3ff-fdeb1e5c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
