<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 21:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) won’t play in Atlanta’s Week 13 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc11-db57-afda-de33d5210000</link>
      <description>He didn’t seem especially close to coming back this week, with Raheem Morris calling him doubtful on Wednesday. London did not practice at all this week. With Tom Pelissero saying the Falcons could be playing things “conservatively” with London, his status for Week 14 remains questionable at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc11-db57-afda-de33d5210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc12-d6c4-abfb-de13e9ff0000</link>
      <description>Neal will presumably start with RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) sidelined. The Dolphins’ run defense allows 5.0 yards per carry and only two teams have allowed more explosive run plays than them (47). Saints TE Taysom Hill could handle a frustrating number of carries, particularly in the red zone, but Neal should at least operate as the lead running back on passing downs, while handling a reasonable rushing workload. Neal is an albeit uncomfortable borderline RB2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc12-d6c4-abfb-de13e9ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (pectoral/IR) is questionable for Miami’s Week 13 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc21-d82c-a79a-ffb51f000000</link>
      <description>Mike McDaniel said his return is in play and we’d tentatively consider Waller an optimistic questionable. If he plays, Waller is a streamable TE1 against the Saints with the Dolphins hurting for secondary options to accompany Jaylen Waddle and De’Von Achane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc21-d82c-a79a-ffb51f000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Jerome Ford (hamstring) is questionable to play in Week 13 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc2d-d6c4-abfb-de2f85920000</link>
      <description>Ford was limited on Wednesday and downgraded to DNP on Thursday, indicating he may have strained his hamstring in practice, causing the limited session. Rookie RBs Quinshon Judkins and Dylan Sampson have dominated snaps over the last two weeks. That should again be the case this week, even if Ford is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc2d-d6c4-abfb-de2f85920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (foot) is not on Miami’s final Week 13 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc32-d82c-a79a-ffb6ca9f0000</link>
      <description>He’ll play against the Saints and should be considered a WR1/WR2, though a Darren Waller return could conceivably keep his ceiling lower than it has been. Waddle will be an easy play in most fantasy leagues regardless of Waller’s status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc32-d82c-a79a-ffb6ca9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (illness) is questionable for Arizona’s Week 13 game against Tampa Bay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc38-d90e-a9da-df3faf070000</link>
      <description>Harrison never did better than a limited session this week, but he did practice all three days. If he plays, he’ll be on the WR2/WR3 line against the Buccaneers, with Michael Wilson suddenly nipping at his heels for targets. The long layoff leaves us thinking he’s truly questionable in this one, but Cardinals.com’s Darren Urban believes Harrison “seems like he is trending to play.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc38-d90e-a9da-df3faf070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) won’t play in Arizona’s Week 13 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3a-d6c4-abfb-de3be0c10000</link>
      <description>Demercado has not practiced since suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 11 and will enter Week 14 on the questionable line. His absence will leave Zonovan Knight and Michael Carter in control of the Cardinals running game against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3a-d6c4-abfb-de3be0c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc38-db57-afda-de3a027e0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield practiced fully on Friday, and head coach Todd Bowles said Mayfield is trending toward playing. From what we can see, we believe him. Mayfield sprained the AC joint in his left, non-throwing shoulder last weekend. This will be a problem if he takes a big hit, or lands directly on it, but he should be able to complete the throwing motion and scramble as needed. The re-injury risk lowers his ceiling, but Mayfield will warrant borderline QB1/2 treatment if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc38-db57-afda-de3a027e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Zonovan Knight (knee) is questionable for Arizona’s Week 13 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3c-d6c4-abfb-de3fd6220000</link>
      <description>He did get in three limited sessions, but the new knee injury appears to at least have him more down than he was last week when the Cardinals cleared Knight off the injury report on Friday. If Knight plays he’ll be a worthwhile FLEX against the Buccaneers as he projects to be the early-down back. If Knight sits, Michael Carter will suddenly find himself in the circle of trust again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3c-d6c4-abfb-de3fd6220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas (ankle) is not on Jacksonville’s final injury report for Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc42-d6c4-abfb-de43b4540000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Thursday and Friday after missing the last three games. Thomas will be on the WR2 line in his return against the Titans, though that’s more due to the idea of volume than anything Thomas and Trevor Lawrence have shown on the field together this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc42-d6c4-abfb-de43b4540000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
