<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 01:29:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns placed RB Jerome Ford (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-04f3-d8cf-affb-bcfb3d4c0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss the next four games, so unless he works out some sort of injury settlement with the team, Ford’s season is over. He managed 24 carries for 73 yards as Cleveland’s third-down back early in the season , but his playing time gradually dwindled, never receiving more than 17 snaps in a game after Week 6. Brown will enter free agency this offseason and likely will draw some interest as a third-down back, but he’s not much of a fantasy asset as this stage of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-04f3-d8cf-affb-bcfb3d4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released K Matt Gay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0529-d77b-adfb-cfabed780000</link>
      <description>Gay made four field goals and four extra points without missing a kick in two games for the 49ers. But starter Eddy Pinero is healthy enough to be active again, and so the 49ers will move on. Gay joins the workout kicker circuit again and figures to get a third opportunity at some point in the last month of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0529-d77b-adfb-cfabed780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans claimed DT Naquan Jones off waivers from the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0547-d77b-adfb-cfc768120000</link>
      <description>The 2021 UDFA was waived Monday to make room on the game day roster for the return of Omarion Hampton. Jones will be a rotational piece for the Texans after they lost Tim Settle for the remainder of the season. They waived Jalen Mills to create space for Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0547-d77b-adfb-cfc768120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0568-d8cf-affb-bd6a441e0000</link>
      <description>London was the only Falcons player listed with a DNP status on Tuesday after head coach Raheem Morris called the 24-year-old “day to day” on Monday. It is unlikely London will be ready to go on a short week ahead of a Thursday game against the Buccaneers, even if he practices in some capacity on Wednesday. London is on the wrong side of questionable as he continues to take time healing from a pesky PCL sprain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0568-d8cf-affb-bd6a441e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-056e-da9b-a9bf-df6f9fc30000</link>
      <description>Pitts was listed as a limited participant for the second straight day with a knee issue. The 25-year-old has seen 18 targets over the last two games with Kirk Cousins at quarterback and figures to continue operating as the offense’s top pass-catcher with Drake London (knee) still working his way back. Fantasy managers should stay tuned for Pitts’ final injury listing on Wednesday, but the limited listings at least indicate it is not a serious issue ahead of a Thursday matchup against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-056e-da9b-a9bf-df6f9fc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (oblique) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0575-d005-a9bf-dd75c8f80000</link>
      <description>Wirfs missed Week 14 against the Saints with an oblique injury. He is listed as a limited participant for both Monday and Tuesday as head coach Todd Bowles said the franchise left tackle could play Thursday against the Falcons. Another practice on Wednesday will give us more confidence that Wirfs will be back protecting Baker Mayfield’s blindside in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0575-d005-a9bf-dd75c8f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (collarbone) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-057e-d8cf-affb-bd7e29820000</link>
      <description>Evans has been a limited practice participant ever since returning to practice from his collarbone injury. He has a chance to play Thursday against the Falcons, pending Wednesday’s final injury status. Evans would return amidst a crucial NFC South race and would not return to WR2 status immediately, but would have FLEX value should be play in Week 15. WR Jalen McMillan (neck) was also limited as he nears a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-057e-d8cf-affb-bd7e29820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0596-d77b-adfb-cf97d3240000</link>
      <description>Otton has now been listed with a DNP on back-to-back days. With a short week ahead of a Thursday game against the Falcons, Otton will likely need to log a practice Wednesday in order to play. If he cannot go, Chris Godwin should see a bump in usage while Payne Durham is next up at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0596-d77b-adfb-cf97d3240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed RB Trayveon Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-059a-d005-a9bf-ddbe8dbd0000</link>
      <description>Williams spent August with the Browns and was released in September. He eventually made his way onto the Chargers’ practice squad in the middle of the season after Omarion Hampton’s injury and appeared in three games, totaling three carries for a loss of one yard. The Browns just put Jerome Ford on injured reserve and now add Williams to help fill Ford’s role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-059a-d005-a9bf-ddbe8dbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts QB Philip Rivers has “a very real chance” to start Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-05a7-d8cf-affb-bdafc8bf0000</link>
      <description>The 44-year-old Rivers signed with the Colts on Tuesday and could be immediately thrust into the starting role. With Daniel Jones out for the season, Anthony Richardson still dealing with an eye injury, and Riley Leonard now dealing with a “Grade 1 PCL injury”, Rapoport says there is “a very real chance that Rivers is the starting quarterback for the Colts this Sunday.” We will see how Rivers practices having been out of the league for nearly five seasons, but the Colts may be making the move to start him as soon as Week 15 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-05a7-d8cf-affb-bdafc8bf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
