<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:03:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner (knee/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6a6-db57-afda-f6b66bf50000</link>
      <description>Barner popped up on the injury report nursing both knee and shoulder injuries Wednesday. He was limited, indicating the 23-year-old tight end is still trending to play in Week 14. Barner’s usage makes him a solid TE2 option if he plays against the Falcons on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6a6-db57-afda-f6b66bf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dortch (chest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c1-d6c4-abfb-f6c385ea0000</link>
      <description>Dortch was sidelined Wednesday with a chest injury. The 27-year-old had fantasy viability with Marvin Harrison Jr. out, but saw just two targets in Week 13 with Harrison back. Harrison (heel) also missed practice Wednesday, so the Cardinals’ wide receiver situation is one to monitor heading into Week 14 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c1-d6c4-abfb-f6c385ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c8-d316-abff-f6dba12c0000</link>
      <description>Adams is dealing with a hamstring issue, but it is unlikely to keep him out of the Rams’ Week 14 matchup against the Cardinals. ESPN’s Sarah Barshop reports head coach Sean McVay said he expects all the players with DNP or limited practice designations to play Sunday. Fantasy managers can expect to enjoy Adams’ red zone role yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c8-d316-abff-f6dba12c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers head coach Dave Canales said Rico Dowdle would remain the team’s primary early-down running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d4-db57-afda-f6f65ee30000</link>
      <description>As the Panthers head into their bye week, Canales said he “likes” the backfield balance the team struck in Week 13’s upset of the Rams, when Dowdle saw 18 rushes to 17 carries for Chuba Hubbard. Hubbard, fully recovered from a calf injury, ran 15 pass routes against LA — catching a touchdown on two grabs — while Dowdle logged six routes and caught both of his targets. “Some of it was third-down opportunities. We’ve been using Chuba primarily as our third-down back, and then he gets series as we go,” Canales said. With his pass game involvement reduced to almost nothing, Dowdle will be a low-ceiling, touchdown-dependent RB3 when the Panthers return from bye in Week 15. Hubbard, meanwhile, will have some value in deeper PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d4-db57-afda-f6f65ee30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d2-d6c4-abfb-f6d31cf20000</link>
      <description>Williams suffered an ankle injury and played through it in Week 13. It looks to be a minor issue, though the Rams are being cautious and keeping him limited to open the week. Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said on Wednesday the team want to keep Williams fresh for the playoffs, so fantasy managers should not be surprised to see more limited practice listings moving forward. Williams is in the RB2 range for Week 14 against the Cardinals, but his potential workload limitations may lead to Blake Corum being a standalone FLEX play as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d2-d6c4-abfb-f6d31cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks re-signed RB Myles Gaskin to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e713-d316-abff-f7930c8f0000</link>
      <description>As expected, the Seahawks added Gaskin back to their practice squad after waiving him Tuesday. He saw three carries for six yards in Week 13 as the third back behind Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet. With Cam Akers recently joining the active roster and ready to be active, Gaskin moves down to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e713-d316-abff-f7930c8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker (glute) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e747-d316-abff-f7d7b2bc0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks made a late update to their injury report Wednesday evening, adding Walker as a limited participant for the day’s practice. Walker has been dealing with the glute injury for a couple weeks now, playing through it in Weeks 12 and 13. Though the late addition to the injury report may indicate Walker suffered a setback, fantasy managers should await his practice status the rest of the week as the 25-year-old has a pattern of playing through the injury. The Seahawks are likely to make Cam Akers active should Walker be limited in Week 14 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e747-d316-abff-f7d7b2bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Commanders S Darnell Savage has requested his release.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e9a2-da9b-a9bf-ffafdcd80000</link>
      <description>As expected, Wilson reports Savage will be granted his release. Savage began the year with the Jags but was released and eventually joined the Commanders. He has 16 combined tackles and two pass breakups in total this season. Savage will hit waivers once his release is made official. Expect a contending team to take a shot on him as a depth option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e9a2-da9b-a9bf-ffafdcd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The San Francisco Standard’s David Lombardi reports the 49ers wanted George Pickens “in return for Brandon Aiyuk during those 2024 trade discussions.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea2c-d77b-adfa-eaafac940000</link>
      <description>The Steelers actively pursued Aiyuk last year, but, as Lombardi notes, Pickens was not on the trade block until the 2025 offseason. Aiyuk ultimately stayed in San Francisco on a new contract and the Steelers moved Pickens to Dallas ahead of the 2025 season. The move worked out terrifically for Pickens, who is putting up top-five receiving numbers with the Cowboys. Everyone else involved likely wishes they had handled things differently. Aiyuk has since had guarantees in his contract voided, meaning he and the 49ers are headed for an ugly split after the season. It wouldn’t be surprising to see the Steelers pursue him again next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea2c-d77b-adfa-eaafac940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Justin Herbert (hand) is expected to return to practice today or tomorrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea3a-d005-a9bf-fa3e85750000</link>
      <description>Herbert fractured a finger on his non-throwing hand. He wasn’t on the practice field yesterday, but both Herbert and head coach Jim Harbaugh have told reporters he plans on playing this week. Even a limited practice in the next day or two would bode well for his odds of suiting up. If he can’t go, the Chargers will turn to Trey Lance. Either way, expect a run-heavy approach as Harbaugh attempts to protect his quarterback versus a stout Philly pass-rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea3a-d005-a9bf-fa3e85750000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
