<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared TE Will Dissly, S Elijah Molden, CB Cam Hart, LB Emany Johnson, WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith, and DL Otito Ogbonnia inactive for Week 3 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da3-d93f-ad9d-7fe76ffd0000</link>
      <description>Dissly will sit with a knee injury, leaving Tyler Conklin as the Chargers’ No. 1 tight end against a tough Denver coverage unit. Rookie TE Oronde Gadsden, Jr. could also see some snaps with Dissly sidelined. Conklin won’t be playable in fantasy leagues outside the deepest formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da3-d93f-ad9d-7fe76ffd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Seahawks declared RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) inactive for Week 3 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b1-d6a5-adff-f7f5354f0000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet was seen “doing a pretty extensive workout” during pre-game warmups, which was a bit surprising after the Seahawks listed him as doubtful to play this week. Charbonnet sat out all three practices, but today’s pre-game action bodes positively for his Week 4 availability. Kenneth Walker III will handle a large workload with Seattle’s 1B running back sidelined today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b1-d6a5-adff-f7f5354f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals declared CB Will Johnson, LT Paris Johnson, OL Will Hernandez, RB Bam Knight, LB Xavier Thomas, and WR Xavier Weaver inactive for Week 3 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da4-d93f-ad9d-7fe7653f0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals enter Week 3 undermanned on both sides of the ball. On offense, Kyler Murray will take on a talented San Francisco pass-rush without his left tackle. Paris Johnson was limited in practice throughout the week but will miss this contest with an eye on a Week 4 return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da4-d93f-ad9d-7fe7653f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared TE Evan Engram, RB Jaleel McLaughlin, OLB Que Robinson, DL Sai’Vion Jones, and OT Frank Crum inactive for Week 3 against the Chargers</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da8-d93f-ad9d-7fefd2810000</link>
      <description>Engram’s back injury will keep him sidelined against the Chargers after he missed practice all week. Adam Trautman, who had three catches for ten yards and a touchdown last week against the Colts, will function as the Broncos’ No. 1 tight end with Engram sidelined, Trautman will only be usable in the deepest leagues. McLaughlin will once again be a healthy scratch. That means RJ Harvey, Tyler Badie, and JK Dobbins will split Denver’s backfield workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da8-d93f-ad9d-7fefd2810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (quad) is active for Chicago’s Week 3 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6daf-d1b3-a5dd-6dff4b000000</link>
      <description>As expected, Swift should get the majority of Chicago’s running back reps today in what profiles to be a high-scoring game, keeping him in the RB3/FLEX convo despite a rough start. Inactive for the Bears are: CB Kyler Gordon, QB Case Keenum, CB Jaylon Jones, LB D’Marco Jackson, LB TJ Edwards, and OT Ozzy Trapilo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6daf-d1b3-a5dd-6dff4b000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared RB Jaydon Blue, DE Jadeveon Clowney, CB DaRon Bland, DT Jay Toia, LB Shemar James, OL Ajani Cornelius and OG Trevon Keegan inactive for Dallas’ Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6db1-d93f-ad9d-7ff7f9740000</link>
      <description>Bland remains lost to a week-to-week foot injury. Blue has not been active in any of three Dallas games this season. The rest are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6db1-d93f-ad9d-7ff7f9740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) is questionable to return in Week 3 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da6-dfde-a1bd-7faf9f8c0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin hauled in a 56-yard pass late in the third quarter and was injured while extending the ball toward the goal line. He looked perfectly fine after the play, so reports of him being questionable with a quad injury are somewhat surprising. We’ll likely get a more detailed report after the game, but given the score, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Commanders opted to sideline their WR1 for the remainder of this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da6-dfde-a1bd-7faf9f8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans left the Week 3 game against the Jets in the fourth quarter with an injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dca-d1b3-a5dd-6dfb43c20000</link>
      <description>Evans planted his foot to make a cut on an in-route and immediately came up hobbling. He was able to hobble off the field, but then immediately limped into the locker room with a trainer. The Bucs are up 26-13 with four minutes left, so there is no reason to keep Evans on the sideline, but we’ll have to hope this isn’t an issue that will linger into next week and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dca-d1b3-a5dd-6dfb43c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marshon Lattimore (concussion) exited in the fourth quarter of the the Commanders’ Week 3 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dcf-dfde-a1bd-7fcf28400000</link>
      <description>Lattimore has totaled two tackles and one pass breakup in this one. The veteran corner exited midway through the fourth quarter to be evaluated for a concussion, but he could be a long shot to return even if cleared, given the three-possession lead the Commanders have over the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dcf-dfde-a1bd-7fcf28400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Gardner left Week 3’s game against the Bucs and will be evaluated for a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dcf-d1b3-a5dd-6dff85a40000</link>
      <description>It was a rough day for Gardner before he got hurt late in the fourth quarter. He kept the Bucs’ first drive alive with a brutal holding penalty on a 3rd and 30. He was beaten a few times later during the game by both Mike Evans and Emeka Egbuka. Gardner was hurt trying to make a tackle in the fourth quarter, and the Jets will hope he passes the requisite concussion tests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6dcf-d1b3-a5dd-6dff85a40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
