<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1315-deb1-a39b-331f07a40000</link>
      <description>Diggs missed the Cowboys’ Week 7 game against the Commanders after suffering a concussion in some sort of at-home accident. He is seemingly unlikely to play in Week 8 against the Broncos. Cowboys S Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder) also remains sidelined on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1315-deb1-a39b-331f07a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (glute) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1319-d5d8-a3ff-fb796f970000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. The Cowboys’ offensive line health had been improving as of late and this week, they are tasked with fending off the Broncos’ pass rush, keyed by EDGE Nik Bonitto, who ties for an NFL-high 10 sacks through seven weeks. Hopefully, Guyton can continue practicing on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1319-d5d8-a3ff-fb796f970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed DE Carl Lawson, formerly of the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-131f-d5d8-a3ff-fb7fd06a0000</link>
      <description>Lawson tallied 27 quarterback pressures and six sacks in his seventh NFL season, playing as a Cowboy last year. He gives the Ravens some much-needed assistance in the pass-rush department. The Ravens’ 28.0 percent quarterback pressure rate ranks 29th among NFL defenses. Lawson will likely begin as a rotational player, and could increase his role with quality play as the season progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-131f-d5d8-a3ff-fb7fd06a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (calf) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1326-d5d8-a3ff-fb672dc40000</link>
      <description>Goedert should be good to go for Week 8 against the Giants, which is great news for an Eagles offense that could be without WR A.J. Brown (hamstring), who has yet to practice this week. Goedert posted season-highs in targets, reception and yards against the Giants in Week 6, catching 9-of-11 targets for 110 yards and one touchdown. He is a high-end TE1 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1326-d5d8-a3ff-fb672dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1329-deb1-a39b-332f208c0000</link>
      <description>Purdy’s limited practice sessions continue. Until he can consistently practice in full, we expect Mac Jones to remain the starter. The 49ers are one of three NFC West teams with a 5-2 record, and undoubtedly hope to preserve their starting quarterback’s health for a playoff run. Jones is a borderline QB1/2 against the Texans this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1329-deb1-a39b-332f208c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1318-dab4-a3fb-9b782ef10000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reporters yesterday that Pearsall has not suffered a setback of any sort. Instead, the injury has simply taken longer to heal than expected. The 49ers’ 25-year-old wide receiver initially sprained his PCL in Week 4 and has not yet resumed practicing. Jauan Jennings will operate as the team’s No. 1 wide receiver with Pearsall likely sidelined again this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1318-dab4-a3fb-9b782ef10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) is active for Week 8 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1340-dab4-a3fb-9b70ebbb0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers are also getting RT Trey Pipkins III (knee) back this evening. This is great news for QB Justin Herbert as he prepares to face the Vikings’ top-tier blitz-based defensive scheme. The Chargers declared RB Hassan Haskins, CB Nikko Reed, OLB Kyle Kennard, OL Jamaree Salyer, OT Austin Deculus, WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith and TE Will Dissly inactive for Week 8 against the Vikings. With Haskins out, the Chargers have elevated RBs Nyheim Hines and Jaret Patterson from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1340-dab4-a3fb-9b70ebbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is active for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1348-d245-adfb-975fcf070000</link>
      <description>The Vikings listed Darrisaw as a non-participant on Wednesday, briefly causing a scare, but the Vikings’ left tackle evidently feels good enough to play after going through a pre-game workout. Starting QB Carson Wentz will, unfortunately, be without RT Brian O’Neill (knee), who logged just one limited practice session this week. The Vikings also declared OLB Chaz Chambliss, DT Elijah Williams, FB C.J. Ham, LB Andrew Van Ginkel and QB J.J. McCarthy (emergency 3rd QB) inactive for Week 8 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1348-d245-adfb-975fcf070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Vikings “hope” QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) is “ready” to play in Week 9 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-134e-deb1-a39b-334eba710000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that if fill-in starting QB Carson Wentz “throws for 400 yards” tonight against the Chargers, “that will be taken into consideration” when deciding which player starts in Week 9. Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell is “not going to put McCarthy out there until he can be successful,” though Rapoport adds that McCarthy is “close” to returning. McCarthy has been sidelined by a high-ankle sprain since Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-134e-deb1-a39b-334eba710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derwin James Jr. has been ruled out for the remainder of their Week 8 game against the Vikings with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1347-deb1-a39b-334f948a0000</link>
      <description>James injured the ankle during the first half of the contest against Minnesota, and the 29-year-old defender won’t be able to continue. Kendall Williamson and R.J. Mickens will see the snaps for the remainder of Thursday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1347-deb1-a39b-334f948a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
