<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers placed CB Zyon McCollum (hip) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234c-d8cf-affb-bf6e80d20000</link>
      <description>Assuming the Buccaneers do not advance out of the wild card round, this will be a season-ender for McCollum. He started 13 games for the Bucs after signing a three-year extension ahead of the 2025 season. McCollum ends the regular season with a 61.9 PFF coverage grade in 766 defensive snaps, playing roughly equivalent to his 2024 numbers by the same metric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234c-d8cf-affb-bf6e80d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he will have an answer on his Week 16 QB by Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2349-d8cf-affb-bf6b90aa0000</link>
      <description>Glenn’s delayed decision to name a starter could be due to injuries, as Justin Fields (knee) and Tyrod Taylor (groin) were both unable to play in Week 15, or he just wants more time to evaluate his QB room full of backups. Brady Cook threw for 176-1-3 in his first career start against the Jaguars in Week 15, and would get the Saints in Week 16 if he were to be named the starter. The situation is a clear: ¯\_(ツ)_/¯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2349-d8cf-affb-bf6b90aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said Philip Rivers will start in Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2377-d005-a9bf-fb77993f0000</link>
      <description>Was there ever any doubt? After nearly five years away from the game, Rivers was thrown into the fire in Week 15 against a top-ranked Seahawks defense and nearly came away with the victory. Rivers knows Steichen’s offense after years of playing in his system and is widely viewed by Steichen and the staff as the best man for the job. He’ll have a slightly easier matchup on tap against the Niners in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2377-d005-a9bf-fb77993f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports an MRI confirmed a torn ACL for Teddye Buchanan, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2384-d1bc-a3fb-a7a47c910000</link>
      <description>Buchanan’s impressive rookie season comes to an end. The rookie fourth-rounder played his way into a starting role in training camp and wound up totaling 93 tackles, five TFLs, and one forced fumble in 14 games. Buchanan will now have to undergo surgery and rehab in hopes of being ready for next season, although, given the late nature of his injury, it wouldn’t be surprising if he wasn’t ready by Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2384-d1bc-a3fb-a7a47c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor believes Gardner Minshew is “expected to be the team’s starter for the final three games of the season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2389-d77b-adfb-eb8be3570000</link>
      <description>Andy Reid never confirmed as such at a presser today — the last three games of the Chiefs season are not exactly a pressing topic right now for some reason — but Minshew replaced Patrick Mahomes after Mahomes tore his ACL in Week 15. A date against the Titans is promising for some superflex QB2 consideration this week, but the Broncos over Christmas in Week 17 will likely be a game where the Chiefs just try to survive on offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2389-d77b-adfb-eb8be3570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Joe Burrow will start the final three games of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-239e-d005-a9bf-fbbe4b310000</link>
      <description>When asked why Burrow will remain the starter, Taylor, whose Bengals sit at 4-10, said, “Because we want to win.” Big if true. Burrow didn’t look too interested in winning during parts of Sunday’s shutout loss at home to the Ravens, but fantasy managers hoping the Bengals show some fight for at least two more weeks will be happy to hear this news. Burrow and the Bengals draw the Dolphins in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-239e-d005-a9bf-fbbe4b310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Commanders have decided to shut Jayden Daniels down for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b1-d1bc-a3fb-a7b51ad70000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, Daniels’ elbow injury was re-evaluated today, and he was not cleared to play. Given this, and the fact that the Commanders will face the Cowboys on a short week in Week 17, the team has decided to shut him down for the season and ride with Marcus Mariota the rest of the way. In the way everything seemed to go right for Daniels in 2024, the exact opposite could be said of his 2025 season. Daniels didn’t get to work much with his no. 1 receiver in training camp due to a contract dispute, and his on-field play took a noticeable step back when healthy. The real story, however, is injuries. Daniels appeared in only seven games for the Commanders this season due to a knee sprain he suffered in Week 2, a hamstring injury he sustained in Week 7, and a dislocated elbow he suffered in Week 9. He was knocked out of Week 14’s game against the Vikings when he attempted to return from his elbow injury, and is now officially out for the season. There was always fear that Daniels’ slender frame would leave him susceptible to injuries at the pro level, and he didn’t beat the allegations this season. Hopefully, a fully healthy offseason, coupled with revamped tools in the passing game, will yield better results for the 2024 Offensive Rookie of the Year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b1-d1bc-a3fb-a7b51ad70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (finger) will undergo surgery and miss the remainder of the regular season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b0-d77b-adfb-ebb3502f0000</link>
      <description>“He should be back for the playoffs,” writes NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo. Not that Tuten was threatening much playing time in the near term anyway for Travis Etienne, but this does set the Jaguars lead back with a Chase Brown-level of workload for the final three games of the regular season (and two games of fantasy playoffs for most leagues) against Denver, Indianapolis, and Tennessee. Tuten finishes the regular season with a 78/284/4 rushing line and added 10/79/2 through the air. He’s still the likely incumbent for this backfield in 2026 unless this season has convinced Jaguars decision makers that they actually need Etienne more than they believed six months ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b0-d77b-adfb-ebb3502f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said he’s hoping Christian Darrisaw (knee) “is back at some point.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b5-d005-a9bf-fbb5b1990000</link>
      <description>He called it both a “week-to-week” and “day-to-day” situation. Darrisaw was active for Week 14, but missed Week 13 and Week 15 while spending very little time at practice. With the Vikings officially eliminated, it doesn’t make much sense for him to gut this out. We expect Minnesota to shut him down unless his health improves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23b5-d005-a9bf-fbb5b1990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said LT Laremy Tunsil (oblique) will play Saturday “if he can.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23c9-d8cf-affb-bfebcfb30000</link>
      <description>“We’ll have to see what the strength looks like for him -- the movement, the strength -- over these next couple days,” he said. The star left tackle left Washington’s win over the Giants in Week 15. Tunsil has had his best season in years per PFF, with an 84.7 overall offensive grade while cutting his penalties from 19 last year to eight in 2025. The Commanders, 4-10, have not lived up to their part of the bargain with Tunsil, and with nothing to play for, don’t have a reason to push him out there in Week 16 if he’s not healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23c9-d8cf-affb-bfebcfb30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
