<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a68d-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdc550000</link>
      <description>Assuming he dodges a questionable listing on Friday, Taylor looks likely to be a TE2 against a Cowboys defense which has been picked on by everybody, even Russell Wilson, in Week 5. Taylor was also limited on Wednesday. He had a 5/65 game against the Dolphins in Week 4 and could be establishing himself as the No. 2 receiver in this limited passing offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a68d-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdc550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a697-d6e9-af9d-ae9758790000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session, but it is a big step towards playing in Week 5 against the Giants. Johnson managed to play through the Bills game with the injury but spent a lot of time with the training staff. This doesn’t have the look of something serious enough to keep him out, but we wouldn’t be surprised if he finished the week on the questionable line. Friday will be huge for Johnson’s status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a697-d6e9-af9d-ae9758790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB/TE Taysom Hill (knee) and TE Foster Moreau (knee) were both limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a699-deb6-a7fd-f7df9c470000</link>
      <description>They maintain the same status. We don’t yet know if Hill or Moreau will be active for Week 5 — either could cut deeply into Juwan Johnson’s fantasy value if officially activated from the PUP list after being designated to return on Monday. The Saints have a 21-day window from Monday to do it, so there’s not necessarily an urgency to activating Hill or Moreau for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a699-deb6-a7fd-f7df9c470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots DT Milton Williams (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ac-deb6-a7fd-f7ffde8e0000</link>
      <description>Williams was limited yesterday, which could indicate that he suffered the injury in practice. His absence on Thursday casts doubt on his Week 5 availability. Williams ranks third on the team in both quarterback pressures (11) and sacks (two), and ties for the sixth-most defensive stops (six). The Patriots will have a tough time containing the Bills’ ground game if Williams is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6ac-deb6-a7fd-f7ffde8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OLB Odafe Oweh (eye) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6b6-d95b-addb-eef6c2a00000</link>
      <description>The Ravens’ injury woes continue. Oweh apparently suffered the eye injury in practice today, jeopardizing his Week 5 availability. Oweh leads Ravens defenders with 11 quarterback pressures but has yet to actually record a sack. Texans QB C.J. Stroud should have fairly comfortable pockets to throw from this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6b6-d95b-addb-eef6c2a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders ruled out WR Terry McLaurin (quad) for Week 5 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6b8-dca3-a9fb-bfb9039d0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reported yesterday that McLaurin “could need another week or two” before returning. He was right. The Commanders’ receiving corps is in rough shape. No. 2 WR Deebo Samuel (heel) failed to practice on Wednesday and Thursday and No. 3 WR Noah Brown (groin/knee) has been ruled out. Youngsters, WR Jaylin Lane and WR Luke McCaffrey, could creep into FLEX territory before kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6b8-dca3-a9fb-bfb9039d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c0-d95b-addb-eec69e540000</link>
      <description>For the second straight week, a Commanders beat reporterdeclaredan injured player had returned to practice after seeing them trot out to a side field for individual work with the training staff. In this case, it was Samuel. Unfortunately, this does not constitute a return to practice. The Commanders’ No. 2 wide receiver remains sidelined. Nos. 1 and 3 WRs, Terry McLaurin (quad) and Noah Brown (groin/knee), have been ruled out, leaving slot receiver Jaylin Lane and No. 4 WR Luke McCaffrey with a path to potential FLEX-relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c0-d95b-addb-eec69e540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c1-d95b-addb-eec789230000</link>
      <description>Collins is on track to play in Week 5 against the Ravens’ injury-depleted defense, as expected. The opportunity provides Collins with a clear runway to a WR1 performance. The Ravens could be without their two most productive pass rushers and one or more starting defensive backs. Keep Collins locked into lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c1-d95b-addb-eec789230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6e3-d6e9-af9d-aef31aa10000</link>
      <description>Ridley is now on the wrong side of questionable for Week 5 against the Cardinals. The 30-year-old wide receiver is having a disappointing season, and may only return to matchup-based FLEX status when he becomes available again. Titans rookie WR Elic Ayomanor is taking over as the team’s No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6e3-d6e9-af9d-aef31aa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c7-d95b-addb-eec73f240000</link>
      <description>The Titans desperately need Spears’ speed on the field, but they have been smartly conservative with his rehab program thus far. He will probably need to graduate to full practice participation before they activate him on game day. Unfortunately, while Spears could provide Cam Ward with a helpful receiving presence out of the backfield, he only profiles as a PPR FLEX option for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a6c7-d95b-addb-eec73f240000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
