<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 2-of-4 targets for 27 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc43-d94a-a79d-cd4f613b0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a two-score Week 5 and generating some fantasy buzz, Johnson had a quiet night in a huge Giants upset victory. One of his missed connections was a rough third down drop. Despite the recent scoring binge (three TDs between Weeks 4-5), Johnson has still yet to surpass 34 yards receiving. He’s established a bare-minimum floor but hasn’t really hinted at a ceiling ahead of Week 7 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc43-d94a-a79d-cd4f613b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy rushed four times for six yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc46-dd4c-afb9-efc73a3c0000</link>
      <description>Active for the first time since Week 3 as the G-Men pulled off a stunning upset victory, Tracy got out-touched 21-4 by Cam Skattebo, who generated 110 yards from scrimmage and three touchdowns. Pro Football Focus charted Tracy as playing just 21 snaps to Skattebo’s 49. Four touches is probably Tracy’s absolute floor, but it’s tough to say he’s a 1B back at this time. Skattebo has taken over the backfield, and Tracy is a second-tier contingency back as a fumbler in an offense that would be wary of giving him big workloads in the event of a Skattebo injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc46-dd4c-afb9-efc73a3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil’Jordan Humphrey caught 4-of-8 targets for 55 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc49-db72-a199-fe4b3ae60000</link>
      <description>Elevated from the practice squad with Darius Slayton sidelined with a hamstring injury, 27-year-old journeyman Humphrey somehow matched a career high with his eight looks. Several of them came in the end zone, where Humphrey unfortunately committed a drop. He also drew a defensive holding call. We’re sure the Giants were happy with the effort from a role player on short notice, but this could easily be the last time all year you hear Humphrey’s name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc49-db72-a199-fe4b3ae60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalin Hyatt caught 3-of-5 targets for 17 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc4c-def2-abdb-dd6d66320000</link>
      <description>Yet to catch a pass on three targets this season coming into this evening, Hyatt got more run with Darius Slayton (hamstring) sidelined. Unfortunately, he got out-targeted 8-5 by practice squad elevation Lil’Jordan Humphrey. Hyatt also had something of an end zone drop that thankfully resulted in a DPI call that set the Giants up for a one-yard Cam Skattebo touchdown. In theory a big-play threat who could be a little livelier down the stretch as this offense perks up with Jaxson Dart under center, the reality is Hyatt seems extremely unlikely to ever make re-draft fantasy noise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc4c-def2-abdb-dd6d66320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Chris Godwin (fibula) is not expected to play in Week 6 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce21-dd4c-afb9-efe127780000</link>
      <description>Godwin has been a DNP all week with a fibula inury that comes a week after he returned from the fractured fibula he suffered in 2024. Back-to-back DNPs to open the week served as the early sign that he would miss Week 6’s game against the Niners, but Fowler’s report suggests the veteran receiver will officially be ruled out before the weekend. We’ll check back in once the Buccaneers give word on Godwin’s availability, but his absence would give a slight boost to Sterling Shepard’s fantasy stock for those in deep leagues in need of a dart throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce21-dd4c-afb9-efe127780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall said “I want to be here. I want to be a New York Jet” when asked about any trade rumors surrounding him.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce8f-def2-abdb-dfef54a00000</link>
      <description>It’s not often you hear people admitting to wanting to be a Jet, but Hall did exactly that when questioned by the British media about his name being involved in potential trade rumors. Hall has handled 50 percent of the Jets’ rush attempts this season and has totaled 501 yards on 83 touches through the team’s first five games. He has yet to find the end zone, but Hall’s 5.3 YPC and and 6.0 yards per touch are both his highest marks since his rookie year, and he’s easily the Jets’ top option based on where things stand right now. Hall is in the final year of his rookie contract, and if the Jets don’t want to re-sign him in the offseason, then trading him to a contender for picks may be the most logical approach. Whether or not the team truly wants to move him at the deadline is anybody’s guess, but the 0-5 Jets should be listening to any deals that come their way between now and the November 4th deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce8f-def2-abdb-dfef54a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars HC Liam Coen said Greg Newsome will have “an opportunity to play” in Week 6 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce9d-d94a-a79d-cf9d0be70000</link>
      <description>Speaking with the media on Friday, Coen said there’s some crossover between what the Jaguars do defensively and what Newsome did with the Browns that should put Newsome in line to see some snaps. Whether or not he draws the start is to be determined, but it doesn’t sound like the Jaguars will waste too much time getting Newsome on the field in a meaningful capacity, especially after they traded starting corner Tyson Campbell to acquire him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ce9d-d94a-a79d-cf9d0be70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced it has “initiated a review of the application of the concussion protocol involving Giants QB Jaxson Dart during last night’s game against the Eagles.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cea4-d94a-a79d-cfad137e0000</link>
      <description>This decision comes less than 24 hours after Dart was speedily run through his evaluation for a concussion. The cameras caught head coach Brian Daboll urgently pushing — some may even say yelling at team doctors — for Dart to return to the field during a pivotal moment of the Week 6 matchup, which may or may not have led to the league’s decision to review Dart’s evaluation. Dart missed only two offensive snaps before returning to the field in Thursday’s win. The review will be conducted with the NFLPA and may result in a fine if the Giants are found to be in violation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cea4-d94a-a79d-cfad137e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said LB Tyrel Dodson (concussion) will not play in Week 6 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ceb5-def2-abdb-dff517b30000</link>
      <description>Dodson suffered a brain injury in last week’s loss to the Panthers and will remain in concussion protocol through the weekend. The sixth-year linebacker has started all five games he’s appeared in for the Dolphins this season, totaling 46 tackles, two sacks, and four TFLs while also recording one forced fumble. Linebacker K.J. Britt is listed behind Dodson on the depth chart and will presumably start in his place. In addition to Dodson, the Dolphins have also ruled out S Elijah Campbell (quad).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ceb5-def2-abdb-dff517b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets listed Brandon Stephens (neck) as limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ced2-db72-a199-fedb6b2c0000</link>
      <description>Being a Friday addition to the injury report is never a good sign, so consider Stephens legitimately questionable for Sunday’s contest against the Broncos in London. Stephens allowed a season-high 60 receiving yards in last week’s loss to the Cowboys and has allowed opposing pass-catchers to go for 15-166-3 on 22 targets this season, per PFF. The Jets, who already rank 28th in YPA through the air defensively, could be in for a tough time through the air if Stephens is unable to take the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ced2-db72-a199-fedb6b2c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
