<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested permission to interview 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f2c-d35e-a1bf-dfee586a0000</link>
      <description>Since our last hit on Saleh, he’s picked up interview requests from the Falcons and Titans, so this takes him up to four interview requests in silly season after the Cardinals broke the seal on Tuesday. It’s clear other NFL teams don’t hold him accountable for what happened with the Jets in the ill-fated Aaron Rodgers Era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f2c-d35e-a1bf-dfee586a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9edf-d35e-a1bf-dfdfd04b0000</link>
      <description>NBC Sports Houston’s Aaron Wilson reported this morning that testing confirms Jordan suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 18 against the Colts. He was unsurprisingly unable to practice on Thursday. The Texans face the Steelers on Monday. Veteran RB Nick Chubb would get his old job back as the team’s No. 2 rusher if Jordan cannot play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9edf-d35e-a1bf-dfdfd04b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Lions have “reached out to” former Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel about their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f50-dc7a-af9b-dfff89c10000</link>
      <description>It’s certain to be the first of several OC interview opportunities for McDaniel if he wants to go that route. With several head-coaching positions open, it wouldn’t be surprising if he wound up receiving an interview for one of the big chairs as well. We’ll see how quickly McDaniel wants to play this, but he’d be hard-pressed to find better weapons to work with than Amon-Ra St. Brown, Jahmyr Gibbs, and Jameson Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f50-dc7a-af9b-dfff89c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans designated S Jaylen Reed (forearm) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f47-dc7a-af9b-dfff9cc80000</link>
      <description>Per NBC Sports Houston’s Aaron Wilson, Reed “practiced for the first time since aggravating a forearm injury against the Indianapolis Colts and undergoing surgery.” Reed was placed on injured reserve, post-op, and he notably began the year on the reserve/physically unable to perform list due to a knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f47-dc7a-af9b-dfff9cc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f5e-dc7a-af9b-dfff82240000</link>
      <description>It sure sounds like Prater will be Buffalo’s kicker if healthy on Sunday, and the full designation would appear to have it lean that way. If it isn’t Prater, it will be recent practice-squad addition Matthew Wright.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f5e-dc7a-af9b-dfff82240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports that the Falcons, Cardinals and Titans have requested to interview Packers DC Jeff Hafley for their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f5b-dc7a-af9b-dfffebe70000</link>
      <description>Hafley has received head-coaching buzz since August. The list of suitors is unsurprising. SNY’s Connor Hughes also previously reported that the Giants could be interested in interviewing Hafley as well. The Packers’ defense allowed the NFL’s ninth-fewest yards per play (5.0) despite suffering consequential injuries in the pass-rush unit this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f5b-dc7a-af9b-dfffebe70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (Achilles) is not on Green Bay’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f61-d56e-afff-ffe91b0a0000</link>
      <description>Golden practiced in full all three times this week, but doesn’t currently have enough of a role to be a recommended DFS starter against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f61-d56e-afff-ffe91b0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) is questionable for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f62-dc7a-af9b-dfff796b0000</link>
      <description>Wicks didn’t progress past a limited participant stage all week, so he may find it tough to clear concussion protocol. He does still have some time to do so ahead of Saturday’s late kick, but we’ll probably know by mid-day Saturday if he can’t go. Wicks went for 6/94/2 against the Lions on Thanksgiving and 24/238/0 on 39 targets in his other 13 games this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f62-dc7a-af9b-dfff796b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (hamstring) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f62-d968-a19b-dff38c780000</link>
      <description>Outstanding. Williams may only participate in a limited capacity today, but his return is promising. Williams is no stranger to playing through injury, though this is his first career hamstring strain. His 49ers squad faces the Eagles on Sunday afternoon. Hopefully, he upgrades to full participation tomorrow and remains setback-free.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f62-d968-a19b-dff38c780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Malik Willis (shoulder/hamstring) is questionable for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f65-d56e-afff-ffed7cc00000</link>
      <description>He never progressed past a limited session this week, just as it was ahead of Week 18’s game where he was ultimately the inactive emergency quarterback. If Willis can’t go this week, Desmond Ridder will be Green Bay’s backup against the Bears. The fact that Ridder was signed to the active roster early in the week seems to forecast that there’s a real chance of Willis sitting again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f65-d56e-afff-ffed7cc00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
