<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 19:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said Joe Mixon (foot) is “making progress” and the team will have a better idea of his availability for the year “in a few weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf30-def2-abdb-bf71c6e30000</link>
      <description>Caserio declined to put a timetable on a potential return for Mixon, but it sounds like he at least has a chance to play at some point this year. Mixon popped up with a mysterious foot injury early in the offseason, but beat reporters insisted it was a minor issue, likely hearing that from Mixon’s camp. Training camp came and went and Mixon never took the field once. The team then put him on the NFI list and updates on his status have been few and far between. The fact that he hasn’t been ruled out for the year yet is at least a modestly positive sign, though it’s unlikely he has any impact on the fantasy landscape in 2025. Woody Marks and Nick Chubb will continue to split the backfield for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf30-def2-abdb-bf71c6e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Lions CB Terrion Arnold’s shoulder injury “is not as bad as feared” and he could return “sooner than expected.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf69-def2-abdb-bf693f4a0000</link>
      <description>Arnold underwent testing on his shoulder earlier today. He was expected to be done for the year, but the Lions received good injury news seemingly for the first time in over a year. Now Arnold could return before the end of the month, according to Schefter. Detroit will still be severely undermanned for the next few weeks, but this is as good of news as Lions fans could have hoped for, given the expectation for Arnold heading into Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf69-def2-abdb-bf693f4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf91-def2-abdb-bff1b1990000</link>
      <description>The Giants held another walkthrough today. Head coach Brian Daboll told reporters Slayton would not have been able to practice if it were a live session. With two DNPs to start the week, Slayton is looking unlikely to play on Thursday versus the Eagles. Beaux Collins and Jalin Hyatt will likely see more work in his absence, though neither wideout is on the fantasy radar for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf91-def2-abdb-bff1b1990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart (hamstring) “will be ok” for Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf96-dd4c-afb9-ffd74e330000</link>
      <description>Dart tweaked his hamstring in his first start back in Week 4. He played through the injury on Sunday without any issues. The Giants then listed him as limited for the team’s Monday walkthrough. Dart may continue to have his reps monitored in practice, but he’s at no risk of missing Thursday’s game against the Eagles. His rushing output will keep him in the QB2 ranks despite a tough matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf96-dd4c-afb9-ffd74e330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said he is optimistic Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) will play in Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf9c-dd4c-afb9-ffdddabc0000</link>
      <description>Tracy returned to practice last Friday but was held out of Sunday’s game. He remained limited for Monday’s walkthrough and was once again available on Tuesday. Tracy will likely play a limited role given the short turnaround the Thursday’s game, but it sounds like he will at least be active. Fantasy managers will likely want to wait a week before they consider putting Tracy in their lineups. Cam Skattebo still projects to lead the way versus Philly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf9c-dd4c-afb9-ffdddabc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals acquired QB Joe Flacco and a 2026 sixth-round pick from the Browns for a 2025 fifth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfac-d94a-a79d-bfad690f0000</link>
      <description>Flacco may help steady fantasy values for Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins, but it’s not like the Bengals have a significantly better offensive line than the Browns. They may, in fact, have a worse running game. Flacco jumps in to the superflex QB2 consideration zone while Chase and Higgins don’t take an appreciable step forward, but perhaps grab a little extra floor. This is a patch job for the Bengals, who simply couldn’t keep giving snaps to Jake Browning after his disastrous showings and lack of confidence the last few weeks. Browning is a drop in all leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfac-d94a-a79d-bfad690f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OC Nick Holz said he “could see” TE Gunnar Helm’s targets going up moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfba-dd4c-afb9-fffbe5860000</link>
      <description>Last week after saying that his opportunities would increase, Helm had a career-high five targets and played a career-high 44 snaps for the Titans. Chig Okonkwo saw a season-low 42 snaps, though he did come alive in garbage time. Helm is definitely someone to monitor with an eye towards a TE1 rank, especially with bye weeks here, but the two so far have cannibalized each other’s production enough that Helm would need another step forward to be more than a TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfba-dd4c-afb9-fffbe5860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said the “arrow is pointed up” for Jaylen Warren (knee) to return in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfbe-d94a-a79d-bfbfbd6e0000</link>
      <description>It didn’t seem like Warren had much of an injury and he apparently showed well in Monday’s (non-injury report required) practice. Tomlin also said that Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) and Alex Highsmith (ankle) were likely to be back this week. Warren will slide right back into an RB2/FLEX role on most fantasy rosters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfbe-d94a-a79d-bfbfbd6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed S C.J. Gardner-Johnson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfc4-def2-abdb-bfe5b6a50000</link>
      <description>The Texans released Gardner-Johnson after Week 3 and much came out about him freelancing, blowing assignments, and complaining about his role. The Ravens defense is at a juncture where they’d probably take that if it came with some competent NFL-level play, too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfc4-def2-abdb-bfe5b6a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed K Michael Badgley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfef-db72-a199-ffef9ef30000</link>
      <description>Badgley suffered a torn hamstring and missed the entire 2024 season. He’ll be tasked with replacing Spencer Shrader as Indianapolis’ main kicker and will likely be a top-10 option the rest of the way given how well the Colts offense has played through five weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfef-db72-a199-ffef9ef30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
