<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 18:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune’s Brad Biggs believes the Bears would probably need “a second-round pick (or two picks equaling that value)” to make it “worthwhile” to trade Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a10d-d89c-a1be-afdf6f950000</link>
      <description>“I’m not sure a team would offer a Round 2 pick for Bagent. It’s worth noting the Bears have had meetings with agents representing some No. 2-type quarterbacks, so they’re putting contingency plans in place,” Biggs continues while specifically pointing out that the Jets are a team that could look to go the budget route at quarterback. Of all the things that happened during the NFL Combine, the hard-launching of the Tyson Bagent Trade Complex was definitely one of them. The desperation is real for those without a solidified quarterback position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a10d-d89c-a1be-afdf6f950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane believes a decision by the Eagles on keeping or trading A.J. Brown will be made “in the next 10 days” ahead of the start of the legal tampering period.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a117-d042-afbc-fdd7a1e60000</link>
      <description>McLane has talked to several sources about this at the combine and doesn’t make a real guess on if Brown will be traded — the article is full of Mike Vrabel quotes, if you want a sense of a lean — but also mentions the Ravens and Bills as teams that could use a Brown to get over the championship hump. He notes that if Howie Roseman doesn’t get the compensation he wants, he’ll simply keep Brown. Brown’s 2026 team will determine a lot about the next few weeks in the NFL, but it sounds like it will simply unfold based on how willing the market will be to give Roseman the kind of premium draft assets he’d desire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a117-d042-afbc-fdd7a1e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan Alexander believes that the Texans could consider a trade for De’Von Achane.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a122-d042-afbc-fdf250420000</link>
      <description>Achane is mentioned as part of a major section of Alexander’s combine takeaways titled “A push for a running back,” starring Kenneth Walker and also featuring Travis Etienne and Rico Dowdle. But towards the very end, it notes that the Texans did trade for a back after missing out on the free-agent market for Saquon Barkley when they snagged Joe Mixon. We doubt that the Dolphins would part with Achane for something negligible — they’d likely require real draft compensation — but the situation certainly looks to be focused on the long-term there and Achane is entering the final year of his rookie contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a122-d042-afbc-fdf250420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan Alexander reports that support for C.J. Stroud “remains strong inside the organization.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a131-d042-afbc-fdf3c08f0000</link>
      <description>He adds that the Texans will engage in talks with Stroud’s representation “at some point” about a long-term contract, the expectation is that any potential long-term extension wouldn’t get done this offseason. It’s sensible for the Texans to not get out ahead of the Stroud talks after last year’s playoff flatlining. It’s also sensible for the Texans to look at all 52 games that he’s played, rather than just his last two, when thinking about what they expect from him going forward. The Texans will try to build up around Stroud ahead of the last two years of his rookie contract to see what they can get out of him, and Alexander believes an improved running game should also take some of the pressure off of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a131-d042-afbc-fdf3c08f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens head coach Jesse Minter said “I don’t know that he needs to run more, I actually think there’s times where he can run less” when asked about Lamar Jackson running more.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a161-d89c-a1be-affff5e00000</link>
      <description>There’s an element of this answer that nods to an ideal world, because the times where he can run less are based on “if you build an offense that takes advantage of the under center, the downhill run game. Now that opens up a lot of boots and play actions.” But it’s not what fantasy football managers want to hear after last season’s scant 67/349/2 line while struggling through injuries. Entering his age-29 season, it wouldn’t be surprising if Jackson’s game evolved. It certainly sounds like his head coach would rather it evolve than not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a161-d89c-a1be-affff5e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Alaina Getzenberg believes Khalil Shakir is “likely taking on a bigger role” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a170-d042-afbc-fdf23fcd0000</link>
      <description>Joe Brady said he was one of the team’s best football players and said that there are other ways to get the ball in his hands than just in the screen game. We’re not sure how seriously to take this at the combine, before the Bills bring in what the actual competition will be — we don’t think Shakir is going to take on a bigger role if A.J. Brown or D.J. Moore show up — but it’s at least worthwhile to note that Brady loves Shakir and he seems ticketed to have a major role in the passing offense in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a170-d042-afbc-fdf23fcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers did not tender restricted free agent RB Emanuel Wilson, making him a free agent</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a1ea-dbf6-abdd-effb7b1e0000</link>
      <description>This is a calculated ploy by the Packers, but we’re still a little surprised they did this after Wilson rushed for 496 yards on 125 carries and generally played as a pretty good backup runner. It leaves MarShawn Lloyd and Chris Brooks as backups behind Josh Jacobs. Wilson turns 27 in May and should be able to find work elsewhere if he doesn’t wind up back with the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a1ea-dbf6-abdd-effb7b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired former Titans offensive coordinator Nick Holz as their passing game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a1ef-d629-a1bc-b1ff61090000</link>
      <description>Holz returns to where he started as an NFL coach. He was Titans OC for two years before Brian Callahan’s regime went down, and also has passing game coordinator experience with the Jaguars in 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a1ef-d629-a1bc-b1ff61090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will restructure contracts of QB Dak Prescott, WR CeeDee Lamb and OG Tyler Smith, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a490-d89c-a1be-afdf7d790000</link>
      <description>Restructuring the contracts of Prescott, Lamb and Smith will create $66 million in cap space. Schefter also passes along that Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said the Cowboys will rework the contracts of DTs Kenny Clark, Quinnen Williams and Osa Odighizuwa, who are scheduled to count around $63 million against the cap. With the new cap set at $301.2 million, the Cowboys had negative-$56.1 million in cap space. These moves help Dallas become compliant and have money to work with this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a490-d89c-a1be-afdf7d790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patriots have explored a trade for WR A.J. Brown, but feel the Eagles’ asking price is unserious, according to the Boston Herald’s Andrew Callahan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a52c-d89c-a1be-afff5fe00000</link>
      <description>The Patriots are an obvious fit for Brown, who was previously coached by Mike Vrabel in Tennessee. New England also has the need for another offensive weapon and cap space to take on a contract as large as Brown’s. According to a previous report by the Athletic’s Chad Graff, the Patriots will be active in trade talks for Brown, though they could be reluctant to give up their first-round pick. It’s difficult to imagine the Eagles moving Brown without receiving top draft capital in return. Brown is one of the biggest offseason dominos yet to fall, though a resolution should be expected ahead of the legal tampering period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a52c-d89c-a1be-afff5fe00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
