<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c227-d6c4-abfb-d627696d0000</link>
      <description>Knight played through an ankle injury last week, but he is no longer listed with the issue on the team’s injury report. Late in last week’s game against the Jaguars, Knight remained down after a play, grabbing at his right knee before scooting off the field to meet with trainers. The fact that he is practicing in a limited capacity is a great sign for his short-term health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c227-d6c4-abfb-d627696d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) was limtied in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c230-d82c-a79a-f3b4097c0000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as head coach Dann Quinn said earlier today he expects McLaurin to practice this week. McLaurin has already attempted to return from the quad issue once. It did not go as planned and he reaggravated the issue during his first game back. We expect the Commanders to be extremely cautious this time around, which means it could be another week until McLaurin is back on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c230-d82c-a79a-f3b4097c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayloin Lane (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c232-db57-afda-d632765a0000</link>
      <description>In addition to Terry McLaurin, Noah Brown and Treylon Burks were also limited today. It’s tough to say which depth options will suit up this week. With Marcus Mariota expected to make another start, it’s a situation fantasy managers don’t need to get bogged down by. Deebo Samuel is the only game in town until McLaurin returns. Zach Ertz is also in the mix as a volume-based TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c232-db57-afda-d632765a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (foot) limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c22f-d6c4-abfb-d62fae500000</link>
      <description>Waddle was not listed with the foot injury on the Dolphins’ Week 11 injury report, pre-bye, though the veteran wide receiver regularly plays through injury. His participation early in the week puts him on track to play. Hopefully, he graduates to full participation on Thursday or Friday. He has a great matchup against the Saints’ defense this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c22f-d6c4-abfb-d62fae500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (pectoral) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c219-d6c4-abfb-d61b5f660000</link>
      <description>Waller has been on injured reserve for a little over four weeks. In his four active games this season, he finished as the half-PPR WR2, WR5, WR18 and WR54. Waller has a chance to play this weekend, though the team has a 21-day window to observe him in practice before they have to make a decision on his status. The Dolphins face the Saints on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c219-d6c4-abfb-d61b5f660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (foot/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c239-d90e-a9da-df3f53e60000</link>
      <description>Left guard Donovan Jackson also missed practice with an ankle injury. Darrisaw left Week 12 with the foot injury during the fourth quarter and did not return. He had been playing through the knee issue up to that point. A DNP today puts him on the wrong side of questionable to open the week. Max Brosmer’s first career start might come behind a ramshackle offensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c239-d90e-a9da-df3f53e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Surtain (pec) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c243-d6c4-abfb-d643ebff0000</link>
      <description>Surtain suffered a pec strain in Week 8 and has been out ever since. The team declined to place him on injured reserve, meaning they thought he would be out fewer than four weeks. A limited practice is a step in the right direction, but the Broncos could hold him out one more game to make sure he doesn’t re-aggravate the issue. Either way, we expect Denver to handle business versus the Marcus Mariota-led Commanders this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c243-d6c4-abfb-d643ebff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions activated EDGE Marcus Davenport (chest) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c24e-d6c4-abfb-d64ff9ea0000</link>
      <description>Offensive guard Miles Frazier was also activated. Running back Craig Reynolds was waived in a corresponding move. Davenport appeared in two games this year, logging one sack, before going on IR with a chest injury. He will return to a part-time role for the Super Bowl contender Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c24e-d6c4-abfb-d64ff9ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Alex Singleton returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c25c-d90e-a9da-df5fa10e0000</link>
      <description>Singleton has missed a few games after undergoing surgery for testicular cancer. Luckily, the cancer was caught early and Singleton is already back at practice. Both he and shutdown corner Pat Surtain could be back for Week 13. Singleton has 89 tackles, one sack, and a forced fumble this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c25c-d90e-a9da-df5fa10e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c260-d6c4-abfb-d663d1f40000</link>
      <description>Thomas was limited for all thre practices last week before being ruled out ahead of Sunday’s game. He is inching closer to a return, but the Jags might need to see a full practice from BTJ before he is cleared to return. Thomas would return for a WR2 fantasy ranking versus a beatable Titans defense. This will be one of the more important injury reports to follow throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c260-d6c4-abfb-d663d1f40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
