<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kris Rhim reports Najee Harris (eye) continues to work out on side fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd3a-dbe3-a9bb-fd7b42f60000</link>
      <description>We haven’t gotten an update on Harris in a week or so, but it doesn’t seem like much has changed since he made it back to practice. Jim Harbaugh’s last update on Harris was that there’s a chance he’d be ready for Week 1, but with only a few weeks before the start of the season, we’d need to see a drastic ramp-up to believe that is in the cards. Harris may avoid being placed on the IR or the PUP list based on how often he’s been working to the side, but it’s hard to recommend him in fantasy until he gets back on the actual practice field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd3a-dbe3-a9bb-fd7b42f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson is not practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd63-de13-afdc-cfeb93350000</link>
      <description>He left Wednesday’s practice early after having his foot stepped on — the Ravens released a statement saying that he was fine. Ravens reporters saw him flexing his hand and wrist on the sideline. We don’t have an official injury diagnosis and don’t believe Jackson is seriously hurt, but any time Jackson isn’t practicing it’s newsworthy. Further updates from the Ravens should be coming at some point in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd63-de13-afdc-cfeb93350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Kaleb McGary (leg) will “miss time” at the start of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd72-db7b-a5dd-ed76d8ef0000</link>
      <description>The severity of his leg injury is not yet known, but McGary went down in practice and required an MRI yesterday. With Storm Norton also hurt, the Falcons will be on RT3 at the start of the season at the very least. It’s possible that this is an injury that sends McGary to IR-return, and we wouldn’t rule out that it was a season-ender based on the descriptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd72-db7b-a5dd-ed76d8ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (undisclosed) is close to returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</link>
      <description>Quinn added that the “arrow is pointing up for him.” The oft-injured wideout hasn’t participated much in training camp to this point. This paints a picture of a return for Week 1, but Quinn did not exactly promise that with words. Brown should probably be the Commanders’ No. 3 receiver when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR Johnny Wilson (knee/ankle) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</link>
      <description>Wilson suffered the injury at Tuesday’s practice and was carted off. While Wilson’s a fun player at 6-foot-6 and shaped like a tight end, he wasn’t expected to have a major role in the Eagles offense this year. The 2024 sixth-rounder will instead look to get ready for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn says he “see[s] the ascension taking place” with Jaylin Lane.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders fourth-round pick this year, Lane reportedly can “apply it very quickly” when given coaching points. Lane has a chance to eventually take over for Noah Brown in three-wideout sets at some point this season, and should make for an intriguing stash in dynasty at the very least given his youth relative to the rest of the Commanders wideout room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions C Graham Glasgow (leg) left Friday’s joint practice against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</link>
      <description>No word yet on the severity of the injury, but it would be yet another blow to the Lions’ interior line if Glasgow missed real time. We’d expect an update from Detroit sometime in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond will play in preseason Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</link>
      <description>Bond has practiced three times since the Browns signed him on Monday. He needs all the reps he can get, and the Browns are in need of playmakers. He presumably has a long way to go before he is even moderately familiar with the playbook and is not a recommended re-draft bench stash. He could be worth a waiver wire add later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-rays of Lamar Jackson’s foot showed “no damage.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</link>
      <description>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said Jackson’s foot is “a little sore today,” but deemed the star quarterback “fine” after holding him out of Thursday’s practice. We can breathe a sigh of relief. Following his recovery will be worthwhile but fantasy managers can continue drafting Jackson as an elite QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Ja’Lynn Polk (shoulder) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal development for the second-year wide receiver. Polk was reportedly not a lock to make the Patriots’ roster after being outplayed by his teammates in spring practices. Hopefully, he can resume training individually before long. On 15 preseason snaps, Polk earned zero targets and rushed once for one yard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
