<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:30:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes “it’s clear the 49ers don’t intend to make [Brock] Purdy active again until he’s healthy enough to reclaim his starting job.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb4-d673-a39e-efb5f85d0000</link>
      <description>So here are the facts on the ground: After the Giants game last week, Kyle Shanahan “acknowledged that Purdy likely wouldn’t return to full health at any point this season as he deals with turf toe.” Shanahan later said “Our dilemma or what we’re trying not to do is put him out in the situation we did versus Jacksonville six weeks ago ... I do believe he’s closer and further along than what he was at that time. Hopefully he’ll have a chance this week.” What does it mean to be healthy enough? Purdy certainly didn’t play well against the Jaguars in Week 4. But if he’s never going to be fully healthy again this season, it doesn’t take an expert between-the-lines reader to see a scenario where Mac Jones simply keeps starting every week. Especially if the 49ers continue losing and fall out of playoff contention. We’re not saying that this is what is going to happen. But it shouldn’t be surprising if the 49ers continue to start Jones. As Wagoner puts it: “Purdy could, hypothetically, reach 90% health but is that better than Jones at full strength? It would be easy enough for the 49ers to continue riding with Jones given the possibility Purdy could struggle or, worse, reaggravate the toe injury again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb4-d673-a39e-efb5f85d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said he will continue to stick with Joe Brady as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb9-d713-ad9e-6ffd91460000</link>
      <description>A 13-point performance against a bad Dolphins team is just the latest flop for a Bills team that has scored 20 or fewer points in its three losses this season. Brady replaced offensive coordinator Ken Dorsey during the 2023 season and helped fix an offense that was falling well short of what we’d expect from a Josh Allen-led attack. Now, it’s Brady’s offense that’s struggling to take advantage of Allen’s skillset, as the Bills currently rank 23rd in deep pass attempts and 24th in dropbacks through the first 10 weeks of the season. At some point, Brady should lean more into his MVP quarterback who ranks in the top six among his peers in both EPA per dropback and offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb9-d713-ad9e-6ffd91460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones suffered a torn Achilles in Week 10’s loss to the Seahawks and will be out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fc2-d45b-affe-7fd6e24f0000</link>
      <description>Jones felt his Achilles pop in Sunday’s loss and was assisted off the field by medical trainers. The nine-year vet has caught 12 passes for 183 scoreless yards this season and re-upped with the Cardinals on a one-year deal earlier this offseason. The 30-year-old receiver will now have surgery to repair his Achilles, but could be set to join a team next offseason once healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fc2-d45b-affe-7fd6e24f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers waived S Juan Thornhill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fce-d45b-affe-7fde83430000</link>
      <description>Thornhill will now hit waivers but will be free to sign with any team if he goes unclaimed. The veteran safety joined the Steelers on a one-year contract this offseason after previously playing for the Browns. Thornhill has totaled 23 tackles and one pass breakup this season while playing primarily as a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fce-d45b-affe-7fde83430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers hosted free agent CB Asante Samuel Jr. for a visit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fdd-d713-ad9e-6fdde2980000</link>
      <description>Samuel continues to make his rounds with teams in search of his services. The fifth-year corner was medically cleared to return to play after undergoing a spinal fusion surgery, and could help any secondary in need of a boost before the postseason. Samuel has started 47 of the 50 games he’s appeared in during his career, totaling 176 tackles, six interceptions, and 37 pass breakups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fdd-d713-ad9e-6fdde2980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan is hopeful that Ricky Pearsall (knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ff1-d713-ad9e-6ff58a230000</link>
      <description>Pearsall has missed six straight games since suffering a PCL strain in Week 4. The injury has kept him from the practice field for several weeks, so a return in any capacity would be a good sign at this point. Pearsall has totaled 20 receptions for 327 scoreless yards in the four games he appeared in this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ff1-d713-ad9e-6ff58a230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Austin Hooper (concussion) did not practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ffd-d45b-affe-7fff6e710000</link>
      <description>The team did not hold a practice on a short week, meaning the report was just an estimation, but it would be a long shot to expect Hooper to play on Thursday after being diagnosed with a concussion. Jack Westover could see additional run behind Hunter Henry when the Patriots take on the Jets on Thursday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ffd-d45b-affe-7fff6e710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) is not expected to play in Week 10 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7017-d713-ad9e-7c5700d30000</link>
      <description>The Packers reportedly held out hope as long as they could considering the season-ending injury to Tucker Kraft, but the talented rookie wide receiver will be unable to play against the Eagles on Monday Night Football. Romeo Doubs, Christian Watson, and Luke Musgrave stand to benefit in his absence, while Malik Heath could see an increase in snaps as well. Savion Williams, also listed as questionable, could see his highest snap rate of the season, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7017-d713-ad9e-7c5700d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared CB Jaire Alexander, RB A.J. Dillon, QB Sam Howell, C Cam Jurgens, CB Mac McWilliams, and DT Ty Robinson inactive vor Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-701a-d673-a39e-f49b3f3f0000</link>
      <description>Both Jaire Alexander and A.J. Dillon came into the league with the Packers but will be inactive for Monday Night Football. The continued absence of Cam Jurgens could influence the team’s tendencies near the goal line considering he is a primary piece of the tush push. The Eagles get back A.J. Brown coming out of their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-701a-d673-a39e-f49b3f3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) is inactive for Week 10 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-702b-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb81b60000</link>
      <description>This was expected after NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reported as much about a half an hour prior to inactives being released. Both Dontayvion Wicks and Savion Williams are active and will play after coming into Monday listed as questionable. Also inactive for the Packers are CB Nate Hobbs, K Lucas Havrisik, OL Jacob Monk, OL Donovan Jennings, and DL Lukas Van Ness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-702b-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb81b60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
