<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:04:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught 4-of-7 targets for 44 yards in the Browns’ Week 10 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6af6-d1e7-a1fa-7afe47cb0000</link>
      <description>Playing through a hamstring injury, Fannin looked no worse for the wear as he hit his weekly floor. The problem is, David Njoku got the touchdown, while Dillon Gabriel struggled for 167 yards on 32 attempts. Fannin has proven he’s a legit NFL pass catcher and future weekly TE1, but this offensive environment is not good enough to lock him into the top 12 as a rookie. He is right on the periphery, of course. He isn’t a bad option for Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6af6-d1e7-a1fa-7afe47cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku caught 2-of-2 targets for 21 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 10 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6afb-d713-ad9e-6effe39e0000</link>
      <description>Njoku’s nine-yard somersaulting score in the first quarter was his second in two weeks and third in four. Good stuff, though he got out-targeted 7-2 by Harold Fannin, and hasn’t reached 50 yards in over a month. No longer the primary target commander up the seam in Cleveland, Njoku is struggling for top-18 value in this bottom-five offensive environment. That will include for Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6afb-d713-ad9e-6effe39e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai had seven rushes for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 10 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b06-d713-ad9e-6f5669520000</link>
      <description>Monangai was involved early after his Week 9 explosion against the Bengals, but ceded the clear RB1 role to D’Andre Swift in the second half as Swift returned from a groin injury. Monangai, who had an inside-the-ten touchdown in the first quarter, ceded almost the entire pass-catching role to Swift, who caught five of his eight targets on the day. Monangai will be a top-30 option next week against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b06-d713-ad9e-6f5669520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedric Tillman caught 2-of-4 targets for 11 yards in the Browns’ Week 10 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6aff-d713-ad9e-6efff2f60000</link>
      <description>Active for the first time since Week 4 as he returned from his hamstring injury, Tillman briefly visited the blue medical tent but managed to finish the contest. Apparently once again the Browns’ No. 2 wideout over rookie Isaiah Bond, Tillman is a distant No. 4 weapon behind Jerry Jeudy, Harold Fannin and David Njoku. He doesn’t have much of a path to 12-team league value, including for Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6aff-d713-ad9e-6efff2f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared S Tony Jefferson, CB Tarheeb Still, OLB Kyle Kennard, T Bobby Hart, T Foster Sarell, WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith, and TE Will Dissly inactive for Week 10 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b08-d713-ad9e-6f5c733b0000</link>
      <description>Still’s absence boosts the individual matchup of the Pittsburgh tight end cadre, although his undersized stature was already a mismatch for the towering tight ends of the Steelers. Rookie Lambert-Smith has been in and out of the game-day roster throughout the season and does not create any meaningful fantasy changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b08-d713-ad9e-6f5c733b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinshon Judkins rushed 22 times for 75 yards in the Browns’ Week 10 loss to the Jets, adding two receptons for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b08-d673-a39e-ef99715a0000</link>
      <description>Judkins was ceding more third down snaps than usual to Dylan Sampson, but still piled up 24 touches. Yards were harder to come by as Dillon Gabriel failed to threaten the Jets’ defense in the rain. We don’t doubt the Browns would like to evaluate Sampson more down the stretch, but it’s not going to come at the expense of Judkins’ carries, and receptions are not a big part of his fantasy game right now. He will remain a workload-based RB2 for Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b08-d673-a39e-ef99715a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Scotty Miller, LG Isaac Seumalo, S Jabrill Peppers, LB Cole Holcomb, DT Logan Lee, and DT Brodric Martin inactive for Week 10 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b0a-d45b-affe-7f9e0f1e0000</link>
      <description>Seumalo’s absence leaves a noticeable gap on the left side of the interior offensive line. Spencer Anderson is the only other true guard remaining on the team’s depth chart. The former seventh-round guard could be asked to step into the starting role against the Chargers. None of the other absences for the Steelers come as a surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b0a-d45b-affe-7f9e0f1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson rushed two times for -4 yards in the Browns’ Week 10 loss to the Jets, adding a three-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b0d-d713-ad9e-6f5dcf3f0000</link>
      <description>An awful box score, but Sampson was spending more time as the Browns’ primary third-down back this afternoon. That doesn’t matter for early-down workhorse Quinshon Judkins, but it’s not a great development for Jerome Ford. That being said, with Judkins the engine of this offense, Sampson doesn’t have much of a path to carving out receptions-based RB3 value in this awful overall environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b0d-d713-ad9e-6f5dcf3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 1-of-2 targets for four yards in the Jets’ Week 10 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b10-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa3b7f0000</link>
      <description>Taylor’s one reception ... tied for the team lead. Justin Fields was just that bad in what was somehow a win. Taylor has been catching 3-4 passes more weeks than not as a rookie, but “than not” might become more frequent if the Jets don’t make the switch to Tyrod Taylor. Regardless of who is under center for Thursday’s short-week matchup with the Patriots, Taylor doesn’t have a great top-18 case right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b10-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa3b7f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
