<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs OG Luke Haggard (shoulder) is inactive for Week 10 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa21200000</link>
      <description>Third-year pro Haggard has made four starts this season, but he’s been battling a shoulder issue. Joining Haggard on the sidelines are EDGE Haason Reddick, RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin Jr., DL C.J. Brewer, EDGE Markees Watts and fellow OG Elijah Klein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa21200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Hunter Renfrow, G Chandler Zavala, DE Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, WR Brycen Tremayne and DT Cam Jackson inactive for Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d713-ad9e-6d7d63760000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is inactive once again with Tetairoa McMillan and Jalen Coker active. The Panthers are at full strength as they matchup with the Saints in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d713-ad9e-6d7d63760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared K Graham Gano, CB Paulson Adebo, OLB Victor Dimukeje, DL Chauncey Golston, C John Michael Schmitz, G Evan Neal, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 10 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac4d40000</link>
      <description>Younghoe Koo, who was cut by the Falcons last month, will take over as New York’s kicker against the Bears in poor Chicago weather. Koo won’t be fantasy viable for Week 10. The Giants defense remains one of the most injury-ridden in the league and should be exploited by Caleb Williams and the run-heavy Chicago offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac4d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) is active for Week 10 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d45b-affe-7dfe3b940000</link>
      <description>Gordon suffered an ankle injury in week 9 but always looked likely to suit up for today’s game. As massive underdogs to Buffalo this week, the Dolphins aren’t likely to establish much of a ground game. Gordon is nothing more than an RB5. Inactive for the Dolphins are QB Quinn Ewers, S Ashtyn Davis, CB Rasul Douglas, OLB Chop Robinson, LB Andre Carter II, WR Dee Eskridge, and TE Julian Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d45b-affe-7dfe3b940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is active for New Orleans’ Week 10 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d45b-affe-7dfe06970000</link>
      <description>The pattern continues. Kamara is limited in practice most weeks, but makes it to Sunday just fine. Kamara will be a RB3/FLEX candidate against the Panthers given how good their defense is and how Kamara is splitting snaps of late. DT Bryan Bresee (back) is also playing off a questionable tag. Inactive for the Saints are: DT John Ridgeway, DT Khristian Boyd, CB Rejzohn Wright, DB Ugo Amadi, and TE Jack Stoll (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d45b-affe-7dfe06970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Harrison Bryant (shoulder) is active for Houston’s Week 10 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697e-d713-ad9e-6d7e4b100000</link>
      <description>The Texans ruled out six on Friday: C.J. Stroud (concussion), Jalen Pitre (concussion), Tytus Howard (concussion), Ed Ingram (knee), Ka’imi Fairbairn (quad), and Christian Harris (shoulder) — they’ll be joined by healthy scratch Jarrett Kingston on the inactives list today. Bryant was questionable and doesn’t figure to be much of a fantasy factor today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697e-d713-ad9e-6d7e4b100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 32 times for 244 yards and two touchdowns in the Colts’ Week 10 win over the Falcons, adding three catches for 42 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69ab-d1e7-a1fa-7beb72e70000</link>
      <description>Taylor was stifled by the Steelers in Week 9, running for a season-low 45 yards in a loss. He took out his frustrations against the Falcons with a historic performance, highlighted by an 83-yard sprint to the end zone late in the fourth quarter to give the Colts the lead. The game eventually made its way into overtime, where Taylor put a bow on his blowup with an eight-yard touchdown to bring home the win. This is Taylor’s fourth game of the year with three rushing touchdowns and his fifth with three touchdowns in total. It goes down as a career-high in scrimmage yards for Taylor, who is now the frontrunner for the Offensive Player of the Year award. As you may have guessed, Taylor will sit atop the RB1 ranks when he returns from Indy’s Week 11 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69ab-d1e7-a1fa-7beb72e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones completed 19-of-26 passes for 255 yards, a touchdown and an interception in the Colts’ 31-25, Week 10 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69cd-d45b-affe-7ddf9cec0000</link>
      <description>After turning the ball over five times against the Steelers last week, Jones was tasked with taking care of the ball versus Atlanta. He lowered the turnover total, but only to two. Jones struggled under pressure, putting the ball on the ground three times, all of which were strip-sacks. The Colts were fortunate to come away with two of the fumbles. Jones was sacked seven times in total. He did, however, add 53 rushing yards on seven attempts. Pressure and ball security are becoming issues for the veteran passer. He will need to tighten things up for a showdown with the Chiefs after the Colts’ Week 11 bye. Jones will return to action as a low-end QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69cd-d45b-affe-7ddf9cec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 8-of-10 targets for 99 yards in the Colts’ Week 10 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69db-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbc4290000</link>
      <description>Warren was heavily involved once again, easily leading the Colts in targets en route to a monstrous 38 percent target share. He also came up clutch late in the overtime win with a fourth-down conversion to set up a game-tying field goal. Warren later hauled in a 22-yard heave from Daniel Jones in overtime, which eventually led to a Jonathan Taylor touchdown. After a pair of quiet games, Warren got back on track today with season-highs in yards and catches. He will remain near the top of the TE1 ranks when the Colts face the Chiefs after their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69db-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbc4290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed 11 times for 57 yards and two touchdowns in the Falcons’ Week 10 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69ee-d673-a39e-edff8b680000</link>
      <description>The Falcons loaded Allgeier up with red zone touches versus the Colts. Five of his 11 looks came in the red zone and both of the drives that saw him get a red zone touch ended in the end zone. Bijan Robinson still out-touched him 19-11, but high-value touches were enough to tip the fantasy scales in Allgeier’s favor. He will remain a touchdown-or-bust RB3 when the Falcons face the Panthers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-69ee-d673-a39e-edff8b680000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
