<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 22:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ray-Ray McCloud caught 3-of-5 targets for 51 yards in the Falcons’ Week 1 loss against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-261c-de13-afdd-66dfdd470000</link>
      <description>McCloud took on a full-time role in the Atlanta offense with Darnell Mooney sidelined with a shoulder injury. Playing mostly from the slot, McCloud did most of his damage on a 25-yard catch-and-run reception in the fourth quarter. If the Falcons remains as pass heavy as they were in Week 1’s loss, and if Mooney remains out, McCloud could be an option in deeper fantasy formats next week against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-261c-de13-afdd-66dfdd470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara rushed 11 times for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Saints’ Week 1 loss to the Cardinals, adding two catches for 12 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2614-dbe3-a9bb-3657d12f0000</link>
      <description>Kamara showed the most burst out of the Saints’ offensive weapons, but did not get a high volume of rushing opportunities as New Orleans trailed for most of the game. He got the first Saints’ touch of the game and scored an 18-yard rushing touchdown in the first half. Kamara was later dropped for a loss at the goal line in the fourth quarter on one of several drives the Saints could not capitalize on. Kendre Miller mixed in behind him, but Kamara is still the primary back and top weapon in the Saints offense. He is a borderline RB1 for Week 2 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2614-dbe3-a9bb-3657d12f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield completed 17-of-32 attempts for 167 yards and three touchdowns in the Bucs’ 23-20 Week 1 win against the Falcons, adding five rushes for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2620-dbe3-a9bb-36732f0b0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was all over the place in this one. He missed a few easy intermediate throws and got away with a couple interception-worthy attempts in the second half. Mayfield, who entered the regular season as a prime touchdown regression candidate, continued running hot on the TD front, connecting with rookie WR Emeka Egbuka for two scores and Bucky Irving for another. He added 39 yards on patented tough runs on third downs, taking massive shots along the way. Mayfield should be a top-15 fantasy play in Week 2 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2620-dbe3-a9bb-36732f0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught just 1-of-7 targets for nine yards in the Jaguars’ Week 1 win over the Panthers, saving face in fantasy with a nine-yard rushing touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-261d-de13-afdd-66dfee560000</link>
      <description>BTJ’s shockingly inefficient outing came in a bizarre game that featured a lengthy lightning delay and “just” 31 Trevor Lawrence pass attempts as the Panthers struggled to match points on the other side of the field. Not great, but his nine-yard rushing score on an end-around prevented Week 1 fantasy calamity. Thomas’ seven looks came as Travis Hunter drew eight, catching six balls for 33 yards. Definitely interesting, though Hunter out-gaining Thomas is unlikely to be a new trend. It is possible Hunter stacks up more looks as a middle-of-the-field target. Week 2 should be more telling from a season-long perspective in what forecasts as a road shootout with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-261d-de13-afdd-66dfee560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendre Miller rushed five times for 24 yards and a touchdown in the Saints’ Week 1 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2620-db7b-a5dd-a624ba410000</link>
      <description>Miller operated as the backup running back to Alvin Kamara, seeing five carries against the Cardinals. He was in the doghouse during Dennis Allen’s years as head coach, but now looks to be involved in Kellen Moore’s gameplan. He showed burst on his first 10-yard carry of the game and was breaking tackles throughout all of his touches. Miller is the handcuff to Kamara without enough of a role for standalone value yet. Third-string rookie Devin Neal saw two carries for nine yards on the day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2620-db7b-a5dd-a624ba410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans caught 5-of-8 targets for 51 yards in the Bucs’ Week 1 win against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2627-dbe3-a9bb-3677b3f80000</link>
      <description>It was rookie WR Emuka Egbuka, not Evans, who caught two of Baker Mayfield’s three touchdowns, including the game winner in the fourth quarter. Evans led the team with a hefty 25 percent target share, a rate that should deliver better stat lines in the coming weeks. Mayfield and Evans appeared to not be on the same page a couple times against Atlanta, something they’ll likely get ironed out in Week 2 and beyond. Evans gets the Texans in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2627-dbe3-a9bb-3677b3f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said he has confidence in Russell Wilson but declined to name him the starter for Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2623-d332-a1fd-b6375bff0000</link>
      <description>Daboll continually declined to name Russ the starter even when pressed by reporters multiple times. He did reiterate that he has confidence in the veteran passer and Sunday’s loss wasn’t exclusively on Wilson. As expected, Daboll told the media he will need to look at the tape before making any decisions. It’s a textbook non-answer from Daboll, but the fact that he couldn’t definitively name Wilson the starter is an ominous opening to his tenure as a Giant. Wilson was dreadful in Week 1, completing 46 percent of his passes at a 4.5 YPA. The Giants also reportedly had a package of plays for rookie Jaxson Dart heading into this game, though Dart never actually saw the field. While Wilson may ultimately be named the starter for Week 2, his days under center are likely numbered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2623-d332-a1fd-b6375bff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 16 times for 143 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 1 win over the Panthers, adding three receptions for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-262a-db7b-a5dd-a62ecdfc0000</link>
      <description>One of summer’s mystery men in fantasy football, Etienne came out as the Jaguars’ clear lead back, posting the second most rushing yards of his career. This is a tough game to predict. Etienne’s 19 touches were 11 more than Tank Bigsby and Bhayshul Tuten’s combined total. One game is one game, but that’s a powerful data point in locking Etienne back in as a clear-cut RB2 for a Week 2 road matchup with the Bengals that could easily devolve into a shootout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-262a-db7b-a5dd-a62ecdfc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 7-of-13 targets for 54 yards in the Saints’ Week 1 loss to the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2628-d332-a1fd-b63e26910000</link>
      <description>The Saints offense failed to push the ball downfield, leading to much of Olave’s receptions coming in the short-yardage area. The 25-year-old had a team-high 13 targets, though those led to just 54 total yards on the day. He headed to the blue medical tent on multiple occasions throughout the game, most notably heading out for a chest injury after getting rocked by Cardinals CB Will Johnson. Olave re-entered the game each time, indicating the Saints may have been exercising caution after his multi-concussion 2024 season. Spencer Rattler missed Olave in the endzone on fourth-and-goal to end a high-volume game for the receiver. Fantasy managers should stay tuned into Olave’s healthy, but he should be a fantasy WR3 heading into Week 2 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2628-d332-a1fd-b63e26910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
