<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills GM Brandon Beane said Tre’Davious White (leg) will play again this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eccf-de13-afdc-eecf034b0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t rule him out of Week 1, though that seems aggressive. Buffalo will be relying on pieces like Dorian Strong or Ja’Marcus Ingram to fill out the Week 1 depth chart at outside corner next to Christian Benford while White heals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eccf-de13-afdc-eecf034b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed RB Clyde Edwards-Helaire to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ecdb-db7b-a5dd-ecdfea7e0000</link>
      <description>It’s been done. He’ll be joined by QB Chris Oladokun, FB Carson Steele, WR Hal Presley, OT Chu Godrick, OL C.J. Hanson, DT Coziah Izzard, DT Brodric Martin, CB Melvin Smith Jr, CB Kevin Knowles and FS Mike Edwards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ecdb-db7b-a5dd-ecdfea7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said there’s a “possibility” Najee Harris (eye) plays in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ece5-d332-a1fd-fef7a8c50000</link>
      <description>That stops short of guaranteeing Harris will be available. We’re likely going to have to monitor practice reports for Harris next week, but there’s a chance he’ll step in and split carries with Omarion Hampton in Week 1. We’ve yet to see any reports of Harris practicing in full, though Harbaugh says Harris will practice this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ece5-d332-a1fd-fef7a8c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed G Dalton Risner.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed13-de13-afdc-efdb92530000</link>
      <description>He’ll probably step in as an instant starter at right guard, with the Lucas Patrick and Cody Ford tandem struggling in the preseason. Risner had a 67.0 PFF blocking grade in 2024 and has been roughly an adequate guard over his six NFL seasons. That makes him a huge upgrade on what the Bengals had in-house. Risner took visits with the Bengals and Seahawks before picking Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed13-de13-afdc-efdb92530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed LB Junior Colson (shoulder) on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</link>
      <description>Colson started just one game in his rookie season as a 2024 third-round pick, posting a PFF coverage grade of 34.0. He was a possibility to challenge Denzel Perryman for playing time in 2025, but that will go by the wayside now that he’s missing the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed RB Audric Estime to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb76520000</link>
      <description>The second-year back will get a fresh start in Philadelphia, perhaps eventually pushing A.J. Dillon off the roster. Also on Philadelphia’s practice squad are: LB Chance Campbell, WR Elijah Cooks, G Kenyon Green, TE E.J. Jenkins, CB Brandon Johnson, OLB Patrick Johnson, TE Cameron Latu, WR Terrace Marshall, QB Kyle McCord, CB Parry Nickerson, T Hollin Pierce, OLB Antwaun Powell-Ryland, CB Eli Ricks and S Andre Sam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb76520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Mike Reiss reports the Patriots are planning to waive Javon Baker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed37-de13-afdc-efffecac0000</link>
      <description>New England has an open spot on their practice squad and wants Baker back, but he can gauge interest leaguewide before committing to a return. This doesn’t come as a huge surprise given New England’s remaking of the wideout room, and most reports about Baker this offseason believed that he was squarely on the roster bubble after a 1/12 rookie season on four targets. He played 90 offensive snaps in his first year with the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed37-de13-afdc-efffecac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed G Cole Strange and WR Malachi Corley to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3b-db7b-a5dd-ed3f0b7d0000</link>
      <description>Strange picked a great landing spot after getting released yesterday, as the Browns have almost zero starting linemen with guaranteed contracts for 2026. Corley will look to develop his skills and could perhaps challenge for an end-of-roster spot later in the season. The Browns also added QB Bailey Zappe, TE Brendan Bates, TE Sal Cannella, WR Kaden Davis, S Christopher Edmonds, DT Ralph Holley, CB LaMareon James, DT Sam Kamara, RB Ahmani Marshall, DE Julian Okwara and RB Trayveon Williams to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3b-db7b-a5dd-ed3f0b7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed Jacob Cowing (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3f-db7b-a5dd-ed3fe5020000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four games of the season. Cowing dealt with problems in the hamstring throughout training camp and ultimately won’t be able to take advantage of a golden chance while Brandon Aiyuk is out early in the season. The 49ers re-signed P Thomas Morstead to take Cowing’s spot on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3f-db7b-a5dd-ed3fe5020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed42-de13-afdc-efcb6c1a0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like he’s in any danger of missing Week 1 at this point. Yosh Nijman would be the backup left tackle if that changed for whatever reason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed42-de13-afdc-efcb6c1a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
