<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills interviewed Ravens assistant special teams coach Anthony Levine for their special-teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32f-d56e-afff-e7ef978f0000</link>
      <description>Levine, a long-time special teams standout for the Ravens in a decorated playing career, is the latest to interview for the Buccaneers special teams coordinator job. Levine may or may not be interested in coming along with John Harbaugh to join the Giants, so he has a lot of options on paper. The Buccaneers also reportedly interviewed Eagles special teams coordinator Michael Clay for the role in what would be a lateral move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32f-d56e-afff-e7ef978f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers interviewed passing-game coordinator Marcus Brady for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c332-dc7a-af9b-cfbf379f0000</link>
      <description>Brady is the first candidate to interview for the Chargers’ OC role, and undoubtedly not the last. He did interview for the Bucs and Patriots OC openings last year., as well as for three vacancies for an OC role in 2024. The veteran passing-game coordinator coordinated the Colts offense briefly in 2021-2022 — those were the Carson Wentz and Matt Ryan/Sam Ehlinger/Jeff Saturday year,s if you want help dating yourself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c332-dc7a-af9b-cfbf379f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida-Times Union’s Ryan O’Halloran believes Travis Etienne “understand[s his] time here is likely over.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c337-d56e-afff-e7ff94490000</link>
      <description>“The figurative writing was on the wall for Etienne and Lloyd in the last month when the Jaguars extended receiver Jakobi Meyers and left tackle Cole Van Lanen to ensure they wouldn’t hit the market,” O’Halloran writes, continuing: “Did the Jaguars choose Meyers/Van Lanen over Etienne/[Devin] Lloyd? Ultimately, yes.” If Etienne does leave Jacksonville, O’Halloran believes Bhayshul Tuten will be the No. 1 back in 2026 with LeQuint Allen as the “No. 2/third-down back/kick returner.” Etienne isn’t much of a between-the-tackles pounder (see Trevor Lawrence’s red zone rushing role) and is probably a better committee back, but he might have a chance to find his way into a No. 1 role in free agency after a strong 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c337-d56e-afff-e7ff94490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers general manager Joe Hortiz said LB coach NaVorro Bowman is stepping away from the team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c323-dc7a-af9b-cfbf6de40000</link>
      <description>Bowman’s son is reportedly “a top-ranked high school basketball player” and Bowman intends to be “more involved in his future.” Good for him. Bowman has held his current role for two seasons. He signed on with the Chargers after spending the 2022 season, his first career coaching role, as a defensive analyst at Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c323-dc7a-af9b-cfbf6de40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer believes it is “likely” that Cowboys K Brandon Aubrey will receive a second-round tender in restricted free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c349-dc7a-af9b-cfff4b120000</link>
      <description>It would be a $6 million cap figure for Aubrey if so, something that would put him easily in the top five kickers by average annual value. The Cowboys and agent Todd France “never got close” on extension talks with Aubrey last season. It’s one more thing the Cowboys need to figure out while they worry about how to pay George Pickens and rebuild their back seven this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c349-dc7a-af9b-cfff4b120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35c-d35e-a1bf-c7de1e7f0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full the Thursday ahead of Chicago’s Wild Card game against the Packers and we’re expecting this to be a similar situation. Odunze hasn’t exactly been as huge a part of the offense as he was earlier in the season since returning, but he should still be a key figure in Chicago’s passing game against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35c-d35e-a1bf-c7de1e7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35e-dc7a-af9b-cfffbb350000</link>
      <description>This is the same knee listing he had ahead of last week’s game that he played in, and we see little reason to believe he has much of a chance of missing the team’s Divisional Round date against the Rams. Moore will likely be removed from the injury report on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35e-dc7a-af9b-cfffbb350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35d-d56e-afff-e7fda49d0000</link>
      <description>Minter interviewed with the Ravens yesterday and the Raiders earlier today. Three down. Five to go. The Chargers’ defensive coordinator is a sought-after candidate in this hiring cycle. He has coached under head coach Jim Harbaugh with the Chargers (2024-2025) and Michigan (2022-2023) over the last four years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c35d-d56e-afff-e7fda49d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports the Ravens are targeting Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36a-d968-a19b-dbfbbae10000</link>
      <description>Todd Monken was quickly labeled as a likely Harbaugh offensive coordinator in New York, but we had to wait about 12 hours to get a good leak about the defensive coordinator. Weaver makes plenty of sense as a former Harbaugh defensive line/assistant head coach in the early 2020s before taking his current job as Dolphins defensive coordinator. Weaver has interviewed for several head-coaching positions this cycle, so it’s possible he gets a shot as a head man, but it seems like he’d be in good hands if those didn’t shake out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36a-d968-a19b-dbfbbae10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested an interview with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36f-d35e-a1bf-c7efb7aa0000</link>
      <description>He’ll interview Sunday, per Ian Rapoport. Saleh has drawn requests from Miami, Baltimore, and Arizona this offseason. The 49ers DC has done an admirable job holding down the fort this year while missing stars Fred Warner and Nick Bosa for most of the season. For the Titans, he is one of19different interviews they’ve conducted so far. They’ll move past the initial round after this one and try to nail down a list of finalists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c36f-d35e-a1bf-c7efb7aa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
