<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 17:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 23-of-49 passes for 229 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Texans’ 27-19, Week 7 loss to the Seahawks, adding two rushes for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0575-d99b-a1df-3f7d69bb0000</link>
      <description>Stroud was under duress from start to finish in this one and nearly had a fumble lost added to his box score. On the play in question, Seahawks LB Ernest Jones spun Stroud around after grabbing hold of the quarterback on a blitz. Stroud attempted to throw the ball away but a weak-armed toss put it on the turf. Seahawks LB Thomas Drake recovered it and nearly returned it for a touchdown, but Texans WR Braxton Berrios saved the day by forcing a fumble and recovering the football in the end zone before being downed for a touchback. Stroud’s box score successes are remarkable, given the pressure constantly being generated by the Seahawks’ defense. Stroud is a QB2 against the 49ers next week, though WR Nico Collins was forced from play after suffering a concussion, so Stroud’s receiving corps could be short-staffed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0575-d99b-a1df-3f7d69bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylin Noel caught 4-of-7 targets for 77 yards in the Texans’ Week 7 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0580-d99b-a1df-3f8c466f0000</link>
      <description>With WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) declared inactive and Nico Collins (concussion) exiting mid-game, Noel seized the moment. The rookie wide receiver looked good as a route runner and helped generate the Texans’ longest pass play, a 29-yarder during the two-minute drill. He significantly outplayed WRs Xavier Hutchinson (four targets) and Jayden Higgins (three targets). Hutchinson caught just one pass for 13 yards while Higgins caught zero. Noel warrants waiver wire consideration with the wide receiver corps ailing this week. The Texans face the 49ers next Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0580-d99b-a1df-3f8c466f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 9-of-10 targets for 98 yards in the Texans’ Week 7 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0584-da18-a39a-df979f6d0000</link>
      <description>Schultz played hard in this one, earning double-digit targets for the first time this season. His workload was boosted by WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) being ruled out before kickoff and WR Nico Collins (concussion) leaving early, but Schultz deserves credit for making tough catches and fighting through contact to pick up extra yards. He deserves TE1 consideration in Week 8 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0584-da18-a39a-df979f6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb rushed five times for 16 yards in the Texans’ Week 7 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0585-df81-ab9b-7fc735e40000</link>
      <description>The Texans tried to get Chubb going early on, but the game quickly fell into a losing game script, which benefited rookie RB Woody Marks. Chubb’s receiving contributions include both a five-yard loss and a disappointing drop on the Texans’ sixth drive, which occurred after QB CJ Stroud miraculously evaded pressure by snaking up the middle of a collapsing pocket. The drive culminated in a field goal, getting the Texans on the board at 14-3. The veteran running back is a touchdown-dependent RB3 against the 49ers in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0585-df81-ab9b-7fc735e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 10 times for 15 yards in the Texans’ Week 7 loss to the Seahawks, adding three receptions for 20 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0588-d99b-a1df-3f8ca6310000</link>
      <description>Marks benefited from the Texans’ trailing game script, but RB Dare Ogunbowale is still rotating in, which hurts Marks’ upside. The rookie running back is far and away the most explosive player in the Texans’ backfield, and he was encouragingly on the field for third and fourth downs, the two-minute drill and in the red zone. Late in the game, Marks was involved on three straight plays in scoring position. On the first, Texans QB CJ Stroud targeted Marks just inside the end zone, but Seahawks LB Drake Thomas knocked the pass out of Marks’ hands. Marks was bottled up for a one-yard loss on the second play, but Stroud looked his way after escaping pressure and the two successfully connected in the end zone thanks to a diving catch by the rookie running back. Marks seemingly winced in pain after securing the diving catch, so his Wednesday practice participation is worth monitoring. He is a low-end RB2 against the 49ers in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0588-d99b-a1df-3f8ca6310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes QB Tyrod Taylor is a better fit for the Jets offense than Justin Fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0225-d99b-a1df-3a2dded00000</link>
      <description>Fields was benched in favor of Taylor last week against the Panthers after a miserable first half for Fields. Taylor completed ten of 22 attempts for 126 scoreless yards, along with two picks. Even so, he got the ball out on time and pushed the ball downfield a handful of times in the second half. “With protection, Taylor can be functional from the pocket, which seems to fit better with offensive coordinator Tanner Engstrand’s scheme,” Cimini said. Taylor, who ranks among the top ten most accurate quarterbacks this season, would be a fantasy boon for Garrett Wilson and the rest of the team’s pass catchers if he takes over for Fields. Taylor should be rostered in all superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0225-d99b-a1df-3a2dded00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports Vikings QB Max Brosmer “could be an option” for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-06ec-d651-a9df-6ffd7ec20000</link>
      <description>With Carson Wentz (shoulder) once again banged up following the team’s Week 7 loss to the Eagles, Brosmer might be forced into action on Thursday against the Chargers. J.J. McCarthy, apparently still dealing with his ankle issue, appears to be a long shot for Week 8. “We’ll see how [Wentz] turns over,” Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said after the team’s Week 7 loss. “I know Max was ready to go today and J.J. was the emergency three, but J.J. was able to get some work last week. We’ll see how he feels as well and on a short week.” Brosmer would likely be a major downgrade for Justin Jefferson and the rest of the Minnesota pass catchers against a solid Chargers secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-06ec-d651-a9df-6ffd7ec20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins was diagnosed with a concussion after the Texans’ Week 7 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-06f5-da18-a39a-def7c8d30000</link>
      <description>Collins’ head slammed against the turf on a fourth quarter incompletion on Monday Night Football. He exited the game and did not return. Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said the team would monitor Collins in the coming days. Collins will likely enter the NFL’s concussion protocol and is in danger of missing Houston’s Week 8 game against the Niners. If Collins is sidelined, the Texans will be forced to rely on Xavier Hutchinson and the rookie duo of Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel against the 49ers. Christian Kirk has been sidelined with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-06f5-da18-a39a-def7c8d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacksonville.com’s Demetrius Harvey believes Travis Hunter’s role in the Jaguars offense is “ever evolving.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-073a-da18-a39a-df3b680e0000</link>
      <description>Hunter last week finally broke out in a loss to the Rams, catching eight of his 14 targets for 101 yards and a touchdown. Hunter was targeted on 27 percent of his pass routes — far higher than his season-long rate of 19 percent. Harvey said Hunter’s role in the offense could remain somewhat limited going forward. “They currently play him in slot only. That does limit him because of the lack of two wideout sets,” Harvey said. A Brian Thomas absence could change that calculus, however. Thomas left last week’s game with an apparent shoulder injury. Hunter played just 14 defensive snaps against the Rams, one of his lowest totals of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-073a-da18-a39a-df3b680e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) could return to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0749-d99b-a1df-3f4d9f7c0000</link>
      <description>Tomlin said Tuesday that he’s “optimistic” Austin can return to game action in Week 8 against the Packers after missing the past few weeks with a serious shoulder injury. Austin had been operating as the team’s WR2 behind DK Metcalf before the injury, seeing 17 targets over four games. Austin would barely be a deep league WR option if he’s able to suit up this week against Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0749-d99b-a1df-3f4d9f7c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
