<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:31:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Klint Kubiak said he wants EDGE Maxx Crosby “to be a part of our success going forward, there’s no doubt about that.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4919-d89c-a1be-efdf5cd00000</link>
      <description>This is mostly cold water on the idea of a Crosby trade from the team’s new head coach, but we’ll see what happens going forward here. There have been too many reports of Crosby wanting out — including one of him telling Tom Brady he’d never play for the Raiders again — to fully invest in the idea that a trade won’t happen. Still, it’s broadly good news that Crosby was at the introductory presser and had coffee with Kubiak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4919-d89c-a1be-efdf5cd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall believes franchise-tagging Kyle Pitts “makes the most sense” for the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-492d-d89c-a1be-efffc9dc0000</link>
      <description>Kendall notes that he believes Pitts is “likely to remain in Atlanta” either way, but that with the new executives and head coaches mostly not commenting on him, it would give everyone a year involved to see how good Pitts can be in Kevin Stefanski’s offense. The franchise tag for tight ends is not exorbitant, and Kendall notes that Pitts’ agent would likely ask for at least the tag (a little over $16.3 million) in average annual value anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-492d-d89c-a1be-efffc9dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall believes Drake London “could get a new deal this offseason.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4931-d355-a5bd-cf75ec0c0000</link>
      <description>Kendall notes that new GM Ian Cunningham proactively gave an extension to DJ Moore in Chicago, and writes that “getting the deals done sooner rather than later should be the team’s approach.” London enters 2026 on his fifth-year option and is scheduled to make $16.8 million. An extension would obviously make plenty of sense after London established himself as one of the best receivers in the NFL over the past two seasons despite inconsistent quarterback play. Kendall believes London “likely sees himself” as a $30 million a year player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4931-d355-a5bd-cf75ec0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana quarterback Fernando Mendoza said he’s a “huge fan” of Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-493f-d042-afbc-7dffcd540000</link>
      <description>“Throughout this entire season, we actually had a little bit of a Kubiak-[Sean] McVay system, not for our RPO system but our play-action,” Mendoza told reporters in San Francisco during Super Bowl week. “The way [Kubiak] is able to incorporate outside zone and get the edge with the run game, where the running back can collect the edge, hit the hole or cut back and do play-action off of that, and the way he has developed Sam Darnold has been phenomenal,” Mendoza noted. Not that we needed a whole lot of convincing that this would eventually happen, but it sure sounds like Mendoza is excited by his likely fate to be a Raider with the No. 1 overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-493f-d042-afbc-7dffcd540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OC Zac Robinson said he sees Bucky Irving “in a very similar light [to Bijan Robinson] there with what he can do in the passing game.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4943-d89c-a1be-efdfcf720000</link>
      <description>“There’s not a run concept that he can’t run,” Robinson said. It was certainly a disappointing 2025 season between injury and an inability to stick on the field in the red zone, but Irving appears to be entering 2026 as the lead back for an offensive coordinator who believes in him. And with Rachaad White a free agent, to boot, it seems likely that Irving is primed for a 2026 rebound.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4943-d89c-a1be-efdfcf720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT Rob Havenstein retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4967-d89c-a1be-efff77fa0000</link>
      <description>He announced it on his Instagram. Havenstein started 148 games over 11 years with the Rams as their main right tackle, playing in two Super Bowls and winning one. The stalwart protector struggled with injuries over the past couple of seasons and couldn’t suit up for the Rams after Week 11 of the 2025 season. He had a 70 or higher PFF grade in nine of his 11 years and, while he likely isn’t a real Hall of Fame candidate, he was an incredibly successful pick by the Rams who should have a shot at some Ring Of Honor-type recognition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4967-d89c-a1be-efff77fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Raiders coach Klint Kubiak said he’ll call plays for the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4986-d042-afbc-7dd6e3bf0000</link>
      <description>As expected. He dressed it up by saying it would be a collaborative effort with the staff, but them being part of the game plan wasn’t going to stop the offensive mind from getting to use his difference-making ability as a playcaller. Kubiak should be ready to call plays for his new quarterback (obviously Fernando Mendoza) in 2026 after helping pull the best out of Sam Darnold en route to a Super Bowl win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4986-d042-afbc-7dd6e3bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed P Tress Way to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-498f-d042-afbc-7ddffe120000</link>
      <description>Way made his third Pro Bowl this past year and allowed a career-low 114 return yards. Entering his age-36 season, he’s been with the Commanders since 2014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-498f-d042-afbc-7ddffe120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns hired Packers assistant special teams coordinator Byron Storer as their special teams coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-49cc-d042-afbc-7dde9c460000</link>
      <description>New head coach Todd Monken is continuing to build his staff, hiring the 41-year-old Storer as the Browns’ new special teams coordinator. Storer spent the past four seasons as the Packers’ assistant special teams coordinator and previously served in the same role with the Raiders as well. He is a disciple of long-time NFL special teams coordinator Rich Bisaccia and now gets his first special teams coordinating job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-49cc-d042-afbc-7dde9c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed QB Shane Buechele to a reserve-future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4a09-d629-a1bc-fa1d02060000</link>
      <description>Buechele, 28, has spent his NFL career bouncing between the Chiefs and Bills quarterback rooms, now returning to Buffalo for the offseason. The Bills also signed WR Jalen Virgil to a reserve-future deal; he spent the 2024 season with the team. Familiar faces return to Buffalo with reserve-future deals at the start of the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4a09-d629-a1bc-fa1d02060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
