<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson told reporters he’s “hopeful” WR Luther Burden (quad) can play against the Lions in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7567-d968-a19b-7df765910000</link>
      <description>Burden was carted off the field after injuring his quad on the last play of the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported earlier this week that the injury isn’t thought to be serious. Johnson’s comments Wednesday seem to confirm that report. With the Bears hopeful Burden can play against the Lions this week, he’ll likely be available for the playoffs even if he’s ultimately held out this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7567-d968-a19b-7df765910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFluer told reporters QB Jordan Love (concussion) will practice on Wednesday, though he remains in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756b-dc7a-af9b-ffffce780000</link>
      <description>LaFluer also confirmed that the Packers plan on resting some of their starters in Week 18 against the Vikings. It makes plenty of sense with Green Bay already locked into the No. 7 seed in the NFC Playoffs. Love would seem to be a prime candidate to get the week off even if he clears concussion protocol in time this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756b-dc7a-af9b-ffffce780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFluer told reporters QB Malik Willis (shoulder) will be limited in practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756f-d56e-afff-f7efe1b90000</link>
      <description>Willis left Week 17’s loss with a shoulder injury, though he impressed with 288 yards passing, 60 yards rushing and three total touchdowns against the Ravens. Clayton Tune finished out the game with Willis and Jordan Love sidelined. With Love still in the NFL’s concussion protocol and the Packers locked into the No. 7 seed in the NFC Playoffs, Willis could start again in Week 18 against the Vikings if he’s healthy enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756f-d56e-afff-f7efe1b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn told reporters QB Marcus Mariota (quad) is doubtful for Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7579-d968-a19b-7df949280000</link>
      <description>Not much has changed since Quinn met with reporters Monday. Mariota still isn’t practicing and his coach called him a long-shot to play and even added that he’s “likely doubtful.” Barring a miraculous recovery, Josh Johnson will be under center for Washington in Week 18 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7579-d968-a19b-7df949280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn told reporters QB Brady Cook will start against the Bills in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-757c-dc7a-af9b-ffff7bd10000</link>
      <description>Cook has done very little to elevate the Jets’ offense in his three starts so far. He’s had less than 200 passing yards in all three games and has one touchdown to seven interceptions. He’ll get one more chance to make a lasting impression on the new Jets’ regime in Week 18 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-757c-dc7a-af9b-ffff7bd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said he “has not heard anything” that would keep Stefon Diggs or Christian Barmore from playing in Week 18 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-759e-dc7a-af9b-ffbf49540000</link>
      <description>Diggs is facing felony strangulation or suffocation and misdemeanor assault and battery charges. His arraignment is set for January 23rd. Barmore has an arraignment in February that stems from an alleged domestic incident in August. Things could change with both players as these stories develop, but the legal process is slow and the NFL may ultimately wait to step in until that process plays out. For now, both players appear to be available for NFL’s postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-759e-dc7a-af9b-ffbf49540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots DT Christian Barmore is facing a domestic assault charge, which stems from an alleged domestic incident that occurred in August.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75a4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3a610000</link>
      <description>Barmore is charged with one count of assault and battery on a family/household member. His arraignment is set for February. Mike Vrabel told reporters today he has not heard anything that would prevent Barmore from playing in Week 18. The NFL will likely let the legal process play out before stepping in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75a4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3a610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said the team’s starters will play in Week 18 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75a9-d968-a19b-7df9ee4a0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots are still fighting for the No. 1 seed in the AFC and the bye that comes with it. They need to win versus Miami and the Broncos need to lose to the Chargers. With Justin Herbert out for Week 18, the second leg of that parlay is looking rather unlikely. Still, Drake Maye and company will be out there on Sunday, though we suspect he will be on a shorter leash than usual. If the game isn’t close at halftime or the end of the third quarter, expect Vrabel to be quick to pull some of the team’s big names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75a9-d968-a19b-7df9ee4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b0-d56e-afff-f7f8c17e0000</link>
      <description>As expected, David Njoku also remained out of practice. Njoku is likely out for Week 18, while head coach Kevin Stefanski is leaving the light on for Fannin. With the Browns only playing for a better draft pick, there isn’t much reason to push either player to suit up on Sunday. Backup tight ends Blake Whiteheart and Sal Cannella would be in line for more work if both starting options are ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b0-d56e-afff-f7f8c17e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b9-d35e-a1bf-75fb89650000</link>
      <description>Williams went down with a shoulder injury in Week 17 against the Commanders. He left in the second quarter and was listed as questionable to return but never did so. Malik Davis would be an option for the Cowboys, but his availability for Week 18 is also in doubt because of an eye issue. Jaydon Blue would be the next man up if both backs are ruled out for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b9-d35e-a1bf-75fb89650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
