<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:03:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons denied the Cowboys’ request to interview DC Jeff Ulbrich for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a00a-d35e-a1bf-e5ca70760000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Todd Archer, “a potential interview can be revisited later” if the Falcons hire a head coach “who has a different coordinator in mind.” One assumes that Falcons team owner Arthur Blank is pleased with Ulbrich’s performance last season. The defense cannot be described as an elite unit, but Ulbrich appears to be a respected figure in the organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a00a-d35e-a1bf-e5ca70760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a014-dc7a-af9b-efbfff830000</link>
      <description>Pearsall is now on the wrong side of questionable for the 49ers’ Wild Card Round game against the Eagles. The 49ers’ talented route runner aggravated his PCL sprain in Week 17 against the Bears and was unable to play on it last week. It is possible that the team is just taking it easy with him, but things are not looking good.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a014-dc7a-af9b-efbfff830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a013-d56e-afff-e6fb75250000</link>
      <description>Kittle is on track to play, though it would be great to see him practice fully on Friday. The 49ers could be short-staffed when they face the Eagles this week. No. 1 WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) has not yet resumed practicing since aggravating the PCL sprain in his knee in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a013-d56e-afff-e6fb75250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested to interview Broncos assistant head coach and defensive passing game coordinator Jim Leonhard for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a017-d35e-a1bf-e5d7b53c0000</link>
      <description>Shortly before issuing this report, ESPN’s Todd Archer let it be known that the Falcons had denied the Cowboys’ request to interview DC Jeff Ulbirch. The Cowboys are smartly casting a very wide net to fill their vacant defensive coordinator role. Leonhard served as the Broncos’ DB coach and defensive passing game coordinator in 2024 before swapping out the DB coach role for an assistant head coach promotion in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a017-d35e-a1bf-e5d7b53c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested to interview Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a022-dc7a-af9b-efbf91df0000</link>
      <description>Jones was initially hired by the Vikings to coach only the defensive backs in 2022. They added defensive pass game coordinator to his title in 2023. ESPN’s Kevin Seifert believes Jones “would be on a very short list to replace Brian Flores as the Vikings’ defensive coordinator, if Flores departs.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a022-dc7a-af9b-efbf91df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys requested to interview Browns S coach Ephraim Banda for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a022-dc7a-af9b-efbfcf880000</link>
      <description>Banda has coached the Browns’ safety group since the team brought him aboard in 2023. The unit stands out in a league that now frequently utilizes two-high safety looks. The Browns’ defense allowed the league’s ninth-fewest yards per pass play (6.61) despite Banda’s unit logging an NFL-high 773 defensive snaps with just one safety lined up deep this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a022-dc7a-af9b-efbfcf880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets requested to interview Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a041-d35e-a1bf-e5c3360d0000</link>
      <description>Jones now has two defensive coordinator interview requests. Good for him. He is also considered a candidate to replace Vikings DC Brian Flores, if were Flores to leave the Vikings’ organization for another opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a041-d35e-a1bf-e5c3360d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that Chargers assistant general manager Chad Alexander and Packers vice president of player personnel Jon-Eric Sullivan are finalists for the Dolphins’ general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a047-d968-a19b-f8f7bded0000</link>
      <description>Alexander has close ties to former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh, which could give him an edge with Dolphins owner Stephen Ross. Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer deserves credit for his reporting late last week, when he identified Sullivan as a candidate for the job in Miami. Per Breer, the Dolphins are expected to “have three guys atop the football side—the head coach, the new GM and [senior vice president of football and business administration Brandon] Shore.” He believes the team is seeking a general manager “with a strong player-evaluation background” to complete the trio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a047-d968-a19b-f8f7bded0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders completed their interview with Cowboys TE coach Lunda Wells for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a04d-d35e-a1bf-e5cf77590000</link>
      <description>That was fast. ESPN’s Todd Archer reported on the Commanders’ request to interview Wells just a few hours ago. Wells ostensibly has a relationship with Commanders head coach Dan Quinn from their time together with the Cowboys in 2021-2023, and Wells is said to have been a “big part of game planning” since the Cowboys hired him in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a04d-d35e-a1bf-e5cf77590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Jon-Eric Sullivan as general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a34d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf04d20000</link>
      <description>One day after firing head coach Mike McDaniel, the Dolphins made another major move in adding Sullivan as the general manager. The Packers’ VP of player personnel since 2022, Sullivan joined Green Bay as an intern in 2003 and worked his way up through various positions, which include a scouting background. Sullivan has stated in interviews how important it is to build through the draft, an approach that likely makes the most sense for this Dolphins rebuild. He is the son of Jerry Sullivan, who spent 25 years as an NFL coach, mostly coaching wide receivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a34d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf04d20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
