<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes Kevin Stefanski “is expected to have second interviews for multiple head coaching jobs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c70d-d968-a19b-dffd0f800000</link>
      <description>Stefanski said he believes the Titans, Falcons, and Ravens “are all potential landing spots” for the two-time coach of the year. Stefanski has been highly sought after since being fired by the Browns following a 5-12 season marred by problems at quarterback. Stefanski lost out to John Harbaugh for the Giants’ head coaching job, but with eight more openings, he’ll have plenty of opportunities to land elsewhere if he wants to continue his career elsewhere as a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c70d-d968-a19b-dffd0f800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will interview Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c738-d56e-afff-e7f83a290000</link>
      <description>Minter has been in high-demand this offseason after leading the Chargers to a top-10 finish in points and yards allowed in his second season as a DC under Jim Harbaugh. The 42-year-old coach recently completed head coaching interviews with the Dolphins, Falcons, Raiders, and Ravens, and field eight interview requests in total. He seems like a lock to land a head-coaching role somewhere in the coming days, although he’s clearly taking his time vetting all options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c738-d56e-afff-e7f83a290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers interviewed Steelers ST cDanny Smith for the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7a9-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77310000</link>
      <description>A true veteran of the game, Smith, 72, has spent the last 13 seasons leading the Steelers’ special teams unit, and spent time as the special teams coordinator for the Bills (2001-2003), and Commanders (2004-2012) before that. Smith’s special teams units with the Steelers were often some of the best the league had to offer, making him an enticing candidate for the Buccaneers, who struggled mightily in that area last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7a9-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports Browns DC Jim Schwartz will have a second interview for the team’s head-coaching vacancy on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7c6-dc7a-af9b-cfffc7780000</link>
      <description>Schwartz isn’t the only candidate who will get a second interview to fill the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy, per Cabot, but the longtime defensive coordinator has already secured one. Schwartz has spent the last three seasons as the Browns’ defensive coordinator and served as the Lions’ head coach from 2009 until 2013. Promoting Schwartz to head coach would make for an easy transition for a defense that finished fourth in yards allowed last season and that has been among the league’s best in two of Schwartz’s three seasons at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7c6-dc7a-af9b-cfffc7780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports Browns OC Tommy Rees “is not expected to interview a second time” for the team’s head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7df-d56e-afff-e7ffb29f0000</link>
      <description>Rees is still cutting his teeth as a coach and was always considered a long shot for the Browns’ head coaching vacancy. The 33-year-old joined the Browns in 2024 as a pass game specialist and tight ends coach and was promoted to offensive coordinator for the 2025 season. Now out as a candidate for the Browns’ job, it’s fair to assume his days as the team’s offensive coordinator could be numbered once a new head coach is locked in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7df-d56e-afff-e7ffb29f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers DC Jeff Hafley will interview with the Steelers for their head-coaching vacancy on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7e5-d968-a19b-dff53df60000</link>
      <description>The Steelers requested an interview with Hafley on Thursday and have now been granted a chance to speak with the second-year defensive coordinator. Hafley has led a top-12 defense or better in each of his two seasons with the Packers since being named as the team’s defensive coordinator in 2024, and has also fielded interview requests from the Dolphins, Raiders, Titans, Cardinals, and Falcons this coaching cycle. He’s clearly in high-demand and is one of the safer bets to land a head coaching job in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7e5-d968-a19b-dff53df60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is questionable for New England’s Divisional Round game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7fb-d968-a19b-dffb5be30000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez was a full participant yesterday and will likely be a full participant in practice today. We’d suspect he’s on the optimistic side of questionable to play against the Texans on Sunday, but concussion protocols can be tricky and there’s probably a small chance he sits out still.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7fb-d968-a19b-dffb5be30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jenna Laine reports Mike McDaniel is meeting in person with the Buccaneers to discuss their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c80e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf33eb0000</link>
      <description>McDaniel won’t be without a job for long, but whether or not he lands a job as a head coach or an offensive coordinator is still to be determined. The former Dolphins head coach last spoke with the Ravens on Thursday regarding their head coaching vacancy, and is reportedly at the top of the list for the Eagles to fill their offensive coordinator vacancy. McDaniel also interviewed for the head coaching vacancies for both the Browns and Falcons. McDaniel would likely have full autonomy over the Bucs’ offense should he join the team, and could help turn around an offense the regressed in its first season sans Liam Coen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c80e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf33eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Falcons OC Zac Robinson is meeting with the Eagles to discuss their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c81a-d56e-afff-eefa7d600000</link>
      <description>Robinson is a branch off the Sean McVay coaching tree and has spent the last two seasons guiding the Falcons’ offensive unit. The 39-year-old coach led an offense that ranked 13th in points scored in 2024 but saw it fall outside the top 20 last season, thanks in part to injuries and the limited quarterback play of Michael Penix and Kirk Cousins. A lateral move to an offense with far more elite playmakers would bode well for Robinson, who could develop into a future head coaching candidate if he excels in his next OC role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c81a-d56e-afff-eefa7d600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Raiders head coach Antonio Pierce for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c812-d56e-afff-eefa7c200000</link>
      <description>Pierce had also been on the docket for the Giants, but with John Harbaugh all but sewn up it feels unlikely to happen. It does not feel likely that Pierce, 47, will rejoin the head coaching ranks this offseason. He spent 2025 as a CBS Sports analyst, which gives him a natural link to Falcons “president of football” Matt Ryan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c812-d56e-afff-eefa7c200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
