<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Barrows believes that “if [Christian McCaffrey] is not back to his 2023 form, he’s pretty close to it.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beb1-d45c-a7fc-bebb4d780000</link>
      <description>With a lot of uncertainty in the wideout corps due to injuries, Barrows expects the 49ers “will lean on” McCaffrey and George Kittle early in the passing game. That is music to the ears of fantasy managers. McCaffrey being in tip-top shape is also huge news — though we’re sure we’ll see plenty of him on the injury report as always this year. The fact that he objectively looks close to 2023 form after a short 2024 comeback where he didn’t appear to be himself is great news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beb1-d45c-a7fc-bebb4d780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Chad Graff believes Patriots S Kyle Dugger “may not make the team.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bec4-df63-a199-ffef08a50000</link>
      <description>Dugger was playing deep into the fourth quarter with third-stringers in New England’s second preseason game, and he finished 2024 with a ghastly 34.8 PFF coverage grade — by far the worst of his five-year career. The Patriots wouldn’t get much cap relief from releasing Duggar, who is making $14.5 million a season, but Graff believes “they might do it anyway.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bec4-df63-a199-ffef08a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs placed DE Felix Anudike-Uzomah (hamstring) on injured reserve, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bed8-d90d-a5bd-bedb0eb30000</link>
      <description>Anudike-Uzomah was a first-round pick of the Chiefs back in 2023 and has totaled three career sacks in the 34 games he’s appeared in this season. He has yet to live up to the hype that made him a top pick and will now hope to rebound in 2026 in what will be a contract year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bed8-d90d-a5bd-bedb0eb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said DeAndre Hopkins is “working on his knee a little bit” when asked about an injury update.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bee8-d90d-a5bd-befbae9d0000</link>
      <description>It’s not much of an update, but Harbaugh also didn’t sound like a coach overly concerned about Hopkins’ Week 1 availability. Hopkins’ knee injury was first reported on July 24, but the veteran receiver has still participated in some practices since then. We’ll assume that Monday’s absence isn’t much more than a management day until the team gives us reason to fear otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bee8-d90d-a5bd-befbae9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there’s an increasing feeling that the Browns will carry four QBs on their 53-man roster.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bef2-d05a-adda-bef2b8df0000</link>
      <description>The Browns’ decision to keep four quarterbacks on the roster has felt like a possibility ever since they drafted Shedeur Sanders in the fifth round, following his unprecedented fall. Both Sanders and fellow rookie Dillon Gabriel have always been near locks to make the roster, and with Joe Flacco the unquestioned QB1, the only decision to really be made was whether or not to retain Kenny Pickett. The Browns’ quarterback room isn’t great. At best, it’s a room full of question marks that may or may not have a franchise quarterback in the waiting, such as Gabriel or Sanders, but that’s still to be determined. Rostering four quarterbacks in hopes of getting a look at the younger guys later in the season feels like the most logical move for a team that has plenty of questions to answer at the position this season and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bef2-d05a-adda-bef2b8df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed EDGE Matthew Judon, formerly of the Falcons, to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bf00-d45c-a7fc-bf1a46820000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz was the first to report the actual signing. Judon will head to the Fins to serve in what will likely be a situational pass-rush role. During three seasons with the Patriots, Judon totaled 32 sacks in 38 games, but managed just 5.5 sacks in 17 games with the Falcons last season. Set to enter his age-33 year, it’s fair to assume his best years are behind him, but Judon should still have enough in the tank to offer a defense in a lighter-used role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bf00-d45c-a7fc-bf1a46820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots GM Eliot Wolf praised UDFA Efton Chism on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdc0-df63-a199-fdeb0f230000</link>
      <description>The undrafted Eastern Washington product has been tearing up the preseason gridiron after a hype-filled offseason program. “I think he’s got tremendous football instincts,” Wolf gushed. “I think he’s tremendous at the top of the route. His play strength for a shorter guy is very good. We’re excited about what he can bring to our football team.” Quotes can be deceiving this time of year, but Wolf is certainly talking like Chism will make the 53-man roster. Fantasy managers need to remember that is Step 1. Step 2 — generating actual value — probably wouldn’t come until 2026, but Chism remains an intriguing end-of-bench stash in Dynasty leagues, and maybe, just maybe someone to put on re-draft watch lists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdc0-df63-a199-fdeb0f230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR Jonathan Mingo (PCL) to miss 4-6 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfa7-d45c-a7fc-bfbf6cd60000</link>
      <description>The injury effectively closes the door on the team’s WR3 battle, with third-year pro Jalen Tolbert almost assuredly in line to start the season in the starting lineup alongside CeeDee Lamb and George Pickens. Mingo has yet to fully pan out in the NFL and joined the Cowboys during the 2024 regular season, with the team hopeful a change of scenery could ignite his career. It appears as if he has avoided surgery but he could start the season on injured reserve/designated to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfa7-d45c-a7fc-bfbf6cd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow completed 9-of-14 passes for 62 yards and one touchdown in the Bengals’ preseason Week 2 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfac-d90d-a5bd-bfff93190000</link>
      <description>That now makes five offensive drives with the starters for Burrow this preseason. The Bengals have scored on four of those possessions while Burrow has gone a combined 18-of-24 for 185 yards and three touchdowns. The offense surely looks to be ready for games to count. The same cannot be said of the Cincinnati defense. Burrow and the Bengals could be forced into similar game environments to what they grew accustomed to in 2024, typically needing to maximize scoring with each possession due to the shortcomings of their defense. Things are certainly setting up for massive volume for Burrow and the rest of the core offensive pieces in the coming season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfac-d90d-a5bd-bfff93190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 11 times for 46 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfe2-d45c-a7fc-bffaeb5c0000</link>
      <description>It was Chris Rodriguez that drew the start after Brian Robinson and the Commanders mutually agreed that the veteran back would not play amidst news of the team shopping him, but both backs looked spry in the preseason tuneup. Roriguez got the fun started with a 40-yard scamper on the team’s first possession before Jacory, ahem, Bill, Croskey-Merritt found paint from 27 yards out on the following possession. The two almost certainly sealed the fate of Robinson in Washington with the team seemingly more than content moving forward without his services during a contract year. It shouldn’t take long for Bill to assert himself in this backfield if we are to believe the glaring reports coming from camp this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bfe2-d45c-a7fc-bffaeb5c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
