<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed eight times for 38 yards in the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers, adding nine yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6870-dc7a-af9b-efff30480000</link>
      <description>Monangai was handily out-gained by backfield mate D’Andre Swift, the latter of whom also scored twice on the ground in the loss. The fact the electric rookie wasn’t able to get more involved in the offensive game plan in a game where both offenses combined for over 940 yards is a bit disappointing for fantasy managers counting on his production in Championship week, although dynasty managers can rest easy knowing he has significantly outperformed expectations entering the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6870-dc7a-af9b-efff30480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden caught 8-of-9 targets for 138 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6872-d35e-a1bf-6df27a540000</link>
      <description>Burden’s only incompletion when targeted went down as a drop, which was really the only blemish in an otherwise sparkling game for the talented rookie. He served as the primary receiver with Rome Odunze on the shelf, in a game where both offenses combined for over 940 yards of total offense. Burden has continued to show his electric abilities with the ball in his hands this season and has made a case as one of the true rising stars in the league while ranking in the top five in fantasy points per route run at the position. Of note, Burden remained down on the field following his target in the end zone to end the game and it was reported that he was carted off the field as a result. Stay tuned for updates on his health in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6872-d35e-a1bf-6df27a540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 6-of-10 targets for 94 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6875-dc7a-af9b-efff6ad70000</link>
      <description>The talented rookie right end led the team with 10 targets and caught one of the two touchdowns thrown by quarterback Caleb Williams, almost contributing to another with under 30 seconds to play when he pitched the ball to running back D’Andre Swift on a hook-and-ladder trick play inside the red zone. Swift was stood up at the three and the Bears were sent to their fifth loss on the next play when Williams’ pass to the end zone fell incomplete as time expired. Loveland’s fantasy value skyrocketed this season as one of the primary points of emphasis for an up-and-coming offense under Ben Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6875-dc7a-af9b-efff6ad70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 1-of-4 targets for seven yards in the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6878-dc7a-af9b-efff3c730000</link>
      <description>19 of Caleb Williams’ 42 passes were directed at rookies Luther Burden and Colston Loveland, each of whom also scored a touchdown in a game with over 940 yards of total offense. The two teams became the first teams since at least 1970 to each score three or more touchdowns within the first 18 minutes, eventually combining for 49 points before the half. That makes is even more staggering that Moore was so little involved in the offense, particularly to fantasy managers relying on his services in Championship week. The emergences of Burden and Loveland and the presence of electric second-year receiver Rome Odunze make Moore a declining fantasy asset, even though his recently-signed extension ties him to the Bears through the 2029 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6878-dc7a-af9b-efff3c730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 24-of-33 passes for 303 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in the 49ers’ 42-38, Week 17 win over the Bears, adding 28 yards and two touchdowns on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6893-dc7a-af9b-efbf0b1e0000</link>
      <description>Purdy’s only blemish on an otherwise spectacular outing occurred on the first offensive play from scrimmage, when a tipped ball resulted in a pick-six to ignite the game environment in what would become the game of the season. The former Mr. Irrelevant completely willed the team to victory to keep their chances of the No. 1 seed in the NFC intact, now requiring only a win over the Seahawks in Week 18 to secure. Arguably the most insane play was a touchdown pass to Kyle Juszczyk towards the end of the third quarter in which Purdy avoided two separate would-be sacks before nonchalantly flipping the ball to the perimeter for a score to his fullback. There were numerous other shining plays in the win, making his highlight reel on the evening one of the better ones to go back and watch for admirers of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6893-dc7a-af9b-efbf0b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 23 times for 140 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears, adding 41 yards on four receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6899-d35e-a1bf-6ddb6dad0000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey accomplished something he had yet to do in his illustrious career by gaining more than 100 yards on the ground in the first half alone, amassing a ridiculous 121 rushing yards and 20 receiving yards in the first 30 minutes of play. A season-high 41-yard inside run was the primary contributor to the eruption. Although unlikely, McCaffrey needs 110 yards through the air in Week 18 to become the first running back in NFL history to accumulate 1,000 yards on the ground and through the air in the same season multiple times, with only he, Marshall Faulk, and Roger Craig accomplishing that feat to date. He can do so when the 49ers host the Seahawks in a battle for the No. 1 seed in the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6899-d35e-a1bf-6ddb6dad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall caught 5-of-8 targets for 85 yards in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall showed no ill wear after missing Week 16, immediately returning to lead the team in receiving on a night the two offenses combined for more than 940 yards of total offense and 80 points. The only thing he didn’t do for fantasy managers was find the end zone. He could have more target competition after it was reported that tight end George Kittle is likely to make a return to the game-day lineup when the 49ers host the Seahawks in Week 18 for a battle for the No. 1 seed out of the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 7-of-9 targets for 60 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</link>
      <description>Tonges was active throughout as a primary outlet for quarterback Brock Purdy over the middle of the field, also seeing numerous designed targets in the flat. His target total was bolstered by a game in which the two teams combined for over 940 yards of total offense and 80 points, immediately making it the game of the season to the observer. Although the outburst in production was welcomed sight to fantasy mangers that scooped Tonges as a plan B option to Kittle, his role appears likely to take a significant hit with Kittle expected back for Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 2-of-4 targets for 42 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ four targets ranked behind fill-in tight end Jake Tonges, Ricky Pearsall, and Christian McCaffrey, although he saved his fantasy outing with a 38-yard touchdown in the fourth quarter to give the 49ers their final lead of the game. It was the first NFL regular season game in NFL history that was tied at seven, 14, 21, 28, and 35 points, with the 49ers eventually emerging victorious following an incomplete pass in the end zone as time expired. Jennings is unlikely to see his target volume surge significantly considering tight end George Kittle is expected to return to the game-day roster in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Juszczyk caught both targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</link>
      <description>Juice scored on an unreal play from quarterback Brock Purdy in which the former Mr. Irrelevant evaded two would-be sacks to deliver the football to the left corner of the end zone and into the waiting hands of Juszczyk. The veteran fullback remains unlikely to see meaningful volume on a weekly basis but his moderate snap rates keep a sporadic touchdown within his range of outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
