<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes Diontae Johnson “has been outplayed at camp” and may be on the wrong side of the roster bubble.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3d6-dbe3-a9bb-f3d7ed6b0000</link>
      <description>“Even though his role would be different than [new signing Isaiah] Bond’s, that addition doesn’t help his chances, either,” Jackson added. Johnson has been listed behind Jamari Thrash on the depth chart for a bit, and the Browns may be choosing between Johnson and special teams helpers for their end-of-roster spots. Even if he does make the roster, Johnson’s role is so unsettled that he’s hard to trust in fantasy drafts at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3d6-dbe3-a9bb-f3d7ed6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Mac Jones (knee) sustained a sprain against the Raiders, but will be available in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3de-db7b-a5dd-e3deb4570000</link>
      <description>That further explains the Nate Sudfeld signing. Jones has by all accounts been a fine backup for the 49ers in training camp and shouldn’t see his 53-man spot at any risk assuming Shanahan’s forecast of his injury is correct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3de-db7b-a5dd-e3deb4570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB isaac Guerendo (shoulder) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3ff-db7b-a5dd-e3ff36910000</link>
      <description>He missed just over two weeks with a shoulder injury. Guerendo should slot right back in as Christian McCaffrey’s main backup over Jeff Wilson going forward. It’s possible Guerendo gets a little run in the final preseason game to make sure he’s fully ready for the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3ff-db7b-a5dd-e3ff36910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Neal (hamstring) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c410-db7b-a5dd-e4143f7d0000</link>
      <description>It’s worth noting that Saints media only gets access to positional drills now that they’re in “regular season mode,” so we’re not entirely sure if Neal is going to get eased in or if he’s practicing with full contact just yet. If healthy, Neal is a candidate to get some run in the third preseason game for New Orleans. He missed roughly two weeks with the hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c410-db7b-a5dd-e4143f7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints head coach Kellen Moore said he is “really, really close” on deciding the team’s starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c466-de13-afdc-c6efc06a0000</link>
      <description>Moore and the Saints have yet to decide on a starting quarterback for Week 1 and the preseason finale against the Broncos will be the last chance for Tyler Shough and Spencer Rattler to make their cases. Both have had perfectly fine outings so far, with Rattler starting the first preseason game and Shough the second. Rattler had subpar performances starting last season, while Shough is the oldest rookie quarterback with a shot to start. Neither will be an appealing fantasy option for the redraft format.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c466-de13-afdc-c6efc06a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Denzel Ward left Tuesday’s practice with a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c48b-d332-a1fd-d6bffc3c0000</link>
      <description>Ward left practice with a shoulder issue, but Jordan Schultz reports the “belief is that he’ll be fine.” The 28-year-old is one of the Browns’ starting corners, tallying 19 passes defended and two interceptions in 16 games last season. He will undergo further testing and his availability for Week 1 will be determined later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c48b-d332-a1fd-d6bffc3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Anthony Richardson’s agent said trust is “questionable” with the front office after Daniel Jones was named the starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c498-d332-a1fd-d6be4eb30000</link>
      <description>Richardson’s agent, Deiric Jackson, said he and the Colts “have a lot to discuss.” Indy just named Daniel Jones as the starting quarterback for 2025, leaving Richardson on the bench. The former No. 4 overall pick has dealt with his struggles and benching in the past and Jackson believes the Colts’ decisions have damaged the team’s credibility. Obviously an agent believes his client should be starting, but the Colts seem headed for an overhaul at the quarterback situation at the end of the season. Whether or not Richardson remains a Colts by 2026 will be in question moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c498-d332-a1fd-d6be4eb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton praised WR Pat Bryant’s unselfishness and blocking in Tuesday press conference.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c4a7-db7b-a5dd-e4a711550000</link>
      <description>Bryant is a third-round rookie from Illinois who has displayed some flash in camp and preseason. Payton boldly compared the big wideout to Michael Thomas and called him “an unselfish player” for his blocking in last weekend’s preseason game against the Cardinals. The 22-year-old has posted six receptions for 91 yards in the preseason while competing to be a top-three pass-catching option. Payton’s praise is a vote of confidence in Bryant, who is worth a late-round flier in season-long fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c4a7-db7b-a5dd-e4a711550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Brooke Pryor reports Steelers DT Cameron Heyward returned to practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c4af-dbe3-a9bb-f4ff78e90000</link>
      <description>Heyward has been holding-in since training camp on August 7th. He is awaiting a new contract after an All-Pro season last year. The Steelers signed him to a two-year, $29 million deal last September, but that average annual value ranks outside the top-20 interior defensive lineman. Heyward is 36, but is still a game-wrecker in the middle of the Steelers’ defense. There is still not progress on a new deal, but Heyward is practiced in individual periods on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c4af-dbe3-a9bb-f4ff78e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
