<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (ankle) doesn’t need to be “130 percent” to see game action.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c2d-df81-ab9b-7eefd58a0000</link>
      <description>A month and a half after McCarthy injured his ankle and a month after he shed his walking boot, O’Connell is still speaking indirectly about how McCarthy might get back on the field in 2025. He said Tuesday that the QB has to be able to “do his job for 60 minutes without having any setbacks” before he’s under center again. When that might be is anyone’s guess as the Vikings play rhetorical games with McCarthy’s status after his abysmal start to the season. Carson Wentz (shoulder) is expected to start the team’s Week 8 game against the Chargers, and Max Brosmer is expected to serve as the backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c2d-df81-ab9b-7eefd58a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said he’s hopeful David Njoku (knee) will be available for Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c72-d651-a9df-6d77a24e0000</link>
      <description>Njoku, who did not play in Week 7, remains day to day with his knee injury, per Stefanski. Harold Fannin caught four of his five targets for 36 yards in a run-heavy attack in Week 7 against Miami with Njoku sidelined. His fantasy prospects would take something of a hit if Njoku returned this week against the Patriots. Both players would be usable in 12-team formats however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c72-d651-a9df-6d77a24e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns OT Jack Conklin cleared the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c78-d99b-a1df-3e7cf19b0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin Stefanski confirmed as much during his Wednesday press conference. Conklin was sidelined last week against the Dolphins after suffering the head injury in Week 6 against the Steelers. He should be available in Week 8 against the Patriots. Cleveland needs all the offensive line help it can get: Pro Football Focus grades the Browns line as the league’s worst pass-blocking unit and the tenth worst run-blocking unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c78-d99b-a1df-3e7cf19b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said a backfield split would be an ideal approach to the team’s running game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c96-df81-ab9b-7ed7af400000</link>
      <description>When asked about De’Vone Achane’s massive workload — Achane has 212 touches through seven games — McDaniel said he would like to see Ollie Gordon more involved in the rushing attack. Game script for the lowly Dolphins often doesn’t allow such a distribution, however, as Achane remains the team’s primary pass-catching option. McDaniel mentioned the Dolphins’ Week 3 game against Buffalo as an ideal backfield distribution, with Achane seeing 12 carries to nine for Gordon. Achane had seven catches in that game, and remains one of the most reliable running backs in fantasy. Gordon should be stashed on benches for now in case Achane misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0c96-df81-ab9b-7ed7af400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn would not announce a starting quarterback for Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cac-da09-adde-bdfe1bc50000</link>
      <description>Glenn apparently wants to launch a last-minute sneak attack against the Bengals. The Jets are reportedly leaning toward starting Tyrod Taylor after Justin Fields’ abysmal play over the past few weeks, but Glenn isn’t ready to make the move official. Taylor, who is now dealing with a knee injury, would be an upgrade for the team’s pass catchers and should be rostered in all superflex formats against a soft Bengals defense. The potential for an in-game Fields benching makes him a risky fantasy play if he gets the Week 8 nod.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cac-da09-adde-bdfe1bc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) is day to day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0caf-deb1-a39b-2dafed580000</link>
      <description>With the Jets reportedly leaning toward starting Taylor in Week 8 against the Bengals, he might be unavailable and leave the team with no choice but to stick with Justin Fields. Fields has been horrific through Week 7. He ranks 25th out of 33 qualifying QBs in accuracy and 24th in drop back success rate. Fields has taken a sack on a league-high 14 percent of his drop backs this year. Taylor would be a significant upgrade for the New York pass catchers if he’s able to play through his knee issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0caf-deb1-a39b-2dafed580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed TE Darren Waller (pec) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cc7-deb1-a39b-2dcf3e180000</link>
      <description>The injury isn’t expected to require surgery, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, but Waller will miss at least the next four weeks while recovering from the pec injury he sustained in Week 7 against the Browns. Waller had become an important part of the Miami passing offense, recording ten receptions and four touchdowns over three games while running most of the routes in the Dolphins offense. With Waller out, look for De’Von Achane to see even more targets than usual. Malik Washington could also see a slight target bump over the next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cc7-deb1-a39b-2dcf3e180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Post’s Nicki Jhabvala reports Jayden Daniels (hamstring) won’t play in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd0-d245-adfb-9ddf9c960000</link>
      <description>Jhabvala said Daniels will sit and Marcus Mariota will get his third start of the season against Kansas City on Monday night. Mariota has proven an adept game manager with some fantasy appeal in his two 2025 starts, throwing three touchdowns and two interceptions while rushing for 94 yards and a touchdown. Daniels’ absence will be a downgrade for all Washington pass catchers and the general scoring environment of this Washington-KC matchup. Mariota should be started in all superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd0-d245-adfb-9ddf9c960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) is out for Week 8 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</link>
      <description>Irving hasn’t played since Week 4 as he struggles with injuries to his foot and shoulder. Rachaad White will continue as the Bucs’ lead back this week against the Saints, a middle rush defense. White’s involvement in the pass game has kept him afloat as a top-20 option with Irving sidelined. He should remain in lineups this week against a New Orleans defense allowing 104 rushing yards per game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
