<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Tee Higgins (concussion) “arrived with a helmet for the last minute of practice.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32de-dc7a-af9b-ffff30e40000</link>
      <description>Technically, Higgins could end up being listed as a limited participant, though this participation level is hardly encouraging for his Week 16 availability. Hopefully, Higgins can practice fully tomorrow, or at least increase his limited participation level. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32de-dc7a-af9b-ffff30e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (calf) was not present during the portion of practice open to the media on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32e6-dc7a-af9b-ffff86000000</link>
      <description>Sampson played through the calf injury in Week 14. Perhaps that was a mistake. The Browns’ rookie running back has neither practiced nor played since then. He is firmly on the wrong side of questionable for Week 16, likely leaving Quinshon Judkins and Trayveon Williams as the Browns’ top-two running backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32e6-dc7a-af9b-ffff86000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32ea-dc7a-af9b-ffff8e090000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports that Lamb “was involved in the meetings this morning,” which is encouraging for his Week 16 availability. The Cowboys (6-7-1) are clinging to the playoff bubble. Unless something goes awry, they should have their No. 1 wide receiver on the field for their Week 16 game against the Chargers. He is a WR1 if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32ea-dc7a-af9b-ffff8e090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32e7-d087-addf-b3f7d5a20000</link>
      <description>Even if Njoku plays this weekend, he does not belong in 12-team re-draft lineups. The 29-year-old veteran has been fully supplanted by rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr., who is a weekly TE1. Should Njoku sit out, as expected, it will likely increase Fannin’s route participation level, which is great for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32e7-d087-addf-b3f7d5a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) will not practice on Thursday, but there is a “possibility” he plays in Week 16 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32d8-d087-addf-b3f8fe230000</link>
      <description>Per 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan, Pearsall is “doing a lot better today than he was on Monday.” That is nice to hear, but Shanahan’s wide receiver-related prognostications have been unreliable this season, and although Pearsall may be feeling better, he was unable to practice. The 49ers face the Colts on Monday night, giving the No. 1 wide receiver an extra day to rehab the knee and ankle issues. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32d8-d087-addf-b3f8fe230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out WR Rome Odunze (foot) for Week 16 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f0-dc7a-af9b-ffff6e7f0000</link>
      <description>Odunze was listed with heel and ankle injuries in October and November. On December 5th, he was reportedly considered week-to-week with a stress fracture in his foot. The Bears held him out of their Week 14 game on December 7th, but allowed him to resume practicing in Week 15. He then aggravated the stress fracture during pre-game warmups. It’s an extremely unfortunate series of events. The Bears will also be without WR Luther Burden (ankle) against the Packers on Saturday, reducing target competition for TE Colston Loveland and WRs DJ Moore and Olamide Zaccheaus. Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) and TE Cole Kmet (ankle/knee) are questionable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f0-dc7a-af9b-ffff6e7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out WR Luther Burden (ankle) for Week 16 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f0-dc7a-af9b-ffffb3480000</link>
      <description>Burden injured his ankle in Week 15 and was completely unable to practice this week. He and WR Rome Odunze (foot) have both been ruled out, while RB D’Andre Swift (groin) and TE Cole Kmet (ankle/knee) are listed as questionable to play. Bears TE Colston Loveland and WRs DJ Moore and Olamide Zaccheaus stand to benefit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f0-dc7a-af9b-ffffb3480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 16 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f2-d087-addf-b3f208ea0000</link>
      <description>Swift was added to the injury report on Wednesday and got in limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. He’ll be worth waiting around for on Saturday, and it’s great news that he hit the questionable line and practiced again after the surprise addition. Swift will be on the RB2 line if he plays, particularly with the Bears down a pair of important pass-catchers on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f2-d087-addf-b3f208ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (ankle/knee) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 16 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f4-dc7a-af9b-ffff5c9b0000</link>
      <description>He upgraded to a full practice on Thursday and would appear to be on the optimistic side of questionable after practicing all week. Normally his presence is a sign to dial back expectations for Colston Loveland in fantasy, but it’s possible the Bears could use a ton of two tight-end looks in Week 16 with both Luther Burden and Rome Odunze ruled out. Loveland will be a playable low-end TE1, while Kmet is on the TE2 line at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32f4-dc7a-af9b-ffff5c9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (foot/ankle) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32fc-d35e-a1bf-77fe66600000</link>
      <description>The rookie wideout will likely only log a limited session on Thursday, but it should push the chances of him playing on Sunday in Carolina’s must-win against the Buccaneers up. McMillan practicing on Friday would likely lead him to be an optimistic questionable or removed from the injury report altogether. Despite his stats taking a hit of late, McMillan will be a low-end WR2 in an enormous NFC South showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32fc-d35e-a1bf-77fe66600000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
