<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fba-d968-a19b-dffb8b080000</link>
      <description>Goedert, 31, is now up to two limited sessions in the lead-up to the Eagles’ Wild Card Round game against the 49ers. We expect Goedert to suit up. Although we would like to see him practicing fully, the team could just be limiting the veteran player’s reps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fba-d968-a19b-dffb8b080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed their interview with Broncos passing game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fc5-d35e-a1bf-dfc76cde0000</link>
      <description>Webb has just three years of coaching experience under his belt, having been hired as the Broncos’ quarterbacks coach in 2023. He managed to add the passing game coordinator title last offseason. Interviewing for the Ravens’ head-coaching vacancy this quickly is quite an accomplishment. Thus far, Webb has also been linked to the Raiders, who reportedly requested to interview him earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fc5-d35e-a1bf-dfc76cde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders requested to interview Cowboys TE coach Lunda Wells for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fcf-d968-a19b-dfff1a9a0000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Todd Archer, “Wells has been [a] big part of game planning” since the Cowboys hired him away from the Giants in 2020. He coached the same position there from 2018-2019 after serving as the assistant offensive line coach from 2013-2017. Wells “was on staff with Commanders head coach Dan Quinn for three years, when Quinn served as the Cowboys’ defensive coordinator from 2021-2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fcf-d968-a19b-dfff1a9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fd8-d968-a19b-dff975ce0000</link>
      <description>Eagles LB Nakobe Dean (hamstring), S Marcus Epps (concussion), OLB Azeez Ojulari (hamstring) and OLB Jaelan Phillips (ankle) are all practicing fully. Carter’s continued participation is a good sign. Hopefully, he upgrades to full participation on Friday. The Eagles face the 49ers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fd8-d968-a19b-dff975ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f64-dc7a-af9b-dfff70530000</link>
      <description>Johnson could be seen hopping on one foot during a ladder drill at today’s practice. We take this as a good sign for his availability this week, but nothing is certain. Johnson has rigorously rehabbed after suffering a Lisfranc injury in Week 11 against the Lions. Hopefully, he is good to go for his team’s game against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f64-dc7a-af9b-dfff70530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fce-dc7a-af9b-dfff0a950000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Chargers OC Greg Roman told reporters, before practice, that RB Hampton would be “involved some today” in practice. Instead, Hampton worked off to the side. Roman added that Hampton is “working through his process with the medical group” and is “ready mentally with the game plan.” That last bit makes it sound like Hampton is preparing as though he really does have a chance to play. Two absences to begin the week are worrying, though. No. 2 RB Kimani Vidal would likely operate as the team’s starter if Hampton is unable to face the Patriots this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fce-dc7a-af9b-dfff0a950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fd3-d56e-afff-fffb56920000</link>
      <description>Lambert-Smith is now on the wrong side of questionable, having missed the last two practices. The speedy rookie has not yet established himself as a reliable pass catcher, but he would be nice to have available on game day. The Chargers’ offense has been hit hard with injuries this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fd3-d56e-afff-fffb56920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans will interview former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ff7-d56e-afff-ffff2bf20000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the interview will take place “next Saturday.” McCarthy worked with Titans president of football operations Chad Brinker during their time together with the Packers. Whether that gives McCarthy an edge remains to be seen. The Titans are casting a wide net. McCarthy will also interview for the Giants’ open role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ff7-d56e-afff-ffff2bf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots C Garrett Bradbury (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ff7-d968-a19b-dff7a6e80000</link>
      <description>Patriots OLB Anfernee Jennings (illness) and OT Morgan Moses (illness) resumed practicing in full. Patriots OT Vederian Lowe (illness) remained sidelined, and did DT Khyiris Tonga (foot). All ill players have a chance to play in the Patriots’ Wild Card Round game against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ff7-d968-a19b-dff7a6e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fea-dc7a-af9b-dfff20b20000</link>
      <description>Mid-week additions to the injury report typically indicate that the player suffered a new injury in practice that day. We fear this is the case here. Boutte notably dealt with a hamstring strain earlier this season, costing him two games. He is not a big-time player in the Patriots’ offense, but he helps keep safeties honest in his field-stretching role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9fea-dc7a-af9b-dfff20b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
