<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (neck) is not on Dallas’ final Week 3 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a6-d6a5-adff-f7e7cf3e0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full during each of the last two days of the practice week. Given how much of a shootout Cowboys/Bears projects to be, Turpin isn’t a half-bad DFS punt or FLEX play despite his limited workload. Turpin has played just 42 snaps this year in two games, though he did leave Week 2’s game early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a6-d6a5-adff-f7e7cf3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a4-d1b3-a5dd-63f5dc4d0000</link>
      <description>Speaking to reporters earlier today, Likely said he is taking things “day-by-day” and does not yet know if he will be able to play on Monday night. Now is the time to stash Likely on benches where available. Mark Andrews, now 30 years old, has earned just four targets with Likely sidelined. Whenever he retakes the field, Likely has a real chance to make good on the promise he’s shown in the past. If he seizes the role, he can return TE1 value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a4-d1b3-a5dd-63f5dc4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers TE Tucker Kraft (knee) is questionable for Week 3’s game against Cleveland.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a9-d93f-ad9d-7bef79690000</link>
      <description>It’s surprising that he’s on the questionable line after not practicing today, but it looks like he still has a chance to go. We expect the #sources to be busy on Kraft over the weekend. Even if he’s dinged up and against the Browns in a game that has running the clock written all over it, Kraft would probably be a TE1 play for most teams if he’s active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63a9-d93f-ad9d-7bef79690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (ankle) is not on Green Bay’s final injury report for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63ae-dfde-a1bd-7faf29d20000</link>
      <description>He’ll play and be a locked-in RB1 against the Browns in a game that figures to give him plenty of volume. Jacobs hasn’t been wildly through two weeks, with “only” 150 rushing yards and two scores through two games. But the volume is great and there’s no reason to be concerned with his role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63ae-dfde-a1bd-7faf29d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Nate Wiggins (groin) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-639d-d1b3-a5dd-63fd579a0000</link>
      <description>Wiggins’ return is a step in the right direction. The talented cornerback was injured after his teammate, CB Chidobe Awuzie, jumped on his back for a post-interception celebration. Unfortunately for the Ravens, DT Nnamdi Madubuike (neck) remains sidelined through two Week 3 practices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-639d-d1b3-a5dd-63fd579a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is off Las Vegas’ final Week 3 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b0-d1b3-a5dd-63f11d720000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited practices this week. While he didn’t exactly look like he was going full-strength on Monday night, there’s no obvious reason to sit Bowers in Week 3 given he practiced more this week and no tight end in the league has the ceiling case that Bowers grants while healthy. If he’s fully healed from the Week 1 injury, Bowers should be the featured component of Vegas’ passing game against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b0-d1b3-a5dd-63f11d720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (biceps) is not on Los Angeles’ final Week 3 injury report against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7624b0000</link>
      <description>He’ll be full-go in Week 3 against the Broncos, it’s not an easy matchup, but McConkey should be able to exploit the middle of the field in the same way Josh Downs was able to last week against Broncos slot corner Brandon Jones. He’ll be on the WR1/WR2 borderline for Week 3 despite getting off to a (comparatively) slow start compared to Keenan Allen and Quentin Johnston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7624b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) will not play in Week 3’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b6-d1b3-a5dd-63f7c3320000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week. Tyler Conklin and Oronde Gadsden figure to see more opportunities with Dissly gone, though neither of them are better than TE2 dart throws for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b6-d1b3-a5dd-63f7c3320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Daiyan Henley (illness) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 3 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b8-d6a5-adff-f7fd7b230000</link>
      <description>It’s kind of surprising that the illness has lasted this long — Henley drew another DNP in practice on Friday after also missing Wednesday — and even despite him playing through it on Monday Night it’s certainly possible he sits this game out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b8-d6a5-adff-f7fd7b230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out TE Evan Engram (back) for Week 3 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d1b3-a5dd-63f3a6210000</link>
      <description>Like many 31-year-olds, Engram’s back is aching. Unfortunately for him, Engram plays professional football and is also coming off a calf injury. He was completely unable to practice this week, as was LB Dre Greenlaw (quad). At some point, Engram may regain his health and allow us to fully measure how much talent he has left in the tank, but for now, Engram can be dropped if an injured tight end like Dallas Goedert or Isaiah Likely is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d1b3-a5dd-63f3a6210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
