<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk caught 2-of-6 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c0-d56e-afff-f7e8f1800000</link>
      <description>One of Kirk’s missed connections was a hellacious first quarter drop. A Wild Card hero, Kirk was one of many Divisional Round goats despite his 10-yard touchdown in the second quarter. Mostly a 4-6 target player out of the slot this season, Kirk was able to hold off third-round rookie Jaylin Noel, but only just. Now heading into his age-30 campaign as he prepares for free agency, Kirk could be a victim of the Texans’ receiver youth movement. Wherever he plays in 2026, the best he could hope for in fantasy is low-ceiling WR4 status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c0-d56e-afff-f7e8f1800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Hutchinson caught 4-of-13 targets for 44 yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c6-d968-a19b-dbf723ab0000</link>
      <description>With the Texans in skill corps injury crisis as C.J. Stroud imploded vs. Mike Vrabel’s defense, Hutchinson somehow commanded 10-plus targets for the first time in his three-year corps. Bizarre, and not a harbinger of things to come. Although Christian Kirk is headed to free agency, Nico Collins isn’t going anywhere, while rookies Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel both intrigued in 2025. Hutchinson will probably make the 53-man roster in the final year of his rookie deal, but that’s not locked in. He has 55 catches over 49 career contests. Admittedly, 35 of those came in 2025. This coaching staff probably likes Hutchinson enough to keep him around one more year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c6-d968-a19b-dbf723ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 20-of-42 passes for 258 yards in the Rams’ 20-17, Divisional round win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d401-d968-a19b-dcf1c6970000</link>
      <description>The Rams’ offense struggled to get going in the wintry conditions at Soldier Field, but a solid defensive effort kept the game within reach and gave the Rams plenty of chances to pull out the win. Despite not throwing a touchdown pass in this one, Stafford did his part to keep the offense on schedule, coming up with multiple big gains through the air on the Rams’ two touchdown drives that both ended with Kyren Williams finding the end zone. Stafford saw two sack fumbles take favorable bounces into the hands of Rams players to keep his turnover total to zero on the day, and will now look to pull off a third-straight road win against the Seahawks next week for the right to represent the NFC in the Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d401-d968-a19b-dcf1c6970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Williams completed 23-of-42 passes for 257 yards, two touchdowns, and three interceptions in the Bears’ 20-17, Divisional round loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d43a-dc7a-af9b-dfbf52c20000</link>
      <description>Williams and the Bears appeared to be setting the stage for yet another comeback in this one. Facing a fourth-and-four with under 30 seconds left on the game clock, Williams dropped back and found himself immediately under duress. After dropping back over 25 yards beyond the original line of scrimmage, and with three defenders in his face, Williams heaved a perfectly thrown ball off his back foot into the end zone for Cole Kmet, who secured the pass for a 14-yard touchdown to force overtime. An errant pass on what appeared to be a miscommunication between Williams and DJ Moore resulted in an interception that ended the Bears’ only overtime possession, as the Rams went on to capitalize on the turnover with a Harrison Mevis 42-yard field goal to end the game and the Bears’ season. Williams thrived in his first season under head coach Ben Johnson, turning in multiple highlight-reel throws will pulling off an NFL record seven comeback wins. His final regular season line of 3,942-27-7 set new career highs, and he added another 77-388-3 on the ground. With plenty of young weapons already locked in for next season, Williams should continue to improve in 2026 with another year of experience under his belt and more time to learn under Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d43a-dc7a-af9b-dfbf52c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams rushed 21 times for 87 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ Divisional round win over the Bears, adding four catches for 30 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d452-d56e-afff-f6fa2f040000</link>
      <description>Williams found the end zone twice in this one. The fourth-year back punched in a four-yard score on the Rams’ opening possession to give his team an early 7-0 lead, and later found the end zone on a five-yard run in the fourth quarter to break a 10-10 tie. Williams never found much room to run in this one, with his longest runs coming on two 10-yard gains. The Rams didn’t truly lean on Williams until late in the game, as 14 of his 21 carries came in the fourth quarter or overtime, but his two scoring plays more than made up for his rather pedestrian total on the ground. Williams will face another tough test in next week’s NFC Championship Game when he goes on the road to face a stout Seahawks defense that held him to 23-70-0 on the ground the last time the two teams met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d452-d56e-afff-f6fa2f040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 5-of-10 targets for 56 yards in the Rams’ Divisional round win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d459-d56e-afff-f6f91ea80000</link>
      <description>Nacua’s 56 receiving yards tied with Colby Parkison for the team high in Sunday’s win over the Bears. His 10 targets led all Rams players, but Nacua was unable to get much of anything going through the air after going for 10-111-1 in last week’s win over the Panthers. The third-year receiver’s biggest play of the game came on a third-and-six in overtime when he converted a first down on a 16-yard gain to help move the Rams within field goal range. Kicker Harrison Mevis would nail a 42-yard field goal four plays later to send the Bears packing, as Nacua and the Rams now prep for an NFC West showdown with the Seahawks and a trip to the Super Bowl on the line. Nacua went for a whopping 12-225-2 the last time the Rams played the Seahawks, and will hope to replicate some of those numbers next week in the Conference Championship game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d459-d56e-afff-f6f91ea80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 2-of-6 targets for 24 yards in the Rams’ Divisional round win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d461-dc7a-af9b-dfffd1fe0000</link>
      <description>Adams was mostly a non-factor in this one, although his 12-yard reception in the fourth quarter did help set up an eventual touchdown run by Kyren Williams to give the Rams a 17-10 lead. Adams appeared to have briefly left the game with an injury, but was later back on the field taking snaps. He also secured a 12-yard pass on the Rams’ final drive in overtime to help set up the team’s game-winning field goal. Sunday’s game against the Bears wasn’t the kind of game we have been accustomed to seeing from Adams this season. He’ll look to bounce back in next week’s road matchup against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d461-dc7a-af9b-dfffd1fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrance Ferguson caught 1-of-5 targets for 19 yards in the Rams’ divisional round win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d465-d35e-a1bf-d5e7598f0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson’s five targets set a new high for him this season, but the rookie tight end was unable to capitalize on the volume in Sunday’s win. Ferguson came up with a 19-yard reception in the second quarter to extend a drive that was set back by a Matthew Stafford sack, but it was a forgettable day for the rookie second-rounder. He’ll hope to have a little more success in next week’s Conference Championship game against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d465-d35e-a1bf-d5e7598f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed six times for 19 yards in the Rams’ Divisional round win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d469-dc7a-af9b-dfff9e050000</link>
      <description>Corum has been a fairly safe bet to see double-digit touches this season, but the second-year back was held to just six carries on Sunday and has now seen that total twice in his last three games. The fact that he averaged a meager 3.2 YPC on those carries gave even greater reason for the Rams not trust him too much in Sunday’s do-or-die game. Corum could see his volume bounce back in next weeks Conference Championship road game against the Seahawks, but we would expect Kyren Williams to continue to handle the majority of the work after back-to-back solid performances this post season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d469-dc7a-af9b-dfff9e050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift rushed 19 times for 76 yards in the Bears’ Divisional round loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d46f-d968-a19b-dcff32280000</link>
      <description>Swift did not see a target in this one, as all the passing-down work instead went to rookie Kyle Monangai. Swift’s season ends with a regular-season rushing line of 223-1,087-9, marking the second time in his career that he has surpassed 1,000 yards in a season. Operating as the “lightning” to Kyle Monangai’s “thunder,” Swift was a key player in head coach Ben Johnson’s two-man committee approach, and wound up leading the bears in carries, rushing yards, and rushing touchdowns. Still under contract through next season, Swift should be back with the Bears but could be at risk of seeing more of a split backfield with Monangai likely poised for a bigger role in his second season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d46f-d968-a19b-dcff32280000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
