<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 19:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (pec) is active for Week 13 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59d-d90e-a9da-df9f20ae0000</link>
      <description>Waller was activated from injured reserve over the weekend but still drew the questionable tag, largely as a procedural matter. He will likely be on a pitch count on his first game back, keeping him in the TE2 ranks for a week despite him putting up TE1 numbers before going on IR. Inactive for the Phins are QB Quinn Ewers, CB AJ Green III, LB Andre Carter, WR Tahj Washington, and DT Matthew Butler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59d-d90e-a9da-df9f20ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared G Laken Tomlinson inactive for Houston’s Week 13 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59d-db57-afda-d7bf95ce0000</link>
      <description>After starting seven games this year, Houston has moved away from Tomlinson in the interior line. He was active in Week 10 and Week 11, but recorded zero offensive snaps in each game. Also inactive for the Texans are LB Jamal Hill (hamstring), QB Graham Mertz (third quarterback), T Jarrett Kingston and WR Braxton Berrios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59d-db57-afda-d7bf95ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared WR Mason Kinsey, CB Jalyn Armour-Davis, S Jerrick Reed, S Kendell Brooks, G Drew Moss, C Lloyd Cushenberry, and DT Shy Tuttle inactive for Week 13 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d597-d90e-a9da-df9f16500000</link>
      <description>Cushenberry was ruled out due to a foot injury. His absence will force the Titans to reach into their offensive line depth against a solid Jaguars pass rush. Meanwhile, Mason Kinsey is made inactive with Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) officially active and Xavier Restrepo playing again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d597-d90e-a9da-df9f16500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Jerome Ford (hamstring) is active for Week 13 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59f-d6c4-abfb-d79ffa550000</link>
      <description>There was some question as to whether Ford would play in Week 13 after being downgraded to a DNP on Thursday as he deals with a lingering hamstring issue. Ford being active is a slight hit to Quinshon Judkins’ fantasy prospects, though the Browns should be run heavy enough for Judkins to deliver RB2 numbers. The Browns declared G Zak Zinter, T Cornelius Lucas, WR Jamari Thrash, TE Brenden Bates, DE Alex Wright, and DT Adin Huntington inactive against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59f-d6c4-abfb-d79ffa550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared WR KhaDarel Hodge, WR Drake London (knee), ILB Josh Woods (hamstring), OL Michael Jerrell, WR Casey Washington and DL Elijah Garcia inactive for Atlanta’s Week 13 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a1-d90e-a9da-dfaf02580000</link>
      <description>Since receiving eight targets in Week 8, Hodge has one target in four games and now is a healthy scratch. London didn’t practice all week and is a question mark for Week 14. Star guard Chris Lindstrom (toe) continues to play through an injury on the questionable line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a1-d90e-a9da-dfaf02580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared CB Jaycee Horn, LB Christian Rozeboom, LB Claudin Cherelus, C Cade Mays, WR Hunter Renfrow, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, and DT Cam Jackson inactive for Week 13 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59b-db57-afda-d7bb6bd10000</link>
      <description>Half of these players, including Horn, were ruled out on Friday due to various injuries. Renfrow is a healthy scratch, which has been the norm for the veteran receiver who hasn’t seen the field since Week 6. Despite being the home team, the Panthers enter Week 13 as massive underdogs to the 9-2 Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d59b-db57-afda-d7bb6bd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Dyami Brown, RB Cody Schrader, DE Travon Walker, OL Chuma Edoga, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Patrick Mekari, TE Hunter Long, and DT Arik Armstead inactive for Week 13 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a0-d82c-a79a-f7b41e3e0000</link>
      <description>Armstead was a late addition to the injury report with a hand issue and is now officially inactive for Week 13. With Travon Walker (knee) also ruled out, the Jaguars’ defense line is looking sparse against the Titans. Meanwhile, Dyami Brown is a healthy scratch as Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) makes his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a0-d82c-a79a-f7b41e3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared QB Stetson Bennett, RB Jarquez Hunter, CB Derion Kendrick, OL Beaux Limmer, and DE Desjuan Johnson inactive for Week 13 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a2-d90e-a9da-dfaf6d810000</link>
      <description>The Rams enter the day with a 9-2 record and are operating at nearly full strength against the Panthers. Whether by land or by air, the Rams should have no trouble moving the ball against a Panthers defense that ranks 18th in yards allowed but will be without its top corner in Jaycee Horn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a2-d90e-a9da-dfaf6d810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner (calf) left Indianapolis’ Week 13 game against the Texans and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5f6-db57-afda-d7f6e5490000</link>
      <description>Gardner could not put any weight on his left leg. He limped to the medical tent, then was helped off the field between a pair of trainers. It didn’t look good for the Colts main trade deadline acquisition, but a calf is better than it looked like it could have been.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5f6-db57-afda-d7f6e5490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (foot) left Houston’s Week 13 game against the Colts and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d60d-d82c-a79a-f79d628b0000</link>
      <description>A Colts defender knee rolled his ankle. He had three carries for zero yards before leaving. There was no scene upon leaving, but Marks spent some time in the medical tent and jogged to the locker room with trainers. Nick Chubb has taken over as the starting running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d60d-d82c-a79a-f79d628b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
