<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a322-d82c-a79a-b3b6ef7b0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs told reporters that this isn’t a “pain issue” but is a “range of motion” issue, which makes it sound like something that may not be entirely in his hands at this point. He also noted that his “worst-case scenario” is missing this week, and that he’s adamant about playing against the Lions on Thanksgiving. These are all promising things in the grand scheme of things, but it still sounds like Emanuel Wilson has a chance to head a committee against the Vikings this week. Jacobs probably will get to the questionable line at this point if the Packers don’t shut him down on Friday. The fact that he’s speaking to the media at all is another point in favor of him playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a322-d82c-a79a-b3b6ef7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Flacco (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a321-db57-afda-f7337c120000</link>
      <description>Flacco took reps as the QB2 today, while Joe Burrow (toe) took snaps with the first-team offense. It sure looks an awful lot like Burrow will be the Week 12 starter, though the team could hold him out for one more week. If Flacco gets the start against the Patriots, he is a borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a321-db57-afda-f7337c120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a327-d82c-a79a-b3b7337f0000</link>
      <description>So were Romeo Doubs (wrist), Matthew Golden (shoulder/wrist), Dontyavion Wicks (calf), Savion Williams (foot), Robert Brooks, Jordy Nelson, and Corey Bradford. Most of these injuries were played through last Sunday, with Williams (foot) getting the lone Wednesday DNP. We wouldn’t trust any of these receivers beyond the FLEX line at this point, with Watson leading the rankings there, but we bet most of them will be active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a327-d82c-a79a-b3b7337f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a336-d82c-a79a-b3b6fa990000</link>
      <description>Jackson sat out yesterday before upgrading to full today. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said this would be the case. The Ravens face the lowly Jets in Week 12, so Jackson’s dual-threat talents may not be fully needed. Still, his ability to break slates keeps him squarely in the QB1 tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a336-d82c-a79a-b3b6fa990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d413-ad9f-b7fd92e70000</link>
      <description>Likely is firmly in the questionable camp for the Ravens’ Week 12 game against the Jets. He, unfortunately, can only be viewed as a touchdown-dependent TE2, who takes a backseat to TE Mark Andrews in the red zone. If Likely sits, Andrews should snag an extra target or two here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d413-ad9f-b7fd92e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d82c-a79a-b3bd8ab50000</link>
      <description>Bateman has not yet recovered enough from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 10 to resume practicing. The Ravens’ field-stretching wide receiver is unlikely to be needed against the Jets anyway. Hopefully, he can return in time for the Ravens’ Week 13 game against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d82c-a79a-b3bd8ab50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33f-d90e-a9da-bf3f8d100000</link>
      <description>Kamara cleared the century mark last week, and has a chance to sneak into RB2 territory against a friendly Falcons run defense in Week 12. The veteran back’s 159 offensive touches rank 19th at the position. He is no longer an elite player, but he should continue returning decent stat lines this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33f-d90e-a9da-bf3f8d100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed WR Mecole Hardman on injured reserve with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a348-db57-afda-f77a74350000</link>
      <description>Hardman will now miss at least four games. He does not need to be rostered in any format. The Bills also elevated WR Gabe Davis from the practice squad to the active roster for tonight’s game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a348-db57-afda-f77a74350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-db57-afda-f772106c0000</link>
      <description>Jurgens is making progress in the NFL’s concussion protocol, but he has a ways to go before he can be viewed as more than questionable. Having their reliable center on the field would be great for a struggling Eagles offense as they take on the division-rival Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-db57-afda-f772106c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys QB Dak Prescott (hip) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-d413-ad9f-b7df18c70000</link>
      <description>Prescott was surprisingly limited on Wednesday after head coach Brian Schottenheimer told reporters that the Cowboys’ quarterback would handle a “normal workload” at Wednesday’s walkthrough. Regardless, Prescott is now practicing fully and can be treated as a QB1 entering a Week 12 showdown with the division-rival Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a352-d413-ad9f-b7df18c70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
