<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (knee) is practicing in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a64-d214-a3b9-3e7ca77e0000</link>
      <description>Pierce’s fantasy value is shot between his deep-ball talents, Daniel Jones’ disinterest in throwing deep unless someone is wide open, and a tough Broncos defense. He probably doesn’t need to be in lineups for Week 2 outside of desperation scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a64-d214-a3b9-3e7ca77e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts EDGE Laiatu Latu (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a66-d5f6-abfd-bb7f1b760000</link>
      <description>Beware the mid-week downgrade. Latu got a limited session in on Wednesday. Latu was the highest-graded Colts defensive player per PFF in Week 1, notching a 91.5 grade despite no sacks and just one hurry. His absence would be felt by the Colts as they try to hold down Bo Nix and the Broncos in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a66-d5f6-abfd-bb7f1b760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a69-d5f6-abfd-bb7d35fc0000</link>
      <description>Two limited sessions put London on track to play, but it also suggests he may be a little sore. London should again lead his team in target share against the Vikings. Downfield WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is trending toward making his 2025 debut, which should keep safeties honest against London. He’s a WR1 in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a69-d5f6-abfd-bb7d35fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf/rest) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a6e-d5f6-abfd-bb7f69be0000</link>
      <description>We assume this will be a full session based on beat reporter quotes, but even if it was a limited, McCaffrey is well on track to play against the Saints on Sunday. He should get an easy RB1 workload and the 49ers will desperately need him to deliver production with George Kittle and Brock Purdy out and Jauan Jennings’ status still under some question.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a6e-d5f6-abfd-bb7f69be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a6e-da68-ad9d-ff7e59e90000</link>
      <description>This makes five straight limited sessions for Mooney, who did not suit up in Week 1 against the Buccaneers. His continued participation seemingly puts him on track to play in Week 2 against the Vikings, but it would be great to see him practice in full on Friday. Mooney’s downfield speed would be very valuable against the Vikings’ blitz-happy defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a6e-da68-ad9d-ff7e59e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinshon Judkins (not injury related) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-d214-a3b9-3e7d6be10000</link>
      <description>The Browns have been evasive on the plan for Judkins in Week 2, but a full practice is a great sign for his status from a conditioning standpoint. It’s possible the Browns slowplay Judkins as he didn’t get a training camp. We wouldn’t be relying on an instant Week 2 impact. But he is worth picking up and holding as a potential bell-cow back once the Browns are actually ready to use him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-d214-a3b9-3e7d6be10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-d5f6-abfd-bb7df9030000</link>
      <description>Taylor dealt with a high-ankle sprain during training camp and Jets head coach Aaron Glenn told reporters that Taylor recently injured the same ankle. The full diagnosis was not shared though. Taylor’s return to limited participation is a good sign. Taylor is only a bench stash at this point, having earned just one target in his NFL debut last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-d5f6-abfd-bb7df9030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Sauce Gardner (groin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a77-da68-ad9d-ff7f42e90000</link>
      <description>Gardner dealt with a reported calf injury in August before appearing on the Week 1 injury report with a fibula issue. He practiced in full yesterday and was not on the injury report at all. The development suggests Gardner suffered the injury in practice today, but its severity is currently unknown. The Jets are tasked with containing the Bills’ passing game this weekend. Hopefully, Gardner is able to practice in some capacity tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a77-da68-ad9d-ff7f42e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Josh Reynolds (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-da68-ad9d-ff7b54380000</link>
      <description>Reynolds is not fantasy-relevant but the Jets already possessed a terribly thin receiving corps. His three targets ranked second on the team last week. The Thursday downgrade makes it unlikely that he suits up against the Bills this weekend. Garrett Wilson should again comfortably pace the Jets in targets once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-da68-ad9d-ff7b54380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a80-dc44-a9d9-3fe6a7460000</link>
      <description>Bowers is “hoping to play” in Week 2 against the Chargers, but said that “we’ll see how it’s feeling throughout the week.” The Raiders are understandably giving Bowers an extra day off, with this week’s game scheduled for Monday night. The elite TE1’s practice participation on Friday and Saturday can tell us far more about his availability than today’s absence. In the meantime, for those who currently have Bowers in their starting lineup, stashing No. 2 TE Michael Mayer on fantasy benches is worthwhile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a80-dc44-a9d9-3fe6a7460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
