<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 01:29:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught all four of his targets for 89 yards and two touchdowns in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb65-d8cf-affb-ff6febb60000</link>
      <description>Watson operated as the team’s top wideout in this game. His four targets were tied for a team-high. His elite efficiency allowed him to blow by the test of the team’s wideouts in terms of production. The home-run hitter went yard again this week by taking a routine slant 41 yards to the house in the third quarter. That was after he scored a 23-yard touchdown in the first half. Watson won’t find the big play every week, but his involvement is trending in the right direction just as the fantasy playoffs are getting underway. Watson will enter the WR3 mix next week despite a tough matchup with the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb65-d8cf-affb-ff6febb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 20 times for 86 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears, adding two catches for six yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb6c-d005-a9bf-fb7cc85f0000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Jacobs soaked up volume and dished out body blows, drawing defenders into the box to open up shot plays for Jordan Love. Per usual, it worked. Love threw three touchdowns, all from more than 20 yards out, and Jacobs cashed in at the goal line late in the game. His touchdown would ultimately prove to be a game-winner. Jacobs will keep his spot in the RB1 ranks next week, even with a tough Denver run defense on tap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb6c-d005-a9bf-fb7cc85f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught all four of his targets for 31 yards in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb74-d005-a9bf-fb7425370000</link>
      <description>Reed also turned two rush attempts into 22 yards. Matt LaFleur was eager to get Reed involved early in the game. Jordan Love’s first throw of the day went to Reed. One of his rush attempts also came on the first drive and he caught another pass later in the drive. Reed wound up running just over 60 percent of the available routes on the day and tied for a team-high in targets. After missing over two months with foot and shoulder injuries, this was as good a role as fantasy managers could hope for in his first game back. He will sit in the WR4 ranks for his Week 15 date with the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb74-d005-a9bf-fb7425370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs failed to catch either of his targets in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb7a-da9b-a9bf-ff7ffe010000</link>
      <description>With Christian Watson emerging as the Packers’ No. 1 receiver and Jayde Reed back in the mix, Doubs simply couldn’t earn targets in a suddenly-crowded receiver room. Things have been trending in this direction for a while. Doubs most recently topped 23 yards in Week 11 and his last game with more than four catches came in Week 8. He can safely be dropped in all 12-team fantasy formats heading into Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb7a-da9b-a9bf-ff7ffe010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 3-of-4 targets for 11 yards in the Broncos’ Week 14 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb82-d8cf-affb-ffaa67130000</link>
      <description>Franklin had a forgettable Week 14 showing. He may have banged the left side of his hip while being leveled by Raiders S Isaiah Pola-Mao on a downfield incompletion, but Franklin returned after a play or two. Franklin’s most consequential play occurred on the Broncos’ third drive, when he bobbled a reception on 4th-and-3. He initially met the ball while in first-down territory but was knocked backward as he was securing the catch and the officials ultimately ruled him down behind the first-down marker. It was inconsequential for fantasy purposes. Franklin is a risky FLEX against the Packers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb82-d8cf-affb-ffaa67130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 4-of-4 targets for 32 yards in the Broncos’ Week 14 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb59-d8cf-affb-ff7bcbc90000</link>
      <description>Bryant produced a couple of chunk gains via leaping grabs in this one, though he unfortunately failed to secure the one target that really mattered. The Raiders turned the ball over on downs with three seconds left in the second quarter, giving the Broncos possession on the Raiders’ 44-yard line. Broncos QB Bo Nix uncorked an on-target pass that Bryant high-pointed in the end zone. Unfortunately, Bryant only pawed at it with both hands, and the pass fell to the ground, incomplete. Bryant remains stuck on the boom-bust FLEX spectrum against the Packers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb59-d8cf-affb-ff7bcbc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 1-of-1 targets for five yards in the Broncos’ Week 14 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb83-d005-a9bf-fbb7b9520000</link>
      <description>Mims’ receiving role is almost a non-factor, but the shifty wide receiver did manage to return a second-quarter punt for a 48-yard touchdown, marking his first such trip to the end zone. Mims also rushed once for two yards. He does not need to be rostered in re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb83-d005-a9bf-fbb7b9520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden failed to catch his only targets in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb81-da9b-a9bf-ff8d13ac0000</link>
      <description>Golden was active for the first time since Week 11. He has missed the previous two games because of a wrist issue and missed time with a shoulder injury before Week 11. The Packers barely played him this week, putting him on the field for just four routes. Bo Melton ran five routes and came down with a 45-yard touchdown on his only catch of the day. It’s hard to say how much of the Packers’ decision to limit Golden’s role was based on his health. Fantasy managers, however, don’t need to get bogged down in the specifics. Golden is not on the fantasy radar for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb81-da9b-a9bf-ff8d13ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 2-of-4 targets for 22 yards in the Packers’ Week 14 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb8c-d8cf-affb-ffae0beb0000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Musgrave, along with Christian Watson and Jayden Reed, led the Packers in targets. The bad news is that Matt LaFleur deployed a three-headed committee at tight end. Musgrave, Josh Whyle, and Josh Fitzpatrick all run between 30 and 40 percent of the routes. Until Musgrave separates from the pack, he will be on the outside of the TE2 ranks looking in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb8c-d8cf-affb-ffae0beb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 2-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Broncos’ Week 14 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb8f-d77b-adfa-fb8f403d0000</link>
      <description>Engram caught his first pass of the day on a six-yard slant route during the Broncos’ third drive, at which point the broadcast began pouring out their large amount of pre-game notes on the sporadically involved pass catcher. He managed just one more reception thereafter. Engram is a moderate TE2 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb8f-d77b-adfa-fb8f403d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
