<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:05:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes A.J. Brown will seek a trade this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2956-d355-a5bd-af5656560000</link>
      <description>Berman ominously writes “it might be difficult to put toothpaste back in this tube, and there’s too much smoke here for me to answer this question differently,” though he admits that this remains just a guess. Brown figures to be one of the major turning points of the offseason for both the Eagles and the entirety of the NFL. None of the smoke that has come out about the relationship between the Eagles and Brown has looked encouraging for him staying in Philadelphia, and GM Howie Roseman would only resort to vague hypotheticals about how hard it is to find great players when asked about a potential Brown trade after the Eagles were eliminated from the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2956-d355-a5bd-af5656560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes Dallas Goedert will “play elsewhere” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-295c-d355-a5bd-af5caabf0000</link>
      <description>Goedert and the Eagles danced around a separation for most of last offseason, including trade rumors around the NFL Draft, but Philadelphia couldn’t find a real replacement for the 31-year-old tight end. An impending free agent, we’d expect Goedert to have an interesting market but he might struggle to land a multi-year deal considering his advanced age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-295c-d355-a5bd-af5caabf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes believes Jacoby Brissett is “a potential trade target” for the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2980-d042-afbc-7dd218010000</link>
      <description>Brissett checks the boxes of “has worked for Frank Reich before” and “is a functional NFL quarterback.” The real question is: Why would the Cardinals give him up? He averaged 240.4 yards per start and threw 23 touchdowns in just 12 starts. Arizona has reportedly been more interested in moving on from Murray than Brissett, who GM Monti Ossenfort drafted in New England and made a priority to sign last offseason. We’d be surprised if the Jets could do this without getting fleeced by Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2980-d042-afbc-7dd218010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants hired NFL chief football administrative officer Dawn Aponte as their vice president.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-298e-d629-a1bc-b99f3d430000</link>
      <description>Aponte was interviewed for the Chargers GM job in 2024 and also has worked for the Dolphins, Browns, and Jets. Her top experience level with the Dolphins was as executive VP of football administration, so it’s likely this role will be somewhat similar to that one. The NFL will have someone else reading draft cards on Day 2, sadly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-298e-d629-a1bc-b99f3d430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) said he is confident he will play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ab-d042-afbc-7dfb25d20000</link>
      <description>Spillane missed time late in the regular season with the ankle issue. He played in all three playoff games but aggravated the injury during the AFC Championship game. Despite missing some time in practice, it sounds like he isn’t at risk of missing the biggest game of the year. That’s good news for New England. Spillane totaled 97 combined tackles, two interceptions, and one sack in 13 regular season games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ab-d042-afbc-7dfb25d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo called Raiders interim offensive coordinator Greg Olson a “name to watch” for the Eagles’ quarterbacks coach position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-29f6-d89c-a1be-afff9fcc0000</link>
      <description>Scot Loeffler is currently Philly’s quarterbacks coach, but it’s possible the Eagles let him go, allowing new OC Sean Mannion to pick his replacement. In a similar vein, Olson should be let go by the Raiders once they land Klint Kubiak as their next head coach. Mannion previously played under Olson in Seattle. Per Garafolo’s sources, Mannion would be interested in reuniting with his coach in Philly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-29f6-d89c-a1be-afff9fcc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers GM Brian Gutekunst said Jordan Love did not require any offseason surgeries or procedures.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a05-d355-a5bd-af5545700000</link>
      <description>Love underwent surgery on his left thumb during training camp ahead of the 2025 season. The issue cropped up in the middle of the year but never seemed to cause him much trouble. Love also injured his non-throwing shoulder. He, again, did not miss any time. Love has battled through numerous injuries over the past two seasons. The good news is that, as of now, none of them are lingering into 2026. He should have a normal offseason routine as he and the Packers look to avenge their Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a05-d355-a5bd-af5545700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Steelers are finalizing a deal to hire Vikings pass game coordinator Brian Angelichio as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a0d-d629-a1bc-ba1da0490000</link>
      <description>Angelichio served as the tight ends coach under Mike McCarthy in Green Bay for three years. He has been in the NFL for nearly two decades and has held the role of tight ends coach for almost his entire pro coaching career, spanning six teams. He also coached college football at Pitt, making this a homecoming of sorts. He now returns to Pittsburgh for the first offensive coordinator gig of his career. It’s safe to assume that McCarthy will serve as the team’s play-caller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a0d-d629-a1bc-ba1da0490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Ravens will not retain quarterbacks coach Tee Martin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a28-d042-afbc-7ffa58cb0000</link>
      <description>Martin joined the Ravens in 2021 as a wide receivers coach. He was eventually promoted to quarterbacks coach and, as Schultz notes, was one of the people closest to Lamar Jackson in the organization. With Jesse Minter replacing John Harbaugh as the head coach and Declan Doyle taking over as OC, Martin will be replaced by a hire from the new braintrust. Martin received several head coaching interviews over the year, including meetings with the Commanders and Lions a month ago, so there should be plenty of interest in him this offseason. It would not be surprising to see Martin follow John Harbaugh to New York, potentially in the same role, for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a28-d042-afbc-7ffa58cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired former Jets offensive coordinator Nathaniel Hackett as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a32-d629-a1bc-ba3f6ecf0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins tabbed Hackett as their quarterbacks coach earlier in the offseason. With the Cardinals offering him a better position, Hackett will instead join Mike LaFleur in Arizona. The two have never worked together directly, but Hackett spent three years under Matt LaFleur as Green Bay’s offensive coordinator. He also rejoined the Packers as a defensive analyst in 2025. Hackett has largely flamed out since his first stint in Green Bay. His offenses never finished better than 24th in scoring across two seasons as the Jets’ OC and one as the Broncos’ head coach. As long as LaFleur is the one calling plays, this hire shouldn’t be viewed too negatively, even if it’s clearly based on his familiarity with the system as opposed to his recent track record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a32-d629-a1bc-ba3f6ecf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
