<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d7-d82c-a79a-f3d781120000</link>
      <description>Horn and LB Claudin Cherelus both did not practice due to concussions suffered in Week 12. It will be a tall task to pass protocol to play in Week 13. Also not practicing was LB Christian Rozeboom (hip/hamstring). The Panthers will enter Week 13 against the Rams banged up defensively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d7-d82c-a79a-f3d781120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers OG Chandler Zavala (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d9-d90e-a9da-dfdfc71d0000</link>
      <description>Zavala suffered the calf injury in Panthers’ Week 12 loss to the 49ers and starts out the week not practicing. Also out was C Cade Mays (ankle). Jake Curhan and Austin Corbett are in line to start for Zavala and Mays, respectively, if neither can play in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d9-d90e-a9da-dfdfc71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams EDGE Byron Young (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2dc-db57-afda-d6fe56d10000</link>
      <description>Rams S Kamren Kinchens (shoulder) also did not practice. Both Young and Kinchens are starters and key contributors to the Rams defense, so losing both would leave the team short-handed against the Panthers in Week 13. They will need to log practice time in order to have a chance at playing on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2dc-db57-afda-d6fe56d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Derrick Brooks upheld Panthers S Tre’von Moehrig’s one-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2df-d6c4-abfb-d6df307e0000</link>
      <description>Moehrig was suspended for punching 49ers WR Jauan Jennings in the groin in the Panthers’ loss to the 49ers on Monday night. He appealed the suspension, but hearing officer Derrick Brooks, jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA, denied his appeal and upheld the suspension. Moehrig will now miss Week 13 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2df-d6c4-abfb-d6df307e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs (knee) feels “pretty close to 100 percent” for Week 13’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5b8-d82c-a79a-f7bcb7900000</link>
      <description>If true, fantasy managers can expect Jacobs to see his full assortment of touches. After missing Week 12’s game against the Vikings, Jacobs will suit up for a Thanksgiving tilt with the Lions, who rank 11th in total rushing yards allowed but sixth in yards per carry allowed (3.9). Despite the Lions profiling as a tough matchup, Jacobs will be a near must-start for those rostering him this week. Backup Emanuel Wilson isn’t expected to have much standalone value, but remains a high-upside stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5b8-d82c-a79a-f7bcb7900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated CB Jaylon Johnson from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5ce-d82c-a79a-f7def7dc0000</link>
      <description>Johnson and fellow corner Kyler Gordon will both be activated in time for Week 13’s game against the Eagles, giving the Bears two key members of their secondary. Johnson (groin) hasn’t played since Week 2’s game against the Lions, but has totaled six interceptions and 18 pass breakups since 2023. He should provide an immediate boost to a secondary that ranks 21st in yards allowed and 29th in yards per attempt this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5ce-d82c-a79a-f7def7dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated CB Kyler Gordon from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c611-d82c-a79a-f7957b810000</link>
      <description>Gordon has been dealing with a hamstring injury this season and has appeared in just two games as a result. The fourth-year corner will join Jaylon Johnson in returning to the Bears’ secondary ahead of Week 13’s game against the Eagles, and is coming off a 2024 campaign in which he earned his highest PFF coverage grade of 76.0 while allowing just 472 yards and one touchdown on 57 targets while breaking up six passes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c611-d82c-a79a-f7957b810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Steelers expect Aaron Rodgers to play in Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c618-d90e-a9da-df1f90a70000</link>
      <description>Rodgers started the practice week as a DNP. We’ll see if his status changes at all come Thursday, but this isn’t the first time we’ve heard the Steelers expect Rodgers back for Week 13. His status remains one to watch until the team releases its final injury report on Friday, but Rodgers appears to be trending in the right direction by all accounts, despite Wednesday’s DNP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c618-d90e-a9da-df1f90a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared C Graham Glasgow, S Kerby Joseph, EDGE Joshua Paschal, WR Kalif Raymond, TE Brock Wright, OL Miles Frazier, DL Mekhi Wingo, and DL Tyler Lacy inactive for Week 13 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c624-d90e-a9da-df2f32cb0000</link>
      <description>Key players like Glasgow, Joseph, Paschal, and Wright were all ruled out before Thursday’s game, so this doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Lions will hope to get most of these players back after some extended rest. The good news, however, is that Terrion Arnold and Penei Sewell will both be active after entering the day as questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c624-d90e-a9da-df2f32cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared WR Matthew Golden (wrist) inactive for Week 13 against the Lions</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c62e-d82c-a79a-f7be04da0000</link>
      <description>Despite being limited in practice throughout the week and listed as questionable on Wednesday, Golden will be sidelined for Thursday’s Thanksgiving Day tilt. The rookie receiver has caught 24 passes for 286 scoreless yards this season. In addition to Golden the Packers also declared LB Quay Walker, DE Lukas Van Ness, DT Karl Brooks, WR Savion Williams, CB Nate Hobbs, and OL Donovan Jennings inactive for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c62e-d82c-a79a-f7be04da0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
