<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said he hopes QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9afa-d6e9-af9d-9afadb240000</link>
      <description>It’s become clear the Vikings will take their sweet time with getting McCarthy back into the lineup, if he gets his job back when he’s fully cleared. McCarthy is not wearing a boot or brace and is reportedly OK after his mysterious Week 2 ankle injury, which was only revealed after the game. Look for Carson Wentz to start this week against the Browns after completing 67 percent of his passes for four touchdowns and two interceptions over the past two outings. McCarthy should be on waiver wires for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9afa-d6e9-af9d-9afadb240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings OT Brian O’Neill (knee) is considered week to week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b25-deb6-a7fd-dbff4e050000</link>
      <description>O’Neill appears unlikely to suit up for the Vikings this week against a ferocious Browns front seven. The Vikings could be without multiple offensive line starters this week in London. Pro Football Focus grades O’Neill as 52nd out of 197 qualifying offensive linemen in pass blocking. Carson Wentz could face considering pressure against Myles Garrett and the Browns this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b25-deb6-a7fd-dbff4e050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) is questionable for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b39-d95b-addb-fb7fec3f0000</link>
      <description>Purdy was an estimated DNP on Monday ahead of the Niners’ Thursday night game against the Rams. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said Purdy’s status remains “up in the air,” with Mac Jones ready to start for the 49ers if Purdy sits. “We will take every precaution to make sure Brock’s all right,” 49ers general manager John Lynch said, adding that Purdy had follow-up MRI exams on his toe following Week 4’s game against Jacksonsville. “I think he is. Now it’s just a matter of, can he turn it around on a short week?” Jones, meanwhile is dealing with a nagging knee injury that could limit his mobility. The Rams defense will be a good fantasy option against the injury-marred Niners offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b39-d95b-addb-fb7fec3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed WR Robbie Chosen, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b86-dca3-a9fb-bf9fbead0000</link>
      <description>The well-traveled journeyman will join the Washington practice squad ahead of Week 5. The Commanders are dealing with a spate of receiver injuries, including Terry McLaurin (quad) and Noah Brown (knee, groin). Chosen would only play a rotational role if he’s active for Week 5. He should remain on waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b86-dca3-a9fb-bf9fbead0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) is questionable for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b96-deb6-a7fd-dbdf1d570000</link>
      <description>Pearsall exited Sunday’s game against the Jaguars with a knee injury and did not return. He was estimated to have missed practice this week ahead of the Niners’ Thursday night clash with the Rams. Fantasy managers should prepare for be without Pearsall, who’s leading the 49ers in both targets and air yards. His absence would be a major hit to Brock Purdy if he’s able to play through a nagging toe injury that he aggravated on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b96-deb6-a7fd-dbdf1d570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OC Nick Holz said he expects TE Gunnar Helm’s “opportunities to increase.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b98-dca3-a9fb-bf99e2490000</link>
      <description>This isn’t going to do a major number on most of your fantasy squads, but an increase in Helm’s reps would likely render Chig Okonkwo unplayable in the TE2 sphere. Helm has 92 snaps in four weeks and Okonkwo is coming off a season-low 35 snaps against the Texans in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b98-dca3-a9fb-bf99e2490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed OL Jarrett Kingston off the Panthers practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba1-d95b-addb-fbe7f12e0000</link>
      <description>Kingston will replace Cam Robinson on the active roster. The 2024 sixth-rounder was active for seven games with the Panthers last year, but had just one offensive snap. It means he has less negative NFL tape in 2024-2025 than most Texans offensive linemen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba1-d95b-addb-fbe7f12e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said LB Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) and Brian O’Neill (knee) won’t practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba8-d95b-addb-fbeee1a70000</link>
      <description>It would appear to be implicit in that statement that will neither will play in Week 5 against the Browns, though it wasn’t explicitly said. O’Connell said IR is not a consideration for O’Neill and that the team is “evaluating every avenue and all options to get” Van Ginkel “100%.” Reading between the lines, it seems like an IR stint is still in play for Van Ginkel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9ba8-d95b-addb-fbeee1a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Baltimore Sun’s Brian Wacker reports Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is “likely” to miss Week 5’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bb5-d95b-addb-fbf726db0000</link>
      <description>He adds per one of his sources that given “the nature of the injury, he also could be out for up to 2-3 weeks.” The Ravens have a Week 7 bye, but it sounds like Jackson-reliant fantasy managers should be going ahead with waiver claims on the idea that Jackson won’t play in Week 5 and perhaps Week 6 as well. We’re sure this will be one of several Lamar updates this week unless John Harbaugh rules him out early on Wednesday. Cooper Rush would take over as the starter at quarterback if Jackson were to be sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bb5-d95b-addb-fbf726db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jets RB Braelon Allen (knee) suffered and MCL sprain and will likely land on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bc2-d95b-addb-fbc6c4270000</link>
      <description>Isaiah Davis will likely absorb some snaps, but this should be great news for Breece Hall-reliant managers as Allen’s goal-line/early-down role would seem to fit Hall much better than Davis. Allen is still looking at different opinions on the injury, meaning we’ll probably get an update with a firm timetable when he’s actually placed on injured reserve. For the next few weeks at least, though, Hall is likely to get an uptick in usage that should put him in a good place to showcase his skills ahead of the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bc2-d95b-addb-fbc6c4270000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
