<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) is likely to return to practice next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d005-a9bf-d97c3d560000</link>
      <description>Johnson is set to miss his fourth consecutive game in Week 15 against the Raiders, which was his original target for return. The 35-year-old right tackle is dealing with a Lisfranc sprain, but Rapoport passes along that Johnson will likely return to practice next week and depending on how that goes he could be active against the Commanders in Week 16 or Bills in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d005-a9bf-d97c3d560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers RB Emanuel Wilson (illness) plans to play against the Broncos in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d55-d1bc-a3fb-9d75362a0000</link>
      <description>With Josh Jacobs (knee) expected to play, Wilson’s availability doesn’t appear to be crucial for the first round of the fantasy playoffs. He’s still listed as questionable. The team already elevated Pierre Strong from the practice squad and he could fill in as the backup if either of the Packers’ top two backs are ultimately ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d55-d1bc-a3fb-9d75362a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) is expected to play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5a-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e1c2a0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs is still listed as questionable with a knee injury. He’s missed one game already this season because of his balky knee, but is expected to play against the Broncos in Week 15. Jacobs’ backup Emanuel Wilson is also questionable with an illness, though he plans to play. In a tough matchup at less than 100 percent, Jacobs is a midrange RB2 in the first round of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5a-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e1c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) isn’t expected to play against the Cardinals in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5e-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e4f700000</link>
      <description>Chubb practiced just once this week, in a limited fashion on Friday. The 29-year-old running back is still listed as questionable with a rib injury, but isn’t expected to play, according to Schefter. Woody Marks is set up nicely for a bell cow role in a good matchup against the Cardinals. Marks is a solid RB2 in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5e-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e4f700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) is expected to play against the Texans in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d62-d1bc-a3fb-9d66249b0000</link>
      <description>Demercado has been sidelined since suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 11. He’s expected to be active, according to Schefter, after getting in three limited practices during the week. Bam Knight has consistently out-touched Michael Carter in recent weeks and even if Demercado is active, he doesn’t figure to command even a third of the backfield touches in his first game back. None of the Cardinals’ running backs are particularly enticing against the Texans defense in the fantasy playoffs and Knight is truly the only usable option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d62-d1bc-a3fb-9d66249b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (illness) is expected to play against the Giants in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d67-d77b-adfb-dfe747960000</link>
      <description>Samuel missed practice with an illness Friday and landed on the injury report as questionable. The 29-year-old receiver is expected to play, according to Schefter. He’ll be in the WR3 mix in the first round of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d67-d77b-adfb-dfe747960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez (groin) is a game-time decision against the Giants in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d6a-d8cf-affb-bd6a0bd50000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez missed practice Wednesday before getting in two limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. He’s a game-time decision, according to Schefter. Rodriguez will test his groin pre-game to see if he can play. If active, he’s somewhat of a risky play in a great matchup against the Giants. Even when Rodriguez is 100 percent, he splits backfield touches with Jacory Croskey-Merritt and Jeremy McNichols. It wouldn’t be a surprise to see his touches scaled back given his condition. If Rodriguez is ruled out, Croskey-Merritt is a plug-and-play option in a fantastic matchup against the incredibly weak Giants run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d6a-d8cf-affb-bd6a0bd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane was removed from the injury report ahead of Week 15’s game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d88-d1bc-a3fb-9dacd48b0000</link>
      <description>Achane had been on the injury report with a rib injury, but is all systems go against the Steelers in Week 15. The 24-year-old running back had 92 yards and a touchdown before suffering the injury against the Jets last week. Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel told reporters he decided to hold Achane out and that he could’ve returned against the Jets. Achane is a locked in RB1 in the first week of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d88-d1bc-a3fb-9dacd48b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Darnell Washington cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 15 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d8f-d77b-adfb-df8f1b370000</link>
      <description>Washington practiced in a limited fashion on Thursday and Friday. The 24-year-old tight end cleared concussion protocol Sunday morning and is set to play against the Dolphins on Monday Night Football in Week 15. With all three of the Steelers’ tight ends available Monday, none of them will be fantasy viable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d8f-d77b-adfb-df8f1b370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d92-d77b-adfb-df93d7bc0000</link>
      <description>Austin popped up on the injury report Friday with a calf injury that caused him to be limited in practice. The 26-year-old receiver was back to a full participant in practice Saturday and enters the matchup with the Dolphins without an injury designation. Austin isn’t worth rostering in most fantasy leagues with new additions Marquez Valdes-Scantling and Adam Thielen passing him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d92-d77b-adfb-df93d7bc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
