<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:02:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos OL Mike McGlinchey (shoulder) is questionable for Denver’s Week 15 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1487-d005-a9bf-dcb735790000</link>
      <description>McGlinchey popped up on the injury report as a Friday DNP after being healthy earlier in the week. Not auspicious. Geron Christian and Frank Crum are the backup tackles on the roster for Denver, and one of them could be pressed into service on Sunday if McGlinchey can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1487-d005-a9bf-dcb735790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns DT Mason Graham (rib) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148d-d77b-adfb-de8ffd560000</link>
      <description>Graham was limited on Friday, but didn’t practice on either Wednesday or Thursday. He did play through the injury in Week 14 against the Titans. The rookie No. 5 overall pick has a 68.8 PFF defensive grade in 572 snaps this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148d-d77b-adfb-de8ffd560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) is questionable to play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148e-d77b-adfb-de8fcb150000</link>
      <description>Add backup RB Emanuel Wilson wherever available. Jacobs is seemingly on track to play on Sunday, but it cannot hurt to be safe. Wilson operated as the team’s featured running back with Jacobs sidelined against the Vikings a few weeks ago, rushing 28 times for 107 yards and two touchdowns. The Broncos’ elite defense will put up a fight, but Wilson would be a volume-based RB2 if Jacobs cannot play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148e-d77b-adfb-de8fcb150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB MarShawn Lloyd (calf/hamstring) is listed with a new injury and has been ruled out for Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1488-d005-a9bf-dcbc1f640000</link>
      <description>Brutal. The Packers placed Lloyd on injured reserve with a hamstring injury in late August. He picked up a calf injury while on the injured reserve list, delaying his return. The Packers opened his 21-day practice window on December 1st. He resumed practicing in a limited capacity after that, but was sidelined today, and is now listed with a new hamstring injury. The development could jeopardize his rest-of-season availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1488-d005-a9bf-dcbc1f640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe40fa0000</link>
      <description>Golden is good to go for his fantasy-unfriendly role as a rotational wide receiver. Golden could catch a long pass, but he does not have the snap share requisite for season-long, re-draft FLEX consideration. He does not need to be rostered at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe40fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe3b400000</link>
      <description>Reed and WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) are ready to rock against the Broncos this week. Both players are forced to play efficiently thanks to the team’s deep receiving corps, but Reed can still be started in the FLEX. Wicks is a bit more volatile, but is capable of making big plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe3b400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (illness) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14b0-d77b-adfb-deb3e7f70000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey practiced fully on Friday after logging a limited session on Thursday. He can be treated as an elite RB1, per usual, against the Titans this week. He leads the NFL with 322 touches this season, boasting 59 missed tackles forced per PFF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14b0-d77b-adfb-deb3e7f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Darnell Washington (concussion) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e0-d77b-adfb-dee316cc0000</link>
      <description>That is unfortunate. One would hope to see Washington increase his participation every day, as he works his way through the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol. It is possible he stalled out in the third phase. Hopefully, he upgrades to full tomorrow and can be on the field when his team faces the Dolphins on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e0-d77b-adfb-dee316cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “certainly seems like” QB Philip Rivers will start for the Colts in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e4-d8cf-affb-bcee46860000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s segment broke no news, but he has ostensibly been working the phones since last night’s pre-game report. Rivers is taking “some” first-team reps and, per Rapoport, is throwing the football “well.” Rookie QB Riley Leonard would seemingly have a better chance of rushing his way to QB2 viability, but the Colts apparently prefer Rivers’ theoretical pocket-passing ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e4-d8cf-affb-bcee46860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the franchise tag is “potentially” in play for Falcons TE Kyle Pitts at the end of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</link>
      <description>Pitts is in the fifth and final year of his rookie contract. Last night, he caught 11-of-12 targets for 166 yards and three touchdowns in the Falcons’ Thursday Night Football victory over the Buccaneers. Before the game, Falcons owner Arthur Blank reportedly visited the NFL Network’s pre-game broadcast set. Rapoport followed up the visit with a televised report saying Blank will “evaluate” all football operations after the season. Although head coach Raheem Morris and general manager Terry Fontenot may end up being let go, Pitts may have played his way into a new contract, or at least a one-year deal on the lucrative franchise tag. Rapoport notes, though, that Pitts’ agent, David Mulugheta, “hates the franchise tag” and could play hardball in pursuit of a long-term deal. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
