<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833a-d6e9-af9d-8bba030d0000</link>
      <description>Jones continues through practice after re-injuring the PCL sprain he suffered during training camp, which is a great sign for his Week 4 availability. Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) is on track to play, so Jones is unlikely to be called upon. His expected availability helps insulate the 49ers’ pass catchers in fantasy, though, in the event that Purdy suffers a re-injury of some sort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833a-d6e9-af9d-8bba030d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that Terry McLaurin (quad) does not need to undergo surgery “as of right now.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffad460000</link>
      <description>Garafolo introduced the segment by lightheartedly referring to McLaurin’s “quad, hip, groin” injury, which affirms concerns that this injury is not necessarily limited to one singular muscle group. If McLaurin were to undergo surgery, it would potentially require “six-to-eight” weeks of recovery. McLaurin is currently not expected to play in Week 4 against the Falcons, but we will know for sure on Friday. Deebo Samuel will operate as the Commanders’ No. 1 wide receiver in McLaurin’s stead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffad460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence was forced from Seattle’s Week 4 game against the Cardinals with a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-83ef-d95b-addb-ebef3cb10000</link>
      <description>Initially announced with a thigh injury, Lawrence told the Amazon broadcast it was actually his quad. It’s almost certainly some sort of deep bruise. Lawrence was announced as doubtful early on then officially ruled out at halftime. The only good news is he has 10 days to get healthy for Week 5 against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-83ef-d95b-addb-ebef3cb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold completed 18-of-26 passes for 242 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ 23-20, Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8408-d95b-addb-ec4e84900000</link>
      <description>Darnold added a 24-yard rush. He also fumbled, but the Seahawks managed to recover. It was a nice overall night, but Darnold probably needed to hit another big throw or two. He found Jaxon Smith-Njigba zero times in the first half, for instance. The Seahawks had opportunities to bury the Cardinals early but couldn’t execute, allowing a 17-3 third quarter lead to turn into a late 20-20 mad dash. Thankfully for Seattle partisans, they had just enough time to get into field goal range for Jason Myers to kick a walk-off 52-yarder. Darnold is still taking sacks, but at a tolerable rate. He is playing efficient, largely pristine football as the Seahawks have gotten off to a 3-1 start. He is looking very unlikely to spike weeks in fantasy in an offense that wants to run the ball and is running low on passing-game weapons, but Week 5 against the Bucs is a potential shootout spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8408-d95b-addb-ec4e84900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyler Murray completed 27-of-41 passes for 200 yards, two touchdowns and two interceptions in the Cardinals’ 23-20, Week 4 loss to the Seahawks, adding five rushes for 41 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-840f-d6e9-af9d-8e9fe9990000</link>
      <description>It was the tale of two halves for Murray and the Cardinals, who were stunningly dreadful as they fell behind 14-3 in quarters one and two. They were lucky it was only an 11-point deficit as Murray completed 12-of-19 throws for 67 yards and both his picks. Each miscue was arguably the fault of Marvin Harrison Jr., who stopped his route on INT No. 1 and let a perfect pass bobble out of his hands on INT No. 2. MHJ appeared disconsolate as Murray seemed bewildered. Things finally clicked into gear after a bogus holding call turned a third quarter Seahawks touchdown into a field and 17-3 lead. Murray and MHJ went to work, eventually tying the game at 20 with 0:28 remaining. Seattle then promptly got into field goal position and kicked a 52-yarder to win it. Despite the late heroics, Murray was more dreadful than admirable, averaging fewer than five yards per pass for the second time in five days. Going full horizontal raid as he struggles to get on the same page with his No. 1 wideout, Murray is giving himself little chance of spiking weeks in fantasy. That being said, the Titans will be an appetizing Week 5 matchup on 10 days rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-840f-d6e9-af9d-8e9fe9990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 6-of-10 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8415-deb6-a7fd-d7df1d190000</link>
      <description>It would be inaccurate to say MHJ played a good game — of his four first half targets, he personally turned two of them into interceptions — but he saved himself from an all-time dreadful one by turning his six second half looks into 5/58/1. That included a 16-yard touchdown where he skied above Devon Witherspoon in the end zone. It was a badly, badly needed score for both team and player, as evidenced by the fact the second-year pro was emotional after catching it. Looking like he had zero confidence before the break, MHJ seemed freed by the Cardinals having to play faster as they attempted to erase a 17-3 third quarter deficit. He has still yet to come particularly close to 100 yards receiving this season, but this is now 2-of-4 on solid efforts. Arizona was expecting better than solid, of course. Perhaps they will get it in Week 5 against the hapless Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8415-deb6-a7fd-d7df1d190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Benson rushed eight times for 35 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 4 loss to the Seahawks, adding five receptions for 19 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-841a-d6e9-af9d-8e9ad7a50000</link>
      <description>Oh dear. Obviously not what you were signing up for if you paid a pretty FAAB penny for Benson following James Conner’s season-ending ankle injury, but Benson did have poor game flow to contend with. The Cards were down 14-3 at halftime following a host of miscues in the passing game. More concerning was the feared immediate re-emergence of Emari Demercado as a passing-down complement/two-minute drill back. Demercado handled just four touches, but one of them was a seven-yard touchdown reception with 0:28 remaining. It’s not surprising the Cards’ backfield looked a little different tonight than it did following Conner’s Week 3 injury — coaches always change it up with they actually have time to game plan — but this was still on the poorer end of the most likely outcomes. They now have 10 days to mull things over before a soft Week 5 date with the Titans. Benson will remain in the RB2 mix for that one, especially with bye weeks beginning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-841a-d6e9-af9d-8e9ad7a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker rushed 19 times for 81 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals, adding a 29-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8421-d6e9-af9d-8eb162850000</link>
      <description>As usual, Walker made sure his 20 touches were a journey, sprinting wildly every which direction as he ultimately produced a solid, efficient line. A solid, efficient line that didn’t include a touchdown, of course. Zach Charbonnet was the main man at the goal line, converting a short carry for a score and having another called back by a bogus Jaxon Smith-Njigba holding penalty. As has become the theme, Charbonnet was far less productive on his 14 handles, but it’s clear his work won’t be going away. The Seahawks’ coaching staff has a fixed vision of this backfield, one where they seem to trust Charbonnet a little more on the most critical downs even if he’s the less explosive back. Either way, Walker is getting enough work to remain an RB2 for Week 5 against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8421-d6e9-af9d-8eb162850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet rushed 12 times for 39 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals, adding two receptions for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8425-d6e9-af9d-8eb5b3060000</link>
      <description>Returning from a one-game absence with an apparently minor foot issue, Charbonnet converted a one-yard score in the second quarter after getting stuffed on an earlier goal-line tote. He appeared to have another score in the fourth frame, a sever-yarder, but it was called back by a bogus Jaxon Smith-Njigba holding penalty. Frustrating for Charbonnet managers, but a complete nightmare for Kenneth Walker III impresarios. KWIII didn’t come particularly close to the end zone this evening, rotating work with Charbonnet on early downs and mostly ceding passing-game work to his less efficient 1B back. Charbonnet is less efficient but has greater coaching staff trust in higher-leverage situations. That is for now at least. Maybe something changes in the 10 days Seattle has to prepare for Tampa. We still wouldn’t count on it, keeping Charbonnet locked in as a high-floor FLEX despite his paltry yards per carry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8425-d6e9-af9d-8eb5b3060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
