<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed RB Chase Edmonds, formerly of the Buccnaeers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e19-da67-a99f-cefdbe690000</link>
      <description>Edmonds last played a regular-season snap in 2023 with the Buccaneers. The 29-year-old running back suffered a season-ending knee injury last year toward the end of camp and did not draw much, if any, interest this offseason. This move is somewhat predictable, as Edmonds is a “system-knower” who spent three seasons (2019-2021) playing under offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury during their days in Arizona. It seems unlikely that Edmonds would make an immediate impact, but if he looks good in practice, he could eventually be elevated to the roster to serve in a third-down role. As far as fantasy is concerned, there’s no reason to stash Edmonds at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e19-da67-a99f-cefdbe690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans and DT Jeffery Simmons agreed to a revised contract for the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e34-d294-a19b-eef4c37f0000</link>
      <description>Simmons will receive a pay raise of $632,529 for the 2025 season, which, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, “stems from the 17th game check Simmons did not receive in 2023 under his previous contract.” Under this deal, Simmons becomes the first player to retroactively receive a bonus for a game that was not in a deal because his rookie contract was signed at a time when the league was still playing 16-game seasons. It would not be surprising if other players and their agents attempted to recoup some of this money on past deals in the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e34-d294-a19b-eef4c37f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson is out indefinitely with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e55-d294-a19b-eef592720000</link>
      <description>This isn’t the news a defense ranking last in YPA (9.2) allowed through the first two weeks of the season wants to hear. Johnson, a Pro Bowl corner, is still undergoing further evaluations, per Schefter, and the team is weighing whether or not surgery will be necessary to correct the issue. Johnson was sidelined throughout all of training camp with a groin injury, so it wouldn’t be surprising if this turns out to be something serious. We’ll likely have a clearer answer soon, but Johnson sounds like a virtual lock to miss Week 3’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e55-d294-a19b-eef592720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Steelers LB Alex Highsmith (ankle) “is not likely to be placed on IR.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e5a-d294-a19b-eefaa9910000</link>
      <description>Highsmith avoiding injured reserve would indicate that the Steelers believe he can return before missing the requisite four games required of any player placed on IR. The veteran linebacker exited Sunday’s game against the Seahawks after further aggravating an ankle injury he had suffered in Friday’s practice. Highsmith benefits from the Steelers having a Week 5 bye. Should he need only three weeks to recover, it’s possible he misses only two games and is back in action by Week 6 when the Steelers play host to the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e5a-d294-a19b-eefaa9910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed LB Denzel Perryman (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e5b-d294-a19b-eefbc8280000</link>
      <description>Perryman had already been ruled out for Week 2’s game against the Raiders, but now the veteran linebacker will miss at least the next four weeks and be eligible to return in Week 6 against the Dolphins. Perryman was injured in the Chargers’ season-opener against the Chiefs and was initially considered week-to-week. Back linebacker Try Dye is listed behind Perryman on the depth chart and looks like the early favorite to replace him for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e5b-d294-a19b-eefbc8280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Saints DT Vernon Broughton is expected to miss the remainder of the season with a hip injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e64-d294-a19b-eef4f5730000</link>
      <description>Broughton was a third-round pick of the Saints this offseason and made his pro debut in Week 2’s loss to the 49ers. The rookie lineman appeared on 24 defensive snaps, per PFF, and assisted on three tackles. According to Garafolo, the Saints are still seeking multiple opinions to see if surgery will be required to repair Broughton’s hip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e64-d294-a19b-eef4f5730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Kyle Van Noy could miss multiple games due to a hamstring injury he suffered in Week 2’s win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e75-dc44-a9d9-4f77ba680000</link>
      <description>This would be a brutal blow to a Ravens defense that was led by Van Noy’s 12.5 sacks last season. The veteran pass rusher exited Sunday’s game in the second quarter and did not return to the field, and could now miss multiple weeks with the injury. Fowler reports that Van Noy “is hoping the injury is short-term,” but we should have more clarity in the coming days. Van Noy has totaled four tackles in the two games he has appeared in this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e75-dc44-a9d9-4f77ba680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams placed CB Ahkello Witherspoon (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e78-dc44-a9d9-4f7e0dd80000</link>
      <description>He left Los Angeles’ Week 2 game against the Titans early with the injury and wound up playing just 16 snaps. Cobie Durant got the majority of the playing time in his stead as Emmanuel Forbes drew the start. Witherspoon will miss at least the next four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e78-dc44-a9d9-4f7e0dd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OL Kevin Zeitler (elbow) left Tennessee’s Week 2 game against the Rams and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe70da50000</link>
      <description>Blake Hance played in his stead. The Titans have now allowed 11 sacks in two games after emphasizing the offensive line this offseason. It was against two playoff teams from last year, but that sack pace has Cam Ward looking like someone to stream defenses against right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe70da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans told an in-house radio show that he would like to get Nick Chubb more touches.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e85-d294-a19b-eef5f7890000</link>
      <description>Chubb took 13 carries for 60 yards last week and seems primed to be a volume-heavy low-end RB2 or FLEX this week. He likely won’t play passing downs, so the Texans will need to be in good game scripts for Chubb to deliver. The Texans certainly seemed to like what they saw from Chubb in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e85-d294-a19b-eef5f7890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
