<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Tyjae Spears (ankle) is expected to play in Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b457-deb6-a7fd-f7df4ae50000</link>
      <description>Spears went down with an ankle injury during training camp and was placed on injured reserve to start the year. He returned to practice this week and the Titans activated him on Sunday, but they still listed him as questionable for today’s game. It seems like that was largely a procedural matter, as Spears is good to go. Expect a small role for the shifty back in his first game of 2025. Playing for a dysfunctional Titans offense, Spears isn’t on the fantasy radar for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b457-deb6-a7fd-f7df4ae50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Malik Nabers is expected to undergo surgery this week for a torn ACL and a torn meniscus.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b45b-deb6-a7fd-f7df078f0000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Nabers is expected to be back for the start of training camp. Per Schefter, the time off will also allow a partially torn labrum and a turf toe injury to heal. Nabers is seemingly dealing with some minor injury every week and the toe issue has been a problem since his days at LSU. As Schefter notes, Nabers will likely be the healthiest he has been since high school the next time we see him on a practice field. His injury was a crushing blow to fantasy managers, but it shouldn’t affect the broader outlook of his career. Wan’Dale Robinson will operate as the team’s top wideout for the remainder of the season. Darius Slayton will handle more work as an intermediate and deep threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b45b-deb6-a7fd-f7df078f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Brock Bowers has been playing through “a PCL injury and bone bruise on his knee that has impacted his performance.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b461-d95b-addb-fc6774810000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, doctors have told Bowers the only way to recover is rest, which he has been “unwilling to do.” This is a classic case of a player having too much dog in him. Bowers suffered the knee injuries in Week 1 against the Patriots and hasn’t looked right ever since. The issue has seemingly reached a breaking point with Bowers not expected to play versus the Colts this week. A week or more off appears to be what the young tight end needs, even if he doesn’t think so. Fantasy managers will be hoping Bowers gets his rest in Week 5 and looks like his usual self versus the Titans in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b461-d95b-addb-fc6774810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) is expected to play in Week 5 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b468-dca3-a9fb-bdf97bfe0000</link>
      <description>Johnson went down with a groin injury in Week 2 and has been out ever since. He is listed as questionable for Week 5. The rookie was playing a part-time role to start the year and will likely return to something similar for his first game back. Johnson had four pass break-ups and four tackles through two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b468-dca3-a9fb-bdf97bfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots DT Milton Williams (ankle) “should be good to go” for Week 5 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b46c-deb6-a7fd-f7ff368e0000</link>
      <description>Williams is officially listed as questionable after missing Thursday’s practice. He returned on Friday but did appear legitimately uncertain for tonight’s game. A free agent addition for the Pats this offseaosn, Williams has been a standout for Mike Vrabel in their first year in New England. Williams already has two sacks and five TFLs to his name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b46c-deb6-a7fd-f7ff368e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Rachaad White is expected to get the “vast majority of carries” in Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b470-d95b-addb-fc76d2790000</link>
      <description>Bucky Irving is out with a foot injury, leaving the starting gig up for grabs. Third-string running back Sean Tucker has touched the ball once this year, while White has consistently spelled Irving when needed. Per Pelissero, the team also has a plan for Tucker, though it sounds like a minor role at most. White is locked in as an RB2 for his first start of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b470-d95b-addb-fc76d2790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “there is a real chance” Lamar Jackson (hamstring) misses Week 6 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b475-dca3-a9fb-bdfd27b20000</link>
      <description>Jackson did not practice this week before being ruled out on Friday. The Ravens get their bye in Week 7, so one more missed game would give the superstar passer plenty of time to fully recover. Barring a surprise next week, we expect the Ravens to take this approach with Jackson’s hamstring issue, meaning Cooper Rush will draw two starts for the team. Rush is a solid game-manager, but nothing more than a low-end QB2 for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b475-dca3-a9fb-bdfd27b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports there is “no indication” the Eagles will trade A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b478-d95b-addb-fc7eedb90000</link>
      <description>Brown has once again taken to social media, posting more cryptic nonsense in the midst of his team’s inability to generate passing output. He has topped 27 receiving yards in one of four games this year, though the Eagles are 4-0. It has naturally stirred some scuttlebutt about a potential trade, but Garafolo was quick to rule that out. He did note that teams have been calling the Eagles to ask about Brown’s availability for months. The Eagles are in a win-now window coming off a Super Bowl win over the Chiefs. Trading Brown would make no sense for them at this time. He isn’t going anywhere this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b478-d95b-addb-fc7eedb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “the expectation is that” Shedeur Sanders will play at some point this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b480-d95b-addb-fcc625680000</link>
      <description>Sanders remains the QB3, now directly behind Joe Flacco, who was benched for Dillon Gabriel this week. Per Rapoport, the Browns have seen consistent improvement from Shedeur. The reason they didn’t make him the backup was that they want to have a specific game plan prepared for him whenever he does take the field. Gabriel will get at least a few weeks as the starter, but it sounds like the Browns are more than willing to make another quarterback change if the rookie struggles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b480-d95b-addb-fcc625680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) was downgraded to doubtful for Week 5 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b485-d6e9-af9d-be95b8990000</link>
      <description>Decker didn’t practice once this week before being listed as questionable. That normally leads us to believe a player won’t suit up on Sunday, but Taylor previously played in Week 3 after missing all three practices. It’s possible Decker’s shoulder issue is getting worse, causing the team to give him a week off. Giovani Manu is likely to take his spot in the lineup versus Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b485-d6e9-af9d-be95b8990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
