<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Gibson rushed seven times for 28 yards in the Patriots’ Week 3 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e05-dfde-a1bd-7e8d99830000</link>
      <description>Rhamondre Stevenson put the ball on the ground twice. The Pats replaced him with Gibson following his second fumble of the day. Gibson lasted two carries before coughing up a fumble of his own. Rookie TreVeyon Henderson saw the bulk of the snaps after Gibson’s fumble. Gibson had a chance to carve out a larger role after Stevenson was benched. He blew the opportunity and is unlikely to be a relevant fantasy option for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e05-dfde-a1bd-7e8d99830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 3-of-4 targets for 63 yards in the Raiders’ Week 3 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e06-dfde-a1bd-7e8f53270000</link>
      <description>On the bright side, Meyers has gone for 60-plus yards in each of his three games this season. The four targets he saw on Sunday marked his fewest of the season, but in a game where the Raiders had four three-and-outs, targets will prove hard to come by. It also doesn’t help that Tre Tucker and Geno Smith were vibing late, as the two combined for 145 yards and three touchdowns through the air. Meyers, whose longest play came on a 45-yard strike on the first play of the game, was averaging 11.5 targets per game heading into this one. We would expect him to earn a few more looks in Week 4’s game against the Bears, where he will be on the WR3 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e06-dfde-a1bd-7e8f53270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 16 times for 56 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 3 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e04-dfde-a1bd-7e8d29490000</link>
      <description>We’d like to say that Etienne knifed expertly through the Texans defense, but they essentially allowed him to score on a low-effort carry to get the ball back with more time on the clock. Fantasy managers will take it! Etienne took 38 of 70 offensive snaps and remains locked in a fantasy RB2 lead back role with Jacksonville. He’ll look to extend his scoring streak to three next week as the Jaguars try to move to 3-1 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e04-dfde-a1bd-7e8d29490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans caught 4-of-8 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in a Week 3 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e08-dfde-a1bd-7e8d83cf0000</link>
      <description>Evans was battling with Sauce Gardner for much of the day and also drew a crucial holding penalty on a deep pass to help convert a 3rd and 30 in the first quarter. Unfortunately, Evans left the game with a hamstring injury in the fourth quarter and was seen throwing his helmet in frustration as he limped into the tunnel. Given Evans’ history of hamstring injuries, he may be sidelined for a couple of weeks, which would leave Emeka Egbuka as the team’s top receiving option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e08-dfde-a1bd-7e8d83cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle rushed 10 times for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 3 win over the Falcons, adding one reception for eight yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e08-d6a5-adff-fecd1b660000</link>
      <description>Dowdle rotated in as the second running back to Chuba Hubbard, playing about 40 percent of the team’s offensive snaps. He remains involved, getting the occasional drive to himself in the Panthers backfield. His touchdown came on a goal-line carry in the fourth quarter after Chuba Hubbard was tackled at the one-yard line on the previous play. Dowdle has handcuff value, but is unlikely to have consistent stand alone fantasy value moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e08-d6a5-adff-fecd1b660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sterling Shepard caught 4-of-5 targets for 80 yards in a Week 3 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d2aef0000</link>
      <description>Shepard was used as the team’s third receiver for much of the game, but stepped into a starting boundary role late in the fourth quarter with Mike Evans (hamstring) in the locker room. Shepard made a huge catch on that drive and showed good shifitness after the catch to get the Bucs into field goal range. With Chris Godwin still unlikely to return by Week 4 and Evans looking likely to miss a couple of weeks, Shepard could slide into a starting role for the Bucs next week. He’ll get a tough matchup against the Eagles, but would be a low-end WR3/FLEX option because of the volume he’d see.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d2aef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (ankle) left Dallas’ Week 3 game against the Bears and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e05-d93f-ad9d-7ec7a77b0000</link>
      <description>Bears defender Noah Sewell came down on Lamb’s ankle awkwardly on a tackle and Lamb slowly jogged off to the bench with trainers. He eventually wound up in the blue medical tent. It’s unclear at this time if Lamb will return — he had not recorded a catch before leaving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e05-d93f-ad9d-7ec7a77b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson caught 10-of-13 targets for 84 yards and a touchdown in a Week 3 loss to the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0e-d1b3-a5dd-6f7f7e0f0000</link>
      <description>Today was an easy answer that, yes, Tyrod Taylor can support the fantasy value of Garrett Wilson if he’s forced to start. Tyrod looked Wilson’s way early and often, and the two showed good timing with one another. Wilson’s touchdown was early in the fourth quarter when the Bucs had taken their foot off the gas, but it was a nice in-breaking route that set up the open look. Wilson is going to have plenty of volume regardless of who is at quarterback, and that should keep him a WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0e-d1b3-a5dd-6f7f7e0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed six times for 21 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 3 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d306e0000</link>
      <description>He only played 12 snaps — it’s worth noting that he did wear a non-contact jersey for his shoulder all week — but Tuten was able to deliver the game’s first touchdown to cap an early scoring drive for the Jaguars. It is mildly concerning to see LeQuint Allen (21 snaps) almost double Tuten’s snap count, but Allen managed only one target and no touches on the ground, so it was clear that Tuten was still getting the majority of the work. Tuten would be a riskier FLEX option with this workload against the 49ers in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d306e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed eight times for 26 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 3 win over the Raiders, adding one catch for five additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0a-d93f-ad9d-7ecf99910000</link>
      <description>JCM didn’t see any work until the Commanders’ third drive of the game, but the rookie did find the end zone late in the third quarter on a one-yard plunge to put the Commanders up by three possessions. Those hoping for Croskey-Merritt to take over the backfield will need to wait at least another week — or longer. The Commanders involved three different running backs in this one while also giving Deebo Samuel three carries. Croskey-Merritt shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a touchdown-dependent option in Week 4 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e0a-d93f-ad9d-7ecf99910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
