<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 14:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 3-of-5 targets for 34 yards in the Texans’ Week 14 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc54-d8cf-affb-fc7e33d10000</link>
      <description>Higgins continues to churn out meaningful production for a Texans team in dire need of secondary options behind alpha wide receiver Nico Collins. The towering rookie was kept out of the end zone but made two key grabs to keep the chains moving and could continue his ascension towards the end of the season. Up next is a plus matchup against the battered Cardinals in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc54-d8cf-affb-fc7e33d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 14-of-33 passes for 160 yards and three interceptions in the Chiefs’ 20-10, Week 14 loss to the Texans, adding 59 yards on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc5c-d77b-adfa-fedf08a30000</link>
      <description>This will be one to forget for Mahomes and the Chiefs as multiple aspects of their game plan came crashing down in a must-win game. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-7 and advanced odds now give them a measly 16% chance to make the postseason. Minutes after C.J. Stroud set the benchmark for consecutive incompletions this season with nine, Mahomes followed it up with 10 straight passes without a completion in the second half. Two of those were key interceptions while both Rashee Rice and Travis Kelce were charged with two drops during the streak. The 10 straight incompletions were also a career-worst for Mahomes, it was only the third time in his career where the Chiefs were shutout in a half, and it was only the fourth game in his career with three or more interceptions. The Chiefs must quickly lick their wounds ahead of a showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc5c-d77b-adfa-fedf08a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 12 times for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc65-da9b-a9bf-fe6d52cd0000</link>
      <description>It as a far from inspiring performance from the backfield duo behind an offensive line missing three starters. Both backs managed only 30 yards, with Isiah Pacheco’s coming on only nine carries. The two continue to operate in a near-even split, although Hunt continues to see higher value touches near the end zone. There doesn’t appear to be much fantasy value remaining in the Kansas City backfield ahead of a showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc65-da9b-a9bf-fe6d52cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 3-of-4 targets for 55 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs struggled to move the football throughout against the league’s top defense, with quarterback Patrick Mahomes setting a career high in consecutive incompletions with 10 in the second half. The one good aspect of Worthy’s game was that he failed to account for any drops, which both Travis Kelce and Rashee Rice could not say leaving the game. Worthy continues to see modest volume with both primary options healthy, a trend likely to hold ahead of a Week 15 showdown with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 4-of-8 targets for 34 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</link>
      <description>Not only did Rice fail to return a usable fantasy outing, but two of Patrick Mahomes’ four incompletions when targeting Rice went down as drops. The worst instance came on fourth down half way through the fourth quarter when Rice saw the pass go straight through his hands. The poor outing can be viewed as a slight blip for fantasy’s overall WR1 in fantasy points per game ahead of a must-win game against the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 1-of-5 targets for eight yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</link>
      <description>Kelce’s night looks bad enough on paper before you realize two of Patrick Mahomes’ incompletions when targeting the veteran tight end were drops. Additionally, Kelce bobbled a pass on the team’s penultimate possession that was picked off by Azeez Al-Shaair with under four minutes remaining and down by a touchdown. That would allow the Texans to run down the clock to under 30 seconds after kicking a field goal to go up by 10. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-7 with only a 16% chance of making the playoffs. Kelce will be needed in a must-win showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Butker went 1-for-2 in field goal attempts in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</link>
      <description>He connected from 36 yards and made his only point after attempt, missing from 43 yards at the end of the second quarter when his kick hit off the left upright. That missed field goal contributed to the Chiefs being shutout in the first half for only the third time in quarterback Patrick Mahomes’ career, making the failed conversion slightly more meaningful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Mevis converted his lone field goal attempt and al six of his extra point attempts in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</link>
      <description>Mevis has proven a fine weekly fantasy play thanks to the high-powered Rams offense and the positive game script it creates. He’s made all three of his field goals this season and has yet to miss an extra point. He should be in fantasy lineups next week against the Lions in what should be a high-scoring affair. The Lions have allowed 1.7 field goal tries per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Loop converted all three of his field goal and one of his two extra point attempts in the Ravens’ Week 14 loss against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</link>
      <description>Loop has been excellent all season, making 25 of his 27 field goal tries. He hasn’t missed a field goal since Week 5 against the Texans. Loop will be a top-10 fantasy option in Week 15 against the Bengals. The Ravens are averaging 2.1 field goal tries per game, the 11th highest mark in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports DK Metcalf (stomach) will rejoin the Steelers on Monday after staying the night in a Baltimore hospital on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, Metcalf experienced stomach pain on the team flight and stayed the night in the hospital “out of an abundance of caution.” Given the brief stay and the fact he’s rejoining the team on Monday, we’ll assume this is a minor issue until we hear otherwise. With the Steelers playing on Monday Night Football in Week 15, Metcalf will have some extra time to rest up before his next game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
