<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4f-d45b-affe-dfdfc8f60000</link>
      <description>Andy Reid mentioned before practice that Worthy could get in a limited session. The team ultimately chose to hold him out entirely. Reid did note that Worthy participated in the team’s walkthrough. There is still a chance he returns to practice later this week and can play on Sunday, but a DNP for the first session is typically an ominous sign. Worthy’s absence would be more work for Hollywood Brown, who has largely fallen by the wayside since the return of Rashee Rice. If active, Worthy will be a high-risk WR4 versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4f-d45b-affe-dfdfc8f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e53-d673-a39e-bed3a5980000</link>
      <description>Njoku missed one game with a knee injury earlier this year. He hasn’t been on the injury report because of the knee issue as of late, so it’s possible the same issue resurfaced during Week 11. His absence would clear the way for an uptick in Harold Fannin’s role. Fannin would still be stuck in the TE2 ranks even with an increase in targets because of how mightily the Browns offense is struggling this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e53-d673-a39e-bed3a5980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5a-d713-ad9e-fe5e71db0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs is dealing with a knee contusion that he suffered in Week 11 against the Giants. Head coach Matt LaFleur said earlier this week there is “potentially” a chance Jacobs suits up for Week 12 against the Vikings. He starts out this week not practicing and will at least need to get in a limited practice to have a shot at playing this week. In the event Jacobs is out, Emanuel Wilson is in line to be a low-end fantasy RB2 against a stout Vikings defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5a-d713-ad9e-fe5e71db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5b-d45b-affe-dfdfd11d0000</link>
      <description>Jurgens will likely miss Week 12 because of the brain injury. Right tackle Lane Johnson is also out this week. He is dealing with a Lisfranc injury and is expected to miss at least a month. Luckily for the Eagles, their banged-up line is facing Dallas’s bottom-tier pass-rush on Sunday. There are certainly worse matchups to be without two starters for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5b-d45b-affe-dfdfd11d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Romeo Doubs (wrist) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5e-d673-a39e-bedf456d0000</link>
      <description>Nearly the entire Packers pass-catching group was either limited or not practicing on Wednesday. Doubs was listed as a limited participant with a wrist injury, along with three other Packers wideouts listed as limited and Savion Williams (foot) listed as a non-participant. Doubs is the current lead receiver in an offense that does not have a definitive No. 1 receiver. If he were to miss time, Christian Watson would be first up for a bump, followed by the rookie Matthew Golden. Stay tuned to Doubs and the rest of the Green Bay receivers’ statuses this week; the Packers’ fantasy hierarchy could see a shake-up if multiple receivers cannot play Week 12 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e5e-d673-a39e-bedf456d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder/wrist) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e6a-d713-ad9e-fe7e79700000</link>
      <description>The rookie Golden is on the long list of Packers skill players currently hurt. He was listed as a limited practice participant with shoulder and wrist injuries on Wednesday. The shoulder has been ailing Golden since Week 9, but the wrist injury is a new addition. If Golden misses time, we would say Dontayvion Wicks and Christian Watson would get more run, but both Wicks and Watson are also dealing with injuries. Golden is barely a fantasy WR4 when healthy, but would receive a boost if Watson or Romeo Doubs miss Week 12 against the Vikings while Golden is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e6a-d713-ad9e-fe7e79700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e6e-d45b-affe-dffe1b0b0000</link>
      <description>Watson was limited due to a knee issue while Wicks was limited due to a calf issue. Both Watson and Wicks have been listed on practice reports from previous weeks with the same respective injuries, so it is possible this is a procedural practice limitation and both receivers are good for Week 12 against the Vikings. Keep and eye on Romeo Doubs and Matthew Golden, who were also both limited in Wednesday’s practice. If Watson and Wicks are good to go while Doubs and Golden are not, Watson is a borderline WR2/3 while Wicks enters the WR4 conversation. Fantasy managers should stay tuned to see how the banged-up Packers receiving corps practices later in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e6e-d45b-affe-dffe1b0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) was participating in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e74-d713-ad9e-fe74a0bf0000</link>
      <description>Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reported seeing Irving on the field for the walk-through portion of Wednesday’s practice. The 23-year-old is slowly returning from foot and shoulder injuries, getting in limited practices last week. He is ramping back up to full game speed and it is a good sign for his Week 12 availability that he was at practice to open the week. It is unlikely Irving would get a full workload upon his return; he will be in the low-end fantasy RB2 range if he does play in Week 12 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e74-d713-ad9e-fe74a0bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (pectoral) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e7a-d45b-affe-dffe2dd80000</link>
      <description>Parsons popped up on the injury report with a pectoral issue and was listed as limited on Wednesday. Given he still practiced in some capacity, it is possible the Packers are carefully managing Parsons’ pectoral soreness with a lighter practice workload. He is not yet in danger of missing Week 12 against the Vikings, but his practice status later in the week and potential new information about the severity of the injury will shed light on his game status. Fellow EDGE Lukas Van Ness (foot) was also limited in practice as he works his way back to playing for the first time since Week 6. The Packers will hope to have both edge rushers healthy against the Vikings’ stumbling passing offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e7a-d45b-affe-dffe2dd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LB Quay Walker (neck) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e82-d45b-affe-df9672390000</link>
      <description>Walker suffered a stinger in Week 11 and is now listed with a neck injury. He does not practice to start the week, putting his Week 12 status in jeopardy. Also not practicing was CB Nate Hobbs (knee), who has missed each of the last two weeks. Both players will face an uphill battle to play against the Vikings this week, leaving the Packers defense thin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e82-d45b-affe-df9672390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
