<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:30:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared OL Zach Tom inactive for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa46-d968-a19b-faf7752d0000</link>
      <description>Tom is the only one of Green Bay’s questionable players that will sit, which means Malik Willis (hamstring/shoulder) is active as Jordan Love’s backup. Also inactive for Green Bay are: WR Dontayvion Wicks, QB Desmond Ridder, CB Jaylin Simpson, DL Collin Oliver and WR Jakobie Keeney-James.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa46-d968-a19b-faf7752d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) is active for Chicago’s Wild Card game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa49-d35e-a1bf-efcb74b10000</link>
      <description>He was the only questionable Bears player, but after being activated from injured reserve earlier today it would have been surprising if he hadn’t gone. Inactive for the Bears are: QB Case Keenum, DB CJ Gardner-Johnson, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, DL Joe Tryon-Shoyinka, WR Jahdae Walker and OL Luke Newman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa49-d35e-a1bf-efcb74b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 24-of-42 passes for 304 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in the Rams’ 34-31, Wild Card round win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa86-d35e-a1bf-efc655db0000</link>
      <description>If you didn’t see the game, those numbers probably look pretty stellar. Stafford had major problems targeting Carolina’s corners outside, as 184 of the 304 yards came over the middle of the field. He was just 7-of-22 for 94 yards and a pick in the second and third quarters. However, with Panthers CB Jaycee Horn getting checked in the concussion protocol late in the game, he was able to pinpoint a 19-yard pass to Colby Parkinson on the sideline to give the Rams a three-point lead with 38 seconds left. We don’t know exactly where Stafford is going yet next weekend, but the Rams clearly are relying on him to keep them going and he’ll be an obvious staple in DFS lineups for the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa86-d35e-a1bf-efc655db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams rushed 13 times for 57 yards in the Rams’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers, adding two catches for 18 yards and a touchdown on his only two targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa8f-d56e-afff-eeef3bc80000</link>
      <description>Williams’ angle route in the fourth quarter put the Rams back in front in the fourth quarter. The Rams didn’t really do a great job of establishing the run with Kevin Dotson out, and Williams continued to split carries with Blake Corum while out-snapping him 47-28 per the early PFF charting data. Williams will be part of the high-end RB conversation in Divisional Round DFS and Playoff Best Ball next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa8f-d56e-afff-eeef3bc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed 11 times for 45 yards in the Rams’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers, adding two catches for 13 yards on his only two targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa93-d968-a19b-faf304fe0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t score, but Corum went over 10 carries for the fifth time in six games. Neither Corum or Williams found much running room in this one without guard Kevin Dotson, with Corum getting the Rams’ long rushing gain of eight yards. Corum should be involved in the Divisional Round fantasy discussion but is clearly a 1B back looking for a favorable situation to emerge over the next 36 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa93-d968-a19b-faf304fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 10-of-11 targets for 111 yards and a touchdown in Los Angeles’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers, adding three carries for 14 yards and an additional touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa96-d968-a19b-faf7c9620000</link>
      <description>And somehow it could have been better, because his one incomplete pass was a 30-yard downfield pass towards the end of the first half that it hit him right in the hands. Had Nacua caught it, he had a fairly good shot at a third score. The favorite for offensive player of the year continued his grind, helping Matthew Stafford out by breaking up a late would-be interception and using his accuracy to erase some of the trouble Stafford and Davante Adams had getting on the same page throughout the game. Nacua seems destined to continue churning out Overall WR1 Games against whoever the Rams draw in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa96-d968-a19b-faf7c9620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 5-of-13 targets for 72 yards in Los Angeles’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa99-d35e-a1bf-efdbf7b30000</link>
      <description>Adams and Stafford did not exactly look like they were on the same page for most of this game, though it should be noted that Adams dropped a few balls. It also bears mentioning that he’d probably have had 90 yards if not for a helmet-to-helmet breakup in the third quarter that sent Adams briefly for a concussion check. As far as “getting his legs” back fantasy games, it’s hard to ignore the pass volume that Adams was able to generate here despite leaving eight targets on the ground. Adams will clearly be involved in the high-end WR conversation for the Divisional Round, though this game gives us some pause on how high expectations should be set.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa99-d35e-a1bf-efdbf7b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught 2-of-3 targets for 34 yards and a touchdown in Los Angeles’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa9d-d35e-a1bf-efdf37f60000</link>
      <description>It is, amazingly, Parkinson’s ninth touchdown in his last 10 games despite cracking 50 yards just once over that span. The Rams steered away from their 13-personnel sets in this game without Terrance Ferguson, but Parkinson continued to eat up snaps, playing a tight-end-room high 57 of the team’s 75. Can you call someone a touchdown or bust option if he almost always spits up a touchdown? That’s what you’re confronted with in the Divisional Round slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa9d-d35e-a1bf-efdf37f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught 2-of-3 targets for 45 yards in Los Angeles’ Wild Card Round win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aaa0-d968-a19b-faf122630000</link>
      <description>Despite scoring in his return from injured reserve in Week 18, Higbee played 39 of 75 snaps this week and was mostly kept in check as Davante Adams garnered a huge amount of targets. He managed a 36-yard catch in the middle of a busted zone in this one, but otherwise didn’t build much of a TE punt case for next week’s Divisional Round slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aaa0-d968-a19b-faf122630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young completed 21-of-40 passes for 264 yards, a touchdown, and an interception in the Panthers’ 34-31, Wild Card Round loss to the Rams, adding three carries for 24 yards and a touchdown on the ground.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aaa2-d35e-a1bf-efe2794f0000</link>
      <description>It never really felt like the Panthers had efficiency on their side in this one, with Young struggling to complete 50 percent of his passes and dealing with plenty of pressure early. But Young hit some big plays downfield, including a 52-yarder to Jalen Coker, and led the Panthers to a go-ahead touchdown drive with just over two minutes left in the fourth quarter. Given the ball with 38 seconds left down three, Young led a quick four-and-out to end the game. Up and down. Up and down. That’s sort of the story with Young in his third season: He proved capable of big games, but more often than not was struggling to get to 200 yards. The rushing touchdown was his third in 18 games this season, so he isn’t providing much there for fantasy managers. Even with some work to the supporting cast this offseason, Young probably will wind up on the low-end QB2 line in 2026 drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aaa2-d35e-a1bf-efe2794f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
