<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed RB MarShawn Lloyd (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e833-d332-a1fd-fe3700150000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four games of the season after suffering a hamstring injury following the first game of the preseason. Emanuel Wilson and Chris Brooks will carry the workload behind josh Jacobs for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e833-d332-a1fd-fe3700150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed DT Walter Nolen (calf) on Physically Unable to Perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e823-de13-afdc-eeeb576e0000</link>
      <description>Nolen was selected with the No. 16 overall pick in the first round of this year’s draft but suffered a calf injury while gearing up for camp, something that will now cost the talented rookie at least four games. The Cardinals have been dealt multiple blows on the defensive side of the ball before the season even started, with linebacker BJ Ojulari and defensive tackle Bilal Nichols also on the PUP list to start the season. The Cardinals also waived DL Kyon Barrs, LS Aaron Brewer, LB Elliott Brown, OL Jeremiah Byers, RB Michael Carter, OL Jake Curhan, RB DeeJay Dallas, TE Josiah Deguara, WR Simi Fehoko, DL Anthony Goodlow, WR Bryson Green, CB Darren Hall, OL Sincere Haynesworth, CB Jaylon Jones, OL Nick Leverett, OL Royce Newman, WR Tejhuan Palmer, S Jammie Robinson, DL Elijah Simmons, and LB Mykal Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e823-de13-afdc-eeeb576e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans released WR James Proche II.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e838-de13-afdc-eefb103a0000</link>
      <description>This one surprised some Titans beat writers, as Proche was expected to be their returner this year. It’s possible he’ll get brought off the practice squad for a few weeks and the Titans were willing to risk losing him to protect some of their younger players. Also released by the Titans were OL Brenden Jaimes, LB Blake Lynch, CB Amani Oruwariye, and DL Carlos Watkins. To get down to 53 players they also waived LB Brian Asamoah, DB Kendell Brooks, TE Drake Dabney, T Jaelyn Duncan, OLB Ali Gaye, DT Cam Horsley, RB Jermar Jefferson, WR Mason Kinsey, RB Jordan Mims, TE Thomas Odukoya, NT Isaiah Raikes and OL Andrew Rupcich.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e838-de13-afdc-eefb103a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released OT Bobby Hart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e843-d332-a1fd-fe77a45d0000</link>
      <description>Yes, that’s right, Bobby Hart was in an NFL training camp this year. He hasn’t started a game since 2021 and hasn’t been active for an NFL game since 2022. But here he was in Commanders camp. The team also released (they refused to designate between waived and released in their announcement): RB Kazmeir Allen, LB Kam Arnold, DT Ricky Barber, WR Ja’Corey Brooks, TE Lawrence Cager, WR River Cracraft, DT Carl Davis, DT Sheldon Day, C Michael Deiter, RB Demetric Felton, DE Clelin Ferrell, CB Antonio Hamilton Sr., QB Sam Hartman, DE Andre Jones Jr., WR Jacoby Jones, DE Jalyn Holmes, DE T.J. Maguranyanga, WR Tay Martin, S Rob McDaniel, G Timothy McKay, WR Chris Moore, S Ben Nikkel, WR K.J. Osborn, CB Bobby Price, LB Duke Riley, T Foster Sarell, TE Cole Turner, CB Car’lin Vigers and S Daryl Worley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e843-d332-a1fd-fe77a45d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed CB Sharon Revel on the non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e84c-db7b-a5dd-e84c835f0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four weeks of the season. Revel had a setback in his recovery from a torn ACL suffered last college season and wasn’t expected back for Week 1. The Cowboys will roll on with a depth chart of Trevon Diggs, DaRon Bland, and Kaiir Elam for the time being — though Diggs may still miss some time early in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e84c-db7b-a5dd-e84c835f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts waived CB JuJu Brents.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e83c-d332-a1fd-fe3e70950000</link>
      <description>Brents suffered a knee injury in Week 1 last year that kept him sidelined until Week 18. Brents flashed intriguing traits as a rookie, but the Colts are evidently ready to move on from their 2023 second-round pick. Through two seasons, Brents tallied 36 tackles, five pass breakups and one interception. The Colts released RB Khalil Herbert, CB Chris Lammons, TE Sean McKeon, CB Duke Shelley, WR Laquon Treadwell and DT Josh Tupou. They also waived LB Austin Ajiake, WR Ajou Ajou, QB Jason Bean, RB Ulysses Bentley IV, LB Jake Chaney, DT Devonta Davis, LB Solomon DeShields, T Marshall Foerner, C Wesley French, DE Marcus Haynes, CB Alex Johnson, T Marcellus Johnson, WR Tyler Kahmann, DE Isaiah Land, DE Desmond Little, TE Maximilian Mang, CB B.J. Mayes, DE Durrell Nchami, RB Nate Notel, WR Coleman Owen, WR Landon Parker, G Josh Sills, WR Blayne Taylor, S Ladarius Tennison, LB Joseph Vaughn, C Mose Vavao, S Trey Washington, CB Sam Womack III, TE Jelani Woods, RB Nay’Quan Wright and K Maddux Trujillo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e83c-d332-a1fd-fe3e70950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released WR Erik Ezukanma.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e850-de13-afdc-eedb383f0000</link>
      <description>Ezukanma appeared in five games for the Dolphins across three professional seasons, never fully capable of breaking into the starting roster as a mainstay. His services were thusly rendered obsolete with a healthy receiving corps heading into the new season. Miami also released/waived CB Cornell Armstrong, LB Quinton Bell, RB Mike Boone, TE Pharaoh Brown, OT Jackson Carman, CB Cameron Dantzler Sr, DT Matt Dickerson, TE Chris Myarick, CB Kendall Sheffield, CB BJ Adams, WR Andrew Armstrong, OL Mason Brooks, OL Braeden Daniels, OT Ryan Hayes, WR AJ Henning, DT Alex Huntley, LB Dequan Jackson, LB Mohamed Kamara, OL Jalen McKenzie, LB Derrick McLendon, S Patrick McMorris, LB Grayson Murphy, OL Josh Priebe, CB Ethan Robinson, TE Hayden Rucci, S John Saunders Jr, RB Aaron Shampklin, DT Ben Stille, LB Channing Tindall, WR Theo Wease Jr, and OL Addison West. The club waived OT Bayron Matos with an injury designation and waived LB Eugene Asante with an injury settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e850-de13-afdc-eedb383f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys released QB Will Grier.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e83c-de13-afdc-eeff2b960000</link>
      <description>The 30-year-old at one point stood as Dallas’ QB2 this offseason, but Dallas traded for Joe Milton and Grier is likely looking at a practice squad placement yet again. He’s played in just two career games. The Cowboys also released: OL La’el Collins, OL Saahdiq Charles, OL Geron Christian, OL Hakeem Adeniji, CB Israel Mukuamu, DL Earnest Brown IV, CB C.J. Goodwin, CB Michael Ojemudia, CB Robert Rochell, CB Kemon Hall, LB Darius Harris and LB Buddy Johnson. They waived: DT Denzel Daxon, DT Tommy Akingbesote, WR Josh Kelly, WR Traeshon Holden, WR Jalen Cropper, TE Princeton Fant, TE John Stephens Jr., TE Rivaldo Fairweather, TE Tyler Neville, CB Troy Pride, S Mike Smith, S Alijah Clark, LB Justin Barron, RB Malik Davis and DE Tyrus Wheat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e83c-de13-afdc-eeff2b960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed DT Shy Tuttle to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bdb730000</link>
      <description>Tuttle will be a rotational interior piece behind T’Vondre Sweat and Jeffery Simmons. He was released by the Panthers at final cuts, but the Titans appear to value him more highly than Carolina did.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bdb730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said Michael Burton (hamstring) will have surgery and be out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85e-de13-afdc-eedf961d0000</link>
      <description>In other words, he was placed on the season-ending version of injured reserve. The Broncos don’t currently have a fullback after cutting Adam Prentice earlier today, so they’ll likely either add there or use one of their tight ends in the backfield this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85e-de13-afdc-eedf961d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
