<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:30:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed four times for negative four yards in the Buccaneeers’ Week 18 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8672-d35e-a1bf-c7f2f9a00000</link>
      <description>Well that’s not very good. Tucker couldn’t find solid footing in the rainy Tampa Bay conditions, and ends what was a solid — all things considered — 2025 campaign on a down note. The former Syracuse tailback could be worth monitoring if he changes organizations next year, but also could play in a playoff game next week if the Saints beat the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8672-d35e-a1bf-c7f2f9a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 4-of-6 targets for 83 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-867f-d968-a19b-deff49df0000</link>
      <description>McMillan should have reached the century mark, but a long connection with Bryce Young was erased by an abhorrent offensive pass interference call. The wideout did bring in a 40-yard pass that set up a touchdown from Young, and he was the best offensive player on the field for Carolina. McMillan has unreal upside and showed out at times in 2025, and very well could be a WR1 in 2026. His season will be over, however, if the Saints beat the Falcons on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-867f-d968-a19b-deff49df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker caught 6-of-7 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8682-d35e-a1bf-c7c29af90000</link>
      <description>Coker perfectly timed a leaping catch for a touchdown to get the Panthers to within a score with just over two minutes left in the game. The second-year wideout ended the year with three touchdowns, but all three came in the final five games for those looking for positives. Coker should be more involved in 2026 if healthy — he didn’t play until October 19 — and offers some upside for the coming seasons. His chance to play in the playoffs in 2025 will be determined by whether the Falcons beat the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8682-d35e-a1bf-c7c29af90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tremble caught 3-of-4 targets for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8683-d56e-afff-e6eb7f0d0000</link>
      <description>Tremble caught a touchdown pass early from Bryce Young to get the Panthers within a score at 10-7. The former Notre Dame tight end finished with just two touchdowns in 2025, and remains much more effective as a blocker than as a receiver. That should be true next season as well, but he could get a playoff game next week if the Falcons beat the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8683-d56e-afff-e6eb7f0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brycen Tremayne caught 2-of-2 targets for 27 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8684-d35e-a1bf-c7c660560000</link>
      <description>One of the catches was a 20-yard connection. Tremayne finished with just 14 catches for 143 yards in his first season with the Panthers. It’s hard to see fantasy relevance going forward, but he might be an option for Carolina in the playoffs if the Falcons beat the Saints. If not, he’ll compete for a roster spot this summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8684-d35e-a1bf-c7c660560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette caught 3-of-4 targets for 22 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8685-d968-a19b-def504160000</link>
      <description>Legette did not build on a disappointing rookie season — at least statistically — as he finished with just 34 catches for 363 yards despite playing in 16 games. You can’t completely give up on him as a dynasty option, but there hasn’t been much to suggest he’s on the right track. There’s still a chance he could play in the postseason, however, if the Falcons beat the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8685-d968-a19b-def504160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Horn Jr. caught his only target for 15 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8686-d35e-a1bf-c7c601c70000</link>
      <description>Horn was an undrafted free agent from Prime University aka Colorado, and the 23-year-old did see more involvement in the offense than anticipated. Not enough to make him relevant in fantasy formats, but enough to suggest he could be a part of the offense in 2026. Horn will compete for slot reps with the Panthers this summer, but will hope the Falcons beat the Saints so they can play at least one postseason game next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8686-d35e-a1bf-c7c601c70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
