<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:04:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said he’s “optimistic” about WR Tory Horton (ankle) being available for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</link>
      <description>Horton hasn’t practiced since leaving Seattle’s second preseason game with the ankle injury, but it doesn’t seem like he’s at any risk of starting the year on injured reserve based on this update. Horton isn’t someone you need to roster in your home fantasy league right away, but he’s got a chance to grow into a real role in year one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Buccaneers are releasing QB Kyle Trask.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will work out an injury settlement for Trask, as he’s currently dealing with a shoulder issue. A second-round pick for some reason in 2021, Trask has been the backup quarterback for the Bucs over the last four seasons, but that honor will now apparently go to Teddy Bridgewater. Trask is likely a practice squad player for a new organization in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived RB Audric Estime.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e346-dbe3-a9bb-f357e4b70000</link>
      <description>Estime is the odd man out from the Broncos’ running back room, with the team jettisoning him a year after spending a fifth-round pick on him. He tallied 76 carries for 310 yards and two touchdowns in a committee last season, but does not add much as a pass-catcher. With R.J. Harvey and J.K. Dobbins joining Denver’s backfield, Estime’s lack of passing-down work could not beat out the likes of Jaleel McLaughlin and Tyler Badie. He could find work on a team needing a downhill runner in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e346-dbe3-a9bb-f357e4b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions waived RB Deon Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e339-d332-a1fd-f73f17b50000</link>
      <description>Jackson, 26, was signed in August and didn’t stand much of a chance to make the opening roster. The Lions also waived DT Myles Adams and DE Nate Lynn ahead of Tuesday’s deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e339-d332-a1fd-f73f17b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams released LB Brennan Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e362-de13-afdc-e7eb058d0000</link>
      <description>Jackson was second in sacks during the preseason, but that wasn’t enough for him to make the initial roster to begin the 2025 campaign. The 24-year-old is a strong candidate for the practice squad if another team doesn’t procure his services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e362-de13-afdc-e7eb058d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived RB Blake Watson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ backfield is taking shape with Audric Estime and Watson being waived today. Watson had just four carries for 10 yards last season and suffered a PCL strain last week. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports there was some trade interest in him, so he is a candidate to be claimed. If not, the Broncos likely want him back on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles released EDGE Ochaun Mathis, S Andre’ Sam, and CB A.J. Woods.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e373-dbe3-a9bb-f373a4790000</link>
      <description>The Eagles continue to make cuts ahead of Tuesday’s deadline on the defensive side of the ball. Mathis and Sam each played in one game for the Eagles last season while Woods has only appeared in preseason games for the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e373-dbe3-a9bb-f373a4790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released WR DeAndre Carter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e384-db7b-a5dd-e384c6580000</link>
      <description>Carter was brought in by the Browns in March with a chance to be a special teams contributor, but Cleveland will go elsewhere for their returner to open 2025. His speed makes him likely to find a new club at some point this fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e384-db7b-a5dd-e384c6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevon Diggs (knee) was a full participant in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-de13-afdc-e7cfa53b0000</link>
      <description>Diggs was activated Sunday off the PUP (Physically Unable to Perform) list, and all signs point to the stellar 26-year-old cornerback being available for next Thursday’s Week 1 opener against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-de13-afdc-e7cfa53b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived QB Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</link>
      <description>Buechele is a strong candidate to end up on the Bills’ practice squad. He’s the second quarterback Buffalo has dropped Tuesday, as they also waived Mike White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
