<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Dolphins owner Stephen Ross “does not want to fire” head coach Mike McDaniel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f4d-dfde-a1bd-5fcd33a50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport then added that Ross’ view could change if “fans suddenly stop showing up to the stadium,” or “if players stop playing” for McDaniel. While the initial report is positive, the latter almost reads like Ross is laying out a road map for McDaniel’s firing. McDaniel wields a creative playbook and employs star-focused game plans, which bode positively for fantasy productivity. For a multitude of reasons, it would be nice for him to stick around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f4d-dfde-a1bd-5fcd33a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 23-of-35 passes for 161 yards, two touchdowns and an interception in the Dolphins’ 31-21, Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5fdd-d1b3-a5dd-5ffd8e6d0000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa has now thrown at least one pick in all three starts this season, and is averaging just 197 weekly yards despite a 315-yard effort in Week 2. He has failed to exceed 5.0 yards per attempt in 2-of-3 outings. Tagovailoa is pushing the ball down the field less than ever, and when he does, bad things are usually happening. His pick tonight, which came with the Dolphins trying to erase a 28-21 fourth quarter deficit, came after he simply stared down LB Terrel Bernard. Tagovailoa’s contract means he will not be benched, but absent drastic — and immediate — improvement, this whole era of Dolphins football will be coming to an end at season’s end, or perhaps even sooner. Playing on Monday Night Football in Week 4, Tagovailoa has 11 days to come up with something better for the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5fdd-d1b3-a5dd-5ffd8e6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen completed 22-of-28 passes for 213 yards and three touchdowns in the Bills’ 31-21, Week 3 win over the Dolphins, adding four rushes for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ffa-dfde-a1bd-5fff1e410000</link>
      <description>Playing with a visor after busting his nose in a rare scoreless Week 2 outing, Allen bounced back for three scores at home even as he rarely challenged down the field and was less adventurous than usual as a runner. He was simply pin point with his accuracy and spread the ball around everywhere, finding nine pass catchers for at least one reception. That included a five-yard second quarter touchdown strike to No. 3 tight end “Jackson Hawes.” His other scores were a 20-yarder to Dalton Kincaid where the tight end had to make an in-air adjustment, and 15-yarder to Khalil Shakir on a swing pass. Now with 10 days for his nose to heal ahead of a soft Week 4 matchup with the Saints, Allen’s only fantasy concern is that Buffalo won’t be pushed enough when New Orleans comes marching in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ffa-dfde-a1bd-5fff1e410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 19 times for 108 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins, adding three receptions for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ffe-d6a5-adff-ffffe8ed0000</link>
      <description>Churning up big gains seemingly every time he touched the ball, Cook receiving “only” 19 carries was a bit of a disappointment in a game that was closer than anticipated. The main culprit was a lack of overall play volume with both teams featuring long, methodical drives. The Bills ran just 57 total plays. Thankfully Cook still found the end zone even as Josh Allen was locked onto his tight ends in the red zone. Playing hyper efficient football and making the most of his high-value touches when he gets them, Cook has settled back in on the RB1/2 borderline. He should find himself in the top 12 for Week 4 against the Saints at home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ffe-d6a5-adff-ffffe8ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 12 times for 62 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills, adding seven receptions for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6004-dfde-a1bd-7e8d75900000</link>
      <description>Achane’s 12 carries and 62 yards on the ground were both new season highs even as rookie No. 2 Ollie Gordon finally got involved in a meaningful fashion. Up to 15 receptions over the past two weeks, Achane has been one of the Dolphins’ most effective players, but ceiling is proving hard to come by in this collapsing offense, while it’s never ideal when a running back’s floor involves catching at least five passes. This is going to be a rocky road, but Achane’s usage is still enough to keep him in the top 12-15 on a weekly basis. Managers just need to be prepared for the bottom to fall out every once in a while. That is probably unlikely for Week 4, where the ‘Fins will find themselves on 11 days rest for Monday Night Football against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6004-dfde-a1bd-7e8d75900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon rushed nine times for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6008-d6a5-adff-f6cd57b00000</link>
      <description>Gordon was not targeted in the passing game as De’Von Achane soaked up nine targets. No matter, as the rookie’s nine handles were nearly double his combined total from Weeks 1 and 2. Gordon was looking mighty powerful when he got a head of steam, though it’s true that 16 of his 38 yards came on one carry. Featured over Achane in the red zone on the Dolphins’ opening drive, Gordon capped it off with a two-yard scoring plunge. This is the usage fantasy managers have been expecting all along, and it should be something of a necessity for a Dolphins team hurting for answers on offense. They need to get the run game ramped up, as there is only so much Achane can do between the tackles. Gordon remains an intriguing bench stash ahead of Week 4 vs. the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6008-d6a5-adff-f6cd57b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill caught 5-of-10 targets for 49 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600c-d93f-ad9d-7acf26210000</link>
      <description>Hill’s 10 targets were a new season high, though he’s now been held below 50 yards receiving in 2-of-3 contests. The touchdown was his first of 2025. It was a fourth quarter lollipop pass from Tua Tagovailoa. Hill could have had a sixth reception, but fell down on slippery “Highmark Stadium” turf. On the other hand, his first reception probably wasn’t actually a catch, but the Bills didn’t challenge. Hill still looks springy and fast, but Tagovailoa’s play has been dismal through the season’s first three contests. The Jets await for Monday Night Football in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600c-d93f-ad9d-7acf26210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 5-of-6 targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600f-d93f-ad9d-7acf9d0d0000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers will take Waddle’s second touchdown in as many weeks, though he’s now been held under 40 yards receiving in 2-of-3 appearances. Waddle has yet to command more than six targets in a game. Disappointing, especially since the Dolphins’ offense has become so horizontal. Coach Mike McDaniel and Tua Tagovailoa have a strikingly difficult time getting the ball to their No. 2 wideout despite his underneath skill-set. Struggling to rise above middling WR3 status, Waddle faces the Jets in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600f-d93f-ad9d-7acf9d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 4-of-4 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6013-d93f-ad9d-7ad7add20000</link>
      <description>In theory this was a nice bounce-back effort after Shakir’s two-target Week 2, though he now has just six total looks since commanding nine in Week 1. The season opener, of course, was the only game where the Bills have found themselves in a shootout. They were surprisingly forced to match points with the Dolphins this evening, but both teams were grinding out slow, methodical drives. Shakir’s fourth quarter score, which proved to be the game-winner, was a 12-yard catch-and-run on a swing pass. With the Bills content to play safe, station-to-station football when not being challenged, Shakir isn’t looking like a particularly high-upside WR4 for Week 4 against the rebuilding Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6013-d93f-ad9d-7ad7add20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 3-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Bills’ Week 3 win over teh Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6019-d6a5-adff-f6ddb1ae0000</link>
      <description>With the Bills opting for safe, underneath football, Coleman was limited to three catches for the second time in five days. He is now sitting on 6/46 in two contests since his 8/112/1 Week 1 blowup. Week 1, of course, was the only time the Bills found themselves in a shootout. They were actually forced to match points with the Dolphins this evening, but both teams opted for grind-it-out football. That’s not a game you are typically going to win against Josh Allen. Coleman has a plus Week 4 matchup in the Saints, but it doesn’t exactly profile as a game where the Bills will open things up. Coleman is a low-floor WR4 for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6019-d6a5-adff-f6ddb1ae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
