<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7677-d968-a19b-7ef713da0000</link>
      <description>Jones played through an ankle injury last week despite the Vikings having nothing left to play for. He could do so again in week 18, though it’s just as likely that he finally takes a week off. In addition to the ankle and hip injuries, Jones has been on the practice report with shoulder, toe, and hamstring issues this year. He has more than earned a week of rest to close the season. If that does happen, Jordan Mason would be in line for a larger role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7677-d968-a19b-7ef713da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason (ankle) was limited in Wendesdays pracitce.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767a-d35e-a1bf-77fab6240000</link>
      <description>Aaron Jones was held out with a hip injury. Mason missed Week 17 because of his ankle injury but has a shot at returning for Week 18. He would likely split work with Zavier Scott if active. Jones would handle the carries with Scott pitching in on passing downs. Mason would be in the RB3 mix if Jones is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767a-d35e-a1bf-77fab6240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767d-d56e-afff-f6fde3110000</link>
      <description>Hockenson missed Week 17 with the shoulder issue and looks likely to sit out of Minnesota’s season finale. Josh Oliver and Ben Sims each caught exactly one pass in his absence last week. There isn’t a fantasy tight end of note on the team if Hockenson is out for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767d-d56e-afff-f6fde3110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7675-dc7a-af9b-ffffecf40000</link>
      <description>The 31-year-old tight end is the TE9 in half-PPR scoring and ranks second on the team with 78 targets. The Patriots currently hold the AFC’s No. 2 playoff seed and are expected to play their starters for as long as necessary, as the Nos. 1-3 seeds are finalized this week. We tentatively expect Henry to suit up, but this is worth checking on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7675-dc7a-af9b-ffffecf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-dc7a-af9b-ffbf34210000</link>
      <description>Odunze is expected to return at some point this season, though that could be during the postseason. He aggravated the stress fracture in his foot during pre-game warmups in Week 15 and has neither practiced nor played since. He is on the wrong side of questionable at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-dc7a-af9b-ffbf34210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (quad) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767d-d56e-afff-f6fdb7c40000</link>
      <description>Burden’s official participation level is just an estimation, but this is a good start to the week for him. The explosive rookie seemingly collided with a 49ers defender on the final play of the game last week, injuring his quad. It is possible that this is just a contusion, rather than a strain. Either way, Burden’s early-week participation is a great sign. He is on track to play in Week 18 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-767d-d56e-afff-f6fdb7c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten (finger) is practicing in full for Week 18 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768b-d35e-a1bf-77cbe98f0000</link>
      <description>Tuten has been making quick progress in his recovery from the finger injury he suffered in Week 15. The rookie had to undergo surgery and was initially expected to be out until the playoffs. He now appears to be on track for a Week 18 return. Tuten will likely be eased back into the lineup if he is active this week, keeping him off the fantasy radar for the Jags’ regular season finale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768b-d35e-a1bf-77cbe98f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Jeffferson (forearm) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7694-d35e-a1bf-77d674260000</link>
      <description>Jefferson hasn’t caught more than three passes in a game since Week 7 but still runs plenty of routes every week. With nothing left to play for in week 18, the Titans could give him the week off. His absence would free up a few extra looks for Elic Ayomanor and Chimere Dike.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7694-d35e-a1bf-77d674260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Olamide Zaccheaus (illness) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-d968-a19b-7efb1cd40000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus was sidelined by the illness in Week 17. Fortunately, he is now on track to play. Whether Zaccheaus warrants long-shot FLEX consideration depends largely on his teammates’ health and availability. Bears WR Luther Burden (quad) was limited today, while WR Rome Odunze (foot) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-768a-d968-a19b-7efb1cd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769b-d56e-afff-f6fb77820000</link>
      <description>Goedert dealt with a knee issue much earlier in the year. It’s unclear if the two injuries are related. Either way, we fully expect him to get the week off. Nick Sirianni has already said he will rest some of his starters for a mostly meaningless Week 18 contest. Now dealing with a knee injury, Goedert is the perfect candidate to spend a week on the bench. Grant Calcaterra will take his place in the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-769b-d56e-afff-f6fb77820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
