<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 19:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel (hamstring) is expected to start against the Eagles in Week 2 of the preseason on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b366-d45c-a7fc-b37efa1b0000</link>
      <description>Gabriel is dealing with a hamstring injury, but is well enough to play against the Eagles on Saturday. Shedeur Sanders (oblique) and Kenny Pickett (hamstring) won’t play while also dealing with injuries while Joe Flacco will be held out as the likely starter for Week 1. Tyler Huntley figures to come off the bench for Gabriel and play a good amount of reps in reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b366-d45c-a7fc-b37efa1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton left Friday’s Week 2 preseason win over the Chiefs with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3b1-d45c-a7fc-b3bbc6d40000</link>
      <description>Horton made one catch for 12 yards before exiting. Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters that Horton could have reentered if needed, but obviously wasn’t going to take those chances in an exhibition bout. Horton has impressed this summer, and has a chance to be the third wide receiver when the season opens in September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3b1-d45c-a7fc-b3bbc6d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 4-of-7 passes for 46 yards in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f1-d45c-a7fc-b3fb98360000</link>
      <description>Maye and most of the starters played two series for the Patriots against the Vikings. The first drive stalled due to a delay of game penalty which placed them behind the sticks while the second was largely focused on the run game with TreVeyon Henderson and Antonio Gibson, resulting in an eight-yard touchdown scamper from the electric rookie. Maye was without Stefon Diggs in this one, which left Kayshon Boutte as a starter alongside Mack Hollins and DeMario Douglas. Maye connected with Hollins on three of his pass attempts, something this team could need once the regular season roles around considering his deep threat ability. It remains uncertain if Maye and the starters will see action in the final preseason tune-up next week against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f1-d45c-a7fc-b3fb98360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed four times for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f7-d90d-a5bd-b3ff00c70000</link>
      <description>Rhamondre Stevenson was held out in this one, leaving the backfield to Henderson and Antonio Gibson for the team’s first two drives with the starters. It was a mixed bag for Henderson, who got stuffed on his first two carries before ripping off carries of 11 yards and eight yards to cap off his final drive, the last of which resulted in his touchdown. Henderson brings elite play-making ability and plus vision and burst but his end-of-year production likely relies heavily on an offensive line currently ranked as a bottom five unit. Fantasy managers will want to monitor Stevenson’s injury after the veteran missed the previous week of practice in camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f7-d90d-a5bd-b3ff00c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas failed to catch his only target in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fb-df63-a199-fbfbb7050000</link>
      <description>Douglas predictably drew the start but failed to haul in his lone target on two drives worth of action against the Vikings. He is locked into a starting role alongside veterans Stefon Diggs and Mack Hollins, the latter of whom will likely cede snaps to Kayshon Boutte this season. Douglas is clearly more beneficial to rosters in full PPR formats but brings enough to the table as a viable late-round bye week fill in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fb-df63-a199-fbfbb7050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught all three targets for 38 yards in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fe-d45c-a7fc-b3fe38810000</link>
      <description>Hollins operated as Drake Maye’s top target with fellow veteran Stefon Diggs out of action. The highlight of his day was a solid 20-yard snag on the second possession on a ball down the sideline. Hollins should operate as the starting X-type receiver but could cede snaps to Kayshon Boutte as the team looks to introduce packages designed to open up the middle of the field for their primary pass-catchers. That leaves his fantasy value in questionable territory despite the plus showing Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fe-d45c-a7fc-b3fe38810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 6-of-8 passes for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 2 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b410-df63-a199-fd3b4e2f0000</link>
      <description>Stroud played two series, and he ended the second drive with a touchdown pass to Nico Collins on fourth-and-goal. It’s possible Stroud will play in the preseason finale, but the Texans obviously know what they have in the third-year quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b410-df63-a199-fd3b4e2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dalton exited Saturday’s Week 2 preseason game against the Texans with a right elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b417-d45c-a7fc-b61f067b0000</link>
      <description>Dalton completed 2-for-4 passes for 22 yards before leaving. The 37-year-old’s exit appears to be precautionary, but it’s plausible that Dalton will undergo testing to determine the severity of the injury. Jack Plummer has taken over at quarterback and likely will play the remainder of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b417-d45c-a7fc-b61f067b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Goodson left Saturday’s Week 2 preseason game against the Packers with an elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b412-d45c-a7fc-b61aac560000</link>
      <description>Goodson carried twice for 10 yards with a touchdown before the exit. The 24-year-old is competing to be the backup tailback with Khalil Herbert and DJ Giddens. There should be an update on Giddens early next week, at the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b412-d45c-a7fc-b61aac560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel completed 13-of-18 passes for 143 yards with no touchdowns and an interception in the Browns’ Week 2 preseason game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b439-d90d-a5bd-b67b755d0000</link>
      <description>Gabriel also lost a fumble and took two sacks. The southpaw quarterback had some solid moments, but he threw a pass into congestion that was intercepted and taken to the house by fellow rookie Andrew Mukuba. Gabriel is battling Shedeur Sanders to be the third quarterback on the roster, and based on how they played in their exhibition contests, right now it seems to be advantage Sanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b439-d90d-a5bd-b67b755d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
