<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 11 times for 43 yards in the Raiders’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers, adding three receptions for one yard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c2-da67-a99f-dcf71a020000</link>
      <description>Jeanty looked much more explosive than the Week 1 effort against Patriots, but the Chargers’ stout front seven still made running room tough for the rookie. His long gain was a 13-yard scamper, but there were several times where he turned nothing into a little more. Disappointing, but a little more encouraging even without a score. Jeanty will look to put it all together in Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c2-da67-a99f-dcf71a020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed eight times for 24 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders, adding one reception for one yard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c3-d294-a19b-f4f323bd0000</link>
      <description>Hampton lost a fumble late in the contest, and Najee Harris finished off the game. Neither tailback was particularly effective on a day where the passing game was much more effective — again — for the Chargers. Hampton is obviously talented, but he has not exactly hit the ground running. Pun intended. The tough Broncos’ defense is next in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c3-d294-a19b-f4f323bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Najee Harris rushed eight times for 28 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders, adding two catches for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c3-da67-a99f-dcf772060000</link>
      <description>After touching the ball just twice in Week 1, Harris was more involved in the gameplan Monday, and he ended up with 10 touches in Week 2 compared to Omarion Hampton’s nine. It’s also worth noting that Hampton had a late fumble, so Harris finished the game and clinched the win with a seven-yard gain on third down. This is a tough backfield to figure out right now, but it still seems like Hampton will be the leadback even with the turnovers against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c3-da67-a99f-dcf772060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 5-of-7 targets for 61 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d86f-abdd-55fdbf150000</link>
      <description>Allen was able to work his way into the corner of the end zone on a 10-yard seed from Justin Herbert to give the Chargers a 10-3 lead. That makes back-to-back games with a touchdown for Allen, and he was tied with Quentin Johnston for the most targets in the Chargers’ passing attack. The 33-year-old has looked the part after returning to Los Angeles, and the rumors of his demise may have been greatly exaggerated. He’ll be in the WR2 vicinity for Week 3 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d86f-abdd-55fdbf150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 3-of-7 targets for 71 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d294-a19b-f4f4ea660000</link>
      <description>Justin Hebert struggled to get the ball to Johnston for much of this game, but a 60-yard dime from Herbert to the 24-year-old wideout saved the fantasy day. That’s three touchdowns already for the 2023 first-round pick, and while there are some other mouths to feed in this offense, it’s been clear over the first two contests that the Chargers have made getting the football to Johnston a priority. He remains volatile, but there’s a ton of upside even in a touch matchup against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c4-d294-a19b-f4f4ea660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 5-of-5 targets for 48 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-da67-a99f-dcf730940000</link>
      <description>McConkey was efficient, but the second-year wideout was third in targets against the Las Vegas defense, as it appeared the Raiders wanted Keenan Allen and Quentin Johnston to beat them, instead. They did. The 23-year-old had one 19-yard connection with Justin Herbert, but the rest was dink-and-dunk stuff. It could be worse, but it’s not exactly what fantasy managers signed up for. Expect McConkey to be more involved against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-da67-a99f-dcf730940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) caught 5-of-8 passes for 38 yards in the Raiders’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-dc44-a9d9-57e6d6330000</link>
      <description>Some if Bowers’ disappointing game can be blamed on the knee injury. Some of it can be blamed on Geno Smith playing an atrocious football game. Ultimately, it adds up to Bowers doing very little, and his one deep target was overthrown by Smith in the end zone. Bowers is obviously a TE1 as long as he’s healthy enough to play, but fantasy managers are going to need to see Smith play a lot better for him to reach his ceiling in Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c6-dc44-a9d9-57e6d6330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 6-of-12 targets for 68 yards in the Raiders’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c7-d86f-abdd-55ff03470000</link>
      <description>Meyers was the top target for Geno Smith, but Smith struggled to get him the ball as seen in a 50-percent rate of completion rate on those attempts. That does make back-to-back games that the 28-year-old wideout has received double-digit targets, and there was just enough success to call it a decent fantasy game for the clear top wideout in the Las Vegas passing attack. Meyers will likely see a similar amount of action — and hopefully more receptions — against the Commanders in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c7-d86f-abdd-55ff03470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 3-of-8 passes for 12 yards in the Chargers’ Week 2 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c8-d294-a19b-f4f8b1310000</link>
      <description>Geno Smith was wholly ineffective Monday night, and Tucker was one of a few Las Vegas receivers who didn’t have much success on a night where the Raiders didn’t complete a single pass thrown over 10 yards. It’s worth noting that Tucker doubled the targets of Dont’e Thornton (one catch, 20 yards on four passes thrown his way), and he’s pretty clearly the WR2 on the Raiders’ for now. He’s nowhere close to that range from a fantasy perspective for Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50c8-d294-a19b-f4f8b1310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said it would be “hard” to start QB Justin Fields (concussion) if he doesn’t practice on Wednesday or Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5269-da67-a99f-defda9e70000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Fields, who suffered a head injury in the second half of the Jets’ Week 2 loss to the Bills, won’t suit up if he can’t get on the practice field by Thursday. Fields, who had never had a documented brain injury before Week 2, is in the league’s concussion protocol. Tyrod Taylor would be under center for the Jets in Week 3 against the Bucs if Fields can’t go. “We have to get more information so we can be more pinpointed on that, but we do have to look at it that way,” Glenn said. “If Justin can’t play, then Tyrod would be the guy, and we’d build a plan that’s suitable for him.” Glenn said he has “no concerns” about Taylor, 36, who completed seven of 11 attempts for 56 yards and a touchdown against Buffalo. Taylor would be a decent option in superflex formats if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5269-da67-a99f-defda9e70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
