<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson Jr. rushed twice for nine yards in the 49ers’ Week 18 win over the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8732-d56e-afff-e7fa0eb70000</link>
      <description>It’s Robinson’s lowest touch total since Week 8’s loss to Houston where he bageled. Robinson will see out the final days of his rookie contract in the NFC Wild Card round as a pure backup to Christian McCaffrey. He finishes the regular season with 92 carries for 400 yards and two touchdowns on the ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8732-d56e-afff-e7fa0eb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 6-of-8 targets for 84 yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8734-d56e-afff-e7fc764f0000</link>
      <description>A floor game for the third-year star. Smith-Njigba managed no red zone targets as the Seahawks played very run-heavy, and his one near-catch out of that area was heavily contested in double coverage. Smith-Njigba will get next week off as the Seahawks await the Wild Card round results as the NFC’s No. 1 seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8734-d56e-afff-e7fc764f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 2-of-3 targets for 29 yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8737-d968-a19b-dff770d50000</link>
      <description>Kupp was the target on a fourth-and-goal end zone chuck from Sam Darnold, but the ball wasn’t even close enough for him to make a play on it. The veteran did manage to convert two first downs on his only two catches, including a 24-yarder in the fourth quarter where Darnold was drifting towards the line on the move. Kupp didn’t crack 600 yards and managed just two touchdowns in his first year in Seattle. They can probably do better going forward if they want to move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8737-d968-a19b-dff770d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 2-of-3 targets for 14 yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873a-d35e-a1bf-c7fa83780000</link>
      <description>There simply wasn’t enough passing yards for Seattle to build more than this for the second-year tight end. Barner ends the regular season with a thud, but ends the regular season with a 52/519 receiving line that more than doubles his rookie season receiving records. With 10 touchdowns in 34 games, he’s become a reasonable touchdown-or-bust TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873a-d35e-a1bf-c7fa83780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught his only target for two yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe8f30000</link>
      <description>He also drew a defensive pass interference penalty. Shaheed has managed just a 15/188 receiving line for the Seahawks since coming over from the Saints at the trade deadline, and while he had a big punt return touchdown to help win the game against the Rams, it’s hard to say that he’s looked especially integrated into the offense so far. Perhaps a week off ahead of the NFC Divisional Round will help Seattle come up with some new tricks for Shaheed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe8f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-6 targets for 35 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873f-d56e-afff-e7ff10df0000</link>
      <description>He finished behind only George Kittle and Christian McCaffrey in targets, but San Francisco’s pass offense was going nowhere fast against Mike MacDonald’s crew tonight. Jennings will be a reasonable DFS play in the Wild Card Round next weekend. He hasn’t cracked 100 yards in a game all season, but managed a 55/643 seasonal line with nine touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873f-d56e-afff-e7ff10df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle caught 5-of-7 targets for 29 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8741-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f1d0000</link>
      <description>Limited mostly to little dumpoffs on bootlegs, Kittle actually gained 20 of his 29 yards on one of the few sideline balls that Brock Purdy was able to fit in on San Francisco’s best drive of the game. Kittle finishes the regular season with a 57/628 receiving line in just 11 starts. He’ll be available for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against an as-of-yet undetermined opponent next weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8741-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 3-of-4 targets for 24 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8744-d968-a19b-dff5dc120000</link>
      <description>He played 37-of-42 snaps and out-targeted Kendrick Bourne four to one in San Francisco’s finale. Assuming Ricky Pearsall is able to play in the Wild Card round, this won’t matter much. But it is worth noting that Robinson could be the DFS punt we’re interested in — rather than Bourne — if Pearsall is sidelined again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8744-d968-a19b-dff5dc120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaylen Waddle (ribs) is not expected to play in Week 18 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-892b-d56e-afff-efeb09c70000</link>
      <description>The same is true of De’Von Achane, who is listed as doubtful with a shoulder injury. Like most teams with nothing to play for in Week 18, the Dolphins are shutting their key players down this week. The Patriots shouldn’t have any issues versus Miami this week. A win gives them the No. 2 seed in the AFC. An unlikely Denver loss on top of a New England win would give the Pats the No. 1 seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-892b-d56e-afff-efeb09c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports De’Von Achane (shoulder) is not expected to play in Week 18 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8930-d56e-afff-eff8b91d0000</link>
      <description>This really isn’t much of a surprise. Achane was listed as doubtful after missing all three practices this week. The Dolphins are out of the playoff hunt, so there’s no reason to play Achane through the shoulder issue. Jaylen Wright should handle the bulk of the backfield touches for Miami this week, putting him on the RB2/3 border for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8930-d56e-afff-eff8b91d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
