<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>WR David Bell retired from the NFL after three seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45f-dd4c-afb9-e7df31760000</link>
      <description>The 24-year-old noted that he was dealing with an “off-field injury that was beyond my control, which put my football future in jeopardy.” We know that Bell underwent hip surgery in September of 2024. He had 41 catches for 408 yards in three seasons with the Browns, and looked like he was in the mix to be a starter at times. Alas, the 2022 third-rounder could not get back to full health and walks away from the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e45f-dd4c-afb9-e7df31760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed G Matt Peart (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e47a-db72-a199-fe7b6e640000</link>
      <description>Peart filled in for Ben Powers, who went on injured reserve last week, against the Jets in London. Denver will need to go back to the bench for Week 7’s game against the Giants. Peart will miss at least the next four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e47a-db72-a199-fe7b6e640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Treylon Burks is visiting the Broncos on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e48d-d94a-a79d-ed8d02300000</link>
      <description>He’ll add the Commanders to the visit card tomorrow. The 25-year-old probably doesn’t have major untapped fantasy potential at this point, but he’s got the NFL size and speed to hang on at the end of rosters for a few years if he can catch a coaching staff’s eye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e48d-d94a-a79d-ed8d02300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals DE Trey Hendrickson (hip) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e497-db72-a199-fedfc4d10000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimation. We also should note that the injury designation changed from “back” to “hip” on Monday. Hendrickson is probably enough of a vet to suit up on Thursday with no practice, but it feels like the odds of it actually happening are getting slim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e497-db72-a199-fedfc4d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Tanner Hudson (concussion) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e499-d94a-a79d-ed9d81270000</link>
      <description>He’ll almost certainly be ruled out. Noah Fant has some TE2 and single-game slate upside on Thursday night with Mike Gesicki likely heading to injured reserve and Hudson not stealing snaps from him. That’ll leave just Fant and Drew Sample as oft-used cogs of the Bengals tight end room that are still healthy enough for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e499-d94a-a79d-ed9d81270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent quarterbacks Kyle Trask, Tanner Mordecai, Jarren Hall, and Jeff Driskel visited with the Colts on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e49b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbaeb60000</link>
      <description>None of the four of them signed yet, so it’s possible the Colts are just doing some homework on a potential Anthony Richardson replacement at backup quarterback rather than settling for this pool of candidates. Trask hadn’t had a workout since being released by the Bucs at last cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e49b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbaeb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said DJ Moore (groin) is “day by day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4a4-d94a-a79d-edad05f20000</link>
      <description>Moore was transported to a hospital following the game, per a statement released by the Bears. He played 60 of 64 offensive snaps in the game, per PFF. Marquee noted that Moore did show a “slight hobble” at some point in the first quarter after being hit on his lower left side. This will be something to watch out for on Wednesday’s injury report. Moore being down would seem to give Luther Burden a chance to shine in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4a4-d94a-a79d-edad05f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers released EDGE Clelin Ferrell.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4bf-db72-a199-feff11b30000</link>
      <description>Ferrell was the fourth pick of the 2019 NFL Draft, but he’s come nowhere close to living up to those expectations and served in a reserve role for the Commanders and 49ers over the past two seasons. The 28-year-old defender is released to make room for Jaret Patterson, who was signed to the practice squad in a corresponding transaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4bf-db72-a199-feff11b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived WR Jalen Cropper.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4c7-d94a-a79d-edcfe9cf0000</link>
      <description>Cropper, 24, has only played eight offensive snaps, but has been a contributor to the special teams unit. It wouldn’t be a massive surprise if he rejoined Dallas on the practice squad if/when he goes unclaimed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4c7-d94a-a79d-edcfe9cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Pelissero of NFL Network reports that the Colts are signing Brett Rypien to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4d8-db72-a199-fedb29190000</link>
      <description>The Colts worked out several quarterbacks in the wake of the injury to Anthony Richardson, but it appears Rypien has won that spot. He’ll likely be the third quarterback behind Daniel Jones and Riley Leonard with Richardson on injured reserve due to his orbital fracture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e4d8-db72-a199-fedb29190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
