<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 15:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent DE Drake Jackson is scheduled to meet with the Jets, Commanders, and Ravens in the coming days.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</link>
      <description>Jackson was waived with a failed injury designation earlier this offseason after a knee injury prematurely ended his 2023 campaign and kept him out for all of 2024. Now cleared for a return, the former second-round pick has totaled six sacks in 23 career games, but could provide help to a team in need of bolstering its pass rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (ankle) will play in Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</link>
      <description>Garrett was a DNP to open the week and was upgraded to a limited participant in Thursday’s practice. Garrett’s injury doesn’t appear too severe at this point. We would expect him to see his normal assortment of snaps as he looks to get after Carson Wentz in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Newsome (hamstring) is questionable for Week 5’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</link>
      <description>Newsome popped up on Thursday’s injury report with a hamstring and will officially be questionable entering the week. It’s never a good sign when a player is a late addition to the injury report, and the Browns will need all hands on deck if they hope to slow the receiving duo of Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison. If he’s unable to go, backup Myles Harden appears next in line to receive snaps. In addition to Newsome, RT Jack Conklin (elbow), who hasn’t played since Week 1, is also questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out J.J. McCarthy (ankle) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa27-dca3-a9fb-bfbf8d000000</link>
      <description>It was reported shortly after McCarthy suffered his ankle injury that the Vikings were hoping McCarthy could return for Week 7, so a Week 5 absence has long been expected. McCarthy was a DNP in practice all week, despite hopes he would be able to suit up at some point. McCarthy will have a bye in Week 6 to get right before trying to take the field in Week 7. Carson Wentz will again start for the Vikings in Sunday’s game in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa27-dca3-a9fb-bfbf8d000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out C Ryan Kelly (concussion) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa30-d95b-addb-ea7652f10000</link>
      <description>In addition to Kelly, backup center Michael Jurgens (hamstring) has also been ruled out. The Vikings will also be out RT Brian O’Neill (knee) and LG Donovan Jackson (wrist), leaving the offensive line particularly thin against a physical Browns defensive front that’s led by Myles Garrett. With a Week 6 bye on the horizon, the Vikings will hope a week away will give their team plenty of time to heal up once they return stateside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa30-d95b-addb-ea7652f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) for Week 5 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa35-deb6-a7fd-fbff3c4d0000</link>
      <description>Van Ginkel suffered his neck injury in Week 2 and hasn’t been heard from since. The veteran linebacker has yet to return to the practice field, but will have a Week 6 bye before setting his sights on Week 7 against the Eagles. The Vikings’ decision not to place him on injured reserve suggests they believe he could return after the bye, but the proof will be in his practice status ahead of Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa35-deb6-a7fd-fbff3c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers DT Kalia Davis will undergo surgery to repair a broken hand.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa3a-dca3-a9fb-bfbb8b940000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport was first to report the surgery. According to Rap, Davis “could miss as few as two games,” and the fourth-year lineman is expected to return to play with a club on his hand. Davis has totaled seven tackles and two TFLs in five starts for the 49ers this season, and is quietly stepping into a key role for Kyle Shanahan’s defense after spending the previous two seasons as a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa3a-dca3-a9fb-bfbb8b940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (foot) is expected to miss Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa40-d6e9-af9d-aad077970000</link>
      <description>Things have been trending in this direction ever since Irving first went down. He was spotted in a walking boot and using crutches on Wednesday and was a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday. The reports are that Irving’s injury isn’t believed to be long-term, but the Buccaneers’ RB1 will miss at least one game. With Irving sidelined, the Buccaneers will likely utilize a backfield split with Rachaad White and Sean Tucker, with White as the preferred option on passing downs. He should have some nice value in PPR leagues after thriving as one of the top PPR scams in fantasy since entering the league in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa40-d6e9-af9d-aad077970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joseph Person reports Chuba Hubbard (calf) is not expected to land on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa69-d6e9-af9d-aaf957d50000</link>
      <description>Person reports that Hubbard “will miss Sunday’s home game against the Dolphins, according to a league source,” although we are still waiting for the team to confirm as much when they release their final injury report before the weekend. According to Person, the calf injury Hubbard is dealing with is a similar one that cost him two games at the end of last season. We’ll see if he’s able to practice ahead of Week 6’s game against the Cowboys, but for now, it will be Rico Dowdle leading the Panthers’ backfield into Week 5 against the Fins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa69-d6e9-af9d-aaf957d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LB Nakobe Dean (knee) will not be activated for Week 5 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa79-d6e9-af9d-aaf933260000</link>
      <description>Dean, who began practicing earlier this week, took to his Instagram to share that he will miss Sunday’s game against the Broncos. The fourth-year vet is still working his way back from a torn patellar tendon he suffered last postseason, but is nearing a return after the team opened his practice window earlier in the week. With the Eagles set to play on Thursday night in Week 6, it wouldn’t be surprising if the team also opted to hold him out of the short week before giving him a chance to return in Week 7. Things remain up in the air at this time, but with only 21 days to activate him after designating him for a return, the Eagles will have Dean back in short order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa79-d6e9-af9d-aaf933260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
