<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:03:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Don Van Natta and Seth Wickersham report Bill Belichick was not voted into the Pro Football Hall Of Fame on the first ballot.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-019d-d35e-a1bf-45df86290000</link>
      <description>The Pro Football Hall Of Fame voting process is an annual disaster, so this qualifies as disappointing but not all that surprising. ESPN’s column refers to former Colts general manager Bill Polian as a cheerleader for having Belichick “wait a year” before induction on account of the Spygate and Deflategate scandals. There’s not really a way to tell the story of the modern NFL without the six-time Super Bowl champion head coach who won 333 games over the course of his career, of course. There’s little doubt that he will eventually be a Hall of Famer. (The actual HOF announcements are coming next week.) Because of the way voting is grouped, Belichick was up against Robert Kraft, Ken Anderson, Roger Craig, and I.C. Greenwood. It’s unknown whether any of the members of that group got 80 percent of the vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-019d-d35e-a1bf-45df86290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports new Bills head coach Joe Brady will retain offensive play-calling duties.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01c0-d35e-a1bf-45c2df670000</link>
      <description>Brady spent the past two seasons as the Bills’ offensive coordinator and play-caller after getting the interim offensive coordinator job in 2023. Garafolo reports that Brady will continue to call offensive plays after the Bills promoted him to head coach. Despite Buffalo aiming for some change after firing Sean McDermott, the team retains familiarity on offense. Brady’s offenses ranked top-three in EPA per play in both 2024 and 2025. With offensive play-calling settled, Brady will need to find a defensive play-caller and an offensive coordinator to work with in evolving Josh Allen’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01c0-d35e-a1bf-45c2df670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Cardinals interviewed former Commanders head coach Ron Rivera for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01ca-d35e-a1bf-45ca85ab0000</link>
      <description>Rivera, 64, is currently the general manager for the University of California’s football program. He was head coach of the Panthers from 2011-2019, leading the team to a Super Bowl appearance and winning NFL Coach of the Year twice. Rivera then coached the Commanders form 2020-2023 to more lackluster results, failing to finish with a winning record across four seasons. The Cardinals are continuing to search for the right head coaching candidate and Rivera, who has been out of the NFL for two years, is the latest on the interview list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01ca-d35e-a1bf-45ca85ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt reports the Jets “reached out to Jon Gruden about the idea of joining Aaron Glenn’s staff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01fb-d56e-afff-e7fb09550000</link>
      <description>Gruden, however, “wasn’t interested in the job.” Jets head coach Aaron Glenn is turning over much of his coaching staff after a less-than-ideal first year on the job. Rosenblatt reports the team apparently contacted Gruden, who did not have interest in taking on a role under Glenn. Gruden has not coached since resigning from the Raiders after a scandal involving emails using bigoted language during the 2021 season. He consulted with the Saints in 2023 but has been out of the league since. The Jets’ staff turnover will decidedly not include Gruden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-01fb-d56e-afff-e7fb09550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Broncos passing game coordinator Davis Webb received requests to interview for the Ravens, Eagles, and Giants offensive coordinator vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0295-d968-a19c-5af5aa2b0000</link>
      <description>Webb has been interviewing around the head coaching circuit this cycle and is now getting offensive coordinator requests with head coaching jobs filling up. The Ravens interviewed him for head coach and are now interested in bringing him back in to call plays for Lamar Jackson’s offense. John Harbaugh’s Giants may pivot from Todd Monken at offensive coordinator if Monken takes the Browns’ head coaching job, while the Eagles have yet to fill their offensive coordinator position. With the Broncos parting ways with Joe Lombardi, Webb is a candidate for his current employer’s offensive coordinator role as well. Webb is a highly coveted offensive mind who will likely find an offensive coordinator role this offseason and will be a name we hear again in future coaching cycles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0295-d968-a19c-5af5aa2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers requested an interview Broncos defensive pass game coordinator Jim Leonhard for the team’s defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-04fe-d927-a99f-aefef5280000</link>
      <description>Leonhard, a former Bills safety, has spoken to Buffalo about the team’s defensive coordinator opening. Now he’s getting interest from Jim Harbaugh and the Chargers, who lost defensive coordinator Jesse Minter to the Ravens this month. In LA, Leonhard would take over a stellar defensive group that last year allowed the league’s seventh lowest yards per play and the fifth lowest offensive success rate. Only three defenses allowed a lower EPA per rushing attempt than the Bolts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-04fe-d927-a99f-aefef5280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Browns will hire former Ravens offensive coordinator Todd Monken as the team’s head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0503-d452-afdd-f7336fac0000</link>
      <description>Monken, after coaching one of the NFL’s most efficient offenses over the past three seasons, will take over as Cleveland’s head coach after the team had several coaching candidates withdraw their name from consideration in recent days. Monken, 59, was the Browns offensive coordinator back in 2019, when the team ranked 22nd in most yards and points. He’s also served as OC for the Bucs. “By choosing Monken,” Russini said, “the Browns select a respected offensive mind with experience.” It’s not known whether Monken will retain Browns defensive coordinator Jim Schwartz, who was a candidate for the top job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0503-d452-afdd-f7336fac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets hired former Dolphins pass game coordinator Brian Duker as the team’s defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0576-d452-afdd-f777ec5f0000</link>
      <description>A dark horse to land the New York DC job, Duker, 36, will take over one of the NFL’s worst defenses in 2026 after a season of coaching the Miami secondary. Duker worked with Jets head coach Aaron Glenn when both were in Detroit from 2021 to 2023. Duker will be tasked with improving a New York defense that last year became the first defense in NFL history to not record a single interception. The Jets in 2025 allowed the league’s third highest EPA per play. No team was worse against the pass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0576-d452-afdd-f777ec5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Browns defensive coordinator Jim Schwartz plans to leave the team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-059b-d927-a99f-afbf05500000</link>
      <description>Former Ravens OC Todd Monken got the Browns head coaching job on Wednesday after an extensive search, and after it appeared the Browns were set to promote Schwartz to the top job. Rapoport said the Browns “would like to retain Schwartz, who is under contract. The respected DC may have other plans. He’s coveted.” It looks like Schwartz will coach elsewhere in 2026 after being passed over, though there’s a chance he stays with Cleveland under Monken. Schwartz’s Browns offense in 2025 allowed the league’s fourth lowest success rate and third lowest EPA per play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-059b-d927-a99f-afbf05500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Rams and Steelers have requested an interview with Browns special teams coordinator Bubba Ventrone.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05b9-d452-afdd-f7bbcd800000</link>
      <description>Pelissero said Ventrone, widely seen as one of the NFL’s best special teams coaches, is not expected to stay on with new Cleveland head coach Todd Monken, who will presumably clean house and bring in his own coaches for 2026. The Rams in 2025 had what was by most measures the worst special teams unit while the Steelers were mostly middle of the pack in special teams metrics. Ventrone’s Browns allowed the seventh most yards per kickoff return and the fifth most yards per punt return in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05b9-d452-afdd-f7bbcd800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
