<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions listed C Graham Glasgow (knee) as a DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7b6-db57-afda-f7b65d640000</link>
      <description>LT Taylor Decker (shoulder), RG Tate Ratledge (knee), and RT Penei Sewell (ankle) were all listed as limited on the estimated report. Every player on this list played in Week 12’s game against the Giants and was listed as limited/DNP last week. Monday’s report is probably more of a load management thing, so until we hear otherwise, we’ll assume the Lions’ OL will operate at close to full strength against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7b6-db57-afda-f7b65d640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) is practicing in full ahead of Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7bf-db57-afda-f7bf59810000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as Watson has played through this listing each of the last two weeks and has mainly been limited for maintenance purposes as he works into shape following last year’s ACL tear. He’ll be Green Bay’s No. 1 wideout in Week 13 assuming things go as expected, making him perhaps worthy of a WR3 role in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7bf-db57-afda-f7bf59810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c1-d413-ad9f-b7dd31d60000</link>
      <description>He played through the calf listing on Sunday, catching 32 yards and continuing to be an afterthought in an offense that doesn’t implicitly want to throw. Wicks will only be a factor for Thursday slate contests, and even then he’s hard to trust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c1-d413-ad9f-b7dd31d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers listed WR Romeo Doubs (wrist) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7bf-d82c-a79a-b7bf9fd90000</link>
      <description>Doubs played through the same wrist injury in Week 12’s win over the Vikings and was removed from the injury report by the end of last week. His estimated status to open this week suggests he’ll be good to go for Thursday’s game against the Lions, but there’s little reason for fantasy managers to lean on him this week given his wildly inconsistent production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7bf-d82c-a79a-b7bf9fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savion Williams (foot) did not practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c3-d413-ad9f-b7df07850000</link>
      <description>He played through the foot listing last week, generating zero yards on his lone touch. Non-dynasty managers don’t have to worry about Williams this season between his lack of progress and Green Bay’s lack of interest in throwing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c3-d413-ad9f-b7df07850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c4-d413-ad9f-b7dd53a30000</link>
      <description>We’re not expecting the Packers to activate Reed ahead of Thanksgiving’s date with the Lions, but it’s also not completely off the table after limited sessions on Friday of last week and this estimation here. If Reed did play, the long layoff and likely snap count would render him a hard-to-trust option in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c4-d413-ad9f-b7dd53a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers listed Josh Jacobs (knee) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c3-d82c-a79a-b7d7c72b0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs fought to play in Week 12’s game against the Vikings but was ultimately scratched before kickoff. The veteran running back said last week that he was hoping to miss only one game at most, so it’s safe to assume he’s trending in the right direction for Thursday’s game against the Lions. We’ll continue to monitor him throughout the week, but if Jacobs unable to go, Emanuel Wilson will be a volume-based RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c3-d82c-a79a-b7d7c72b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers listed Matthew Golden (wrist) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c6-d90e-a9da-bfcfe5120000</link>
      <description>Golden didn’t play in Week 12’s game against the Vikings despite being listed as a limited participant all week. Even if he is able to suit up for this week’s game against the Lions, Golden has totaled just six catches for 37 yards and no touchdowns in his last three games. Whether he’s active or not, fantasy managers can pass on Golden in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7c6-d90e-a9da-bfcfe5120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Samaje Perine (ankle) practiced in full on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7cd-db57-afda-f7ffe02f0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimation, but it’s a rapid recovery from Perine after being doubtful for Week 12. Perine left Week 9 against the Bears with a high-ankle sprain and has not played since. His return would prevent Chase Brown from hogging the whole workload pie against the Ravens, much to the chagrin of Brown-reliant managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7cd-db57-afda-f7ffe02f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Burrow is practicing in full for Week 13’s game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7d1-d82c-a79a-b7d59a0e0000</link>
      <description>Burrow has all but announced on Instagram that he’ll be back, Zac Taylor couldn’t bring himself to say the words but we all know what is implied in “anticipating” a return. Burrow will almost certainly start against the Ravens and return to the QB1 line while Joe Flacco (shoulder/finger, limited) heads back to the bench on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7d1-d82c-a79a-b7d59a0e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
