<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e39-deb6-a7fd-7ffff5260000</link>
      <description>Tuten was listed with a shoulder injury for all of last week’s practices, but was ultimately removed from the injury report ahead of the Jaguars’ Week 3 game against the Texans. The rookie carried the ball six times and played just 12 snaps, which could both be a function of the shoulder injury and LeQuint Allen’s rise as the pass-catching back. Tuten is still trending to play in Week 4, but his utilization may still be low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e39-deb6-a7fd-7ffff5260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e3c-d6e9-af9d-febc815a0000</link>
      <description>Adams has a sore hamstring and sat out of Wednesday’s practice, which is generally a rest day for him anyways. Head coach Sean McVay does not anticipate it impacting Adams’ status for Week 4 against the Colts. The 32-year-old has a 13/213/1 stat line through three games and profiles as a fantasy WR2 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e3c-d6e9-af9d-febc815a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e49-dca3-a9fb-7fd9ea4a0000</link>
      <description>Bowers has been dealing with a knee injury since Week 1, but was taken off the injury report after three limited practices ahead of Week 3. He starts out this week as a full participant and is likely to play Week 4 against the Bears. Fellow tight end Michael Mayer (concussion) did not practice after suffering the concussion in Week 3. Bowers has had a pair of middling games since suffering the injury, but he is still a top-three tight end play for fantasy purposes, especially if Mayer is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e49-dca3-a9fb-7fd9ea4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jacory Croskey-Merritt (knee) missing Wednesday’s practice was “precautionary”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e53-d6e9-af9d-fed3f2d10000</link>
      <description>Fowler reports that Croskey-Merritt was “a little sore” after Sunday’s game against the Raiders, but he has felt better and “the hope is that practice rest is precautionary.” Bill’s addition to the injury report is perhaps a result of a violent running style that scored him a touchdown in Week 3. ESPN Commanders beat report John Keim added the injury is “not considered to be anything serious at all.” Expect Bill to play in Week 4 against the Falcons, though he is still in a committee that caps his ceiling in the RB3 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e53-d6e9-af9d-fed3f2d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said Brock Purdy (toe) looked “really good” in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-80c8-d6e9-af9d-8ad86fe80000</link>
      <description>Lynch added, “His progression has been really a good one.” All signs point toward Purdy returning to the lineup in Week 4, though Lynch did note that the team still needs to see how Purdy responds to Thursday’s practice. ac Jones is dealing with an injury of his own, a re-aggravation of the knee injury he suffered in the preseason, so there may be more urgency to get Purdy back in the lineup this week. Assuming nothing goes wrong, Purdy is in line to start versus the Jags. The 49ers will likely lean on their ground game to keep Purdy out of harm’s way, putting him in the QB2 ranks for his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-80c8-d6e9-af9d-8ad86fe80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets coach Aaron Glenn said Justin Fields (concussion) will start in week 4 against the Dolphins if he is cleared to play.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-819c-deb6-a7fd-d3dfc6a20000</link>
      <description>Glenn stoked the quarterback controversy flames when asked about Fields earlier this week. He dodged the question, only saying, “We’ll talk about that today as a staff.” He didn’t leave any room for speculation when addressing the matter today. The Jets play on Monday, meaning their injury report is a day behind most teams. We will get more info on Fields’ availability when the team’s first injury report of the week drops later today, but Fields is expected to practice in some capacity today. Tyrod Taylor will make his second start of the year if Fields is unable to suit up versus the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-819c-deb6-a7fd-d3dfc6a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Josh Reynolds (hamstring) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81b6-deb6-a7fd-d3ff499a0000</link>
      <description>Reynolds ran every route for the Jets in Week 1 but was only targeted three times. He has missed the past two games with a hamstring injury. Even as an every-down player, Reynolds isn’t on the fantasy radar for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81b6-deb6-a7fd-d3ff499a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said Brandon Aiyuk (knee, PUP) is “not close” to returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81c8-deb6-a7fd-d3df6cab0000</link>
      <description>Aiyuk is still working his way back from the multi-ligament knee injury he suffered last year. He tore his ACL but also damaged other ligaments, significantly extending his timeline to return to action. Lynch has consistently taken a cautious approach when talking about Aiyuk’s recovery, so his most recent comments don’t come as much of a surprise. We’re likely at least a month out from seeing Aiyuk back on the field. In fantasy leagues without an injured reserve, it may be tough to hold him for that long.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81c8-deb6-a7fd-d3df6cab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OC Josh Grizzard said Baker Mayfield (biceps) is taking mental reps and preparing to play.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7dc4-d95b-addb-7dc681b10000</link>
      <description>Per Grizzard, Mayfield was limited again on Thursday and is healthy enough to participate in walkthroughs. In avideoposted by the Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Mayfield can be seen taking mock shotgun snaps “with a sleeve on his right throwing arm.” After completing the drill’s quick footwork, he then underhand-tossed the football back to his coach with his right throwing arm. Fantasy managers should view Mayfield as being truly questionable to play in Week 4. Hopefully, he can increase his practice participation on Friday without re-injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7dc4-d95b-addb-7dc681b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers (shoulder) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81e9-dca3-a9fb-bdf94ea20000</link>
      <description>No word yet on Nabers’ participation level. We expect him to be limited today, with decent odds of upgrading to full on Friday. The Giants already have the 22-year-old superstar on a veteran practice plan, which makes sense. Nabers is a game-tilting talent who has been listed with six different injuries in his young career. He is an elite WR1 against the Chargers in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-81e9-dca3-a9fb-bdf94ea20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
