<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:02:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs opened the 21-day practice window for WR Mike Evans (collarbone).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4cc-db57-afda-f6fe51410000</link>
      <description>Evans gained medical clearance, per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, and could suit up as early as this Sunday against the panthers. Evans would likely take over as the team’s No. 1 receiver of struggling rookie WR Emeka Egbuka and Chris Godwin. Evans has 14 catches for 140 yards and a touchdown on 32 targets this season. His return to the Tampa offense is a fantasy boon for Baker Mayfield, whose efficiency has fallen off with Evans sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4cc-db57-afda-f6fe51410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts CB Sauce Gardner (calf) is expected to avoid injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d0-d6c4-abfb-f6d368e00000</link>
      <description>Gardner, Rapoport believes, could return to the Colts lineup within the next four weeks. That opens up the possibility that Gardner could be at full health — or something close to it — if the Colts right the ship and make it to the postseason. The Colts are expected to be careful with Gardner’s calf injury in hopes of not complicating the injury in a way that would jeopardize the corner’s entire season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d0-d6c4-abfb-f6d368e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano believes the Panthers will pick up Bryce Young’s fifth-year option in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d5-d90e-a9da-ffdfd48a0000</link>
      <description>Panthers coaches and front office officials “still believe in” Young despite his ups and downs this season, including a Week 13 meltdown against a weak Niners defense. Young finished the 2024 season on a hot streak after being benched early that season, but started 2025 with baffling decision making and poor throws both in the short areas and downfield. On the season Young ranks 21st out of 33 qualifying quarterbacks in drop back success rate and 30th out of 40 quarterbacks in yards per attempt. Graziano said he expects the Panthers to keep Young around in 2026 “because the cost will be reasonable (around $26.5 million), but then the question becomes what to do after that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d5-d90e-a9da-ffdfd48a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said the team wants Kyren Williams fresh for the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4ea-d90e-a9da-ffefd5350000</link>
      <description>In other words, the LA backfield split between Williams and Blake Corum will continue in the final weeks of the regular season. “LaFleur told me he thinks they’ve been seeing the best version of Williams because he’s fresher and not being asked to carry as much of the load, and the Rams have their sights set on January and February games and want everyone as fresh as possible,” ESPN’s Dan Graziano said. Over the Rams’ past five games, Williams leads the backfield with 76 rushing attempts to 48 rushes for Corum. Williams has an outsized lead in running back routes, but only six targets over the past five games. Williams, dealing with an ankle injury, will be a touchdown-dependent RB2 in Week 14 against the Cardinals if he suits up. Corum should be stashed in all leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4ea-d90e-a9da-ffefd5350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns opened the 21-day practice window for QB Deshaun Watson (Achilles).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e503-d6c4-abfb-f7032cc40000</link>
      <description>The move injects even more drama into the team’s quarterback situation after Shedeur Sanders took over as starter and is expected to remain starter for the final month of the regular season. Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said opening Watson’s practice window was a “good next step” for the veteran, though he wouldn’t commit to a timeline for Watson’s return to game action. Watson, 29, re-ruptured Achilles tendon in the offseason and has been rehabbing ever since. Watson has 19 touchdowns and 12 interceptions for the Browns over his three seasons with the team after signing perhaps the most catastrophic contract in pro sports history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e503-d6c4-abfb-f7032cc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) practiced on a limited basis Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e52e-db57-afda-f73e2caf0000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign that Kincaid could finally return to the Buffalo offense in Week 14 against the Bengals, a defense that has been tormented by opposing tight ends all year. No defense allows more tight end receptions, targets, yards, or touchdowns than the Bengals. If Kincaid suits up for Week 14, he’ll be a must play option in all formats. Kincaid in 2025 has been targeted on 27 percent of his routes, the highest rate in the league among tight ends. Dawson Knox would be an excellent streamer if Kincaid is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e52e-db57-afda-f73e2caf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said EDGE Joey Bosa (hamstring) is considered “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e538-d90e-a9da-ff3f1d1c0000</link>
      <description>Bosa did not practice Wednesday and seems unlikely to play in Week 14 against the Bengals. His absence could make things a little easier for Joe Burrow and the Bengals offense, as the Bills sports the league’s tenth highest QB pressure rate (24 percent) and the 11th highest QB hurry rate (9 percent). McDermott suggested the team’s medical staff believed Bosa wouldn’t be out for long.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e538-d90e-a9da-ff3f1d1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e549-db57-afda-f77b3e340000</link>
      <description>It’s a bad sign for London’s Week 14 availability against the Seahawks. London has missed the Falcons’ past two games and the team doesn’t appear to be in a hurry to rush him back into game action with the postseason out of reach. With London sidelined over the past two weeks, Kyle Pitts has led Atlanta pass catchers with 13 targets and nine receptions. Bijan Robinson has nine targets over those two games and Darnell Mooney has eight. Mooney is a viable 14-team league flex option for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e549-db57-afda-f77b3e340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Josh Palmer (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e554-d6c4-abfb-f75729a40000</link>
      <description>The oft-injured Palmer would seem to be a long shot for Week 14 against the Bengals. Palmer missed Week 13 against the Steelers while dealing with his lingering ankle issue. He has 18 receptions for 272 yards over eight games in 2025 and would not be fantasy relevant if he suits up. Keon Coleman should continue operating as a starter in the run-heavy Buffalo offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e554-d6c4-abfb-f75729a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs placed LT Josh Simmons (wrist) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e55d-d6c4-abfb-f75f1bae0000</link>
      <description>Simmons had surgery on his injured wrist and will miss at least a month, making a postseason return possible if the Chiefs finish the season strong and sneak into the playoffs. The loss of Simmons is significant for Patrick Mahomes and the KC offense: Pro Football Focus grades Simmons 21st in pass blocking out of 85 qualifying tackles this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e55d-d6c4-abfb-f75f1bae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
