<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 6-of-8 passes for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 2 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b410-df63-a199-fd3b4e2f0000</link>
      <description>Stroud played two series, and he ended the second drive with a touchdown pass to Nico Collins on fourth-and-goal. It’s possible Stroud will play in the preseason finale, but the Texans obviously know what they have in the third-year quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b410-df63-a199-fd3b4e2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dalton exited Saturday’s Week 2 preseason game against the Texans with a right elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b417-d45c-a7fc-b61f067b0000</link>
      <description>Dalton completed 2-for-4 passes for 22 yards before leaving. The 37-year-old’s exit appears to be precautionary, but it’s plausible that Dalton will undergo testing to determine the severity of the injury. Jack Plummer has taken over at quarterback and likely will play the remainder of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b417-d45c-a7fc-b61f067b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Goodson left Saturday’s Week 2 preseason game against the Packers with an elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b412-d45c-a7fc-b61aac560000</link>
      <description>Goodson carried twice for 10 yards with a touchdown before the exit. The 24-year-old is competing to be the backup tailback with Khalil Herbert and DJ Giddens. There should be an update on Giddens early next week, at the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b412-d45c-a7fc-b61aac560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel completed 13-of-18 passes for 143 yards with no touchdowns and an interception in the Browns’ Week 2 preseason game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b439-d90d-a5bd-b67b755d0000</link>
      <description>Gabriel also lost a fumble and took two sacks. The southpaw quarterback had some solid moments, but he threw a pass into congestion that was intercepted and taken to the house by fellow rookie Andrew Mukuba. Gabriel is battling Shedeur Sanders to be the third quarterback on the roster, and based on how they played in their exhibition contests, right now it seems to be advantage Sanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b439-d90d-a5bd-b67b755d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones completed 7-of-11 passes for 101 yards in the Colts’ preseason Week 2 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b43e-d90d-a5bd-b67fc0b30000</link>
      <description>Jones also fumbled but was able to recover it. The 28-year-old led the Colts to one score in his three drives before giving way to Anthony Richardson. Jones played decently and was statistically better than Richardson, but it’d be fair to say that neither signal-caller clearly separated themself — nor hurt themself, to be fair — during the preseason contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b43e-d90d-a5bd-b67fc0b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB Tyler Shough will start the team’s second preseason game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b401-d05a-adda-be836a450000</link>
      <description>This makes the most sense from an organizational level as the team hunts for their starting quarterback for the regular season. Shough was selected in the second round of the 2025 NFL Draft but comes into the league as a 25-year-old rookie after a tumultuous collegiate career, having played seven seasons for three different schools. The Saints almost certainly want to see if he can be more than a bridge quarterback in the league considering Spencer Rattler has looked nothing more than a replacement level backup during his short professional career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b401-d05a-adda-be836a450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Richardson completed 6-of-11 passes for 73 yards in the Colts’ preseason Week 2 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b444-d05a-adda-bec60cc50000</link>
      <description>Richardson didn’t get into the game until the second quarter. It’s worth noting that the third-year quarterback did lead the Colts to two scores compared to one for Daniel Jones, but Jones was the better quarterback statistically while completing 7-of-11 passes for 102 yards. The 23-year-old had some issues inside of the red zone, and his best throw — a 38-yard connection with Anthony Gould — was taken away due to penalty. It’s truly a guess at this point who will start for the Colts in Week 1 of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b444-d05a-adda-bec60cc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarShawn Lloyd rushed six times for 15 yards and caught 1-for-4 targets for 33 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b455-d05a-adda-bed7575f0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd wasn’t able to find a ton of room as a runner, but did show off his athleticism on the 33-yard reception. The 24-year-old played ahead of Emmanuel Wilson, and while Wilson outrush Lloyd with 33 yards, Wilson did lose a fumble. Right now, there doesn’t seem to be a clear backup answer to Josh Jacobs in Green Bay, and fantasy managers who roster Jacobs may need to look elsewhere for a safety valve behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b455-d05a-adda-bed7575f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Etienne rushed seven times for 18 yards in the Panthers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b469-d05a-adda-beeb9b6f0000</link>
      <description>Etienne also caught one pass for seven yards on his only target. The 21-year-old is attempting to work his way into a role with the Panthers after being selected in the fourth round, but he hasn’t looked the part in these first two preseason games. Chuba Hubbard was always there starter, but Rico Dowdle will be the backup to open the year with Etienne unlikely to see many touches to begin the campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b469-d05a-adda-beeb9b6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 7 times for 40 yards while catching his lone target for no gain in the Texans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b46f-d05a-adda-beefeab30000</link>
      <description>Marks had a long gain of 12, and looked solid after Nick Chubb exited the game along with the other starters. The former USC tailback has some potential dynasty upside, but isn’t likely to be a helper in redraft leagues this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b46f-d05a-adda-beefeab30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
