<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3351-da28-afbb-f77d41390000</link>
      <description>Reporters expected a DNP, but McDuffie got in a limited session officially. We still consider him at least a bit unlikely to miss Week 16’s game against the Titans, but McDuffie is at least making a play to be active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3351-da28-afbb-f77d41390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez (hamstring) was not on Washington’s final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3353-da28-afbb-f77f3d5b0000</link>
      <description>He got in full sessions all week and should be a usable-if-unexciting FLEX play as Washington’s lead back against Philadelphia, in a game they are expected to trail in. The silver lining is that Jalen Carter (shoulders) was ruled out, so it should be easier sledding inside at least for Rodriguez. “Bill” Croskey-Merritt will likely revert to a backup role in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3353-da28-afbb-f77f3d5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LT Dion Dawkins (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3355-d087-addf-b3f5406d0000</link>
      <description>Players typically play through illnesses, but it would be nice to see Dawkins practice tomorrow after sitting out on Wednesday and Thursday. The Bills’ offensive line is tasked with fending off the Browns’ elite pass-rush unit this week. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3355-d087-addf-b3f5406d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3341-d087-addf-b3f160340000</link>
      <description>Benford injured his toe last Thursday and was unable to play on Sunday. He has since logged two limited sessions, putting him on track to play. The Browns’ wide receiver corps hardly instills fear, and the Bills have playoff aspirations. It is possible that they hold him out this week, just to play things safely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3341-d087-addf-b3f160340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3356-d35e-a1bf-77d654710000</link>
      <description>As was Brian O’Neill (heel), both upgrades from a Wednesday DNP. Christian Darrisaw (knee) remains sidelined. Still, this is a good update for anyone considering playing a Viking against New York’s woeful defense on Sunday. Most of the offensive line is trending towards being up for this contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3356-d35e-a1bf-77d654710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane (ribs) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-335d-d087-addf-b3fd4a670000</link>
      <description>Great news. Achane practiced fully yesterday as well. He seemingly made it through Week 15 without suffering any setbacks. The Dolphins’ featured running back is ready to rock as an elite RB1 for his matchup against the Bengals’ fantasy-friendly defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-335d-d087-addf-b3fd4a670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Burrow (knee) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-335d-d087-addf-b3fd2bd50000</link>
      <description>Burrow is up to two full sessions this week. He is good to go for his team’s Week 16 game against the Dolphins, though his receiving corps could be short-staffed, with WR Tee Higgins still in the NFL’s concussion protocol. Burrow is a low-end QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-335d-d087-addf-b3fd2bd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints placed RB Devin Neal on injured reserve with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-336a-d35e-a1bf-77ea07760000</link>
      <description>Bummer. His season is over. Neal was playing well in RB Alvin Kamara’s (ankle/knee) stead. Neal can be expected to contribute next year, though he may not have done enough to convince the coaching staff that he deserves to be the 2026 starter. The 22-year-old rookie rushed 57 times for 206 yards and two touchdowns, and caught 17-of-19 targets for 104 yards in his first season with the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-336a-d35e-a1bf-77ea07760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle/knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-336e-d087-addf-b3fe23b00000</link>
      <description>Kamara remains sidelined and RB Devin Neal (hamstring) was placed on injured reserve. Brutal. This leaves the Saints with RBs Evan Hull, Audric Estime and Nyheim Hines. Hines could play on passing downs but he has done very little in recent seasons. The Saints face the Jets this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-336e-d087-addf-b3fe23b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Mason Tipton (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3376-dc7a-af9b-ffffddfc0000</link>
      <description>Tipton still has a chance to play, but this is unideal. With WR Devaughn Vele (shoulder) already ruled out, Tipton is slated for No. 2 wide receiver duties. Saints WR Chris Olave and TE Juwan Johnson should handle significant workloads against the Jets this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3376-dc7a-af9b-ffffddfc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
