<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a248-d6e9-af9d-aad8c09a0000</link>
      <description>Bowers has been nursing his knee injury since Week 1 and starts out this week as a limited practice participant. He likely felt soreness between the Raiders’ 4 loss to the Bears and Wednesday, causing him to be limited, compared to last week when he started out as a full practice participant. Bowers’ knee injury still seems to be hampering him as his usage has not been high volume. Fellow TE Michael Mayer (concussion) was a limited participant in practice after missing Week 4. Between Mayer’s potential return and middling usage amid the knee injury, there is reason to be concerned about Bowers’ fantasy outlook, though he is still a fantasy TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a248-d6e9-af9d-aad8c09a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller said there will be “a jump” in his snap count in Week 5 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a4fa-deb6-a7fd-f7ffe6590000</link>
      <description>Waller added the caveat that his reps would jump if that’s what his coaches want. Given that he scored two touchdowns on 16 snaps and the team lost its No. 1 receiver, we’re going to assume that is indeed what Mike McDaniel has planned for Week 5. Waller barely played tight end in his Miami debut, lining up at an inline position on just two of his 12 routes. He could wind up playing a de facto WR2 role for the team with Jaylen Waddle stepping up as the top option through the air. Even on a limited route tree, Waller looks like a viable streaming tight end for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a4fa-deb6-a7fd-f7ffe6590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed RB Braelon Allen (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a530-deb6-a7fd-f7ff07d30000</link>
      <description>Allen’s injury continues to sound worse with every subsequent report. Per ESPN’s Rich Cimini, surgery remains a possibility and it’s “too early to say if it’s season-ending.” Allen is required to miss at least four weeks while on injured reserve, but we expect him to be out much longer than a month. His absence will increase Breece Hall’s role in short-yardage situations, meaning more opportunities for him at the goal line. Allen has six red zone carries this year to Hall’s three. Isaiah Davis is now in line to back up Hall going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a530-deb6-a7fd-f7ff07d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said EDGE Travon Walker underwent wrist surgery and is considered day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a53d-dca3-a9fb-bdbdbb300000</link>
      <description>Coen noted that Walker could even play in Week 5 when the Jags take on the Chiefs on Monday. Walker left Week 4’s game against the 49ers with the wrist issue and was ruled out after a short trip to the locker room. He saw a specialist later in the week and surgery was ultimately the best option. We would still anticipate Walker to miss at least one game, but the good news is that this isn’t a long-term issue. Walker has two sacks and 14 pressures this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a53d-dca3-a9fb-bdbdbb300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (ankle) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a571-d6e9-af9d-aff1a5540000</link>
      <description>McCarthy hasn’t practiced since injuring his ankle in Week 2. He will be ruled out for Sunday’s game in London later this week, giving Carson Wentz his third straight start. Wentz fell behind early in Week 4 but put together a frantic comeback effort, racking up 350 yards and two scores in a losing effort. Facing a punishing Cleveland defense, he is stuck at the back of the QB2 ranks for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a571-d6e9-af9d-aff1a5540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings EDGE Dallas Turner (illness) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a574-deb6-a7fd-f7ff3bb90000</link>
      <description>A midweek addition to the injury report is never a good sign, but players typically play through illnesses. This is a situation to keep an eye on when the Vikings release their final injury report on Friday, but we fully expect Turner to be active on Sunday morning. The second-year EDGE has one sack and 11 pressures this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a574-deb6-a7fd-f7ff3bb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (knee/biceps) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a58c-deb6-a7fd-f7df8ad00000</link>
      <description>Mayfield has a long history of gutting it out through injuries and this week will be no different. He was listed as a DNP for Wednesday’s walkthrough but will at least go down as a limited participant for Thursday’s session. Barring a setback, Mayfield will be on the field for his Week 5 matchup with Seattle. With Bucky Irving likely out, expect plenty of passing volume for the gunslinger quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a58c-deb6-a7fd-f7df8ad00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a590-deb6-a7fd-f7df33610000</link>
      <description>The news comes from FOX Sports’ Greg Auman. Irving could return to practice after the portion open to the media concludes, but we doubt that will happen. It will be his second DNP of the week, all but guaranteeing he misses Week 5. Irving is dealing with a foot sprain that is not believed to be a long-term issue plus a minor shoulder injury. He was spotted on crutches while wearing a walking boot after Week 4. Rachaad White should draw the start on Sunday, making him one of the top waiver wire adds of the week. Sean Tucker will also be in the mix for touches versus the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a590-deb6-a7fd-f7df33610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed RB Khalil Herbert, formerly of the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a595-d6e9-af9d-af95656c0000</link>
      <description>Herbert signed with the Colts in the offseason but didn’t make their 53-man roster. He briefly joined the Seahawks’ practice squad before the Jets offered him a spot on their active roster. With Braelon Allen on injured reserve, Herbert will operate as the team’s RB3 going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a595-d6e9-af9d-af95656c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel (heel) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a5be-dca3-a9fb-bdbf4a480000</link>
      <description>Samuel got banged up in week 4 and missed Wednesday’s practice, causing some concern for his availability ahead of Week 5. Even a limited session today puts him on track to suit up this week. Terry McLaurin is still highly questionable with a quad issue, meaning Samuel could operate as the Commanders’ top wideout once again. Samuel caught all six of his targets for 72 yards and a score in Week 4. He will slot in as a fantasy WR2 if McLaurin remains sidelined on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a5be-dca3-a9fb-bdbf4a480000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
