<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee/hamstring) is not on Green Bay’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8416-d713-ad9e-ec56805c0000</link>
      <description>Nor is Dontayvion Wicks (calf) — Watson will be a usable FLEX option against a weak Giants defense. Wicks probably is only a deep-league FLEX or WR5 call despite the good matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8416-d713-ad9e-ec56805c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Lukas Van Ness (foot) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 11 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8418-d45b-affe-d59e530d0000</link>
      <description>This was the first week that Van Ness made significant progress in attempting to come back from his Week 6 foot injury, garnering limited sessions on both Thursday and Friday. It remains to be seen if Van Ness can come back this week, but he at least looks close to returning in Week 12 if not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8418-d45b-affe-d59e530d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (hamstring) is questionable to play in Week 11 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8405-d1e7-a1fa-deef09590000</link>
      <description>Ridley remained limited through all three practices. He is seemingly on the wrong side of questionable, and would be very hard to trust in fantasy lineups if he were active. The Titans’ matchup against the Texans’ top-tier pass defense only reinforces concerns. Ridley would only be a boom-bust FLEX if the Titans keep him active on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8405-d1e7-a1fa-deef09590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Parker Washington (hamstring) is not on Jacksonville’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841a-d713-ad9e-ec5e601c0000</link>
      <description>He figures to remain a usable WR3 this week between the uncertainty of an acclimating Jakobi Meyers and Brian Thomas’s ankle injury. Washington led Jacksonville’s wideouts in targets and you can certainly argue for a WR2 ranking this week if you believe that Los Angeles will stamp out Jacksonville’s running game and force them to throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841a-d713-ad9e-ec5e601c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841b-d713-ad9e-ec5f9bcb0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo never graduated to full participation this week, which is a bit surprising, given that the Titans were on bye in Week 10. The veteran tight end cannot be trusted to return TE1 value playing hurt, against the Texans’ elite defense, while losing opportunities to rookie TE Gunnar Helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841b-d713-ad9e-ec5f9bcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 11 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841c-d673-a39e-a49d84ee0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week with an ankle injury and should be considered questionable for Week 12 based on this. John Harbaugh said that Devontez Walker would be “the next man up” at the position, and Walker could be a plausible FLEX play based on how much Cleveland focused on stopping Baltimore’s ground game the last time these two teams played.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841c-d673-a39e-a49d84ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Justice Hill (toe) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 11 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841f-d45b-affe-d59f37520000</link>
      <description>Hill did get in a limited session on Friday, but it wasn’t enough for the Ravens to make him active for Week 11. Keaton Mitchell (knee) was taken off the final injury report and figures to be Baltimore’s No. 2 back on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-841f-d45b-affe-d59f37520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (hip) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8420-d1e7-a1fa-deea9aa40000</link>
      <description>Likely is coming off back-to-back four target games and will be in the TE2 pecking order against the Browns, but the production hasn’t been steady enough to push for a TE1 ranking even if we all know he’s talented enough to do it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8420-d1e7-a1fa-deea9aa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions ruled out TE Sam LaPorta (back) for Week 11 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8421-d713-ad9e-ec7561fc0000</link>
      <description>LaPorta was entirely unable to practice this week, which is concerning. The Lions also listed backup TE Brock Wright (ankle) as questionable to play after two limited sessions. Hopefully, LaPorta can return in time for the Lions’ Week 12 game against the Giants. His Week 11 absence adds a potential target or two to WR Amon-Ra St. Brown, WR Jameson Williams and RB Jahmyr Gibbs’ workloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8421-d713-ad9e-ec7561fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions EDGE Aidan Hutchinson (elbow) is not on Detroit’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8424-d673-a39e-a4b510de0000</link>
      <description>Good thing, too, because the entire rest of the Lions defense found their way on to this report. Terrion Arnold (concussion), Kerby Joseph (knee) and Josh Paschal (back) were all ruled out. D.J. Reed (hamstring) and Amik Robertson (hamstring) are questionable. Both A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith should see slight matchup uggrades given the CB injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8424-d673-a39e-a4b510de0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
