<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) is questionable for Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38b-d56e-afff-e7eb0ebd0000</link>
      <description>Uh oh. Darnold was not listed on the injury report at all before today’s practice. This certainly has the potential to tip things. Mike MacDonald is not slated to speak to reporters again until Friday. We’d tentatively assume Darnold will still play, but it can be unpredictable what happens when you get an in-practice injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38b-d56e-afff-e7eb0ebd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfef7d0000</link>
      <description>Two sessions would seemingly give him a real chance to suit up, though it’s unclear if the Texans would make him the No. 2 back ahead of Nick Chubb after Chubb’s output against the Steelers last Monday night. Jordan is probably trending towards a questionable tag on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c38d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfef7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) is questionable for San Francisco’s Divisional Round game against the Seahawks</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c393-dc7a-af9b-cfbff41d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall has been practicing in a limited capacity this week. He was entirely unable to practice last week, so the increased participation is a positive sign. Pearsall aggravated the PCL sprain in his knee at the end of a 30-yard play against the Bears in Week 18. He told reporters that he “landed straight on [his] knee,” and he “just can’t take tackles like that right now.” Instead, he must “adjust a little bit within [his] game.” Getting out of bounds would have been the “wiser move.” Pearsall is seemingly on track to play, but he may be stuck running vertical routes along the sideline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c393-dc7a-af9b-cfbff41d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) said he is “confident” that he will play in Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a2-d968-a19b-dbf323010000</link>
      <description>Darnold adds that there is “close to zero” percent chance that he misses his team’s playoff game against the division-rival 49ers. This is encouraging. He told reporters that he “felt something during routes on air and didn’t want to push it.” Smart move. The Seahawks are one game away from a trip to the NFC Championship Game. We expect him to play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a2-d968-a19b-dbf323010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle underwent surgery to repair his ruptured Achilles tendon and it “went very well.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a8-d968-a19b-dbf93ec40000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan adds that Kittle “is in good spirits,” post-op. That is good to hear. Kittle, 32, ruptured his Achilles tendon in San Francisco’s Wild Card win over the Eagles. He is under contract through 2029, having signed a four-year extension in April 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a8-d968-a19b-dbf93ec40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos DL John Franklin-Myers (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Denver’s Divisional Round game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b2-d35e-a1bf-c7f271f10000</link>
      <description>Franklin-Myers boasts 39 quarterback pressures and eight sacks this season. The impactful interior defender’s return comes at the right time. The Broncos will also get LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) back in the lineup on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b2-d35e-a1bf-c7f271f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out LB Drew Sanders (ankle) for Denver’s Divisional Round game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b0-d56e-afff-e7f89d540000</link>
      <description>The Broncos designated Sanders to return from injured reserve on January 10th, but he is not yet ready to play. He spent the regular season on injured reserve due to complications from a torn Achilles suffered in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b0-d56e-afff-e7f89d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks ruled out TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) for Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3c6-d35e-a1bf-c7c6e7a50000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks designated Arroyo to return from injured reserve on January 7th, opening his 21-day practice window. Evidently, he is not yet ready to resume playing, though he was able to practice fully all week. If the Seahawks beat the 49ers and advance to the NFC Championship Game, Arroyo seemingly has decent odds of making a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3c6-d35e-a1bf-c7c6e7a50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
