<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 02:31:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Bech caught 6-of-6 targets for 50 yards in the Raiders’ Week 14 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbba2610000</link>
      <description>Four of Bech’s targets were thrown to him by backup QB Kenny Pickett, who replaced QB Geno Smith (right shoulder) in the second half. Bech’s upside is unknown, and largely in doubt, but he does seem to have a decent connection with Pickett. Bech could warrant boom-bust FLEX consideration against the Eagles in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbba2610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 7-of-11 targets for 167 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbb73ea0000</link>
      <description>Nacua made easy work of an Arizona defense that wasn’t terribly interested in defending Rams players in Week 14. Nacua dominated the LA passing attack with a 35 percent target share and led the team in air yards. He bullied his way into the end zone for his second touchdown against a dismal Cardinals secondary that allowed 281 yards and three scores to Matthew Stafford. Week 14 was only the fourth time Nacua has exceeded 100 receiving yards this season. His touchdowns were the first time he’s found pay dirt in nearly a month. He’ll be an elite option in Week 15 against a deteriorating Lions coverage unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbb73ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum had 12 rushes for 128 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals, adding one catch for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fba1-d005-a9bf-fbb5e31c0000</link>
      <description>Corum and Kyren Williams — and in the fourth quarter, Ronnie Rivers — were ripping off one chunk gain after another against a lifeless Cardinals defense that didn’t have a whole lot of interest in tackling the hard-running LA backs. Corum blew through the Arizona front seven time and again until he ripped off a 48-yard touchdown in the third quarter without a single Cards defender laying a hand on him. Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur has said he wants to keep Williams “fresh” for the postseason, meaning Corum is live for 12-15 weekly touches depending largely on game script. Corum, averaging nearly five yards per carry this season, will be a viable 12-team flex in Week 15 against Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fba1-d005-a9bf-fbb5e31c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenny Pickett completed 8-of-11 passes for 96 yards and one touchdown in the Raiders’ 24-17, Week 14 loss to the Broncos, adding one rush for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbb4b6c0000</link>
      <description>Raiders QB Geno Smith injured his right, throwing shoulder on the final play of the third quarter and was immediately taken to the locker room, thrusting Pickett into the starting lineup. Pickett took over on 3rd-and-7 from the Broncos’ seven-yard line and eventually turned the ball over on downs. The journeyman quarterback showed a decent connection with rookie WR Jack Bech thereafter and eventually connected with WR Shedrick Jackson, Bo Jackson’s nephew, for a 25-yard touchdown. It is Jackson’s first career reception. Pickett is a potential QB2 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb9b-d8cf-affb-ffbb4b6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 5-of-9 targets for 58 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbab-d005-a9bf-fbbf60ce0000</link>
      <description>McBride trailed Michael Wilson in targets (16) and faced plenty of double teams against a Rams secondary that has been stingy against opposing slot pass catchers in 2025. McBride was open for a fourth quarter garbage time touchdown, but Jacoby Brissett missed him with an overthrow. McBride will continue operating as an elite wide receiver who can be used as a tight end in fantasy lineups next week against the Texans. McBride has 48 receptions over his past five games thanks to Brissett’s ability to see over the Arizona offensive line and his willingness to throw the ball more than five yards downfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbab-d005-a9bf-fbbf60ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 4-of-5 targets for 46 yards and one touchdown in the Raiders’ Week 14 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbab-d005-a9bf-fbbf5b6d0000</link>
      <description>Bowers continues to make the most of his frustratingly small workloads, frequently producing highlight reel plays. Bowers scored a touchdown on the Raiders’ first drive, lining up in the slot and running right past Broncos slot CB Ja’Quan McMillian, who was focused on RB Ashton Jeant’s route out of the backfield. Broncos’ S Talanoa Hufanga opted not to pursue Bowers as he broke outside on a corner route, leaving Bowers wide open in the end zone. Raiders QB Geno Smith got the ball to him for the score. Bowers later made a juggling, one-handed catch on the play where Smith (right shoulder) was injured on the Raiders’ final play of the third quarter. Broncos LB Alex Singleton had Bowers’ left arm trapped, but the talented tight end was evidently unbothered, securing the pass with his right hand before trotting out of bounds. Bowers remains an elite TE1 in Week 15 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbab-d005-a9bf-fbbf5b6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught 3-of-5 targets for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb1-d77b-adfa-fbb3709b0000</link>
      <description>Parkinson’s touchdown — one of three for Matthew Stafford on the day — was his fourth score in five games. He’s operated as the Rams’ TE1 since Tyler Higbee was placed on injured reserve with an ankle injury. Parkinson in Week 14 ran a pass route on 22 of Stafford’s 31 drop backs and was targeted on 23 percent of his routes, a solid rate for a tight end. Parkinson will be a solid streaming option in Week 15 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb1-d77b-adfa-fbb3709b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 10 times for 30 yards in the Raiders’ Week 14 loss to the Broncos, adding two receptions for eight yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb4-d8cf-affb-ffbe91e90000</link>
      <description>Jeanty had a busy start to the day, touching the ball six times on the Raiders’ 10-play, first drive. The Broncos jumped out to a 14-7 lead in the first half before extending it to 21-7 in the third quarter, putting the slow-paced Raiders in an uncomfortable pass-heavy game script. The Raiders’ slow-paced tactics limit the team’s offensive play volume and their overall offensive struggles only exacerbate things. Jeanty is an RB2 against the Eagles in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb4-d8cf-affb-ffbe91e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed 14 times for 57 yards in the Bears’ Week 14 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb0-da9b-a9bf-ffbd72d00000</link>
      <description>Monangai led the Bears in carries but was out-touched by D’Andre Swift 16-15. Swift caught three balls while operating as the team’s top option on passing downs. The rookie also added two points to his fantasy bottom line by punching in a two-point conversion in the second half. Monangai has now out-carried Swift in three straight and the Bears are running the ball enough to keep both backs involved. As home favorites over the Browns in Week 15, the Bears should be able to establish their run-first approach the next time we see them. Monangai will sit on the RB2/3 border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbb0-da9b-a9bf-ffbd72d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 22-of-31 attempts for 283 yards and three touchdowns in the Rams’ 45-17 Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbc2-d8cf-affb-ffea38120000</link>
      <description>Stafford made quick work of a low-energy Arizona defense that was run over on the ground to the tune of 249 rushing yards. Stafford did whatever he wanted against the Cardinals, averaging 9.1 yards per attempt, taking no sacks, and facing only three pressures. It was Stafford’s 11th game of the season with multiple touchdown throws. He now has a league-leading 35 passing scores in a Rams offense that has remained pass-heavy in the red zone. Stafford will look to rack up a few more touchdowns in Week 15 against his former team, the Lions, who have struggled against the pass in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fbc2-d8cf-affb-ffea38120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
