<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 2-of-3 targets for 20 yards in the Chargers’ Week 15 win against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f00-d8cf-affb-bf2a8bd90000</link>
      <description>McConkey and the Bolts pass catchers suffered from a lack of volume once again with the team shifting hard toward the run. McConkey led the team in pass routes but saw just three targets. He now has ten receptions over his past four games. Though he remains the team’s nominal WR1, McConkey isn’t startable in ten-team fantasy leagues and might be little more than a flex play in 12-team leagues next week against the Cowboys. The Chargers’ drop in pass volume has destroyed McConkey’s upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f00-d8cf-affb-bf2a8bd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (hamstring) is questionable to return in Week 15 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ef9-d77b-adfb-defb22aa0000</link>
      <description>Neal scored a four-yard touchdown on his final play before exiting, following his blocks on an outside run to the right side. He broke the plane by dutifully lowering his left shoulder and plowing through contact. Thus far, Neal has rushed seven times for 28 yards and one touchdown, adding one reception for four yards. He is currently in the locker room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ef9-d77b-adfb-defb22aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus caught 0-of-3 targets in the Bears’ Week 15 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1efc-d1bc-a3fb-9ffc0b600000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus has already seen his role in the offense scaled back with the emergence of Luther Burden, but with Rome Odunze out he’s back as the third receiver. Unfortunately, Zaccheaus didn’t endear himself to coaches or fantasy managers with his Tony Snell-esque performance against the Browns. He’ll be a total dart throw even if Odunze is out against the Packers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1efc-d1bc-a3fb-9ffc0b600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall rushed 12 times for 23 yards in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars, adding two receptions for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f02-d8cf-affb-bf2a5f890000</link>
      <description>With the Jets falling behind 21-7 early in the second quarter and 31-10 at halftime, Hall ended up posting his second fewest rushing yards of the season as Gang Green lamentably had to dial up 33 pass attempts for UDFA Brady Cook. Stuck on one total touchdown over his past five games, Hall is having trouble rising above low-end, workload-based RB2 status. Hopefully that will not include for Week 16, where the Jets will be taking on a team more of their own size in the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f02-d8cf-affb-bf2a5f890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 2-of-4 targets for 24 yards in the Browns’ Week 15 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f03-d77b-adfb-df8364270000</link>
      <description>In the third quarter, Jeudy leaped at the goal line and had the ball bounce off his hands for a Bears interception. It was an embarrassing display from a receiver that’s had a down season. Jeudy simply isn’t commanding targets and that makes him a risky WR4 against the Bills in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f03-d77b-adfb-df8364270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Bond caught 2-of-4 targets for 89 yards in the Browns’ Week 16 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f0a-d8cf-affb-bf2a986e0000</link>
      <description>Bond’s day was highlighted by two long catches, his only catches of the game. One went for 47 yards while the other 42. Bond is certainly a useful piece of the offense when Shedeur Sanders decides he just needs to find somebody down there somewhere. He’s just a deep league FLEX option at best in Week 15 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f0a-d8cf-affb-bf2a986e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine rushed 14 times for 42 yards in the Bengals’ Week 15 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ef7-d1bc-a3fb-9ff713260000</link>
      <description>Perine saw one more carry than Chase Brown, but averaged just three yards per carry on the day with his longest gain coming on an eight-yard pickup. Perine briefly left the game in the fourth quarter due to a knee injury, and was carted to the locker room at one point. Despite all of this, he returned to finish out the day and should be good to go for Week 16 against the Dolphins. Even if he is active, fantasy managers can avoid him next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ef7-d1bc-a3fb-9ff713260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten caught a 16-yard touchdown pass in the Jags’ Week 15 loss to the Jets, adding a seven-yard rush.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f12-d005-a9bf-df367dfd0000</link>
      <description>Tuten’s touchdown reception put the Jags up 21-7 in the second quarter. It was also a bit of a red herring, as it ended up being his only target on an afternoon where Travis Etienne somehow stacked up three receiving scores. Etienne is remaining inefficient on the ground, but Tuten is no longer pushing him as a potential 1B option, totaling just four touches over the past two weeks. Tuten might be needed for more work in Week 16 against the Broncos as the Jags try to circumvent their elite pass defense by handing the ball off, but he’s lost all RB3/FLEX benefit of the doubt in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f12-d005-a9bf-df367dfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught 7-of-14 targets for 48 yards in the Browns’ Week 15 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f11-d1bc-a3fb-9f3591110000</link>
      <description>Fannin continues to be the clear top option in the Browns’ receiving game, commanding at least 11 targets for the second consecutive game. On a better offense, we can only dream about the consistent performances we’d get from Fannin. On the Browns, though, it’s a little more difficult for him to hit his ceiling. If David Njoku (knee) is ruled out for Week 16 against the Bills, Fannin will be a top-five TE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f11-d1bc-a3fb-9f3591110000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
