<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 01:29:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Isaac TeSlaa (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3bf-d413-ad9f-b7ffeb6c0000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa is not fantasy-relevant on his own, but with TE Sam LaPorta (back) on injured reserve, his potential absence would have a small ripple effect. The Lions’ offense has racked up explosive gains with head coach Dan Campbell calling plays in recent weeks. TeSlaa’s Friday status is worth keeping an eye on for WR Amon-Ra St. Brown and WR Jameson Williams’ fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3bf-d413-ad9f-b7ffeb6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the “expectation” is Texans QB C.J. Stroud (concussion) to play in Week 13 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3bb-db57-afda-f7bb05ce0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that Stroud likely would have practiced today if the Texans did not have a game this evening. It should be noted that Stroud was limited on Tuesday before sitting out on Wednesday. We do not know why Stroud was downgraded. Perhaps, due for rest. Expect Stroud back next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3bb-db57-afda-f7bb05ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (shin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3da-db57-afda-f7fa2e390000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks removed Horton’s groin injury from the injury report. That must have been some shin injury he suffered at Week 10’s Thursday practice session. The rookie wide receiver appears to be heading toward another game-day absence. Hopefully, he can return next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3da-db57-afda-f7fa2e390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LG Grey Zabel (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3df-d82c-a79a-b3dfa7630000</link>
      <description>Zabel’s knee injury is not as bad as it was initially believed to be. His return to practice is a good sign. Although he may be unable to play in Week 12 against the Titans, he seemingly has decent odds of facing the Vikings in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3df-d82c-a79a-b3dfa7630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d413-ad9f-b7ffd80f0000</link>
      <description>Tuten is on track to play this week, though graduating to full participation tomorrow would be nice to see. Jaguars RB Travis Etienne (shoulder) was a non-contact participant today. Tomorrow’s practice report is worth keeping an eye on. The Jaguars face the Cardinals this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d413-ad9f-b7ffd80f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Brenton Strange (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f0-d82c-a79a-b3f4ac480000</link>
      <description>Strange logged two limited sessions last week before being downgraded on Friday. He did not play on game day. At this point, he is difficult to trust, though typically, two limited sessions put a player on track to play. He is only a stash option at this time. Check back tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f0-d82c-a79a-b3f4ac480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d82c-a79a-b3f7cf730000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals are likely just being cautious with their presumed starter, though RB Trey Benson (knee) is matching Knight as a limited participant thus far. Benson could return this weekend, though next week seems more likely. Assuming Knight is the starter, he should be able to return FLEX value against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d82c-a79a-b3f7cf730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f6-d82c-a79a-b3f618820000</link>
      <description>Benson has a chance to suit up this weekend, though one imagines the Cardinals’ coaching and medical staffs hope to see him get through a full practice before doing so. If active, he will likely split work with RB Bam Knight (ankle), but Benson could be a league-winner down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f6-d82c-a79a-b3f618820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (illness) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e3-d82c-a79a-b3f7be160000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers’ locker room has been hit hard by an illness this week. Egbuka is technically on track to play against the Rams this week, though it would be great to see him upgrade to full participation on Friday. Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) practiced fully today, putting him on track to play. Godwin will command safety attention, at least to some degree, when he gets back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e3-d82c-a79a-b3f7be160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f8-db57-afda-f7faed990000</link>
      <description>An illness has pummeled Buccaneers players this week, but the tough-as-nails Mayfield, perhaps unsurprisingly, is back in action. The Buccaneers quarterback could have both WR Emeka Egbuka (illness) and WR Chris Godwin (fibula) on the field this week, as the team takes on the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f8-db57-afda-f7faed990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
