<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Long (hip/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5623-d45b-affe-57b7c4830000</link>
      <description>Long had been filling in for Brenton Strange, who remains on injured reserve with quad and hip injuries. Johnny Mundt would be the next man up if Long is out for Week 10. We don’t expect Long’s absence to create any fantasy value for Mundt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5623-d45b-affe-57b7c4830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt (tooth) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562a-d45b-affe-57bea0540000</link>
      <description>JCM apparently had some dental work done recently. That is not a joke. The Commanders put him in a non-contact jersey for Wednesday’s practice. There’s no reason to believe he will miss Sunday’s game against the Lions. Bill doesn’t have a role in the passing game, making him entirely dependant on game script. As a massive underdog to the Lions, he is stuck in the RB3 ranks for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562a-d45b-affe-57bea0540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562f-d45b-affe-57bf1d260000</link>
      <description>Fellow starting tackle Taylor Decker also missed Wednesday’s practice with a shoulder issue. He has been dealing with the issue for a while but has played through it for the past two weeks. Sewell’s shoulder injury is new, though it is not believed to be a long-term issue. Left guard Christian Mahogany, however, is expected to miss extended time because of a leg injury. All in, the Lions are either going to be slightly undermanned in the trenches this week or drastically undermanned. The hope will be that both tackles can suit up, but this is a situation to monitor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562f-d45b-affe-57bf1d260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out K Ka’imi Fairbairn (quad) for Week 10 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-563e-d713-ad9e-7e7ed1b70000</link>
      <description>Fairbairn being ruled out this early does not bode well for his odds of returning in Week 11. Matthew Wright will be called up from the practice squad to take his place. Houston is kicking more field goals than any other team this year, putting Wright on the streaming radar for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-563e-d713-ad9e-7e7ed1b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5642-d713-ad9e-7e56c2870000</link>
      <description>If Chubb misses any time, the Texans could finally be forced to turn to Woody Marks as their workhorse back. They flirted with the idea earlier in the season but have since doubled down on Chubb’s role as the grinder. Marks hasn’t seen more than 11 carries in a game since Week 4. He is now the top add this week for leagues that have yet to run waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5642-d713-ad9e-7e56c2870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5646-d1e7-a1fa-5eee2b4d0000</link>
      <description>Schultz didn’t practice on Wednesday or Thursday last week because of the pair of injuries. He still suited up and posted a usable stat line with six catches and 77 yards. Even with Davis Mills drawing the start this week, Schultz is seeing enough work to sit on the TE1/2 border versus the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5646-d1e7-a1fa-5eee2b4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans EDGE Will Anderson (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5648-d673-a39e-f6d91b6b0000</link>
      <description>Anderson is the most notable of several Houston defenders who were held out of Wednesday’s practice. The third-year EDGE has six sacks this season and scored his first career touchdown on a fumble recovery in Week 7. Losing him would be a devastating blow to a Houston team that has already ruled out C.J. Stroud with a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5648-d673-a39e-f6d91b6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) is not expected to participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5652-d45b-affe-57d6fea00000</link>
      <description>Benson has been on injured reserve since Week 4 with a meniscus injury. He is eligible to return Week 10, but head coach Jonathan Gannon said Benson “is not gonna be out there [Wednesday] but he is doing better.” The initial timeline for Benson’s injury was four-to-six weeks, so it looks like he will return on the later end of that. Expect him out for Week 10 with a shot to return Week 11 against the 49ers. Expect Bam Knight and Emari Demercado to lead the backfield committee while Benson remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5652-d45b-affe-57d6fea00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RG Mekhi Becton (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-565b-d673-a39e-f6db0c9f0000</link>
      <description>Becton missed Week 9 due to a knee issue. He has a lengthy injury history and is a key piece for the Chargers’ banged up offensive line. Fellow OL Bobby Hart (knee/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday as the Chargers are reeling from Joe Alt’s season-ending ankle injury. Justin Herbert and company will need Becton and Hart to log practices the rest of the week to have a chance of playing in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-565b-d673-a39e-f6db0c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp (hamstring/heel) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5663-d673-a39e-f6f301150000</link>
      <description>Kupp did not play in Week 9 due to hamstring and heel issues and now starts out Week 10 not practicing. Wednesday was just a walkthrough for the Seahawks, but the DNP estimation indicates Kupp is not trending to play in against the Cardinals. Also DNP were WRs Jake Bobo (calf) and Dareke Young (quad). Newly acquired Rashid Shaheed and rookie Tory Horton will step up next to Jaxon Smith-Njigba with Kupp, Bobo, and Young dealing with injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5663-d673-a39e-f6f301150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
