<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins restructured LB Jordyn Brooks’ contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1122-d245-adfb-957f09a30000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Field Yates, the move clears up $3 million in cap space. For most teams, contract maneuvers at this point in the season would cause some speculation that they are looking to add at the trade deadline. For the Dolphins, the extra cap space would allow them to absorb some dead cap from outgoing contracts. Jaylen Waddle is the biggest name that could be on the move, but Miami also has multiple pass-rushers who will be of interest to contending teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1122-d245-adfb-957f09a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) is unlikely to play in Week 8 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11a3-d245-adfb-95ff5ac00000</link>
      <description>Christian Watson has a chance to return this week, but LaFleur noted that the decision will ultimately come down to the medical staff. Watson is working his way back from the torn ACL he suffered late in the 2024 season. Wicks is dealing with a calf injury that forced him to miss Wednesday’s practice. We’ll assume it’s another DNP for him today. If Watson is back, he could step into a full-time role right away. Savion Williams and Malik Heath would see more work if both wideouts are sidelined for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11a3-d245-adfb-95ff5ac00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) was not seen at Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11e9-deb1-a39b-31efa4bc0000</link>
      <description>Wilson was held out of Wednesday’s practice and looks like a DNP again today. He is a long-shot to suit up on Sunday. With a Week 9 bye up next, Wilson should be back on the field in Week 10 versus the Browns. Until then, Tyler Johnson and Josh Reynolds will operate as the team’s top wideouts. Neither player is awfully appealing for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11e9-deb1-a39b-31efa4bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11fb-d245-adfb-95fff9a90000</link>
      <description>Hunt suffered a bone bruise in his knee in Week 7 against the Raiders. He logged a season-low four carries and was held without a reception for the first time this year. Now he looks unlikely to suit up on Monday versus the Commanders. If Hunt is unable to play, Isiah Pacheco will finally get the chance to dominate the backfield carries, with Brashard Smith also pitching in for more touches than usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-11fb-d245-adfb-95fff9a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RG Trey Smith (back) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1200-dab4-a3fb-9b7077fb0000</link>
      <description>Smith is dealing with back spasms. Head coach Andy Reid expressed some optimism that he will be able to suit up for Monday’s game versus the Commanders. Left tackle Josh Simmons remains out for personal reasons. Simmons isn’t expected to play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1200-dab4-a3fb-9b7077fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans placed CB L’Jarius Sneed on injured reserve with a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1205-dab4-a3fb-9b7514e40000</link>
      <description>A balky knee has impeded Sneed’s play for much of the year. The 28-year-old perimeter cornerback is currently allowing 17.2 yards per reception, 5.3 more than his prior career-worst average. Adding a quad issue to the mix was only going to make things worse. Sneed will now miss at least four games and will be eligible to return in Week 13. The team’s bye occurs in Week 10. CB Darrell Baker Jr. is listed as his backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1205-dab4-a3fb-9b7514e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said WRs Terry McLaurin (quad) and Deebo Samuel (heel) will practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1208-dab4-a3fb-9b78a94b0000</link>
      <description>On Monday, Quinn told reporters that “the plan” was for McLaurin and Samuel to have a “full” week of practice this week. The “full” phrasing seemingly suggests he expects both players to practice in full three times. The injury report issued later today will confirm both players’ statuses, though McLaurin and Samuel are tentatively on track to suit up on Monday night against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1208-dab4-a3fb-9b78a94b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-120b-d5d8-a3ff-fb6b4fe60000</link>
      <description>This is a bit surprising. Jones has logged just two limited practice sessions since the team activated him from injured reserve on Tuesday. Although limiting snaps when players return from injury may be optimal, NFL coaches frequently allow them to play their normal allotment once they retake the field. Consider Jones a volatile RB2 against the Chargers this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-120b-d5d8-a3ff-fb6b4fe60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said WR Deebo Samuel (heel) will practice today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1224-deb1-a39b-332ee7440000</link>
      <description>On Monday, Quinn said “the plan” is for Samuel and WR Terry McLaurin (quad) to have a “full” week of practice this week, seemingly indicating that both players are expected to practice in full from Thursday through Saturday. If so, they can be expected to suit up on Monday night against the Chiefs. The official injury report will reveal Samuel’s participation level later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1224-deb1-a39b-332ee7440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec reports that Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is practicing on Thursday and “seemed to be working at a similar rate as yesterday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1228-d5d8-a3ff-fb691a610000</link>
      <description>Jackson practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday, so if he really is taking a similar number of reps, he likely remains in the questionable to play category. Jackson has been out since straining his hamstring in Week 4, and one assumes that the coaching staff would like to see Jackson practice in full before allowing him to resume playing. If he can upgrade to full participation tomorrow, he should be good to go for Sunday. He will be a QB1 if active. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1228-d5d8-a3ff-fb691a610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
