<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (pectoral) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e7a-d45b-affe-dffe2dd80000</link>
      <description>Parsons popped up on the injury report with a pectoral issue and was listed as limited on Wednesday. Given he still practiced in some capacity, it is possible the Packers are carefully managing Parsons’ pectoral soreness with a lighter practice workload. He is not yet in danger of missing Week 12 against the Vikings, but his practice status later in the week and potential new information about the severity of the injury will shed light on his game status. Fellow EDGE Lukas Van Ness (foot) was also limited in practice as he works his way back to playing for the first time since Week 6. The Packers will hope to have both edge rushers healthy against the Vikings’ stumbling passing offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e7a-d45b-affe-dffe2dd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LB Quay Walker (neck) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e82-d45b-affe-df9672390000</link>
      <description>Walker suffered a stinger in Week 11 and is now listed with a neck injury. He does not practice to start the week, putting his Week 12 status in jeopardy. Also not practicing was CB Nate Hobbs (knee), who has missed each of the last two weeks. Both players will face an uphill battle to play against the Vikings this week, leaving the Packers defense thin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e82-d45b-affe-df9672390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Kris Boyd is “starting to breathe on [his] own” after he was shot and critically wounded Sunday morning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e91-d673-a39e-be9184c70000</link>
      <description>Boyd was shot in the abdomen and critically wounded in New York on Sunday morning. The 29-year-old is recovering in the hospital and is now in stable condition and able to breathe on his own again, according to Boyd’s Instagram story. Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said Boyd is “in good spirits” and will be okay. It’s good news for Boyd has he recovers from a shooting that remains under investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e91-d673-a39e-be9184c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eb7-d713-ad9e-fef7c8050000</link>
      <description>Godwin continues to work back from a fibula issue and was listed as limited in a Wednesday walk-through practice. He was limited in practice all of last week and now has a shot to play in Week 12 against the Rams. Godwin is still ramping up to full health and would be a fantasy WR4 should he return to play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eb7-d713-ad9e-fef7c8050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers EDGE Haason Reddick (ankle/knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eba-d45b-affe-dfbe287f0000</link>
      <description>Reddick has not been able to play since Week 7 and is not yet back at practice. Also not practicing on defense were Jamel Dean (hip) and Chris Braswell (foot). Dean is week-to-week with his injury while Braswell’s is new and Reddick does not have a timeline for his return. The Bucs defense will be sparse if neither of the three can suit up for Week 12 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eba-d45b-affe-dfbe287f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ebe-d45b-affe-dfbec3010000</link>
      <description>Also limited due to illness were WR Emeka Egbuka, OG Dan Feeney, C Graham Barton, OT Luke Goedeke, and DE Logan Hall. The Bucs had a walk-through practice, so the designations are just estimates, but there seems to be a bug going around the team. Neither Mayfield, Egbuka, nor any of the others are in jeopardy of missing Week 12 against the Rams yet, but keep an eye out on the team’s practice statuses later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ebe-d45b-affe-dfbec3010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Sterling Shepard (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec4-d673-a39e-bed5e0800000</link>
      <description>Shepard and OT Tristan Wirfs popped up on the injury report with shoulder injuries on Wednesday. The Bucs held a walk-through, so practice designations were estimates, but still important to note. Shepard has a role as long as Chris Godwin (fibula) remains out, while Wirfs is the team’s franchise left tackle. Neither are in danger of missing Week 12 yet, barring setbacks later in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec4-d673-a39e-bed5e0800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks DT Johnathan Hankins (back) will not play this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec7-d713-ad9e-fed7ea3f0000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said on Wednesday that the 33-year-old Hankins will not play this season due to a back injury. Hankins has been dealing with the injury since July, landing on the non-football injury list. He was re-signed to a one-year deal by Seattle in the offseason, but he did not play and does not expect to play the rest of the 2025 season. Macdonald said, “I’ll probably just leave it private right now with what’s going on with his health, but he won’t be with us this year.” Hankins was a complimentary piece to the Seattle defensive line last year, but will now focus on getting healthy for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec7-d713-ad9e-fed7ea3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking Wednesday, Bears coach Ben Johnson confirmed he believed Luther Burden has earned more playing time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9f8c-d713-ad9e-ffdcf91d0000</link>
      <description>“You get what you earn,” Johnson said. “And I think he’s earned the increased snaps. He’s steadily climbed.” It seems to be confirmation that Burden’s Week 11 ascension ahead of Olamide Zaccheaus will be a permanent feature. It seems like a long-overdue move, though Burden was always more raw as a prospect than some draftniks would have probably liked to admit. Burden is a big play waiting to happen with the ball in his hands, but it still takes some effort to get it there, while the Bears prefer a balanced approach on offense. Burden is growing more viable as a WR4, but he is still someone who is probably best left on 12-team league benches for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9f8c-d713-ad9e-ffdcf91d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Aaron Rodgers (left wrist) is expected to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a1bd-db57-afda-f7bff4690000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was held out of practice on Wednesday but should be back on the field today. As Rapoport notes, the issue is largely a matter of Rodgers’ ability to protect himself. The injury is to his left (non-throwing) wrist. The Steelers will get a better feel for that during today’s practice. Pittsburgh takes on Rodgers’ old rival, Chicago, this week. That matchup undoubtedly means a little more to the grizzled veteran, and we would bet he is pushing to play through the wrist injury for Week 12. Assuming he does suit up, Rodgers will remain a mid-range QB2 versus Chicago. Mason Rudolph would draw the start if Rodgers can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a1bd-db57-afda-f7bff4690000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
