<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) will not play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79a9-d673-a39e-fdb97fd30000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as Wilson is expected to miss 3-4 weeks after reaggravating his knee injury versus the Browns on Sunday. Tyler Johnson and Arian Smith are now the team’s top wideouts. Adonai Mitchell could also be active for the Jets this week after being a healthy scratch in Week 10. No Jets player caught more than one pass last week. There isn’t any fantasy value to be had here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79a9-d673-a39e-fdb97fd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said QB Justin Herbert (ankle) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79b0-d713-ad9e-7df4d0050000</link>
      <description>Herbert was injured in Week 10 against the Steelers when two defenders brought the Chargers’ quarterback to the ground. The first tackler pinned Herbert’s left foot from the outside, causing the classic roll-up injury mechanism often associated with high-ankle sprains. The other tackler hit Herbert from behind, landing on the quarterback’s outstretched lower right leg. Herbert was then seen getting both ankles taped after the play. Regardless, his participation in Wednesday’s practice puts him firmly on track to play in Week 11. High-ankle sprains limited Herbert’s rushing productivity in 2024. Hopefully, that aspect of his game is not impacted this time around. It would be great to see him practicing in full by tomorrow. He is a QB1 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79b0-d713-ad9e-7df4d0050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79bb-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb9ae40000</link>
      <description>Kincaid suffered the hamstring issue in Week 10’s game against the Dolphins and did not return. He was later reported to be “week to week” with the issue. All signs point to him missing Week 11 against the Bucs. Dawson Knox and Jackson Hawes will see more work in his absence. Knox will be a low-end TE2 as the team’s spot-starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79bb-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb9ae40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (ankle/ribs) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79be-d713-ad9e-7dfe4fbc0000</link>
      <description>Both of the injuries are new for Shakir, though a limited session to start the week is typically not a cause for concern. We’ll call it a maintenance day for the veteran receiver unless something changes. With Dalton Kincaid likely out for Week 11, Shakir will easily operate as Josh Allen’s top target this week, putting him on the WR2/3 border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79be-d713-ad9e-7dfe4fbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said TE Oronde Gadsden II (quad) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79bc-d1e7-a1fa-7bfe161c0000</link>
      <description>Steelers LB Payton Wilson accidentally planted his left knee in the lower section of Gadsden’s left quad in Week 10, resulting in a game-ending bruise for the rookie tight end. Gadsden’s early-week participation puts him on track to play in Week 11 against the Jaguars, but it would be great to see him practicing in full by week’s end. We expect pain tolerance to be the biggest issue for him. Hopefully, it will not limit his mobility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79bc-d1e7-a1fa-7bfe161c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer (knee/ankle) is practicing in full for Week 11 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79c3-d45b-affe-7dd712e90000</link>
      <description>Palmer has been out since Week 6 with the pair of injuries. He returned to practice last week but never progressed beyond a limited session. A full practice today suggests he will be back on the field to face the Bucs on Sunday. Palmer will be a boom/bust WR5 for his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79c3-d45b-affe-7dd712e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (shoulder) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79c6-d673-a39e-fdd70d080000</link>
      <description>Moore missed a significant portion of the Bears’ Week 10 win over the Giants after injuring his right shoulder during a second-quarter fall. He returned for nine snaps in the fourth quarter, but failed to earn a target. Moore also entered the Week 10 contest nursing hip and groin injuries. He should be viewed as solidly questionable to play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79c6-d673-a39e-fdd70d080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79cb-d673-a39e-fddbe7d20000</link>
      <description>Bucky Irving also returned as a limited participant. It was only a walkthrough, so Thursday’s practice report will be more revealing. Still, this is a step in the right direction for a player who hasn’t suited up since Week 5. Even if Godwin isn’t back this week, he does appear to be nearing a return. We would expect the veteran wideout to be on a pitch count in his first game back, whenever that is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79cb-d673-a39e-fddbe7d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79cd-d1e7-a1fa-7bef02210000</link>
      <description>On the plus side, the press no longer lists Odunze with a heel injury, though the team’s official injury report could spoil that positive development later today. He was listed with the ankle injury last week as well. We expect Odunze to resume practicing on Thursday and play on Sunday against the Vikings. Should WR DJ Moore (shoulder) miss Week 11, Odunze’s target share stands to benefit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79cd-d1e7-a1fa-7bef02210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79d0-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa0e400000</link>
      <description>Swift has been playing through a groin injury for weeks, missing only Week 9. We suspect the hip listing is a related issue and expected him to play in Week 11 against the Vikings. Swift encouragingly took over as the team’s lead back in the second half and can be expected to do so again this weekend. He is a borderline RB2/3, splitting touches with RB Kyle Monangai.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79d0-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa0e400000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
