<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed DE Nelson Ceaser, formerly of the Seahawks, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a992-d90d-a5bd-abdb99ed0000</link>
      <description>Ceaser logged zero snaps in his 2024 rookie season. The Bills correspondingly waived WR Jalen Virgil and DE Justin Hollins with injury designations. The Athletic’s Joe Buscaglia writes, “Virgil was quite limited during Wednesday’s practice, while Hollins was not on the field for the session.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a992-d90d-a5bd-abdb99ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders worked out free agent OT Cam Fleming on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99a-d05a-adda-ab9a57710000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that Fleming left without a deal but the two sides “plan to remain in touch moving forward.” The 32-year-old offensive tackle most recently played for the Broncos in 2024, earning a 71.3 PFF pass-blocking grade on 80 qualifying snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99a-d05a-adda-ab9a57710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said CB Jaylon Johnson and CB Kyler Gordon are dealing with hamstring injuries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a994-d90d-a5bd-abdf61630000</link>
      <description>It took a while for the team to disclose both players’ injuries but now we know why they are sidelined. Marquee Sports Network’s Scott Bair reports that the Bears “hope” Johnson is “healthy and can return for the Week 1 clash with the NFC North rival Minnesota Vikings.” Gordon is considered week-to-week, and “the Bears are hopeful that he can return before the end of training camp.” Backup CB Tre Flowers left practice early on Thursday. This secondary could be one to target for fantasy purposes in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a994-d90d-a5bd-abdf61630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Breida announced his retirement after seven seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a995-d45c-a7fc-ab9f3da90000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Dolphins recently asked Breida to come in for a workout, but he declined. Breida spent his first three seasons in the NFL with the 49ers, one season apiece with the Dolphins and Bills, and two with the Giants. He did not play in the NFL last year. Over the course of his career, Breida rushed 575 times for 2,652 yards and nine touchdowns and caught 120-of-154 targets for 935 yards and six touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a995-d45c-a7fc-ab9f3da90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said most starters will not play in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9b9-d05a-adda-abbbd7d40000</link>
      <description>Per NBC Sports’ ProFootballTalk, “players like Aaron Rodgers, DK Metcalf, T.J. Watt, Alex Highsmith, Jalen Ramsey, and Cam Heyward,” among others, will not play this weekend. The Steelers will instead use joint practices with the Buccaneers to get the starters valuable reps. Tomlin adds that Ramsey will get all of the reps against Mike Evans today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9b9-d05a-adda-abbbd7d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquee Sports Networks Scott Bair writes, Olamide Zaccheaus “has been so good that rookie Luther Burden III can’t crack the first team.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9d2-d45c-a7fc-abdacd600000</link>
      <description>Per Bair, Olamide “has shown flashes every day of an excellent training camp to this point” and “it’s crystal clear” that Zaccheaus has Caleb Williams’ trust. The Bears’ team-released unofficial depth chart notably shows the team in 12 personnel (two WRs, two TEs, one RB), with DJ Moore and Rome Odunze listed as the two starters. Burden’s raw talent is not in question but Zaccheaus’ presence, coupled with the Bears’ potential 12 personnel reliance, is muddying his path to early-season playing time. Producing a standout showing in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Bills would be very helpful for Burden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9d2-d45c-a7fc-abdacd600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said EDGE Nik Bonitto underwent surgery because he “had a little spur” in his foot and the “goal” is to have him back next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9dd-df63-a199-f9ffd3f20000</link>
      <description>The small procedure reportedly required three stitches. Bonitto and the Broncos are currently in talks about a possible extension following his 15-sack season in 2024. Hopefully, the talented pass rusher returns without issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a9dd-df63-a199-f9ffd3f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) is dealing with scar tissue but is expected to increase his training camp participation next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99e-d90d-a5bd-abdfe63d0000</link>
      <description>Payton also told us Greenlaw would return “next week” on August 1st. He has at least been spotted wearing pads at practice recently, so the claim is more plausible this time around. The fact that Greenlaw is dealing with scar tissue certainly isn’t great though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a99e-d90d-a5bd-abdfe63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said the team believes DT CJ West is “going to be all right” after hyperextending his knee on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa14-df63-a199-fb3fbc070000</link>
      <description>Shanahan said West’s ACL appears to be intact after undergoing initial tests, saying West suffered an injury similar to that of DL Mykel Williams. The team used fourth- and first-round picks on West and Williams, respectively, this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aa14-df63-a199-fb3fbc070000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
