<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:18:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Matt Bowen believes TE Isaiah Likely would be a good fit for the Commanders offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6c8f-d89c-a1be-efdfb5160000</link>
      <description>Likely, an unrestricted free agent, could see interest from multiple teams this spring, including the Commanders, who are likely to move on from veteran TE Zach Ertz after his catastrophic knee injury in 2025. “Likely would bring more upside with his catch-and-run ability. A move player in the formation, Likely would also be schemed to create underneath one-on-ones,” Bowen said. In his four seasons with the Ravens, Likely popped off a few times in a run-heavy offense, usually when Mark Andrews was sidelined. Likely since the start of the 2024 season ranks fourth among all tight ends in ESPN’s open score, which measures a player’s ability to separate from defenders. He would be an intriguing fantasy option as an every-down player in Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6c8f-d89c-a1be-efdfb5160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder reports Anthony Richardson has not requested a trade yet, “but it is beginning to feel inevitable” that he will.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ccb-d042-afbc-7ddb6d400000</link>
      <description>Riley Leonard’s work over the back half of the season has “warmed” the Colts on the idea that he can ascend to their No. 2 job. Richardson is a) probably not going to require much compensation in a trade and b) probably not guaranteed to do more than compete for a starting job wherever he lands. Still, fantasy upside resides in those legs, so we’ll be watching and hoping he lands somewhere where he has a chance to win a job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ccb-d042-afbc-7ddb6d400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS’ Matt Zenitz reports the Raiders will hire Seahawks run game coordinator Rick Dennison.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ccf-d042-afbc-7ddfbf690000</link>
      <description>It’s another Seahawks assistant taking the plane to Vegas to join Klint Kubiak. Dennison has been on Kubiak staffs since the dawn of the internet, so this is no real surprise. The 67-year-old will look to help revitalize Ashton Jeanty’s fantasy stock after a rough rookie season behind a bad offensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ccf-d042-afbc-7ddfbf690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Judy Battista reports Daniel Jones would “certainly [draw] interest from other teams” in free agency and could get franchise tagged “to buy time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cd3-d89c-a1be-efdf01dd0000</link>
      <description>The complicating factor of a tag for Jones, as Battista writes, is that Alec Pierce is also a worthy franchise tag candidate for the Colts. Time flows like a river, and Daniel Jones finds himself in an enviable bargaining position once again. The Colts were expected to open extension talks with Jones “soon” at the Super Bowl and it wouldn’t be a surprise if the Colts and Jones started hammering some terms out at the NFL Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cd3-d89c-a1be-efdf01dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sports’ John Gambadoro reports the Cardinals are “intrigued” by Bears QB Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cdd-d89c-a1be-efdf62cb0000</link>
      <description>This is not a usual source for NFL news, but the long-time Phoenix-based reporter has a strong track record in other sports. Bagent threw six interceptions and three touchdowns in a four-start trial in 2023, but is entering his age-26 season and has two years left on his contract after signing a two-year extension last offseason. In a quarterback landscape this barren for teams looking for solutions, it’s not a surprise that younger backups could be of interest around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cdd-d89c-a1be-efdf62cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Matthew Golden will “be a much bigger part of the game plan” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce5-d629-a1bc-fcfd90580000</link>
      <description>Of course, he also says that he’s “not putting him above Christian Watson or Jayden Reed just yet,” as there’s space to grow from what Golden did as a rookie and still not hit any fantasy-intriguing upside scenarios. He probably deserves to be approached cautiously in offseason best ball formats, though it was nice to see him pop off for 4/84/1 in the playoffs before the Packers collectively turtled on a lost fourth-quarter lead to the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce5-d629-a1bc-fcfd90580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Romeo Doubs “is as good as gone” from the Packers in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce8-d042-afbc-7dfa0c320000</link>
      <description>Doubs profiles as one of the better available receivers after we clear away George Pickens (expected to be tagged) and Alec Pierce (could be tagged), and enters his age-26 season as a likely No. 2 or No. 3 target somewhere. We’d be surprised if his fantasy role grew much, but perhaps he’ll find the exact right spot (Miami?) to be a strong No. 2 target and snag a WR3 ranking in 2026 drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6ce8-d042-afbc-7dfa0c320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes the Packers will move on from EDGE Rashan Gary.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cea-d89c-a1be-efff94cc0000</link>
      <description>“I would be surprised if Gary is on the team next season. I’ll put it like that,” Schneidman notes. Releasing Gary, who disappointed in much better circumstances (next to Micah Parsons) in 2025 to the tune of just 7.5 sacks, would free up $11 million in cap space for the Packers per Schneidman. The career Packer will enter his age-29 season in 2025 with 46.5 career sacks but hasn’t been quite the same caliber of player since a 2022 ACL tear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cea-d89c-a1be-efff94cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers re-signed LS J.J. Jansen to a one-year deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</link>
      <description>The long-time snapper of snaps longer than the average snap will enter his age-40 season with the Panthers in 2026. Jansen has played in every single game of Panthers football since signing with the club as a UDFA in 2009. He has recovered one fumble and made one Pro Bowl. He also has snapped many, many balls a moderate distance away from his person in an attempt to set up some good punts and kicks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Vic Tafur believes “it seems like the 49ers have big plans for second-year player Jordan James.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</link>
      <description>It’s an interesting assertion because James rarely played this year, starting the season with a wrist injury and eventually playing only three offensive snaps in three active regular season games. However, James did close out the Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks with six carries for 28 yards and it appears he could seize the No. 2 role behind Christian McCaffrey if Brian Robinson walks in free agency. Isaac Guerendo, per Tafur, “seems like an easy cut” if Robinson returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
