<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 15:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that “there is still a possibility” for the NFL and Rashee Rice to “agree to a settlement on a suspension, that would allow Rice to be suspended at the start of the season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afe2-d05a-adda-afe2a0950000</link>
      <description>Per Pelissero, the NFL initially proposed a suspension lasting 10-plus games. Rice’s representatives argued for a far shorter suspension, in part because “there is no precedent for suspending someone for over half of the season.” With the two sides reaching an impasse, it was determined Rice’s case would be presented before Judge Sue L. Robinson, which could put Rice’s late-season availability at risk. Losing Rice early in the year would sting as well, with high-profile opponents like the Chargers, Eagles and Ravens on tap in Weeks 1-4. Both the team and the league are incentivized to get this issue sorted out as quickly as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afe2-d05a-adda-afe2a0950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Browns are “cautiously optimistic” that Shedeur Sanders (oblique) can return to practice next week and play in the team’s preseason Week 3 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01b-df63-a199-f93b0a5f0000</link>
      <description>Sanders will not play in the Browns’ preseason Week 2 game against the Eagles tomorrow. Kenny Pickett is rehabbing a hamstring injury and will not play either, though the team is “hoping” that Dillon Gabriel will “wake up feeling good enough” to play on Saturday, after rehabbing a hamstring injury of his own this week. Tyler Huntley will take most reps, if not. Joe Flacco has been bubble-wrapped as the lone healthy, proven player in the room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01b-df63-a199-f93b0a5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Ward completed 2-of-7 passes for 42 yards in the Titans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01a-d90d-a5bd-b25bc2d20000</link>
      <description>Ward played three drives in this one, and his arm strength was evident despite the lackluster results. Among the Titans’ expected Week 1 receiving corps, only Chig Okonkwo and Van Jefferson Jr. joined Ward on the field. Neither player earned a target. Ward instead focused on honing his connection with fellow rookie, WR Elic Ayomanor, who caught 2-of-4 targets thrown to him by Ward for 37 yards. Ayomanor is unlikely to be re-draft-relevant this year but he should be rostered in dynasty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01a-d90d-a5bd-b25bc2d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson reports that Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. is “absolutely going to be involved in the offense.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b041-d45c-a7fc-b25bce180000</link>
      <description>Jackson’s commentary is particularly noteworthy. Back in June, he believed Fannin was “considered more of a long-term project than an immediate contributor.” Jackson now believes the rookie tight end “is ahead of schedule, even if Stefanski won’t directly say it.” Fannin is “going to line up all over the formation,” which fits with his usage at Bowling Green State. Jackson counted Fannin, along with Joe Flacco and Jerry Jeudy, as players whose stock is rising. He counts “the rest of the pass-catching group” among those whose stock is down. Many things must fall Fannin’s way before he can be considered truly re-draft-relevant, but early returns suggest the Browns successfully drafted a capable contributor in Round 3 this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b041-d45c-a7fc-b25bce180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Terry McLaurin will come off the Physically Unable to Perform list on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b2fd-d05a-adda-baff4f6d0000</link>
      <description>Schefter notes that this is the next step in McLaurin’s progression, but ultimately isn’t related to his contract negotiations with the Commanders. McLaurin hasn’t been practicing and even requested a trade in an effort to get the new contract he desires from the team. It’s unclear if the receiver, who turns 30 next month, is any closer to a new deal at this point. We know the ankle injury, which may have allowed him to stage a hold-in as he continues to push for a new contract, is no longer what’s keeping him on the sidelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b2fd-d05a-adda-baff4f6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 2-of-4 targets for 47 in the Titans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b337-d45c-a7fc-b33ffaf30000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor totaled 1844 yards and 12 touchdowns in 24 games over the last two years while at Stanford. Selected in the fourth round of the 2025 NFL Draft, the 22-year-old receiver caught 2-of-4 targets for 47 yards against the Falcons on Friday. Ayomanor played just seven snaps and was targeted by fellow rookie Cam Ward four times, which is bullish for his eventual usage. Van Jefferson dropped what would’ve been a touchdown and Tyler Lockett isn’t the player he once was at this point of his career, which leaves a path for Ayomanor to move up the depth chart as the season goes on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b337-d45c-a7fc-b33ffaf30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 4-of-4 targets for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Titans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Falcons on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b341-d45c-a7fc-b35b87910000</link>
      <description>While Chig Okonkwo is still the top tight end with the Titans, he seems to have legitimate rookie competition in the form of Helm. Okonkwo didn’t suit up Friday, but played every snap with the first team in the Titans’ first preseason game. Helm made the most of his opportunity Friday by catching every pass that came his way and hitting pay dirt. While it’s difficult to get excited about Helm’s fantasy prospects in 2025, he could be relevant enough to negatively impact Okonkwo’s fantasy stock this year. In the long term, Helm could be part of the Titans’ succession plan at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b341-d45c-a7fc-b35b87910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold completed 4-of-4 passes for 34 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 2 preseason game against the Chiefs on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b348-d90d-a5bd-b35b45c20000</link>
      <description>Darnold and the Seahawks offense went through the Chiefs’ defense like a hot knife through butter. The 28-year-old quarterback hit a series of short roll-out passes when the Seahawks running game took a break from gashing the Chiefs. If this drive was any indication of what the regular season will be like, the Seahawks won’t have any trouble putting up points this year with Darnold at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b348-d90d-a5bd-b35b45c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet ran five times for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ preseason Week 2 game against the Chiefs on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b353-d90d-a5bd-b35b634b0000</link>
      <description>Kenneth Walker III didn’t play, but Charbonnet was excellent in the lead back role Friday. The 24-year-old running back from UCLA averaged nine yards per carry. Charbonnet capped the opening drive for Seattle with a 15-yard touchdown run. Heading into the season behind Walker on the depth chart, Charbonnet is a premium handcuff given the Seahawks’ outstanding running game under Klint Kubiak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b353-d90d-a5bd-b35b634b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith ran three times for 22 yards and caught 2-of-2 targets for 16 yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 2 game against the Seahawks on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b35b-df63-a199-fb7b9bea0000</link>
      <description>Smith only had five touches, but showed he has some juice against the Seahawks. The 22-year-old running back made a defender miss in the backfield before bouncing the run outside and gaining 10 yards. Smith also caught both of his targets for 16 yards. He certainly looked better than Elijah Mitchell, who had just nine yards on four carries. Smith figures to mix in as one of a few backs behind Isiah Pacheco this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b35b-df63-a199-fb7b9bea0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
