<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 02:29:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals activated DL Walter Nolen (calf) from the reserve/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b92-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa2d9f0000</link>
      <description>The 16th overall selection will plug into Arizona’s defensive line rotation immediately. The Cardinals also activated CB Garrett Williams from injured reserve ahead of tonight’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b92-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa2d9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Matthew Golden (shoulder) will be day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b91-d45b-affe-5f9757a80000</link>
      <description>It’s an encouraging sign for Golden, who was initially thought to be at risk of missing some time. We’ll see if we get more information on his availability before the team releases its first injury report on Thursday, but fantasy managers don’t need to be too concerned about Golden’s availability. The rookie receiver has caught just 23 passes for 262 scoreless yards in eight games this season and can be dropped in all seasonal formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b91-d45b-affe-5f9757a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers announced T Joe Alt (ankle) will undergo surgery and miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b9f-d673-a39e-ef9fb3d30000</link>
      <description>Alt will have season-ending surgery after suffering a second high-ankle sprain to the same leg. We often see NFL players take their time coming back from high-ankle sprains, and rarely do we get the recurrence. This is a brutal blow for the Chargers and puts some governors on their rest of season output. Trey Pipkins and Bobby Hart will do their best to keep Justin Herbert upright, but the Chargers may be susceptible to down games against good pass rushes. Alt will enter year three of his rookie contract in 2026 and he and Rashawn Slater will try to pick up the pieces of what was supposed to be this year in rehab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b9f-d673-a39e-ef9fb3d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Omarion Hampton (ankle) will not have his window to return opened until after the Chargers’ Week 12 bye week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bab-d673-a39e-efbb52b00000</link>
      <description>This has been the tenor of most updates on Hampton, who was placed on IR after Week 5, as he was still spotted in a walking boot after Thursday’s win over the Vikings. Kimani Vidal will continue to be the main back to roster for the Chargers at the moment, though it’s hard to see Hampton not getting the majority of the reps whenever he eventually is activated off injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bab-d673-a39e-efbb52b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) will not play in Week 9 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bfc-d713-ad9e-6ffce74a0000</link>
      <description>The team was reportedly set to see how the veteran signal caller responded to a pre-game workout, but it now appears as if he will miss a third straight game. Murray’s next chance to take the field will come in Week 10 against the division rival Seahawks, which will mark over a calendar month since he sustained the foot injury when you include the team’s Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bfc-d713-ad9e-6ffce74a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Cowboys have had talks with Bengals on DE Trey Hendrickson and LB Logan Wilson and Dolphins on OLB Bradley Chubb.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c1a-d1e7-a1fa-5efa35300000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys appear intent on adding pass rush help after trading away Micah Parsons to the Packers this offseason, with Schultz going so far as to say, “a deal is getting done somewhere.” it is public knowledge that the Bengals are seeking a first round pick in exchange for Hendrickson, making it slightly more likely the Cowboys eventually land either Wilson or Chubb in the coming hours ahead of Tuesday’s trade deadline. Stay tuned to see how this situation unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c1a-d1e7-a1fa-5efa35300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) is inactive for Week 9 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c1d-d713-ad9e-6c5d481a0000</link>
      <description>The initial plan for Murray was to see how he did in pre-game warmups before deciding how involved he would be against the Cowboys, but that plan reportedly went out the window a couple hours before game time, per ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler. Jacoby Brissett will draw the start under center for the third consecutive game against the Cowboys. Also inactive for the Cardinals are CB Elijah Jones, LB Xavier Thomas, OL Demontrey Jacobs, OL Josh Fryar, and DL Bilal Nichols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c1d-d713-ad9e-6c5d481a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Mazi Smith is inactive for Week 9 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c20-d45b-affe-5db6ec820000</link>
      <description>Smith being a healthy inactive seems to indicate the team is including him in offers for help at pass rusher in the coming hours, while the Dallas secondary continues to suffer through a multitude of injuries. Blue’s status as a game-day inactive is interesting considering Miles Sanders remains on injured reserve, leaving Malik Davis to serve as the primary change of pace option behind Javonte Williams. Also inactive for the Cowboys are S Donovan Wilson, S Alijah Clark, OT Ajani Cornelius, RB Jaydon Blue, OL Hakeem Adeniji, and WR Jonathan Mingo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c20-d45b-affe-5db6ec820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspended Commanders LB Frankie Luvu for one game “for repeated violations of playing rules.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c4a-d45b-affe-5ddea17f0000</link>
      <description>Luvu committed a hip-drop tackle in the first quarter of the team’s Week 9 contest against the Seahawks, his third such infraction of the season. He was fined for the previous two cases, once in Week 4 and again in Week 8, this time drawing the one-game suspension by the league’s disciplinary office. He will serve his suspension in Week 10 when the Commanders host the Lions before being eligible to return against the Dolphins in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c4a-d45b-affe-5ddea17f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans traded LB Dre’Mont Jones to the Ravens for a conditional fifth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c4d-d673-a39e-ecddbe890000</link>
      <description>The fifth-round pick could become a fourth. Jones has gone on a torrid stretch in recent weeks, amassing 4.5 sacks in his previous four games, and provides the Ravens with a veteran pass rush presence as they make a late-season push towards the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4c4d-d673-a39e-ecddbe890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
