<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 18:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants CB Paulson Adebo (knee) is active for New York’s Week 11 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d85-d45b-affe-dd97c17d0000</link>
      <description>Adebo has not played since Week 7, so the Giants will have their big offseason CB addition back in the fold to try to contain Jordan Love on the rare occasions when Matt LaFleur actually unleashes him. Bobby Okereke (shoulder) is also playing off a questionable tag. Inactive for the Giants are: OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder), QB Jaxson Dart (concussion), WR Darius Slayton (hamstring), S Tyler Nubin (neck), DL Chauncey Golston (neck), DL Rakeem Nuñez-Roches (toe) and lone healthy scratch OT James Hudson III.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d85-d45b-affe-dd97c17d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers OG Isaac Seumalo (pectoral) is active for Week 11 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d83-d1e7-a1fa-dfeba3c00000</link>
      <description>Seumalo logged two limited practices to start the week and was downgraded to a DNP on Friday. It’s possible that DNP was more of a rest day, but whatever the case, the veteran guard will be good to go against the Bengals. While Seumalo is active, the Steelers did rule out QB Will Howard, CB Darius Slay, LB Cole Holcomb, LB Alex Highsmith, OG Andrus Peat, DT Brodric Martin-Rhodes, and DT Logan Lee for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d83-d1e7-a1fa-dfeba3c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Hunter Renfrow, S Lathan Ransom, LB Trevin Wallace, C Nick Samac, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, and DT Cam Jackson inactive for Week 11 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d86-d1e7-a1fa-dfee70840000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as the Panthers didn’t have anyone listed as questionable heading into the weekend. Renfrow hasn’t played since Week 6. He remains a healthy scratch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d86-d1e7-a1fa-dfee70840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers K Brandon McManus is inactive for Week 11 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d88-d45b-affe-dd9eae6b0000</link>
      <description>34-year-old McManus is missing too much time with injury for a kicker this season. Lucas Havrisik will handle kicking duties today in New York. He’s a mediocre fantasy option with the Pack’s offense really going through it right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d88-d45b-affe-dd9eae6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans activated TE Cade Stover (foot) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d75-d45b-affe-ddf7d51e0000</link>
      <description>He was questionable but will return from injured reserve today. It’s possible he eats into Dalton Schultz’s snap share a bit. Inactive for the Texans are: DB Jalen Pitre (concussion), QB C.J. Stroud (concussion), K Ka’imi Fairbairn (quad), G Ed Ingram (knee), WR Braxton Berrios, RB Dameon Pierce, and OT Jarrett Kingston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d75-d45b-affe-ddf7d51e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs declared OLB Haason Reddick, RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin Jr., DL C.J. Brewer. OLB Markees Watts, OL Ben Bredeson, and OL Elijah Klein inactive for Week 11 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d88-d1e7-a1fa-dfeafacb0000</link>
      <description>Irving, Godwin, and Reddick were all ruled out earlier in the week. That’s five starters in total who the Bucks will have inactive for Sunday’s game. Sean Tucker will carry much of the load against st a vulnerable Bills run defense and the rest of the Bucs pass rushers will need to step up to try and get to Josh Allen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d88-d1e7-a1fa-dfeafacb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones (soulder/toe) is active for Week 11 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d8b-d673-a39e-ad9b4d430000</link>
      <description>Jones was limited in practice to start the week but got in a full practice session on Friday and will play against Chicago’s exploitable run defense. Jones, after taking over the backfield over the past two weeks, should be considered a top-20 fantasy play against the Bears. Jordan Mason is little more than a contingency option for now. Vikings declared OLB Chaz Chambliss, OLB Jonathan Greenard, T Walter Rouse, TE Ben Sims, and DL Elijah Williams inactive against Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d8b-d673-a39e-ad9b4d430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bills WR Keon Coleman missed a team meeting on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d93-d1e7-a1fa-dffb56330000</link>
      <description>The team disciplined Coleman by making him a healthy inactive for Week 11 against the Bucs. The Bills reportedly planned on playing Coleman in his usual role this week before he missed the Friday meeting. Coleman has 32 receptions on 49 targets this season for 330 yards and three touchdowns. His absence will likely open up more routes and targets for Josh Palmer, who becomes a desperation fantasy option in deeper formats with Coleman being inactive against Tampa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d93-d1e7-a1fa-dffb56330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Kris Boyd “was shot and critically wounded” on Sunday morning and is currently at Bellevue Hospital in critical but stable condition.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d89-d673-a39e-ad9997800000</link>
      <description>Per the New York Post’s reporting, Boyd is currently “clinging to life.” He was shot in the abdomen after a dispute outside a restaurant in Manhattan. Boyd lapsed in and out of consciousness before being taken to the hospital. We will continue to update this story as it develops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8d89-d673-a39e-ad9997800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 14-of-20 passes for 171 yards in the Dolphins’ 16-13, Week 11 overtime win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dc4-d45b-affe-ddd627cd0000</link>
      <description>Tua averaged a respectable 8.6 yards per attempt and didn’t turn the ball over. The Dolphins’ drives, however, stalled out at nearly every turn. Their first two drives ended within the Commanders’ 30-yard line, both of which resulted in field goals. Miami also had two drives stopped at the goal line, the second of which would have given the Phins the lead with under two minutes on the clock. Luckily for Tua and the offense, Miami’s defense picked off Marcus Mariota on his first attempt of overtime. Mike McDaniel then ran De’Von Achane three times and sent out the field goal unit to win the game. Tagovailoa is barely hanging on to QB2 fantasy value, but the Dolphins at least have some momentum heading into their Week 12 bye. They will look to extend their win streak to three when they take on the Saints in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8dc4-d45b-affe-ddd627cd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
