<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 1-of-2 targets for four yards in the Falcons’ Week 17 win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6db0-d56e-afff-eff869fd0000</link>
      <description>London continued to see his playing time monitored in his second game back following a four-game absence, seeing only two targets on a night the Falcons attempted only 20 passes due to increasingly positive game script. The team built a 21-0 lead in the first half on the legs of Bijan Robinson, who accounted for 229 of the team’s 345 yards of total offense against one of the better run defenses in the league. London should remain a top 12 fantasy receiver entering the 2026 offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6db0-d56e-afff-eff869fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 2-of-3 targets for 35 yards in the Falcons’ Week 17 win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6db2-dc7a-af9b-efbf6d0e0000</link>
      <description>Mooney and the rest of the Atlanta pass-catchers simply weren’t needed in this one as running back Bijan Robinson amassed 229 yards of offense against one of the better run defenses in the league. It was actually fill-in receiver David Sills that led the team in receiving with 37 yards on three receptions, which tells the tale of how the game was won. Mooney finishes his regular season against the surging Saints in Week 18 after a disappointing campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6db2-dc7a-af9b-efbf6d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern University hired Chip Kelly, formerly of the Raiders, as the team’s offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f78-d35e-a1bf-6ffa0eb20000</link>
      <description>Kelly lands the Northwestern OC gig after a disastrous season with the Raiders, who fired him in late November after operating one of the NFL’s worst, most inefficient offenses. Plagued by a terrible offensive line coaches by Pete Carroll’s son — one of two Carroll kid who work for the Raiders — Kelly’s offense was near the bottom of the league in both EPA per play and success rate through November. Kelly will take over a Northwestern offense that ranked 53rd in the nation in EPA per play in 2025, and 44th in rushing EPA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f78-d35e-a1bf-6ffa0eb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes the Eagles could rest some starters in Week 18 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f8e-dc7a-af9b-efbf3e700000</link>
      <description>The Eagles could climb as high as the No. 2 seed in the NFC with a victory and a Lions win over Chicago, and Garafolo believes they could beat Washington with some of their key starters resting for the postseason. That could include Jalen Hurts, which would mean Tanner McKee could see significant playing time against a Commanders defense being bludgeoned by opposing QBs. If Saquon Barkley sits, Tank Bigsby — who has been ultra efficient as an Eagle — could see a full workload against the Swiss cheese Washington run defense. It’s a situation to monitor for fantasy managers playing in Week 18 championships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f8e-dc7a-af9b-efbf3e700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colts QB Riley Leonard will start in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f9b-d56e-afff-effba31d0000</link>
      <description>With their season over, the Colts will see what they have in Leonard, the 189th pick in the 2025 NFL Draft out of Notre Dame. Leonard completed 18 of 29 attempts for 145 yards and an interception against the Jaguars in Week 14 after Daniel Jones went down — a performance that led head coach Shane Steichen to sign 44-year-old Philip Rivers as a desperation measure. Leonard completed 61 percent of his passes for 365 yards, one touchdown, and one interception over three preseason appearances in the summer. He took one sacks on 22 pressures in those games and ran for 58 yards on seven rushes. Leonard’s rushing could make him interesting for superflex and DFS purposes in Week 18 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6f9b-d56e-afff-effba31d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports NFL evaluators are concerned about Cam Ward’s throwing mechanics.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6fb2-d35e-a1bf-6ff2498c0000</link>
      <description>Ward’s unorthodox delivery was hotly debated last winter ahead of the 2025 NFL Draft, when Ward, 23, went first overall to the Titans. His mechanics have been shaky at times in his miserable rookie campaign in Tennessee. “While beauty is in the eye of the beholder with a QB’s delivery, there are some around the NFL who are concerned his accuracy will have a ceiling if he doesn’t refine his mechanics,” Howe said. One NFL evaluator who spoke to Howe said Ward’s scrambling ability could compensate for his inaccuracy over the long haul (Ward ranks 31st out of 33 qualifying quarterbacks in completion rate over expected). “The great equalizer is his ability to scramble and make plays,” an NFL executive said. “Who knows if he’ll ever be strong on schedule. It’s hard to know how much it’s sustainable to make plays off schedule outside of the offense.” Perhaps a new coaching staff can clean up Ward’s iffy throwing motion ahead of the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6fb2-d35e-a1bf-6ff2498c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs faces felony strangulation or suffocation and misdemeanor assault and battery charges.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-702e-d56e-afff-f6ee0d8e0000</link>
      <description>The alleged assault, according to Boston 25 News, took place on Tuesday, December 2, after the Patriots beat the Giants on Monday Night Football. Diggs’ attorney said Diggs is in talks with the alleged victim to settle out of court. Diggs is scheduled to be arraigned on January 23, two days before the AFC Championship Game. The Patriots issued a statement saying the team supports Diggs. “The New England Patriots are aware of the accusations that have been made regarding Stefon Diggs,” the team said. “Stefon has informed the organization that he categorically denies the allegations. We support Stefon. We will continue to gather information and will cooperate fully with the appropriate authorities and the NFL as necessary.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-702e-d56e-afff-f6ee0d8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Darnell Washington had surgery to repair his broken arm.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-703b-d56e-afff-f6fbcc640000</link>
      <description>Washington underwent surgery Monday and won’t return to the Steelers this season, even if they manage to beat the Ravens in Week 18 and make the playoffs. Washington ends the 2025 season with 31 receptions on 43 targets for 364 yards and one touchdown. He was third among Pittsburgh tight ends in catches, as Jonnu Smith and Pat Freiermuth remains involved in Arthur Smith’s tight end-heavy offensive scheme. With Washington sidelined, Freiermuth would seem to be the main beneficiary. Both Smith and Freiermuth have a 48 percent route participation rate through Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-703b-d56e-afff-f6fbcc640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said the team would not rest its starters in Week 18 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7056-d968-a19b-78f7bbdd0000</link>
      <description>It’s hard to believe McVay would risk the health of key players — including Puka Nacua and Matthew Stafford — with the Rams all but locked into the No. 6 seed in the NFC after Monday night’s devastating loss to the Falcons. Perhaps the team’s starters will get a few drives before the backups come in against Arizona. That would include Jimmy Garappolo at quarterback and maybe Ronnie Rivers at running back. Keep it locked to Rotoworld for updates on which teams will rest their starters in the regular season’s final week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7056-d968-a19b-78f7bbdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived CB Trevon Diggs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-707f-dc7a-af9b-fffffd2c0000</link>
      <description>Diggs was regarded as one of the better corners in the NFL a few years ago, but has played just 1,208 defensive snaps over the last three years while dealing with injuries. The Cowboys have seemed disinterested in employing Diggs for some time, and the only surprise is that the move happened now instead of this offseason. Diggs’ contract is out of guaranteed money after this year, so it’s possible he is claimed on waivers. Former DC Dan Quinn is in Washington, which is one possible landing spot. It’s also possible that he gets a shot with a playoff team, though it might be a little late to crack anyone’s rotation for the Wild Card round at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-707f-dc7a-af9b-fffffd2c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
