<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 26 times for 68 yards in the Texans’ Week 14 win over the Chiefs, adding eight yards and a touchdown on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc46-d8cf-affb-fc6eed220000</link>
      <description>Marks served as a workhorse following the second quarter departure from veteran Nick Chubb, the latter of whom would not finish the game after only one touch. The budding rookie’s fantasy day could have been even bigger had he not been subbed out inside the five following a hard hit half way through the fourth quarter, resulting in a Dare Ogunbowale touchdown on his only touch of the game. Fantasy managers had already enjoyed lead back status for Marks the previous month of the season, but he could be set up for true workhorse status ahead of a Week 15 meeting with the Cardinals should Chubb be unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc46-d8cf-affb-fc6eed220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins caught 4-of-8 targets for 121 yards in the Texans’ Week 14 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc4a-d77b-adfa-fecb66f20000</link>
      <description>Collins broke free early for a 46-yard gain up the seam against Trent McDuffie coverage, the latter of whom would be injured on the play and miss the remainder of the game. The talented veteran added catches of 53 yards, 18 yards, and four yards before the break but would be blanked in the second half with the team nursing a lead throughout. Collins now has consecutive games of 98 yards or more through the air with C.J. Stroud under center, something he had not done against all opponents other than the Jaguars this season. The Texans now prepare for one of the worst defenses in the league in the Cardinals in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc4a-d77b-adfa-fecb66f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 3-of-4 targets for 22 yards in the Texans’ Week 14 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc50-d8cf-affb-fc7a254d0000</link>
      <description>It was Nico Collins that took advantage of the Chiefs early as the Texans built a 10-0 lead before the half, with the talented wide receiver erupting for 121 first-half yards after Kansas City shutdown corner Trent McDuffie departed with injury. The team’s pass volume dried up after the break due to positive game script, with Schultz ending with a disappointing 22 yards on the evening. Up next is a Cardinals opponent the Texans should be able to move the football against, although volume could once again be an issue for the veteran tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc50-d8cf-affb-fc7a254d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 3-of-5 targets for 34 yards in the Texans’ Week 14 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc54-d8cf-affb-fc7e33d10000</link>
      <description>Higgins continues to churn out meaningful production for a Texans team in dire need of secondary options behind alpha wide receiver Nico Collins. The towering rookie was kept out of the end zone but made two key grabs to keep the chains moving and could continue his ascension towards the end of the season. Up next is a plus matchup against the battered Cardinals in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc54-d8cf-affb-fc7e33d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 14-of-33 passes for 160 yards and three interceptions in the Chiefs’ 20-10, Week 14 loss to the Texans, adding 59 yards on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc5c-d77b-adfa-fedf08a30000</link>
      <description>This will be one to forget for Mahomes and the Chiefs as multiple aspects of their game plan came crashing down in a must-win game. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-7 and advanced odds now give them a measly 16% chance to make the postseason. Minutes after C.J. Stroud set the benchmark for consecutive incompletions this season with nine, Mahomes followed it up with 10 straight passes without a completion in the second half. Two of those were key interceptions while both Rashee Rice and Travis Kelce were charged with two drops during the streak. The 10 straight incompletions were also a career-worst for Mahomes, it was only the third time in his career where the Chiefs were shutout in a half, and it was only the fourth game in his career with three or more interceptions. The Chiefs must quickly lick their wounds ahead of a showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc5c-d77b-adfa-fedf08a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 12 times for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc65-da9b-a9bf-fe6d52cd0000</link>
      <description>It as a far from inspiring performance from the backfield duo behind an offensive line missing three starters. Both backs managed only 30 yards, with Isiah Pacheco’s coming on only nine carries. The two continue to operate in a near-even split, although Hunt continues to see higher value touches near the end zone. There doesn’t appear to be much fantasy value remaining in the Kansas City backfield ahead of a showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc65-da9b-a9bf-fe6d52cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 3-of-4 targets for 55 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs struggled to move the football throughout against the league’s top defense, with quarterback Patrick Mahomes setting a career high in consecutive incompletions with 10 in the second half. The one good aspect of Worthy’s game was that he failed to account for any drops, which both Travis Kelce and Rashee Rice could not say leaving the game. Worthy continues to see modest volume with both primary options healthy, a trend likely to hold ahead of a Week 15 showdown with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 4-of-8 targets for 34 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</link>
      <description>Not only did Rice fail to return a usable fantasy outing, but two of Patrick Mahomes’ four incompletions when targeting Rice went down as drops. The worst instance came on fourth down half way through the fourth quarter when Rice saw the pass go straight through his hands. The poor outing can be viewed as a slight blip for fantasy’s overall WR1 in fantasy points per game ahead of a must-win game against the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 1-of-5 targets for eight yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</link>
      <description>Kelce’s night looks bad enough on paper before you realize two of Patrick Mahomes’ incompletions when targeting the veteran tight end were drops. Additionally, Kelce bobbled a pass on the team’s penultimate possession that was picked off by Azeez Al-Shaair with under four minutes remaining and down by a touchdown. That would allow the Texans to run down the clock to under 30 seconds after kicking a field goal to go up by 10. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-7 with only a 16% chance of making the playoffs. Kelce will be needed in a must-win showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Butker went 1-for-2 in field goal attempts in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</link>
      <description>He connected from 36 yards and made his only point after attempt, missing from 43 yards at the end of the second quarter when his kick hit off the left upright. That missed field goal contributed to the Chiefs being shutout in the first half for only the third time in quarterback Patrick Mahomes’ career, making the failed conversion slightly more meaningful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
