<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 22:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins caught 3-of-4 targets for 85 yards and two touchdowns in Houston’s Week 15 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed4-d8cf-affb-befe30330000</link>
      <description>He kicked off Houston’s offense by housing a middle-of-the-field target for 57 yards on their second play from scrimmage, then added a late touchdown in the fourth quarter on a goal-to-go target over the middle. Letting Nico Collins feast over the middle of the field, as it turns out, a good idea. It’s his first two-score game since last year’s Week 15 win over the Dolphins. Collins will be a WR1 in Week 16 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed4-d8cf-affb-befe30330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Patriots’ Week 15 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed4-d77b-adfb-ded7c0290000</link>
      <description>The Bills were without their top cornerback, Christian Benford, so we expected a little more from Diggs, who was tremendous against his former team earlier in the season. Instead, Diggs was a bit of an afterthought; however, the Patriots controlled much of the game with their running attack and didn’t need to throw heavily until late in the third quarter. Still, once that time hit, Diggs and Drake Maye were unable to make any big plays. They’ll hope for more next week against the Ravens, but Diggs has now had under 30 receiving yards in three straight games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed4-d77b-adfb-ded7c0290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Cook completed 22-of-33 passes for 176 yards, one touchdown and three interceptions in the Jets’ 48-20, Week 15 loss to the Jaguars, adding six rushes for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed8-d77b-adfb-dedbe8f80000</link>
      <description>Although as you can see he threw three interceptions, Cook wasn’t the problem in the Jets’ four-score road loss. Well, ok, at least not the main problem. Processing quickly and looking more decisive than he did sometimes even at Mizzou, Cook didn’t seem rattled by the speed of the NFL in his first start, though the mistakes did mount after Gang Green went down 21-7 early in the second quarter. That’s going to be a problem for any young starter, let alone an undrafted rookie. So if Cook wasn’t the reason the Jets fell behind, he helped make the final score look worse, perhaps most of all when he threw a late inexcusable end zone interception. Trying to find Allen Lazard (which,), Lawrence just kind of lofted the ball up in the air. They do not teach you to do that in the field of play in the red zone. So it was a “learning experience,” but not one screaming “Cook must be benched for Week 16.” That one will find the Jets on the road in New Orleans. As was the case today, Cook will be off superflex radars, and players like Adonai Mitchell will be “play at your own risk.” That, of course, is if neither Justin Fields (knee) nor Tyrod Taylor (groin) can return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed8-d77b-adfb-dedbe8f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught his only target for four yards in Houston’s Week 15 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed6-d1bc-a3fb-9ff6e9f50000</link>
      <description>The bad news is that the target tree narrowed and C.J. Stroud was content to check it down underneath to running backs, the good news is: Higgins still played 48-of-67 snaps and was more involved than most of the other non-Nico Collins wideouts. He’ll still remain a WR4/FLEX play at best against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed6-d1bc-a3fb-9ff6e9f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shedeur Sanders completed 18-of-35 passes for 177 yards and three interceptions in the Browns’ 31-3 loss to the Bears in Week 15, adding two rushes for 24 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ec8-d1bc-a3fb-9fec5d290000</link>
      <description>While Sanders’ line looks ugly, he’s also not getting much help from the rest of the offense. The 23-year-old quarterback was sacked five times and had a touchdown bounce off Jerry Jeudy’s hands for an interception in the third quarter. It’s been a mixed bag for Sander after four starts. He’s just a QB2 option for desperate managers in super flex formats against the Bills in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ec8-d1bc-a3fb-9fec5d290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 7-of-9 targets for 70 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 15 loss against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed7-d005-a9bf-def7a1080000</link>
      <description>Kelce tied for the team lead in receptions and led the Chiefs in receiving yardage thanks in large part to a hurry up approach in the fourth quarter as the Chiefs tried (and failed) to keep their playoff hopes alive. Kelce converted five first downs on the day. It was the fourth time in 2025 Kelce has exceeded 68 receiving yards. His rest-of-season usage is very much an open question with Kansas City eliminated from postseason contention and Patrick Mahomes going down in the fourth quarter with an apparently serious knee injury. Gardner Minshew’s penchant for check downs could keep Kelce alive as a weekly fantasy starter, however. Kelce will face the Titans in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed7-d005-a9bf-def7a1080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 1-of-3 targets for 18 yards in the Patriots’ Week 15 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed9-d8cf-affb-befb9d130000</link>
      <description>The Bills are pretty good against tight ends, and the Patriots’ offense was moving the ball with ease on the ground, which explains Henry’s low target total. However, when the Patriots did need to throw to take back the lead, Hunter Henry dropped a third-down pass that would have been a first down and forced the Patriots to punt with under four minutes left. We’d expect more from him next week against the Ravens, but he’s more of a low-end TE1 with everybody healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed9-d8cf-affb-befb9d130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Hutchinson caught 1-of-2 targets for 16 yards in Houston’s Week 15 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1eda-d8cf-affb-befafd900000</link>
      <description>Of note: Hutchinson’s snap share fell dramatically as the Texans never trailed, he played just 20-of-67 snaps. You probably weren’t relying on him unless you were in a very deep league, but Cade Stover played 41 snaps and the Texans played big with the lead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1eda-d8cf-affb-befafd900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed eight times for 66 yards in the Ravens’ Week 15 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed6-d8cf-affb-befef56c0000</link>
      <description>Mitchell continues to look like the most explosive back in the Ravens’ backfield. He handled three-straight carries on the Ravens’ third possession, picking up gains of eight, four, and 15 yards before an interception by Lamar Jackson ended things. Mitchell nearly broke free for a long score on the final drive of the game, but was knocked out of bounds to hold his gain to 22 yards. Despite his big-play ability, Mitchell’s touches remain limited. He’ll be little more than a desperation FLEX play in Week 16 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ed6-d8cf-affb-befef56c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift rushed 18 times for 98 yards and two touchdowns in the Bears’ Week 15 win over the Browns, adding one catch for negative-two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1edb-d77b-adfb-dedb2d970000</link>
      <description>Swift scored the first points of the game with a six-yard touchdown run midway through the first quarter. It was clear he was on his way to one of his better games of the season early on. He piled on with another touchdown run, this one for 17 yards towards the end of the third quarter. Swift is a solid RB2 heading into a home date with the Packers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1edb-d77b-adfb-dedb2d970000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
