<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals acquired QB Joe Flacco and a 2026 sixth-round pick from the Browns for a 2025 fifth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfac-d94a-a79d-bfad690f0000</link>
      <description>Flacco may help steady fantasy values for Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins, but it’s not like the Bengals have a significantly better offensive line than the Browns. They may, in fact, have a worse running game. Flacco jumps in to the superflex QB2 consideration zone while Chase and Higgins don’t take an appreciable step forward, but perhaps grab a little extra floor. This is a patch job for the Bengals, who simply couldn’t keep giving snaps to Jake Browning after his disastrous showings and lack of confidence the last few weeks. Browning is a drop in all leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfac-d94a-a79d-bfad690f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OC Nick Holz said he “could see” TE Gunnar Helm’s targets going up moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfba-dd4c-afb9-fffbe5860000</link>
      <description>Last week after saying that his opportunities would increase, Helm had a career-high five targets and played a career-high 44 snaps for the Titans. Chig Okonkwo saw a season-low 42 snaps, though he did come alive in garbage time. Helm is definitely someone to monitor with an eye towards a TE1 rank, especially with bye weeks here, but the two so far have cannibalized each other’s production enough that Helm would need another step forward to be more than a TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfba-dd4c-afb9-fffbe5860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said the “arrow is pointed up” for Jaylen Warren (knee) to return in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfbe-d94a-a79d-bfbfbd6e0000</link>
      <description>It didn’t seem like Warren had much of an injury and he apparently showed well in Monday’s (non-injury report required) practice. Tomlin also said that Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) and Alex Highsmith (ankle) were likely to be back this week. Warren will slide right back into an RB2/FLEX role on most fantasy rosters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfbe-d94a-a79d-bfbfbd6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed S C.J. Gardner-Johnson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfc4-def2-abdb-bfe5b6a50000</link>
      <description>The Texans released Gardner-Johnson after Week 3 and much came out about him freelancing, blowing assignments, and complaining about his role. The Ravens defense is at a juncture where they’d probably take that if it came with some competent NFL-level play, too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfc4-def2-abdb-bfe5b6a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed K Michael Badgley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfef-db72-a199-ffef9ef30000</link>
      <description>Badgley suffered a torn hamstring and missed the entire 2024 season. He’ll be tasked with replacing Spencer Shrader as Indianapolis’ main kicker and will likely be a top-10 option the rest of the way given how well the Colts offense has played through five weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bfef-db72-a199-ffef9ef30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals released QB Brett Rypien.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c014-db72-a199-fa5f51130000</link>
      <description>Rypien seems likely to take the role on the practice squad left behind by Mike White now that Joe Flacco has come aboard the good ship Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c014-db72-a199-fa5f51130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Odell Beckham Jr. has been suspended for six games for violating the NFL’s policy on performance-enhancing drugs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c015-db72-a199-fa5ff3530000</link>
      <description>There have been scant rumors of interest in Beckham throughout the offseason. If any of those teams wish to sign him, they’ll have to weather six games without him first.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c015-db72-a199-fa5ff3530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane reports Landon Dickerson (ankle) could miss the next “1-2 games.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c01e-db72-a199-fa5f0cdb0000</link>
      <description>There’s little chance of Dickerson or Grant Calcaterra (oblique) suiting up for Thursday’s game against the Giants. It sounds like Week 7, though, remains in play for both. The Eagles went with Brett Toth when Dickerson suffered the injury against Denver and he’d be the likely replacement on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c01e-db72-a199-fa5f0cdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals OC Drew Petzing said after rewatching Week 5’s loss to the Titans, he felt he didn’t do enough to get the ball to Marvin Harrison Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c024-dd4c-afb9-e7e5e9a70000</link>
      <description>Harrison only had five targets despite a 98-yard day for the Cardinals in Week 5, though some of them were of course buried with the Cardinals trying to kill clock before the hilarious ending of their game. “Going back and looking at it, I think there’s maybe a couple things I could’ve done differently.” Petzing told reporters. These sorts of confessions don’t always lead to increased production the next week, and Petzing seems way too conservative in general to get Harrison to the WR1 land we were promised, but perhaps the combination of a good Colts offense and the #SqueakyWheel narrative could make something come together for Harrison in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c024-dd4c-afb9-e7e5e9a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars placed Brenton Strange (hip) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c036-db72-a199-fa7fb7e30000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least four games. It’s a big loss for the Jaguars, Strange had a 22-yard reception in Week 6 and was one of the team’s leading receivers over the past month. Hunter Long saw a huge boost in playing time, up to 35 snaps after never previously playing more than 22 in a game this year, in in Strange’s absence. It’s hard to recommend Long as a streamer given his lack of career production, but the role is there for him to be a TE2 in some leagues. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reported Strange is expected to miss about a month, which should put him in line for a Week 11 return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c036-db72-a199-fa7fb7e30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
