<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Lions RB David Montgomery (illness) is expected to be active Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e6-d56e-afff-f7eead300000</link>
      <description>The Lions play the afternoon Christmas game and had Montgomery listed as questionable due to an illness. He missed Tuesday’s practice and was limited Wednesday; Garafolo reports he is expected to go Thursday against the Vikings. Montgomery should have more opportunities in the run game this week with a run-heavy game script looking favorable, giving him RB3 upside for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e6-d56e-afff-f7eead300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez Jr. (illness) is inactive for Week 17 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55f3-d56e-afff-f7fb98b50000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez was a late add to the injury report with an illness and is now officially inactive for the Commanders’ Christmas afternoon game against the Cowboys. Jacory Croskey-Merrit is an RB3 with Rodriguez out. The Commanders also declared QB Jayden Daniels, QB Marcus Mariota, QB Sam Hartman, LT Laremy Tunsil, LB Nick Bellore, and DT Daron Payne out against the Cowboys. Payne did not practice all week with a back issue. Jeff Driskel is Josh Johnson’s backup while Sam Hartman is the emergency third quarterback for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55f3-d56e-afff-f7fb98b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) inactive for Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-565e-d56e-afff-f6fef6ae0000</link>
      <description>Flournoy is dealing with a knee injury he suffered in Week 16 against the Chargers. He failed to get in a full practice on a short week and is now ruled out, making KaVontae Turpin the Cowboys’ No. 3 wide receiver for the week. The Cowboys also declared LB DeMarvion Overshown, CB Caelen Carson, RB Jaydon Blue, DT Jay Toia, and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive for Week 17 against the Commanders. Overshown is out with a concussion suffered in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-565e-d56e-afff-f6fef6ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-566a-d35e-a1bf-57ea2c690000</link>
      <description>Decker was already questionable with a shoulder injury that he has been playing through, but now adds an illness designation just hours before the Lions’ Week 17 game against the Vikings. We just saw Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez ruled out with an illness after he was added to the injury report in a similar fashion, so Decker looks to be truly questionable to play on Christmas day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-566a-d35e-a1bf-57ea2c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Jaguars CB Jourdan Lewis will undergo foot surgery and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5698-d35e-a1bf-57da12cf0000</link>
      <description>Lewis started the week not practicing due to the foot issue, which is severe enough to require surgery. As a result, the 30-year-old veteran will miss the rest of the season. It’s a big loss for the Jaguars, who got two interceptions in 12 games out of Lewis after signing him to a three-year deal this past offseason. Jacksonville will reach into its depth to fill the nickel spot, both for this week against the Colts, and for a playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5698-d35e-a1bf-57da12cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-56ea-dc7a-af9b-dfffbabf0000</link>
      <description>Dawson Knox also did not suit up for the second consecutive practice, making the duo’s involvement in Friday’s session paramount to their potential to suit up in a marquee showdown against the Eagles this weekend. Fantasy managers will want to track their practice status closely on Friday, although it currently appears as if both will carry an injury designation into the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-56ea-dc7a-af9b-dfffbabf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (shoulder) is questionable to return to Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-56f3-d968-a19b-5ef36cbd0000</link>
      <description>Williams departed in the second quarter and was seen grabbing at his shoulder. He was deemed questionable to return by the Cowboys before the half. Malik Davis would be in line to serve as the primary back in a solid matchup should Williams fail to return. Williams gained 54 yards and a touchdown on 13 carries prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-56f3-d968-a19b-5ef36cbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared QB J.J. McCarthy, QB Brett Rypien, RB Jordan Mason, LB Austin Keys, T Brian O’Neill, and TE T.J. Hockenson inactive for Week 17 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5719-d968-a19b-5ff9adbe0000</link>
      <description>Both McCarthy and Hockenson had been ruled out earlier in the week. O’Neill’s absence leaves Blake Brandel to start at right tackle and Justin Skule at left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5719-d968-a19b-5ff9adbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RB David Montgomery (illness) and WR Amon-Ra St. Brown are active for Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5720-d35e-a1bf-57e2b9c60000</link>
      <description>Montgomery was added to the injury report early Thursday morning with an illness but is apparently well enough to play against the Vikings. There is the potential for Jahmyr Gibbs to see a slight uptick in snaps and usage considering the illness. St. Brown saw his practice involvement monitored on the short week but is also active. Inactive for the Lions are OL Trystan Colon, OL Taylor Decker, DL Tyler Lacy, WR Dominic Lovett, S Avonte Maddox, OL Michael Niese, and DL Mekhi Wingo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5720-d35e-a1bf-57e2b9c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) will not return to Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5732-d56e-afff-f7fa3a550000</link>
      <description>Ferguson departed in the third quarter with a calf injury and was promptly ruled out for the remainder of the contest. It will be Brevin Spann-Ford operating as the primary tight end for the Cowboys for the final frame. Ferguson caught 1-of-2 targets for a six-yard touchdown prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5732-d56e-afff-f7fa3a550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
