<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson caught 3-of-4 targets for 31 yards and one touchdown in the Saints’ Week 9 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4778-d713-ad9e-6f7cb1a20000</link>
      <description>Johnson turned an otherwise quiet day into a likely TE1 outcome on a curl route run from the Rams’ 11-yard line. Johnson found a soft spot in the Rams’ zone coverage and waited for the ball. Once secured, he shucked off an arm-tackle attempt made by diving LB Nate Landman before powering past two more Rams defenders for the score. Johnson is a low-end TE1 against the Panthers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4778-d713-ad9e-6f7cb1a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taysom Hill completed 0-of-1 passes in the Saints’ Week 9 loss to the Rams, adding four rushes for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4778-d1e7-a1fa-5ffac9e30000</link>
      <description>Hill ripped off a 29-yard rumbling run up the middle on the Saints’ fourth drive and was allowed to stay in for two more plays. He then gained one yard on the ground before throwing an incomplete pass to No. 2 WR Rashid Shaheed. Hill’s most consequential play occurred late in the game, when head coach Kellen Moore subbed out rookie QB Tyler Shough for Hill on 4th-and-2 from the Rams’ seven-yard line. Hill’s seemingly obvious run up the middle was stuffed for a two-yard loss, robbing Shough of a valuable rep. Hill is a boom-bust TE2 against the Panthers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4778-d1e7-a1fa-5ffac9e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 3-of-4 targets for 38 yards in the Raiders’ Week 9 loss against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477c-d45b-affe-57fe152d0000</link>
      <description>Tucker was fourth among Vegas pass catchers in targets, running a pass route on all 46 of Geno Smith’s drop backs. Tucker, who hasn’t scored a touchdown since his three-touchdown Week 3 outburst against Washington, should only be rostered in 14-team leagues. With Brock Bowers back from his ankle injury, it will be difficult for any other pass catcher to put up fantasy-relevant numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477c-d45b-affe-57fe152d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara rushed six times for 14 yards and one fumble lost in the Saints’ Week 9 loss to the Rams, adding one reception for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477a-d673-a39e-e7fb21da0000</link>
      <description>Saints head coach Kellen Moore remains committed to running Kamara inefficiently up the middle, despite the veteran running back’s historic pass-catching prowess. On the plus side, Moore did call Kamara’s number on a 4th-and-1 pitch, on the Saints’ fourth drive, but the play was stopped by officials due to a false start. Later, on the Saints’ lone third-quarter drive, Rams S Kamren Kinchens knocked the ball out of Kamara’s hands on yet another run up the middle. The Rams recovered, and Kamara did not touch the ball on the two remaining drives, giving way to two touches for rookie RB Devin Neal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477a-d673-a39e-e7fb21da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Neal rushed three times for 11 yards in the Saints’ Week 9 loss to the Rams, adding one reception for one yard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477c-d673-a39e-e7fd4f2e0000</link>
      <description>Neal continues to tally notable snap shares without also tallying voluminous touch counts. While the former is a positive, we hope to soon see the latter come to fruition. Perhaps the biggest development this week was starting RB Alvin Kamara’s third-quarter lost fumble. The Saints had two ensuing drives in the fourth quarter, and Neal was the only Saints running back to touch the ball, though he logged just two offensive touches during that span. The rookie running back remains a worthwhile bench stash, though fantasy managers must continue exercising patience, particularly with the Saints on bye in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-477c-d673-a39e-e7fd4f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said he did not have a timeline on Taron Johnson’s (groin) return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4772-d673-a39e-e7f35f000000</link>
      <description>Johnson popped up on Friday’s injury report with his injury and was eventually scratched from Sunday’s game against the Chiefs. McDermott said after the game that Johnson had “no chance to play in the game” before later adding that the team is “taking it one week at a time.” Johnson is one of the league’s top slot corners and has played on 269 defensive snaps in the six games he has appeared in this season, per PFF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4772-d673-a39e-e7f35f000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 23-of-34 attempts for 220 yards and an interception in the Jaguars’ Week 9 win against the Raiders, adding nine rushes for 24 yards and two touchdowns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4781-d673-a39e-e7917ebf0000</link>
      <description>Lawrence struggled to get anything going against a middling Vegas secondary. He was without Travis Hunter (knee, IR) and lost Brian Thomas to an ankle injury in the second half. Lawrence against the Raiders was quick to pull the ball down and take off after one or two reads. One of his rush touchdowns came on a designed run inside the ten; the other came on a QB sneak at the half yard line. Week 9 marked Lawrence’s second multi-touchdown rushing performance of 2025. He now has nine touchdown throws through eight games and profiles as a desperation fantasy option for Week 10 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4781-d673-a39e-e7917ebf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten had nine rushes for 29 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 9 win against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-478b-d713-ad9e-6fdfe2e00000</link>
      <description>Tuten punched in a goal line opportunity after Travis Etienne was stuffed a few times at close range. He ran just right routes on the day and was not targeted, while Etienne caught five of his six targets for 31 yards. Tuten remains one of the game’s best contingency backs. He would likely take over as the Jaguars’ clear lead back if Etienne were to miss time in the second half of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-478b-d713-ad9e-6fdfe2e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty had 13 rushes for 42 yards in the Raiders’ Week 9 loss agains the Jaguars, adding five receptions for 47 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4790-d45b-affe-57967eee0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty was bottled up on the ground, averaging 3.2 yards per carry and posting the week’s fourth worst rush yards over expected, per NextGen Stats. Jeanty got it done in the pass game, however. He ran a pass route on 34 of Geno Smith’s 47 drop backs and scored on a 15-yard reception. No other Raiders running back saw a rushing attempt against the Jaguars. With a death grip on the backfield workload, Jeanty should remain in fantasy lineups next week against a tough Broncos defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4790-d45b-affe-57967eee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mayer caught 3-of-7 targets for 26 yards in the Raiders’ Week 9 loss against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4796-d673-a39e-e79725150000</link>
      <description>Mayer, with Brock Bowers back in the lineup, still ran a route on 34 of the Raiders’ 47 drop backs and earned the second most targets behind Bowers (14). The Raiders’ heavy use of two tight end sets means Mayer can still be involved in the team’s passing attack even with Bowers active. Even so, Mayer is nothing more than a deep league desperation play for Week 10 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4796-d673-a39e-e79725150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
