<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce (concussion) will not play in Week 5 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaff-d6e9-af9d-aaff00240000</link>
      <description>This one comes as a bit of a surprise after Pierce was a full participant on both Wednesday and Thursday. Despite the optimistic practice outlook, it would appear the speedster was unable to clear concussion protocol in time to play in Sunday’s game. Adonai Mitchell will take Pierce’s place against a Raiders defense that enters the weekend ranked 22nd in points allowed and 21st in yards allowed through the first four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaff-d6e9-af9d-aaff00240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes that “there may not be any teams interested in trading for [Russell] Wilson.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a69d-d6e9-af9d-ae9d01280000</link>
      <description>Duggan concedes that the Bengals make sense in theory and that it’s “possible” someone gets desperate enough to trade for Wilson, but notes that he had a limited trade market and just got benched after three games while looking “washed up.” In the offseason, only the Browns and Giants were interested enough to bring Wilson in. Wilson does not look to have any stash value in superflex leagues based on this report, as much as it would make sense for the Giants to move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a69d-d6e9-af9d-ae9d01280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts ruled out CB Kenny Moore (Achilles) for Week 5 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab02-d95b-addb-eb46aac20000</link>
      <description>In addition to Moore, the Colts also ruled out backup RB Tyler Goodson (groin). Week 5’s absence will mark the second missed game for Moore, who was injured in Week 3’s win over the Titans. The abrupt retirement of CB Xavien Howard earlier in the week will leave the Colts thin at corner against a Raiders offense that features decent talent in the passing game despite their slow start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab02-d95b-addb-eb46aac20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports Jaydon Blue is expected to make his Cowboys debut in Week 5 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab0c-d6e9-af9d-ab9cd23d0000</link>
      <description>That tells you all you need to know about Miles Sanders’ odds of getting off the report for Week 5. Fantasy teams don’t need to rush to pick up Blue, but he’ll make for an intriguing stash in deeper leagues while we see how it plays out behind Javonte Williams. Perhaps the rookie can force his way into a real passing downs role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab0c-d6e9-af9d-ab9cd23d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said DT Milton Williams (ankle) is questionable for Week 5 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab17-dca3-a9fb-bf9facb60000</link>
      <description>Vrabel declined to comment on the health of his lineman and what led to his injury, but Williams was limited on Wednesday before being a DNP on Thursday, so it’s safe to assume he is legitimately questionable heading into the AFC East showdown against the Bills. Williams has totaled nine tackles and two sacks this season to go with five TFLs. In addition to Williams, Vrabel also said LB K’Lavon Chaisson (knee), CB Carlson Davis (illness), and LB Jahlani Tavai (calf) would all be questionable for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab17-dca3-a9fb-bf9facb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is not on Cleveland’s final injury report for Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab21-d6e9-af9d-abb163100000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a rough option this week with Dillon Gabriel making his NFL debut and firmly in a snap share with Harold Fannin. Njoku has not cracked 40 yards this season and will be a TE2 at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab21-d6e9-af9d-abb163100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said WR Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) is questionable for Tennessee’s Week 5 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab28-d95b-addb-eb6e8e620000</link>
      <description>Ridley did appear to be practicing in some way on Friday after getting a DNP Thursday, but this is a situation we’d lean towards avoiding in fantasy leagues. Elic Ayomanor has drawn more targets than Ridley when both were healthy, let alone last week when Ridley missed some snaps while dealing with injury. Even if cleared, Ridley is more of a WR5 than WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab28-d95b-addb-eb6e8e620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) will not play in Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-d6e9-af9d-abbafa9f0000</link>
      <description>The Titans could have put Latham on injured reserve after Week 1, but now have spent four weeks without the active roster spot and Latham has barely practiced. Hard to believe such a well-run organization is 0-4. Brian Callahan did say that Latham could be up for Week 6. Oli Udoh is the favorite to start at right tackle in Week 5 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-d6e9-af9d-abbafa9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears (ankle) is questionable for Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-deb6-a7fd-fbff02860000</link>
      <description>Head coach Brian Callahan said he thought Spears looked good during his week of practice, but isn’t ready to commit to Spears returning in Week 5. Fantasy managers should stay away from Spears in Week 5, even if he is active, but he’ll be a player whose involvement is worth monitoring once back on the field. Spears never saw a reliable enough workload in 2024 to emerge as a true threat in fantasy. Known for his ability as a pass-catcher, he averaged just 2.9 targets/gm in 12 games last season, and his 4.7 yards per touch were pretty underwhelming. Still, he’s an interesting stash for fantasy managers in need of help, as he could see a larger role in his second year in Callahan’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-deb6-a7fd-fbff02860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Noah Fant cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 5 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2f-d6e9-af9d-abbf4dcb0000</link>
      <description>Fant will get a chance to suit up against the Lions after missing last week’s game due to his brain injury. The veteran tight end was averaging 4.7 targets per game through the first three weeks of the season, and has yet to top 28 receiving yards in a game. Fant’s return is better for the Bengals than for fantasy managers, as he offers almost no fantasy upside at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2f-d6e9-af9d-abbf4dcb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
