<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:28:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) said he is feeling “great,” and that his absence at Friday’s practice has been “blown out of proportion” due to his injury history.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bd1-d332-a1fd-9ff730d40000</link>
      <description>This is somewhat encouraging. When asked about the injury, McCaffrey assured media members that it’s “nothing serious.” If that’s the case, there’s a chance he handles something close to a normal workload against the division rival Seahawks on Sunday. Regardless, fantasy managers should prepare their backup plans in case McCaffrey needs more time to heal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bd1-d332-a1fd-9ff730d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims Jr. (thigh) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bee-d332-a1fd-9ffeb3020000</link>
      <description>Mims is expected to make his debut, operating as the Broncos’ No. 2 wide receiver behind Courtland Sutton. If he can maintain anything close to the elite efficiency and explosiveness he produced in a part-time role last year, he could fit into fantasy lineups as a WR3. The Titans’ secondary is a beatable unit. Consider him an upside FLEX play for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bee-d332-a1fd-9ffeb3020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) for Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bec-dbe3-a9bb-3bff52910000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw suffered two quad injuries this summer and the second one is apparently still an issue. He was sidelined through all three Week 1 practices. The complete lack of participation is concerning, even for his Week 2 availability. Broncos backup DT Malcolm Roach (calf) is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bec-dbe3-a9bb-3bff52910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WRs Hollywood Brown and Tyquan Thornton are expected “to fill the void” left by Rashee Rice (suspension) in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bf6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7c8b00000</link>
      <description>Brown successfully rehabbed a sprained ankle that he injured during training camp while Thornton made a few splash plays in the preseason. Both players are difficult to trust as more than dart throw FLEX options but for those in need of a risk-reward wide receiver, deploying one of Patrick Mahomes’ pass catchers is not a bad idea. Brown is listed as a starter on the Chiefs’ depth chart and should get the opportunity to produce before Thornton, who currently sits among the third-stringers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1bf6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7c8b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OG Mekhi Becton (illness) is active for Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c0b-de13-afdd-5ecbb86c0000</link>
      <description>Becton was listed as questionable earlier today, after coming down with a last-minute illness. That Chargers’ right guard will be on the field for Week 1, though. The Chargers declared S RJ Mickens, TE Tucker Fisk, CB Nikko Reed, OLB Kyle Kennard, T Foster Sarell, TE Oronde Gadsden II and DL Naquan Jones inactive for Week 1. Gadsden impressed coaches in training camp but the rookie tight end needs a little more time before he is ready for live action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c0b-de13-afdd-5ecbb86c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Elijah Mitchell is inactive for Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</link>
      <description>Mitchell’s deactivation suggests the Chiefs will roll with Isiah Pacheco, Kareem Hunt and rookie Brashard Smith, who notably took a few first-team reps in preseason play last month. He might be worth stashing on benches before kickoff. The Chiefs also declared WR Jalen Royals (knee), TE Jared Wiley, DT Omarr Norman-Lott, OL Hunter Nourzad and DE Malik Herring inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c24-dbe3-a9bb-3c776e3c0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ wide receiver corps will not be at full health, with Christian Kirk sidelined, but it’s still great news for the Rams, who will have their hands full in trying to cover Nico Collins. Witherspoon broke up six passes and recorded one interception last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c24-dbe3-a9bb-3c776e3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c63-de13-afdd-5eebef8a0000</link>
      <description>Worthy collided with Travis Kelce on a crossing route on the Chiefs’ first drive and stayed on the ground for a few beats before walking off while holding his arm. He almost immediately left for the locker room with a towel draped over his head. According to the broadcast, Worthy is currently undergoing X-rays on his shouler. We should get an update on his status soon, but it doesn’t look like he will be back tonight. That leaves Hollywood Brown as the team’s top wideout with JuJu Smith-Schuster and Tyquan Thornton also in the mix for routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c63-de13-afdd-5eebef8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will not return in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c89-d332-a1fd-9ebfd7380000</link>
      <description>Worthy left the opening game of his second season in the first quarter after colliding with Travis Kelce on a crossing route. He was checked out by trainers before walking off the field and into the locker room. Worthy went in for X-rays and was ruled out shortly after. It might be a day or two before we know the nature of the injury, but the mechanism was that of a dislocated shoulder. With Rashee Rice sidelined for the first six weeks while serving a suspension, the Chiefs are down the Hollywood Brown as their No. 1 receiver. Travis Kelce will also be heavily involved until one of Worthy or Rice is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c89-d332-a1fd-9ebfd7380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c8f-d332-a1fd-9ebff3990000</link>
      <description>Perryman went down in the first half and was replaced by backup linebacker Troy Dye. Perryman appeared in 11 games for the Chargers last year, totaling 55 tackles and one sack. Dye has primarily played on special teams throughout his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c8f-d332-a1fd-9ebff3990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
