<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:08:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kimberley A. Martin reports Buccaneers WR Mike Evans will play in 2026 and will explore his free agency options.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d8a-d042-afbc-7ddaf8b80000</link>
      <description>It was sort of assumed that Evans would just run it back in Tampa as a career Buccaneer, but perhaps he’s actually interested in seeing what is out there for him. That’s about how it played out the last time Evans hit free agency, when he wound up with a two-year, $41 million contract with $29 million in guarantees. The Buccaneers have a much better wideout room now than they did in 2024, at least on paper, with Emeka Egbuka, Chris Godwin, and Jalen McMillan under contract. Evans is also entering his age-33 season and coming off a year where he missed time with a broken collarbone, so his market may also be reduced. Still, he played well while healthy. This will be one to watch over the next few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d8a-d042-afbc-7ddaf8b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns and G Joel Bitonio agreed to push the void date on his contract to the end of the league year in March.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6db0-d990-a1de-6dfe633a0000</link>
      <description>Bitonio, who has been contemplating retirement openly, asked the Browns for a few more weeks to do so. The club agreed. If Bitonio plays in 2026, he’ll be entering his age-35 season. Bitonio last carried a PFF grade above 80 in the 2022 season, though he’s remained solid and reliable for the Browns over the last three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6db0-d990-a1de-6dfe633a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Woods retired from the NFL after 12 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6dc1-d629-a1bc-fdddce070000</link>
      <description>He signed a one-day contract to retire as a Ram. Woods peaked with the Jared Goff Era early Sean McVay Rams, where he signed as a free agent after a four-year rookie deal in Buffalo. Woods managed 3,289 yards and 14 touchdowns over a three-year stretch from 2018-2020. His last real action was with the Texans in 2023 and 2024, though he bounced around the Steelers in the 2025 offseason and did a few practice squad stints. Woods retires with 683 receptions for 8233 yards and 38 scores.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6dc1-d629-a1bc-fdddce070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots promoted linebackers coach Zak Kuhr to defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e0e-d89c-a1be-efdfd3740000</link>
      <description>Kuhr was the team’s interim defensive coordinator after former defensive coordinator Terrell Williams underwent treatment for prostate cancer. He first started as a coach in the NFL under Mike Vrabel with the Titans and called a Pats defense that forced eight turnovers in the playoffs en route to a Super Bowl LX appearance. Vrabel now makes Kuhr the permanent defensive coordinator as Williams takes a high-ranking role on the staff, looking to build upon a strong unit for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e0e-d89c-a1be-efdfd3740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers assistant head coach and special teams coordinator Rich Bisaccia is stepping down.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e20-d042-afbc-7ff221b10000</link>
      <description>Bisaccia had been the Packers’ special teams coordinator for the past four seasons under Matt LaFleur, but is now stepping down from his role. The 65-year-old is pausing his coaching career, which includes a stint as the Raiders’ interim head coach in 2021. Meanwhile, the Packers will have to look externally for his replacement, with former assistant special teams coach Byron Storer now the Browns’ special teams coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e20-d042-afbc-7ff221b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs restructured Patrick Mahomes’ contract to save $43.6 million against the salary cap in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-70f8-d629-a1bc-f0fdec230000</link>
      <description>This marks the fourth straight offseason in which the Chiefs have redone Mahomes’ mega-contract to create some cap breathing room. This most recent restructure will have Mahomes’ cap it go from $78.2 million to $34.65 million for the 2026 season. Mahomes’ cap number for the 2027 season will now be over $85 million, according to Over The Cap’s Jason Fitzgerald. Mahomes, entering his age-31 season, is hoping to be ready for Week 1 after suffering a late-season knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-70f8-d629-a1bc-f0fdec230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 49ers will play a regular season game in Mexico City, Mexico in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7108-d89c-a1be-ffdf9fad0000</link>
      <description>Brock Purdy and the Niners will be well traveled in 2026. They will play against the Rams in the first-ever NFL game in Australia along with the Mexico City outing. The 49ers will also fly across country twice in 2026 to face the Giants and Falcons, according to ESPN’s Field Yates. It would seem to be a demanding travel schedule for a team contending for a championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7108-d89c-a1be-ffdf9fad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ reports Rashee Rice was accused of “violent and abusive behaviors” in a lawsuit filed by the mother of two of his children.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7150-d89c-a1be-ffdffcc10000</link>
      <description>Dacoda Jones this week reportedly filed a lawsuit accusing Rice of “choking, strangling, scratching, hitting, and headbutting” Jones over a 19-month period. The lawsuit also says Rice broke furniture and punched holes in walls during arguments with Jones. Much of the violent behavior occurred while Jones was pregnant, according to the lawsuit. Rice’s alleged violence caused “bleeding, swelling, bruising, and other pain and physical injury to her neck, face, mouth, arms, legs, chest, and shoulder,” according to the lawsuit. Jones had previously accused Rice of abusive behavior in social media posts. This is Rice’s most recent run-in with the law after he fled the scene of a major automobile accident last offseason and was suspended by the NFL for the first six games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7150-d89c-a1be-ffdffcc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed former University of Texas defensive coordinator Pete Kwiatkowski as new defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-71ed-d990-a1de-7def227c0000</link>
      <description>This marks Kwiatkowski’s first forray into the NFL ranks after nearly three decades of coaching college football. Kwiatkowski joined Steve Sarkisian in Texas five years ago as the team’s defensive coordinator. After a rough first year, Kwiatkowski’s defenses never finished worse than 28th in the country in points allowed over the following four seasons. The Longhorns fielded the third-best scoring defense in 2024. Kwiatkowski was fired after his unit took a slight step back in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-71ed-d990-a1de-7def227c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Dolphins “have had trade talks with teams regarding” S Minkah Fitzpatrick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7229-d89c-a1be-ffff3ec60000</link>
      <description>Fitzpatrick returned to Miami in 2025 as part of the deal that sent Jalen Ramsey to Pittsburgh. He appeared in 14 games, totaling six pass breakups and one interception. Fitzpatrick also added one sack and two fumble recoveries. The Dolphins have already made the decision to release Tyreek Hill and Bradley Chubb to save cap space. They will almost certainly take a deal to move Fitzpatrick if it gives them more ammunition in the draft. This is shaping up to be a true reset season for Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7229-d89c-a1be-ffff3ec60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
