<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Calvin Austin, DB Chuck Clark, OG Andrus Peat, DT Logan Lee, and DE Demarvin Leal inactive for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-db72-a199-fb5b883d0000</link>
      <description>Austin was ruled out before the weekend. The only player who was questionable for the Steelers was Jalen Ramsey, who is officially active for this week after logging a full practice on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-db72-a199-fb5b883d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared WR Quentin Johnston, WR Derius Davis, FB/DL Scott Matlock, CB Nikko Reed, OL Jamaree Salyer, T Joe Altm and G/T Trey Pipkins III inactive for Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-dd4c-afb9-ffd16dec0000</link>
      <description>Johnston will miss Week 6 with a hamstring issue he picked up last week. His absence should open up more targets for Keenan Allen and Ladd McConkey against a middling Dolphins secondary. McConkey should be in 12-team league fantasy lineups with Johnston sidelined. Justin Herbert’s upside takes a hit with Johnston out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-dd4c-afb9-ffd16dec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is active for Week 6 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d90e-db72-a199-fb4f50550000</link>
      <description>Defensive tackle Milton Williams is also active. Inactive for the Patriots are QB Tommy DeVito, OLB Anfernee Jennings, DE Keion White, S Jaylinn Hawkins, OL Caedan Wallace, and DT Eric Gregory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d90e-db72-a199-fb4f50550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Anthony Richardson is inactive for Week 6 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-def2-abdb-dd71612c0000</link>
      <description>Richardson is a surprise inactive as NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Richardson was injured in warmups. Rookie Riley Leonard will be Daniel Jones’ primary backup in his place. Richardson lost the starting job to Jones at the beginning of the season and is now the third quarterback after suffering an eye injury in warmups prior to Week 6 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-def2-abdb-dd71612c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Ramsey (hamstring) is active for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d916-d94a-a79d-d91f51230000</link>
      <description>Despite being a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday, Ramsey was able to log a full practice on Friday, hinting that the veteran corner would likely be active for this week. Ramsey was not listed on the team’s Week 6 inactives and is officially good to go against a Browns offense that will feature rookie Dillon Gabriel in his second career start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d916-d94a-a79d-d91f51230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared RB Jaylen Wright, CB Storm Duck, QB Quinn Ewers, DT Zeek Biggers, LB Tyrel Dodson, WR Cedrick Wilson Jr., and DB Elijah Campbell inactive for Week 6 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d917-dd4c-afb9-ffd714820000</link>
      <description>Wright is once again inactive while Ollie Gordon continues serving as the Dolphins’ No. 2 running back behind De’Von Achane. A game script dependent fantasy option, Gordon has 18 rushing attempts over the past three games, including some carries in the red zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d917-dd4c-afb9-ffd714820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared S Kahlef Hailassie, RB Cody Schrader, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Robert Hainsey, and DT Khalen Saunders Sr. inactive for Week 6 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5efaf0000</link>
      <description>The Jags are largely healthy heading into Week 6. Abdullah and Hainsey were the only players with injury designations heading into the weekend and both are out versus the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5efaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared WR Adonai Mitchell, RB Tyler Goodson, TE Will Mallory, CB Kenny Moore, QB Anthony Richardson, OT Luke Tenuta, and DE JT Tuimoloau inactive for Week 6 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5b0fb0000</link>
      <description>Mitchell had been trending downward after just six snaps last week. Ashton Dulin now has the WR4 job for the Colts, leading to Mitchell being a healthy scratch this week. He can be dropped in all but the deepest of redraft fantasy leagues. Kenny Moore (Achilles) remains out, while Anthony Richardson (eye) is a surprise inactive as Riley Leonard takes the backup job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5b0fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields completed 9-of-17 passes for 45 yards in the Jets’ 13-11, Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d918-d94a-a79d-d91dba5f0000</link>
      <description>Per usual, the NFL sent a subpar product across the pond, this time with a nine-sack showing from Fields. He lost more sack yardage (55) than he gained via his nine completions. This was just the third time since 2000 a quarterback has accomplished that feat while attempting more than 15 passes. Fields was routinely late to throws, resulting in multiple missed connections with Garrett Wilson, who was visibly frustrated throughout the contest. The day was summed up well by New York’s final drive of the first half. Just as they seemed to gain some momentum on offense via a fourth-down conversion, Fields hurried to the line with the clock running, only to watch more than 20 seconds tick away and the half come to an end. Between the clueless coaching, a lack of pass-catching talent, and Fields’ own shortcomings, nothing is clicking for the Jets. It wouldn’t be surprising for them to turn to Tyrod Taylor ahead of their Week 7 game against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d918-d94a-a79d-d91dba5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 19-of-30 passes for 174 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ 13-11, Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d950-db72-a199-fb5b08dc0000</link>
      <description>Denver put up 10 points in the first quarter and promptly took the next three quarters off. Nix threw for 135 yards and a touchdown in the first half. He managed just 39 yards in the second half. Denver went three-and-out on four of their six second-half drives, excluding a pair of kneel-downs to end the game. They also took a safety on a holding penalty in the end zone in the third quarter. The Broncos are now 4-2, but Nix has thrown for more than 206 yards just twice and has two multi-score games. Even if they continue to grind out ugly wins, Nix has played himself out of the QB1 ranks heading into his Week 7 matchup with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d950-db72-a199-fb5b08dc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
