<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said WR Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) is questionable for Tennessee’s Week 5 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab28-d95b-addb-eb6e8e620000</link>
      <description>Ridley did appear to be practicing in some way on Friday after getting a DNP Thursday, but this is a situation we’d lean towards avoiding in fantasy leagues. Elic Ayomanor has drawn more targets than Ridley when both were healthy, let alone last week when Ridley missed some snaps while dealing with injury. Even if cleared, Ridley is more of a WR5 than WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab28-d95b-addb-eb6e8e620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) will not play in Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-d6e9-af9d-abbafa9f0000</link>
      <description>The Titans could have put Latham on injured reserve after Week 1, but now have spent four weeks without the active roster spot and Latham has barely practiced. Hard to believe such a well-run organization is 0-4. Brian Callahan did say that Latham could be up for Week 6. Oli Udoh is the favorite to start at right tackle in Week 5 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-d6e9-af9d-abbafa9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears (ankle) is questionable for Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-deb6-a7fd-fbff02860000</link>
      <description>Head coach Brian Callahan said he thought Spears looked good during his week of practice, but isn’t ready to commit to Spears returning in Week 5. Fantasy managers should stay away from Spears in Week 5, even if he is active, but he’ll be a player whose involvement is worth monitoring once back on the field. Spears never saw a reliable enough workload in 2024 to emerge as a true threat in fantasy. Known for his ability as a pass-catcher, he averaged just 2.9 targets/gm in 12 games last season, and his 4.7 yards per touch were pretty underwhelming. Still, he’s an interesting stash for fantasy managers in need of help, as he could see a larger role in his second year in Callahan’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2a-deb6-a7fd-fbff02860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Noah Fant cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 5 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2f-d6e9-af9d-abbf4dcb0000</link>
      <description>Fant will get a chance to suit up against the Lions after missing last week’s game due to his brain injury. The veteran tight end was averaging 4.7 targets per game through the first three weeks of the season, and has yet to top 28 receiving yards in a game. Fant’s return is better for the Bengals than for fantasy managers, as he offers almost no fantasy upside at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab2f-d6e9-af9d-abbf4dcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints EDGE Chase Young (calf) won’t play in New Orleans’ Week 5 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab45-dca3-a9fb-bfddfee50000</link>
      <description>We’re 0-for-5 on Young playing this season despite him being fully active. As we wrote earlier, hard to believe this team is 0-4. It’ll remain the Carl Granderson show for the Saints’ defense in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab45-dca3-a9fb-bfddfee50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) is questionable for New Orleans’ Week 5 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab48-d95b-addb-eb4e70f70000</link>
      <description>This isn’t a great sign for Johnson after coming back to a limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. He missed Wednesday’s practice after being in and out of Week 4’s game in Buffalo with the ankle injury. Given possible returns for Taysom Hill and Foster Moreau in the near future, it could be argued Johnson’s fantasy stock is going down with or without the injury. Fantasy managers in shallow leagues can probably freely move on to a different streamer for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab48-d95b-addb-eb4e70f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB/TE Taysom Hill (knee) and TE Foster Moreau (knee) are questionable for New Orleans’ Week 5 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab4c-deb6-a7fd-fbdf31200000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign for both that they practiced all week without setbacks. If Juwan Johnson (ankle) is down in Week 5, one of them could walk in to a big role right away in Kellen Moore’s offense. It’ll probably be Saturday before we know if that’s the case, as each would need to be officially activated off the PUP list. Hill obviously has some fantasy upside if healthy, but he’s also a 35-year-old coming off a serious knee injury. Tread carefully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab4c-deb6-a7fd-fbdf31200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is doubtful for New York’s Week 5 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab55-dca3-a9fb-bfddd52e0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade after he saw some limited work, but this seems to point more towards a Week 6 return for Tracy. Tracy was already appearing to lose his starting gig to Cam Skattebo before he picked up this shoulder injury. When he does come back, he’ll likely be on a low enough snap count to not be worthwhile for most fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab55-dca3-a9fb-bfddd52e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is not practicing Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab58-deb6-a7fd-fbdf7a770000</link>
      <description>Not good. Bowers was a surprise downgrade on Thursday and it seems likely we’ll be dropping a questionable tag at best on him later today. This hasn’t been the season you hoped for when you spent a first or second-round pick on the star sophomore tight end — now fantasy managers should probably be making plans to replace him in their Week 5 lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab58-deb6-a7fd-fbdf7a770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) will not play in Week 5’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab68-deb6-a7fd-fbff00c90000</link>
      <description>He’s now missed three games in a row and hasn’t practiced since getting hurt in Week 2. Stewart had two tackles in 66 defensive snaps in his two active weeks earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab68-deb6-a7fd-fbff00c90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
