<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Sean Tucker (hand) fully practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-db7b-a5dd-b176b89a0000</link>
      <description>Tucker is good to go for Week 1. The 23-year-old running back has flashed intriguing traits at times, though he remains stuck in the Buccaneers’ No. 3 role. If Bucky Irving were to miss time, Tucker would be flex-viable, serving as the likely lead rusher in Tampa Bay’s potent offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-db7b-a5dd-b176b89a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions worked out free agent QB C.J. Beathard on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-dbe3-a9bb-317727680000</link>
      <description>The Lions also worked out free agent QB Nathan Peterman. Ironically, the Jets worked out the same duo on August 14th. The Lions currently have just two quarterbacks between their active roster and practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-dbe3-a9bb-317727680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquise Brown (ankle) practiced in full on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-118a-dbe3-a9bb-31db0cd70000</link>
      <description>Brown’s ankle is holding up nicely. The veteran wide receiver should have a role in both two- and three-wide receiver sets, though he will likely be stuck behind Xavier Worthy and Travis Kelce in the pecking order. Brown draws FLEX consideration for the matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-118a-dbe3-a9bb-31db0cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Kristian Fulton (knee) practiced in full on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1191-dbe3-a9bb-31d3a1330000</link>
      <description>Fulton spent a little over two weeks on the active/physically unable to perform list this summer. He’s been practicing with the team since August 7th, though. Fulton notched five pass breakups and one interception, playing for the Chargers last year. He should be available for his new team’s bout with the Bolts on Friday night. Chiefs OT Jawaan Taylor (knee) is practicing in full this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1191-dbe3-a9bb-31d3a1330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (thigh) is practicing in full for Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1159-db7b-a5dd-b15df3960000</link>
      <description>Mims suffered a groin injury in practice last week. It’s unclear if his current thigh injury is related or something new, though it hardly matters. A full practice for the first session of the week locks him in for Week 1. Mims ran a full complement of routes during the preseason, something he has yet to do in the NFL, even during his breakout over the second half of the 2024 season. A full-time role could elevate him from a boom/bust WR5 to a true WR3 if he can keep generating splash plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1159-db7b-a5dd-b15df3960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119e-db7b-a5dd-b19e90120000</link>
      <description>Head coach Sean Payton has already said the team is being conservative with their approach to Greenlaw’s practice regimen. The 28-year-old linebacker suffered a torn quad while working out in the offseason and recently suffered a new quad injury, which Payton says is unrelated. Expect the veteran linebacker to be on a pitch count if he is active for Week 1. Greenlaw missed most of 2024 with an Achilles injury but totaled 120 tackles, five TFLs, and four pass breakups as a starter for the 49ers in 2023. He will be a strong middle linebacker option for the Broncos’ defense, even if the team has to manage his reps this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119e-db7b-a5dd-b19e90120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans CB L’Jarius Sneed (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1199-db7b-a5dd-b19dc9ea0000</link>
      <description>This should be the norm for Sneed, who underwent a cleanup procedure on his ailing knee this summer. Head coach Brian Callahan said that Sneed’s knee will need to be managed “all the time” so he will likely practice in an abbreviated manner all year. Speedy wide receivers could give him fits in his age-28 season. Titans OT Dan Moore Jr. (ankle) did not practice today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1199-db7b-a5dd-b19dc9ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Jordan James (finger) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11a8-de13-afdd-57eb51a30000</link>
      <description>James underwent surgery to repair a finger fracture in early August. The backfield looks a whole lot different now, with Brian Robinson now occupying the No. 2 spot. James belongs on dynasty rosters but can be left in the free agent pool in re-draft at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11a8-de13-afdd-57eb51a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived S Jordan Poyer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119d-db7b-a5dd-b19d35190000</link>
      <description>The Bills waived Poyer, but it is likely just a formality while the team signs Gabe Davis to the practice squad. Davis will be moved to the injured list with Poyer re-joining the practice squad afterward. The 34-year-old started 16 games for the Dolphins last season after spending seven seasons in Buffalo prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119d-db7b-a5dd-b19d35190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR/CB Travis Hunter (upper body) is not listed on the initial Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11bc-db7b-a5dd-b1bcca2f0000</link>
      <description>Hunter had been dealing with an upper body injury throughout the last couple weeks of preseason. He got back up to practice speed last week and is no longer listed on the injury report. The assumption is that Hunter is healthy and is slated to play Week 1 against the Panthers. Fantasy managers have little reason to believe the upper body injury will slow down the 22-year-old to start the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11bc-db7b-a5dd-b1bcca2f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
