<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers will interview former Raiders ST coordinator Tom McMahon for their special teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7840-d89c-a1be-ffdffaee0000</link>
      <description>McMahon was initially hired for his prior role back in 2022. He was relieved of his duties in November 2025. He has served as an NFL special teams coordinator every year, dating back to 2009, spending time with the Rams, Chiefs, Colts and Broncos. The Packers will also interview Patriots ST coordinator Cameron Achord and Saints assistant special teams coach Kyle Wilber.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7840-d89c-a1be-ffdffaee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Omar Young as their new running backs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-78a2-d89c-a1be-ffff1a020000</link>
      <description>Young spent the last two seasons coaching running backs at Iowa. He has coached with the Patriots, Bears, Packers and Browns, and also has experience at the junior college level, Division-II, FCS and FBS. He played defensive back at Willamette University and earned his bachelor’s degree at Savannah State University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-78a2-d89c-a1be-ffff1a020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams promoted passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase to offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7b42-d042-afbc-7fd2344e0000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase fielded several interviews for head coaching vacancies this offseason, and was once thought to be the front-runner to land the Browns’ head coaching job. Now, the 35-year-old coach will have his hands on the offense a little more with this latest promotion. Scheelhaase first joined the Rams in 2024 as an offensive assistant and passing game specialist, and has now received promotions in back-to-back years. We assume Sean McVay will continue to call plays, but this promotion will bode well for Scheelhaase’s future as he looks to eventually make the leap to a head-coaching role in the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7b42-d042-afbc-7fd2344e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons GM Ian Cunningham said there are “a lot of discussions for us about the entire roster” when asked if Michael Penix (knee) would be the guaranteed starter when he returns from injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7b68-d042-afbc-7ffaf2f40000</link>
      <description>In an article written by ESPN’s Marc Raimondi, Cunningham said the team is “excited about (Penix) and what he’s doing with his rehab,” but didn’t comment on whether he would be locked in as the team’s QB1 for next season. The soon-to-be 26-year-old is rehabbing from a torn ACL he suffered in Week 11, but underwhelmed in his second season, throwing for 1,982-9-3 in the nine starts he made. For his career, Penix has completed just 59.6 percent of his passes while going 4-8 as a starter. With Kirk Cousins likely to be playing elsewhere in 2026, any competition Penix could face for the starting role will likely come from the outside via either the draft or free agency. Penix said during the Super Bowl media week that he “absolutely” expects to be ready by Week 1, but given the timing of his injury, he’ll likely have several hurdles to clear just to be ready in time for training camp. Regardless, we would expect the Falcons to address their QB room in some way this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7b68-d042-afbc-7ffaf2f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos HC Sean Payton said “one of the points of emphasis” this offseason will be looking into more runs from under center.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7bbe-d990-a1de-7ffe78500000</link>
      <description>In an article written by ESPN’s Jeff Legwold, Payton said the team was “able to (run under center) a few times, but not as much as I’d like.” Per Legwold, the Broncos ranked 10th in runs under center last season at 64.9 percent, but trailed the Rams, who led the league in runs under center (87.3 percent) by a wide margin. More runs from under center could result in the team using fewer three-receiver sets next season, with Payton himself saying he would like the options of two-back or multiple-tight end sets also at his disposal. Whether or not JK Dobbins returns next season is still up in the air, but RJ Harvey, who ran for 146-540-7, figures to see a larger role out of the gate next season than he did as a rookie. More runs from under center could help Harvey, who struggled at times as a runner (3.7 YPC) last season, especially if Payton utilizes more tight ends to help create holes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7bbe-d990-a1de-7ffe78500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jesse Newell believes CB Jaylen Watson is “likely to be out of the Chiefs’ price range” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7be9-d990-a1de-7feffa150000</link>
      <description>Watson is a former seventh-rounder who has started 21 games for the Chiefs over the last two seasons. The 27-year-old corner is expected to be one of the top available free agents on the market next month, and allowed just 35 catches for 447 scoreless yards on 59 targets last season, per PFF. Watson has played exclusively on the outside since entering the league in 2022 and hasn’t allowed a receiving touchdown since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7be9-d990-a1de-7feffa150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jesse Newell believes Isiah Pacheco is “likely to sign elsewhere” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c44-d89c-a1be-ffdf38710000</link>
      <description>It was reported last month by ESPN’s Nate Taylor that the Chiefs are “expected” to have a new starting running back for next season. While that didn’t completely rule out the idea of Pacheco re-upping with the team this offseason, Newell’s belief that Pacheco will be playing for another team in 2026 doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Chiefs tried to ride the momentum o the 26-year-old speedster for as long as they could, but injuries have plague Pacheco for the last two seasons, and he’s averaged less than 4.0 YPC over that span. The lack of receiving upside further caps Pacheco’s upside, and as last season went on, it was apparent that a younger, more talented back would help an offense that struggled last season. Plenty of teams should be willing to take a flier on Pacheco this offseason on a one-year prove-it deal, but we would expect most of his touches to come on early downs wherever he lands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c44-d89c-a1be-ffdf38710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs HC Andy Reid said “there’s nothing happening there” when asked if the team has had any talks with Tyreek Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c4d-d629-a1bc-fc5d120e0000</link>
      <description>We’re just days removed from Hill being released by the Dolphins. Furthermore, Reid adds that he doesn’t know if Hill “is healthy right now to do anything.” While Reid didn’t rule out the possibility of a reunion with the veteran receiver, it isn’t all too surprising to hear that the two sides have yet to discuss things. Hill has already said he intends to play in 2026 when he is healthy, but with his availability for training camp already in doubt, Hill may have to prove to teams he is able to play before signing a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c4d-d629-a1bc-fc5d120e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs HC Andy Reid said he underwent a minor knee procedure and will not be available for the interviews at next week’s NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c51-d990-a1de-7c5f04660000</link>
      <description>Reid doesn’t expect to be out of commission for long, but it is notable that he will be unable to meet with prospects next week when so many other teams are gathering intel and speaking with the incoming class. The Chiefs hold the ninth overall pick in this year’s draft and have several positions they could consider addressing given their concerns with the wide receiver room, and a backfield that also needs to be overhauled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c51-d990-a1de-7c5f04660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs HC Andy Reid said “there is communication” with Travis Kelce.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c54-d042-afbc-7dd6761d0000</link>
      <description>Reid added that he believes communication is “the main thing” and that he thinks Kelce wants “to move forward.” Reid declined to say whether Kelce gave him a definite answer on whether he wants to return to the Chiefs in 2026, but it sounds like things are trending in that direction. Kelce, 36, has mulled retirement over the last few offseasons, but the prevailing belief of those close to him is that he will return for at least one more season. Kelce caught 76 passes for 851 yards and five touchdowns last season while averaging 11.2 YPR, his highest yards per reception total since 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7c54-d042-afbc-7dd6761d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
