<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed three times for 21 yards and one touchdown in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d47e-db7b-a5dd-f47e0a8e0000</link>
      <description>Pacheco surrendered the Chiefs’ first touch inside the Bears’ five-yard line to Kareem Hunt, but Hunt gained just one yard and Pacheco punched it in on the following play. Pacheco looked like his normal, hard-running, speedy self in this one. Hunt’s red zone involvement is unideal but Pacheco could return RB2 value via his seventh-round ADP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d47e-db7b-a5dd-f47e0a8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed three times for 15 yards and caught 0-of-1 targets in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d477-dbe3-a9bb-f4779f180000</link>
      <description>Hunt subbed in on the first drive, once the offense got past the Bears’ five-yard line. He immediately got the ball on an inside run but gained just one yard and was yanked in favor of Isiah Pacheco, who promptly scored from two yards out. Securing the scoring position role is likely Hunt’s path to weekly fantasy relevance. He currently profiles as a recommended bench stash with flex-potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d477-dbe3-a9bb-f4779f180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 2-of-3 targets for 32 yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d483-de13-afdc-d6cb123c0000</link>
      <description>Kelce earned a target on the second drive and recorded his first catch on the third. The veteran tight end remains efficient at age-35, though the Chiefs clearly worked on distributing the ball as much as possible here. Kelce is once again a TE1 entering the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d483-de13-afdc-d6cb123c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 1-of-1 targets for nine yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d487-de13-afdc-d6cf6c910000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs focused on divvying up looks to all involved early on. Both Worthy and Travis Kelce touched the ball for the first time on the Chiefs’ third drive. Worthy looked like his typically elusive self in this one, and profiles as a high-upside WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d487-de13-afdc-d6cf6c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said RT Kaleb McGary (knee) will miss “significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d712-db7b-a5dd-f716aa990000</link>
      <description>Things were trending in this direction when McGary’s injury was first reported, but Morris confirmed everyone’s suspicions after Friday’s preseason game against the Cowboys. The veteran tackle signed a two-year, $30 million extension this offseason, and looks like a near lock to open the season on injured reserve. The Falcons will now look to run out their third-string right tackle as Storm Norton (ankle) is also set to miss multiple weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d712-db7b-a5dd-f716aa990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaydon Blue rushed nine times for 25 yards and one touchdown on Friday in the Cowboys’ preseason game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d746-de13-afdc-d7cfc5e00000</link>
      <description>Blue got involved immediately on special teams, recording a tackle on the opening kickoff. On offense, Blue played all offensive snaps on the second and third drives while Deuce Vaughn played on all snaps for the first and fourth drives. Blue forced three missed tackles on five carries and found the end zone from the Falcons’ one-yard line by fighting his way through contact before bouncing outside. Blue’s workload in the final preseason tune-up isn’t what we typically want to see from a player we hope will make a fantasy impact as a rookie, but this was his first and only preseason game as he dealt with an ankle injury late in camp. While he may not make an impact out of the gate, Blue doesn’t have a high bar to clear to pass Javonte Williams and Miles Sanders on the depth chart. He’s a solid late-round stash in fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d746-de13-afdc-d7cfc5e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith rushed two times for one yard in the Chiefs’ preseason finale against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d751-d332-a1fd-d777af3b0000</link>
      <description>Smith didn’t provide much production on the field, totaling just 13 yards from scrimmage on three touches, but the rookie worked early with the first-team offense and saw three targets in his limited outing. He dropped a critical pass that would have converted a first-down, but his early usage was encouraging. For now, Smith still appears buried on the depth chart behind Isiah Pacheco, Kareem Hunt, and Elijah Mitchell, but it’s easy to envision him securing a meaningful role at some point in the season, given his competition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d751-d332-a1fd-d777af3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Mafah had two carries for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ preseason game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d75c-db7b-a5dd-f75c54480000</link>
      <description>The rookie seventh-rounder has given the Cowboys a tough choice as far as roster cutdowns are concerned. Mafah only had 16 yards on his two carries, but his longest run came on a powerful burst up the middle that saw him run break multiple tackles to get down to the Falcons’ two-yard line. He would eventually score on a one-yard plunge. Mafah played with the backups to close out the game, but he has generated plenty of buzz for his work in camp and in the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d75c-db7b-a5dd-f75c54480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns beat writer Mary Kay Cabot says the Browns keeping four quarterbacks on the roster “has always been the plan.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d776-d332-a1fd-d776c0590000</link>
      <description>Joe Flacco was signed to be the Week 1 starter, and Dillon Gabriel was the team’s third-round pick. Both were virtual locks to make the 53-man roster, and Kenny Pickett was widely expected to open the season as the QB2. Rookie fifth-rounder Shedeur Sanders felt like the only true question mark to make the roster entering camp, but between his performance in camp and his first preseason game, he’s done more than enough to warrant a further look. Cabot writes in her latest article that of the four Browns signal-callers, “all will still be on the 53-man roster when the cuts are made Tuesday by 4 p.m.” While it’s a bit unconventional, the Browns are caught between trying to compete — hence Flacco’s return, while also trying to find a QB of the future. Keeping all four QBs allows them the chance to attempt to do both, and could be a sign that we will again see multiple QBs under center for the Browns this season, depending on how the season unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d776-d332-a1fd-d776c0590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Jacory Croskey-Merritt will not play in the Commanders’ preseason finale against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d796-dbe3-a9bb-f7d746df0000</link>
      <description>Both Croskey-Merritt and Austin Ekeler will sit this one out as the Commanders plan to rest nearly all of their starters. For fantasy managers trying to figure out the Commanders’ running back depth chart ahead of Week 1, Croskey-Merritt and Ekeler sitting out the preseason finale could suggest they’re the top two backs on the depth chart, while Chris Rodriguez and Jeremy McNichols both appear set to play. Croskey-Merritt has been picking up steam all offseason and performed well enough for the Commanders to trade Brian Robinson to the 49ers on Friday. While his touch distribution remains a question mark, it goes without saying that he’s worth adding in fantasy drafts in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d796-dbe3-a9bb-f7d746df0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
