<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ ProFootballTalk reports that Vikings S Harrison Smith “is dealing with a personal health issue and is expected to make a full recovery.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</link>
      <description>Smith has reportedly been dealing with the issue throughout August. Details on the matter have not yet been disclosed but the team will continue to evaluate him on a weekly basis. Smith, 36, remains an impactful player in the Vikings’ secondary. Hopefully, he is good to go for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released S Jabrill Peppers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6ac-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff84be0000</link>
      <description>Peppers has $4.32 million in guaranteed money remaining on his contract for this season. The 29-year-old safety started 26 games over the last three seasons with the Patriots. New England could be looking to start Jaylinn Hawkins and rookie Craig Woodson now, according to ESPN’s Mike Reiss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6ac-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff84be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid told reporters WR Jalen Royals (knee) is unlikely to play in the Week 1 matchup against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6c7-de13-afdc-f6cf7ccf0000</link>
      <description>Reid told reporters “it’d be a real rush” for Royals (knee) to play in Week 1 and that “it doesn’t look like he’ll make this week.” With Rashee Rice also missing the game due to suspension, the Chiefs are going to be understaffed against the Chargers. The wide receiver room will be led by Xavier Worthy with Hollywood Brown, JuJu Smith-Schuster and Tyquan Thornton behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6c7-de13-afdc-f6cf7ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans sign DT Timmy Horne, formerly of the Giants, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f24a-dbe3-a9bb-f25bc7560000</link>
      <description>Horne spent 2022 with the Falcons and was signed from their practice squad by the Giants in 2023. The Titans correspondingly released RB Jermar Jefferson and CB Amani Oruwariye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f24a-dbe3-a9bb-f25bc7560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White (groin) returned to practice and is expected to play in Week 1 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f761-dbe3-a9bb-f77393af0000</link>
      <description>Updates have been sparse but White returned to practice last week and has been participating since then without any reported issues. August reports on the Bucs’ backfield have been unfavorable to White, though, with Bucky Irving being considered for a high-volume role that includes “pass-catching work” and head coach Todd Bowles saying he needs to give Sean Tucker the ball more. At this point, White can only be stashed in PPR leagues. His standalone value is liable to evaporate if Irving siphons away passing down snaps and the tackle-breaking Tucker could eat into White’s rushing work. If Irving misses time, White could take on a specialized role featuring his receiving skillset while Tucker leads the way on early downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f761-dbe3-a9bb-f77393af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed OT Kilian Zierer, formerly of the Texans, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f76e-d332-a1fd-f77e561e0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also signed DL Evan Anderson and correspondingly released DE William Bradley-King. Per The Athletic’s Matt Barrows, “Zierer is from Munich and is part of the NFL’s International Pathway Program,” which allows them to have 17 players on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f76e-d332-a1fd-f77e561e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed DT Eric Gregory, formerly of the Bengals, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f729-db7b-a5dd-f72d982e0000</link>
      <description>The undrafted free agent rookie totaled four quarterback pressures and two tackles in the preseason. The Patriots also signed OT Thayer Munford Jr. to the practice squad and released OL Jack Conley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f729-db7b-a5dd-f72d982e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed LB Anthony Walker, formerly of the Buccaneers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f793-dbe3-a9bb-f7d368dd0000</link>
      <description>A knee injury kept Walker sidelined throughout the Buccaneers’ training camp. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported earlier this week that Walker is “healthy and ready to go” and the Colts were evidently pleased with his workout performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f793-dbe3-a9bb-f7d368dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cowboys listed Javonte Williams as the team’s Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7ba-d332-a1fd-f7bec5a40000</link>
      <description>The starting job was Williams’ to lose, and indeed, he did not lose it. The praise stops there. Williams will likely handle a flex-worthy workload against the Eagles’ vaunted defense in Week 1, while Miles Sanders and Jaydon Blue rotate in behind him. Unless Williams regains his long-lost burst, he could end up ceding touches quickly as the weeks progress. Sanders does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues. Buy Blue’s potential ADP dip. The talented receiving back is a good fit for the Cowboys’ expectedly pass-heavy game scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7ba-d332-a1fd-f7bec5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL suspended free agent DT Isaiah Buggs for the first 10 weeks of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f789-de13-afdc-f7cb0f2e0000</link>
      <description>The suspension relates to Buggs’ 2024 arrest for burglary and domestic violence charges. The charges were reportedly reduced to misdemeanor criminal trespass as part of a plea agreement. Buggs had previously been sentenced to 60 days of hard labor after being convicted of misdemeanor animal cruelty, but NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that those charges were dismissed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f789-de13-afdc-f7cb0f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
