<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed K Harrison Mevis, formerly of the Jets, to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-552a-d45b-affe-55befec60000</link>
      <description>The former Birmingham Stallions kicker will provide some competition for Joshua Karty. Karty has struggled mightily this year, connecting on just 10-of-15 field goals and 23-of-26 PATs. Two of his field goal misses came on Sunday against the Saints. Mevis could take the job from Karty as soon as Week 10 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-552a-d45b-affe-55befec60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553a-d673-a39e-f5bba80f0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson didn’t practice at all last week and was ruled out on Friday. A DNP to open the week is not a good sign for his availability in Week 10. TreVeyon Henderson led the backfield with 14 carries for 55 yards versus the Falcons in Week 9. He also caught four passes for 32 yards. On the other hand, backup Terrell Jennings saw 11 carries and operated as the short-yardage back, punching in the team’s only rushing touchdown of the day. Jennings’ presence in the backfield will make it hard to treat Henderson as anything other than a low-end RB2 for Sunday’s game against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553a-d673-a39e-f5bba80f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553f-d713-ad9e-7d7f67f30000</link>
      <description>Boutte suffered a hamstring injury in Sunday’s game against the Falcons. Head coach Mike Vrabel called him day to day earlier this week. A DNP to open the week is not a great sign, but New England’s next two practice reports will be more revealing. Mack Hollins and Kyle Williams will both be in line for more routes in Week 10 if Boutte is unable to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553f-d713-ad9e-7d7f67f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5548-d713-ad9e-7d5c10c70000</link>
      <description>BTJ could get in some work during the portion of practice closed to the media, though we doubt that actually happens. This should go down as a DNP once the Jags release their first injury report. Thomas Jr. is dealing with a “low-grade high ankle sprain,” according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter. Even the lowest of high-ankle injuries typically result in a week or two of missed time. We aren’t holding our breath for BTJ to play this week. Parker Washington and the newly acquired Jakobi Meyers are in line to lead this team in targets on Sunday. Washington will clock in as a WR3. Meyers will get a week in the WR4 ranks while he learns the ropes of Liam Coen’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5548-d713-ad9e-7d5c10c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku said, “I’m not leaving ever,” when asked about playing for the Browns in the future.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-554d-d45b-affe-55dfa8100000</link>
      <description>Njoku paraphrased a famous Wolf of Wall Street quote that we’ll let you Google when pressed by reporters. He was the subject of various trade rumors ahead of Tuesday’s trade deadline, but nothing materialized and he remains a member of the Browns. Njoku told reporters he couldn’t comment on whether extension talks between his camp and the Browns have taken place. He did, however, have a rather large grin when giving his non-answer. Njoku is headed for free agency in the spring, but it looks like he will do whatever it takes to stay in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-554d-d45b-affe-55dfa8100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Garrett Wilson (knee) was seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5568-d713-ad9e-7d7c3de90000</link>
      <description>Great news. Wilson is tentatively on track to play in Week 10 against the Browns. Wilson has been sidelined since injuring his knee in Week 6. He has missed two games thus far, with the Jets having been on bye in Week 9, and the team notably abstained from placing him on injured reserve, which would have required a four-game absence. Wilson seemingly has decent odds of suiting up this week, even if he is limited today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5568-d713-ad9e-7d7c3de90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-556c-d1e7-a1fa-5fee4f900000</link>
      <description>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reported yesterday that Stroud is not expected to practice this week and that Davis Mills will start on Sunday. A DNP today all but confirms that. Stroud hasn’t officially been ruled out yet, but fantasy managers can move forward under the assumption that he won’t play. Mills completed 17-of-30 passes for 137 scoreless yards in relief of Stroud in Week 9. A lack of passing efficiency or rushing production will make it hard for him to crack even the QB2 ranks in Week 10 against the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-556c-d1e7-a1fa-5fee4f900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-556d-d1e7-a1fa-5fef64800000</link>
      <description>At 29 years old, with myriad knee injuries on his record, Chubb is more than qualified to take Wednesday off as a rest day. He has, however, not yet missed a single practice this season. This could ultimately be a non-issue, but fellow Texans RB Woody Marks remains available in some leagues. Adding him is worthwhile, just in case Chubb picked up an as-yet-unreported injury. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-556d-d1e7-a1fa-5fef64800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Joshua Palmer (knee/ankle) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5581-d45b-affe-559777dd0000</link>
      <description>Palmer has been out since getting hurt in Week 6. After earning nine targets in Week 1, he has failed to earn more than three in a single game. Palmer is seemingly on track to run cardio on game day this week though. The Bills take on the Dolphins in Week 10, in what is expected to be a run-heavy affair for Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5581-d45b-affe-559777dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5572-d713-ad9e-7d760c1c0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle labored through the quad injury for most of the Panthers’ Week 9 upset of the Packers. Despite clearly playing through something, Dowdle racked up 25 carries for 130 yards and two scores. Head coach Dave Canales told reporters today that the team is trying to be smart about his injury with the DNP. He also mentioned Dowdle returning to practice tomorrow. Fantasy managers can breathe a sigh of relief. Their newfound RB1 should be good to go for Sunday’s game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5572-d713-ad9e-7d760c1c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
