<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Nick Emmanwori (ankle) will not play in Seattle’s Week 2 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f93-d294-a19b-fff319990000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Michael-Shawn Dugar reported that Emmanwori is dealing with a high-ankle sprain. It sounds like there’s a chance he gets placed on IR on Saturday. Emmanwori only played four snaps in the opener before suffering the injury, limiting the ability of Mike Macdonald to throw out big nickel packages against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f93-d294-a19b-fff319990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets ruled out WR Josh Reynolds (hamstring) for Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f90-dc44-a9d9-3ff62cf20000</link>
      <description>Reynolds’ wind-sprint role could be handled by dusty veteran WR Allen Lazard, who was declared inactive last week. Reynolds’ speed at least provides a nifty element for safeties to take note of but Lazard will likely function as an ineffective mid-depth jump-ball player. He should not be in 12-team lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f90-dc44-a9d9-3ff62cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) is not on Seattle’s final injury report for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f96-d294-a19b-fff692200000</link>
      <description>Nwosu began training camp on the PUP list and practiced in full twice this week ahead of Friday, so he’ll make his 2025 debut in Week 2. He’ll likely be in Seattle’s defensive line rotation to start, and given time to reacclimate before returning to his starter role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f96-d294-a19b-fff692200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Kalel Mullings (ankle) is doubtful to play in Week 2 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f95-d294-a19b-fff548b80000</link>
      <description>Mullings was not expected to handle a notable workload, but his expected absence condenses the backfield to Tony Pollard and Julius Chestnut. Tyjae Spears (ankle) is on injured reserve. Pollard is a high-end RB2, thanks in part to his hefty workload. Chestnut does not need to be stashed on benches, but for those who wish to add a primary backup, he is an option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f95-d294-a19b-fff548b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (glute) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f9a-dc44-a9d9-3ffead0f0000</link>
      <description>The Colts will have their X-receiver on the field as they take on perhaps the NFL’s best defense. Pittman will likely be forced to take many snaps against the reigning Defensive Player of the Year, CB Patrick Surtain II. Pittman remains on the WR3/FLEX radar but this could be tough sledding for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f9a-dc44-a9d9-3ffead0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa5-dc44-a9d9-3fe78f1c0000</link>
      <description>Whether Pierce’s downfield role returns FLEX value is a toss-up, but he will play a critical role in keeping the secondary honest as the Colts’ myriad short-to-intermediate options run routes beneath him. Pierce is a boom-bust FLEX option in a tough matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa5-dc44-a9d9-3fe78f1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (elbow) is questionable to play in Week 2 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa9-dc44-a9d9-3fefaf640000</link>
      <description>Goodson has a chance to play this week, but his status is clearly uncertain. He was limited through two practices before practicing in full on Friday. Whenever Goodson returns, he will go to work against DJ Giddens for the No. 2 role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa9-dc44-a9d9-3fefaf640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was not seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa9-d294-a19b-fff988b40000</link>
      <description>Bowers instead stood off to the side, again wearing a black sleeve on his left leg. The young tight end is talented enough that he probably does not need to practice in order to play, but we would have liked to have seen him practicing in some capacity today. Saints TE Juwan Johnson and Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. were likely already nabbed off waivers this week. If they remain available, pick them up immediately. Raiders backup TE Michael Mayer is TE1-viable if Bowers cannot play on Monday night. Mayer caught 4-of-4 targets for 38 yards in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fa9-d294-a19b-fff988b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (calf) is not on Denver’s final injury report for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3faf-d294-a19b-ffff4a2a0000</link>
      <description>He had back-to-back full sessions to finish out the week and it appears the calf injury that forced him from Week 1 isn’t serious. Engram will be on the low-end TE1 line against the Colts. The Broncos did not target him heavily before he left against the Titans, but it’s not worth panicking yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3faf-d294-a19b-ffff4a2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) will not play in Denver’s Week 2 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fb6-d86f-abdd-7fbfdaaa0000</link>
      <description>He did finally get in a limited practice session on Friday, but it wasn’t enough to sway the coaching staff. Greenlaw should have a better chance of suiting up in Week 3 given the practice session. It’s probably too soon to call him “close” to returning, but the odds are slowly going up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fb6-d86f-abdd-7fbfdaaa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
