<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:33:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught 5-of-6 targets for 91 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 18 win</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c11-d56e-afff-eef9d07f0000</link>
      <description>Higbee came off injured reserve this week after missing over a month with an ankle injury. It took him no time to get back in the swing of things and he easily led the Rams in receiving yards. Higbee gashed the Cardinals for three gains of 20+ yards, including his fourth-quarter touchdown. This goes down as Higbee’s highest receiving total since 2022 and his second-best mark since his epic run at the end of the 2019 season. Higbee is still splitting work with Colby Parkinson, and the latter found the end zone twice this week. The committee approach from Sean McVay will make Higbee a boom/bust fantasy option for the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c11-d56e-afff-eef9d07f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 2-of-5 targets for 30 yards in the Raiders’ Week 18 win against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1c-d35e-a1bf-cddea3ac0000</link>
      <description>Tucker added one rush for four yards. Tucker in 2025 posted a career-high 696 receiving yards and five touchdowns on 57 receptions, functioning as the Raiders’ lone downfield threat for much of the season. Tucker had a career day in Week 2 against Washington, going for 145 yards and three touchdowns — a rare explosion game for a Vegas pass catcher. He had a career high 48 percent receiving success rate despite shoddy QB play. Tucker is someone to monitor for deep league purposes in 2026 if the Raiders are able to significantly upgrade at quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1c-d35e-a1bf-cddea3ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mayer caught 2-of-3 targets for 26 yards in the Raiders’ Week 18 win against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c20-dc7a-af9b-cfbf568b0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career day (nine catches, 89 yards) in Week 17, Mayer was limited to a couple grabs in a low-octane game against the Chiefs. Mayer finishes 2025 with 32 catches for 281 yards and a touchdown as the Raiders’ distant No. 2 tight end behind Brock Bowers. He proved viable as a starter, however, even though the Raiders refused to use two tight end sets at a higher rate. Mayer, with 82 receptions and 767 yards over 37 NFL games, will return to Vegas for his fourth season, and could get an extension if the Raiders plan on using him more in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c20-dc7a-af9b-cfbf568b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed 15 times for 28 yards in the Broncos’ Week 18 win over the Chargers, adding one reception for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c17-d968-a19b-dcf757f60000</link>
      <description>Harvey was seemingly headed toward a big day after totaling 22 yards on five carries, including one from the Chargers’ six-yard line, on the Broncos’ opening drive. The Chargers’ defense simply stonewalled him on the ground from there. Harvey dropped an easy screen pass target on 2nd-and-15 during the Broncos’ third drive, and QB Bo Nix aggravatingly overthrew him on a red zone pass later on. Harvey and the Broncos are on bye next week, having secured the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c17-d968-a19b-dcf757f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon rushed nine times for nine yards in the Dolphins’ Week 18 loss to the Patriots, adding a two-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1f-d56e-afff-eeff8cf50000</link>
      <description>Gordon, again, played second fiddle to Jaylen Wright with De’Von Achane resting his shoulder for this “meaningless” Week 18 tilt. The No. 179 overall pick of the draft, Gordon began the season as the Dolphins’ No. 2 back with Wright nursing a leg injury, but Wright eventually re-took the role and never looked back. Gordon was highly inefficient behind the Dolphins’ much more efficient top-two backs. It doesn’t augur well heading into 2026, though Gordon is still only 22 (next week). He can remain rostered at the end of dynasty league benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1f-d56e-afff-eeff8cf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 3-of-4 targets for six yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 18 loss to the Patriots, adding two rushes for 22 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c26-dc7a-af9b-cfbfdae90000</link>
      <description>Washington was the Dolphins’ No. 1 receiver with Jaylen Waddle resting his sore mid-section for the season finale, but the short-handed ‘Fins had a rough go of it with Quinn Ewers under center. A hyped 2024 Day 3 rookie, Washington didn’t do much his first year in the league but was more involved as a sophomore. At least it felt that way. Washington ultimately out-touched his rookie self “just” 58-31, but he was the Dolphins’ clear No. 2 wideout following Tyreek Hill’s season-ending leg injury. More of a gadget player than actual target commander, Washington would ideally be a No. 4 wideout, one without much of a long-term ceiling in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c26-dc7a-af9b-cfbfdae90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught 4-of-7 targets for 36 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ Week 18 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf380b0000</link>
      <description>Tyler Higbee was back for this game and even exploded for 91 yards and a touchdown, but Parkinson led the room in targets and snaps. Parkinson had already set career-highs across the board coming into this game, and he put an exclamation point on the season with a pair of touchdowns in the second half. He is now up to eight scores on the year. Parkinson will be a touchdown-or-bust DFS play in the Wild Card Round versus Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c1b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf380b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL has announced the schedule for the Wild Card Round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c23-d35e-a1bf-cde3227b0000</link>
      <description>The Rams and Panthers will begin the festivities on Saturday afternoon, followed by the Packers and Bears’ game later that evening. Sunday’s schedule follows the typical kickoff times. The Bills head to Jacksonville for an early bout with the Jaguars before the 49ers take on the Eagles in Philadelphia. Patriots QB Drake Maye will face the Chargers on Sunday Night Football in his first career playoff appearance. The Texans will then face the winner of tonight’s game between the Ravens and Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c23-d35e-a1bf-cde3227b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Westbrook-Ikhine was not targeted in the Dolphins’ Week 18 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c2f-d968-a19b-dcffcdb50000</link>
      <description>Even with Jaylen Waddle (ribs) joining Tyreek Hill and Darren Waller on the shelf, Westbrook-Ikhine couldn’t command a look in what will probably end up his final game as a Dolphin. NWI is signed for $2.45 million in 2026, but is due no guaranteed money after catching just 11 passes all season. The former Titan turns 29 in March and is miles from dynasty league relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c2f-d968-a19b-dcffcdb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 7-of-8 targets for 65 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 18 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c29-dc7a-af9b-cfbf8c020000</link>
      <description>With the single-season receptions record for a tight end already claimed in Week 17, McBride got to put a bow on an already historic season in Week 18. While it wasn’t an elite showing from him to close the year, another seven grabs will make his record even more unattainable for the next tight end to challenge his throne. McBride’s season took off when Kyler Murray went down. Jacoby Brissett took over and cooked the books with absurd passing volume, funneling looks to McBride and Michael Wilson every week. McBride ended the year with a 126/1,239/11 receiving line. He totaled 97 catches, 964 yards, and 10 scores in a dozen Brissett starts. The Brissett takeover allowed him to run away with the TE1 overall crown. His 2025 season goes down as the second-best PPR campaign for a tight end in league history. Brissett is under contract for one more year, meaning he should be back in 2026. Fantasy managers would love to see another 17 games of the Brissett fantasy bonanza, but he will likely return as a bridge to a younger option. Even with some uncertainty around who will be throwing him passes next year, McBride is the uncontested TE1 heading into 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c29-dc7a-af9b-cfbf8c020000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
