<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jackson Powers-Johnson’s ankle injury “could potentially end his season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</link>
      <description>Powers-Johnson will land on injured reserve, but it sounds like he’ll be evaluated later in the season to see if he can return. Powers-Johnson has started every game at right guard for the Raiders this season, earning a PFF grade of 63.8 while being one of the few bright spots of an underwhelming group. Backup Alex Cappa replaced Powers-Johnson in Week 10’s loss and will likely take over as the starter for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Bills DE Landon Jackson suffered a torn MCL and PCL in Week 10’s loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ec4-d713-ad9e-6ed43b0b0000</link>
      <description>The Bills took Jackson in the third round of this year’s draft. The rookie has only appeared in three games this season and has been in on 30 defensive snaps. The team is still determining a timeline for his recovery, but Jackson’s season has now come to an end. He did not record a tackle in his rookie campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ec4-d713-ad9e-6ed43b0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said there is still no timetable for Bucky Irving’s (shoulder) return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ed3-d1e7-a1fa-7efb0a0b0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the Buccaneers are already preparing to be without Irving for Week 11 against the Bills. While we continue to wait for good news regarding Irving’s availability, Bowles did share that Irving’s shoulder injury is the only thing currently holding him back from getting on the field, suggesting that the ankle injury that initially sidelined him is a non-issue at this point. We’ll see if Irving’s practice status changes when the first injury report drops on Wednesday, but we aren’t expecting much at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ed3-d1e7-a1fa-7efb0a0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants fired HC Brian Daboll.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ede-d45b-affe-7fdeb76a0000</link>
      <description>Sunday’s loss to the Bears marked the third-straight season in which the Giants opened with a 2-8 record. It’s been a quick fall from grace for Daboll, who led the Giants to a 9-7-1 record in his first season, as well as their first playoff win since 2011. In that first season, Daboll was able to squeeze decent quarterback play out of Daniel Jones while leading an offense that ranked 15th in scoring and 18th in yards per game. That said, a four-year extension to Jones in the offseason was followed by disastrous quarterback play in 2023 and 2024, although he seemed to have finally found his guy in Jaxson Dart this season. Daboll’s Giants blew four leads this season on their way to their disastrous start and lost a brutal Week 5 game to the Saints. The Giants have already named OC Mike Kafka as the interim head coach, and could hand him the keys to the team in 2026 if he impresses over the final seven games of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ede-d45b-affe-7fdeb76a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants name OC Mike Kafka as interim head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ee8-d1e7-a1fa-7eeaedc70000</link>
      <description>This could prove to be a great move by the Giants in the long run. Kafka has long been viewed as a riser in the coaching ranks and has interviewed with multiple teams for their head coaching vacancies in each of the last two seasons. He received a second interview from the Seahawks in 2024 and the Saints in 2025. A former QB turned coach, Kafka joined the coaching ranks with the Chiefs in 2017 and spent five seasons with them before being hired as the Giants’ OC in 2022. This offseason he was elevated to assistant head coach in addition to serving as offensive coordinator. Five years with a competent organization and coaching alongside Andy Reid are both plusses on Kafka’s resumé. If he proves capable of breathing life into the 2-8 Giants, there’s a good chance the Giants take the interim tag off him in the upcoming offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ee8-d1e7-a1fa-7eeaedc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals designated QB Joe Burrow (toe) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6eef-d713-ad9e-6effaccf0000</link>
      <description>Burrow will practice in a limited capacity this week and can be activated off injured reserve at any time. The Bengals have 21 days to officially activate Burrow from injured reserve or rule him out for the season, so there’s a good chance we could still be a few weeks away from playing on Sundays. Burrow suffered a turf toe injury in Week 2 that required surgery and was expected to sideline him until December. If the Bengals push Burrow up to his 21-day limit, he would be on track to play in Week 14 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6eef-d713-ad9e-6effaccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Giants GM Joe Schoen won’t be fired at this time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f02-d713-ad9e-6f560ac90000</link>
      <description>This news comes minutes after it was announced that the Giants had fired head coach Brian Daboll. Schoen was hired as the Giants’ GM in 2022 and has his fingerprints all over a roster that has opened the season with a 2-8 record for the third-straight year. While the win/loss record doesn’t look great, Schoen seems to have hit on a few important picks in recent years. Wide receiver Malik Nabers looks like the real deal, and rookies Jaxson Dart and Cam Skattebo have both shined in limited action this season. It’s too early to say that Schoen is safe beyond this season, but interim HC Mike Kafka will now have a chance to show what he can do with this roster, which could play a role in determining Schoen’s fate this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f02-d713-ad9e-6f560ac90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Joe Burrow (toe) will not play in Week 11 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f0d-d45b-affe-7f9f51140000</link>
      <description>This news doesn’t come as a surprise. The Bengals announced earlier today that they plan to open Burrow’s return window this week, but according to FOX Sports’ Jay Glazer,Burrow hopes to return “by Thanksgiving.” The Bengals play the Ravens on Thanksgiving night in Baltimore, which could carry playoff implications for at least one of those teams. Joe Flacco will get at least two more starts for the Bengals, but Burrow is clearly trending in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f0d-d45b-affe-7f9f51140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendrickson (hip) is doubtful for Week 11 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f13-d713-ad9e-6f5756b70000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson re-aggravated his hip injury in Week 8’s loss to the Jets and hasn’t played a game since. Despite initially being called “day-to-day” by Taylor, Hendrickson appears to be on track to miss a second consecutive game with his injury. We’ll check back in on Hendrickson’s official status when the Bengals release their final injury report on Friday but it sounds like we can safely assume he will be out in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f13-d713-ad9e-6f5756b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings LB Jonathan Greenard (shoulder) may only miss one game due to his injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f1c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffee71d0000</link>
      <description>Greenard exited Sunday’s game against the Ravens and did not return to the game. His injury didn’t appear too serious when it first happened, and according to Rapoport, it “is believed to be a minor injury that may just cost him a week.” Greenard has totaled 18 tackles and two sacks for the Vikings, who play the Bears in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f1c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffee71d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
