<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team is open to trading one of its two first-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bdc-d89c-a1be-afdf47300000</link>
      <description>This could be a big nothing burger, but Jones said the team is “open-minded” to the idea of trading a pick. The Cowboys currently hold the No. 12 and No. 20 overall picks in this year’s draft, but have plenty of needs to address with those picks, especially on the defensive side of the ball. As is often the case in these situations, anything can be had for the right price. We’ll see if anything piques the Cowboys’ interest as offers are likely to come in their direction in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bdc-d89c-a1be-afdf47300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Najee Harris was seen running five months after undergoing surgery to repair a torn Achilles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bf0-d89c-a1be-afff0f510000</link>
      <description>In a video posted to social media, Harris was reportedly “running with ease at 15 MPH.” The veteran running back still has a long way to go in his recovery since going down in Week 3 of last season, but with free agency looming, Harris is hoping to prove to a team that he’s worth taking a chance on this upcoming season. Whether or not he’ll sign before fully healthy is unknown, but Harris, 27, should have plenty of suitors lining up to bring him in on a one-year prove-it deal this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bf0-d89c-a1be-afff0f510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “it would take a Micah Parsons type package” if the Raiders were to trade Maxx Crosby this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bfa-d042-afbc-fffa95c60000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys received defensive lineman Kenny Clark and two first-round draft picks in exchange for Parsons last offseason. Parsons was also entering his age-26 season when he was traded and is the better defensive player, while Crosby will be 29 at the start of next season. Age will be a factor in any deal regarding Crosby, who totaled 10 sacks and one interception for the Raiders last season, and is among the most feared defenders in the league. We still don’t know if the Raiders will trade Crosby this offseason, but we would expect him to fetch a decent trade offer, even if the “Parsons deal” is a bridge too far for most teams. The Raiders should get a better gauge on potential suitors during this weeks’ NFL Scouting Combine, which could lead to a deal developing sooner than later if they decide a trade is in their best interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8bfa-d042-afbc-fffa95c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs released DE Mike Danna.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</link>
      <description>Danna was selected by the Chiefs in the fifth-round of the 2020 NFL Draft. The veteran pass rusher totaled 21.5 sacks, 25 TFLs, and one interception in 87 games with the Chiefs and was a part of two Super Bowl-winning teams. The release of Danna, who will be 28 at the start of next season, saves the Chiefs $8.940 million against the cap. He should have plenty of suitors on the market as a pass-rushing specialist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c32-d042-afbc-fdf2f62a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released RB Antonio Gibson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</link>
      <description>Gibson suffered a torn ACL in Week 5 of last season and had one year remaining on the three-year deal he signed in 2024. The Patriots will save $3.140 million against the cap with the release of Gibson, who rushed for 25-106-1 in limited action last season. During his two years with the Patriots, Gibson rushed 145 times for 644 yards and two touchdowns while adding another 25-212-0 through the air. The soon-to-be 28-year-old back who had totaled 984 touches in his career should land elsewhere this upcoming season, but he’ll likely have to battle for playing time wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c53-d629-a1bc-bc5fbb8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports “Packers backup QB Malik Willis and Alabama’s Ty Simpson are among the external QBs on the Browns’ radar.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c77-d990-a1de-ec7f40de0000</link>
      <description>With two Pro Bowl quarterbacks already on the roster in Shedeur Sanders and Deshaun Watson, it’s hard to imagine the Browns wanting to add even more to an already loaded QB room. That said, Willis, who is expected to be a highly coveted free agent this offseason, and Simpson could both be considered as options to add to the offense in Todd Monken’s first year at the helm. Watson remains a true question mark entering 2026. While he is under contract with the Browns through next season, the early return on his record-setting deal has been disappointing. Watson is returning from a torn Achilles he suffered in 2024 and has thrown for just 3,365-19-12 in the 19 games he’s played in for them over three years. When it comes to Sanders, the rookie QB is coming off a brutal first season that featured more lows than highs, and as a fifth-round pick, he shouldn’t be viewed as a lock to be handed any starting job. The Browns will have plenty of time to discuss all options at the NFL Scouting Combine this week, but Willis and Simpson will be two names to watch as free agency and draft talk continues to ramp up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c77-d990-a1de-ec7f40de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders re-signed OG Andrew Wylie to a two-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c88-d990-a1de-ecce70390000</link>
      <description>One of the few holdovers from the Ron Rivera era, Wylie appeared in 16 games for the Commanders last season while also making five starts. The veteran lineman has ample experience at both tackle and guard and makes for a solid depth piece along the offensive line. Wylie was slated to hit free agency this offseason but will now be under contract for the Commanders through 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c88-d990-a1de-ecce70390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Bozeman retired from the NFL after eight seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c8d-d629-a1bc-bc9d35ad0000</link>
      <description>Bozeman started his career as a sixth-round pick with the Ravens back in 2018 and also spent time with the Panthers and Chargers. The eight-year vet started 110 of the 129 games he appeared in during his career, and started all 156 games at center for the Chargers last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8c8d-d629-a1bc-bc9d35ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos met with Mike Zimmer last week regarding a “senior coaching position.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</link>
      <description>The former Falcons, Bengals, and Cowboys defensive coordinator and Vikings head coach was not asked to return to the Cowboys following the 2024 season and spent the 2025 season away from coaching. The Broncos are now reportedly interested in his services in a “senior coaching position” capacity, although the extent of the position remain a mystery. The team retained defensive coordinator Vance Joseph through the 2026 hiring cycle. Stay tuned in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8cc3-d89c-a1be-afdf11f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired former Titans GM Jon Robinson as their next Senior Personnel Executive.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</link>
      <description>Robinson will work hand-in-hand with general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan as the Dolphins careen towards a self inflicted rebuild, with the former likely playing a massive role in the direction of the franchise in the coming NFL Draft. The first order of business for the incoming front office will be finding their next quarterback after it was made evident that Tua Tagovailoa will no longer be the face of franchise moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8d3e-d990-a1de-ed7e72800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
