<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:04:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed defensive coordinator Brian Flores to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e319-d35e-a1bf-e7db57b80000</link>
      <description>The Vikings made the announcement Wednesday that they signed Flores to an extension. The 44-year-old led the Vikings defense to back-to-back top-10 finishes by points allowed. He was interviewing for both defensive coordinator and head coaching jobs this offseason, but now guarantees a return to Minnesota if he cannot land a head coaching role. Flores is still in the running for the Steelers and Ravens head coaching vacancies, though he will get more time to build the Vikings’ defense if he does not get hired this coaching cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e319-d35e-a1bf-e7db57b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Packers are interviewing Bears defensive backs coach Al Harris for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e31e-d968-a19b-fbff7e250000</link>
      <description>Harris is the Bears’ defensive pass game coordinator and defensive backs coach. He played a prominent role in building the Bears’ defense this season and is an established leader around the league. With 13 years of coaching under his belt, Harris has spent the last six season with the Cowboys and Bears. A former player for the Packers, Harris is now interviewing for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e31e-d968-a19b-fbff7e250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Commanders are interviewing Bears defensive backs coach Al Harris for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e364-d56e-afff-e7ec973d0000</link>
      <description>Harris coached defensive backs and was the passing game coordinator for a Bears defense that led the league with 23 interceptions this season. He interviewed with the Packers for their defensive coordinator vacancy and will next interview with the Commanders. With Brian Flores signing an extension with the Vikings, the Commanders are pivoting to other options for their defensive coordinator opening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e364-d56e-afff-e7ec973d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Josina Anderson reports the Ravens completed a second interview with Chargers defensive coordinator Jesse Minter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e38b-d968-a19b-fbfbae160000</link>
      <description>Minter has been heavily rumored to be the favorite for the Ravens’ head coaching role and just completed his second interview with the organization. He has ties to the Ravens organization after having worked under former head coach John Harbaugh and former defensive coordinator Mike Macdonald for the team. Anderson reports the Ravens have finished their second interview with Minter and a deal has not yet been reached. He remains on Baltimore’s radar, though the team has a few other second interviews on the docket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e38b-d968-a19b-fbfbae160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Giants have parted ways with Senior VP of Football Operations and Strategy Kevin Abrams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e3b4-d968-a19b-fbf5f8430000</link>
      <description>Rapoport reports Abrams is let go “as part of organizational restructuring.” Abrams has been with the team for nearly 30 years, but with John Harbaugh taking over and wanting more control in the organization, he is out as part of the new organizational structure. With a tenure spanning over four general managers and his own brief stint as interim, Abrams won two Super Bowls with the Giants and was a well-respected member of the front office. He is a candidate to be hired to another front office with plenty of experience under his belt, while the new-look Giants hierarchy starts to take shape with Harbaugh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e3b4-d968-a19b-fbf5f8430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Bucs are finalizing a deal to hire Falcons offensive coordinator Zac Robinson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5db-d56e-afff-e7fb57660000</link>
      <description>Robinson joined Atlanta two years ago when the team hired Raheem Morris as their head coach. He had previously worked under Sean McVay for five years, working his way up to pass game coordinator for the final two. Robinson started off strong, getting Atlanta to 13th in points scored despite Kirk Cousins struggling in his first year as a Falcon. The switch to Michael Penix in 2025 didn’t go as planned and the team cratered to 24th in scoring. The hope for Baker Mayfield and company will be that Robinson was simply dealt a bad hand in Atlanta. The hiring bodes particularly well for Bucky Irving. Atlanta ranked top-10 in rushing yards in both of Robinson’s seasons with the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5db-d56e-afff-e7fb57660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport expects the Bucs to hire Falcons senior offensive assistant Ken Zampese and passing game coordinator TJ Yates.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5e1-d56e-afff-e7e9accc0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a done deal yet, but both coaches should make it to Tampa Bay sooner rather than later. The Bucs are finalizing a deal to bring on Falcons OC Zac Robinson in the same role. As most coaches do, he will bring along some of his lieutenants. Zampese has been coaching in the NFL for over 20 years. Yates joined the coaching ranks almost immediately after his playing career ended in 2017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5e1-d56e-afff-e7e9accc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Ravens assistant head coach Willie Taggart for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5f1-dc7a-af9b-efffe6ec0000</link>
      <description>Taggart also holds the title of running backs coach. He joined the Ravens in 2023 after a lengthy career coaching college football. After a quiet first year on the job, Taggart got to work with Derrick Henry for his next two seasons in Baltimore. Henry exploded with the Ravens, running for 3,516 yards over the past two years. As expected, John Harbaugh plans on bringing as many of his former staffers to New York as possible. Both Taggart and Ravens OC Todd Monken are reportedly in consideration for the OC vacancy in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5f1-dc7a-af9b-efffe6ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles requested an interview with Bears offensive coordinator Declan Doyle for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5ff-d35e-a1bf-e5ff49020000</link>
      <description>While it’s a lateral move on the surface, Doyle doesn’t call plays in Chicago and would do so in Philly. That also means that the Bears can’t turn down the Eagles’ request to interview Doyle. Chicago finished the year ninth in points per game and made their deepest playoff run since 2010. Most importantly, Caleb Williams showed drastic improvement in his second season after Ben Johnson and Doyle took over the offense. The Eagles would hope to get a similar turnaround from Jalen Hurts, who is coming off a career-low in yards per attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5ff-d35e-a1bf-e5ff49020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Texans quarterbacks coach Jerrod Johnson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e61f-d35e-a1bf-e7df55470000</link>
      <description>Johnson received several offensive coordinator interviews following C.J. Stroud’s breakout rookie season. That was all the way back at the end of the 2023 season. Stroud regressed in 2024 and the Texans fired OC Bobby Slowik. Johnson was a candidate to replace him, but the team ultimately chose an outside voice in Nick Caley. With Stroud playing better this year, there is again some interest in Johnson as an OC. Johnson would join a Miami team without any answers at quarterback. Tua Tagovailoa is expected to be released and the team doesn’t have a high enough pick in the draft to land a premier rookie quarterback. It wouldn’t be surprising to see Johnson stick in Houston for another year in search of better opportunities next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e61f-d35e-a1bf-e7df55470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
