<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Nate Wiggins (elbow) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a5e8-dca3-a9fb-bdf97c090000</link>
      <description>The goodnewson the defensive side of the ball ends there. Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) was downgraded to a non-participant after a limited session on Wednesday. Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) and LB Roquan Smith (hamstring) remained sidelined. The Ravens’ injury-depleted defense will have a difficult time containing the Texans this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a5e8-dca3-a9fb-bdf97c090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OT Ronnie Stanley (ankle) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a60f-deb6-a7fd-f7dfc6ce0000</link>
      <description>Stanley was sidelined on Wednesday after trying unsuccessfully to play through the ankle injury in Week 4 against the Chiefs. Ravens C Tyler Linderbaum (calf) continued practicing after getting in a limited section yesterday. The Ravens need their offensive line starters on the field this week to protect pocket-passing backup QB Cooper Rush, with starting QB Lamar Jackson expectedly sidelined by a hamstring injury. They face the Texans’ potent pass rush this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a60f-deb6-a7fd-f7dfc6ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Noah Fant (concussion) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a61b-d95b-addb-ee5f03c30000</link>
      <description>Fant’s potential Week 5 return can hardly be heralded as a difference-making development, but Cincinnati could at least have its tight end platoon intact for its game against the Lions. In three games this season, Fant has caught 10-of-12 targets for 80 yards and one touchdown. He is not on the TE1 radar and does not need to be rostered if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a61b-d95b-addb-ee5f03c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a621-deb6-a7fd-f7ffe3410000</link>
      <description>This is not good. Hubbard was also sidelined on Wednesday. Earlier this week, Panthers head coach Dave Canales said Hubbard’s calf injury was not a “factor” regarding his limited Week 4 workload. No. 2 RB Rico Dowdle totaled nine carries and one target while rookie RB Trevor Etienne logged seven carries. Hubbard’s calf injury certainly could be a factor this week, though. If Hubbard is somehow active against the Dolphins, Dowdle and Etienne should get their fair share of touches, reducing Hubbard’s fantasy ceiling. If Hubbard is inactive, Dowdle could sneak up to the RB2/3 borderline with four teams on bye. Etienne would be a dart throw FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a621-deb6-a7fd-f7ffe3410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) is practicing Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a631-deb6-a7fd-f7fffdc00000</link>
      <description>Goedert missed Wednesday’s practice with a knee issue, but it appears to have been a maintenance day. We have seen him listed with a knee condition earlier this season — it’s possible this is just a nagging injury that continues to get listed every once in a while — but this makes it feel likely that he’ll play in Week 5 against the Broncos. He’d be a low-end TE1 if he made it to game time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a631-deb6-a7fd-f7fffdc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles waived CB Eli Ricks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a632-dca3-a9fb-bfbb0ee50000</link>
      <description>Ricks has not logged a defensive snap this season. He played on 15 snaps in 2024 and 316 as a rookie in 2023. In his career, Ricks has 17 tackles and two pass breakups. The Eagles also waived OLB Antwaun Powell-Ryland and DT Jacob Sykes and DE K.J. Henry to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a632-dca3-a9fb-bfbb0ee50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a636-d6e9-af9d-aeb6273b0000</link>
      <description>Barring a major shift on Friday, it appears likely that Jackson will miss Week 5’s game against the Texans. Cooper Rush will be entrusted with starting quarterback duties if Jackson misses the game and will be a rough superflex play against a good Texans pass defense. Previous reports had Jackson unlikely to play in Week 5 and potentially not up for Week 6’s game against the Rams either. John Harbaugh did nothing to alleviate concerns earlier when he essentially no-commented on Jackson’s availability last night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a636-d6e9-af9d-aeb6273b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns EDGE Myles Garrett (ankle) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a63f-deb6-a7fd-f7ff175e0000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session, but it suggests there’s not much concern about Garrett’s ability to play on Sunday in England. Kevin Stefanski called Garrett “day to day” yesterday, and Garrett has already played off DNPs ahead of Week 1 when he was dealing with a hip injury. Garrett is more than likely going to make Carson Wentz’s life miserable in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a63f-deb6-a7fd-f7ff175e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a641-dca3-a9fb-bfd977320000</link>
      <description>We have no concerns about Njoku suiting up on Sunday. He likely will be removed from the final injury report without a setback on Friday. Njoku figures to be a low-floor, low-ceiling option against the Vikings in Week 5 as Dillon Gabriel makes his NFL debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a641-dca3-a9fb-bfd977320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Greg Newsome (hamstring) was limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a643-d95b-addb-ee47cfa10000</link>
      <description>We never love to see a mid-week downgrade and unfortunately that’s what happened with Newsome today. It’s possible this is a blip, but it also could be a mid-practice injury that sends him to the inactives for Week 5. We’ll check in on him again tomorrow. If Newsome were out, it would increase the appeal of Minnesota’s wideout room as Cleveland’s depth corners behind Denzel Ward and Newsome are not well-regarded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a643-d95b-addb-ee47cfa10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
