<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said the team will continue using a two-back approach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</link>
      <description>Chuba Hubbard outsnapped Rico Dowdle 38-33, but Dowdle out-touched Hubbard 18-16. Six teams on bye probably squeezes each of them into the low-end RB2 ranks against the Bills in Week 8, though perhaps the Bills can squeeze the box tight enough to create an Andy Dalton pass funnel coming out of the bye. It’s clear that Carolina’s best approach is through the ground, and that Dowdle is here to stay as either a pest (complimentary) or a pest (derogatory) depending on who you have rostered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Brock Bowers (knee) and Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) should be “ready to go” after the team’s Week 8 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02cc-df81-ab9b-7ecfb0730000</link>
      <description>It was a reasonable expectation after both were mostly shut down in practice all week. Viewers who tuned into watch Vegas play the Chiefs were treated to what happens without the two as Vegas struggled to even do elementary offensive concepts. While it’s good that both players seem healthy enough to come back in Week 9, neither player profiles as a top-tier option while working for this inconsistent offense. Bowers is probably a mid-tier TE1 until we see his 2024 form again, and Meyers is closer to a WR3 than a WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02cc-df81-ab9b-7ecfb0730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colts EDGE Samson Ebukam “is expected to miss multiple weeks with an MCL injury.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02d8-da18-a39a-dadb01a70000</link>
      <description>According to Fowler, Ebukam is seeking a second opinion, but it doesn’t sound like he’ll be on track to play any time in the coming weeks. The 30-year-old pass rusher was injured in Sunday’s win over the Chargers, and has tallied two sacks and and 14 tackles this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02d8-da18-a39a-dadb01a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports Commanders DE Dorance Armstong “will be out indefinitely” after suffering a knee injury in Week 7’s loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02dc-d651-a9df-6bddaf0d0000</link>
      <description>Armstrong, who is seeking a second opinion on his injury, has been playing well for the Commanders this season, totaling 24 tackles, seven TFLs, and 5.5 sacks in just seven games. His loss is a tough blow to a Commanders defense that has been among the league’s worst through the first month and a half, as they currently rank 21st in points allowed and have allowed the sixth-most yards. We’ll likely get a more definite timeline on Armstrong’s absence in the coming days but it sounds like he could be looking at a multi-week absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02dc-d651-a9df-6bddaf0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said Tua Tagovailoa will remain the Dolphins starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02da-df81-ab9b-7edf86320000</link>
      <description>It’s not like he has any better options with Zach Wilson demoted to third string and the green Quinn Ewers behind Tagovailoa. After back-to-back three-pick games, including a late-game benching in a blowout on Sunday, the seat is hot for both McDaniel and Tagovailoa. In-game benching is certainly a possibility in a matchup against what has been a stellar Falcons secondary in Week 8. Tagovailoa is only a marginal superflex starter this week with the added risk, even with six teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02da-df81-ab9b-7edf86320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans activated DL Denico Autry (knee) from the reserve/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02de-da18-a39a-dadf3c590000</link>
      <description>He’ll play in tonight’s game against the Seahawks, as will rookie safety Jaylen Reed, who was also activated off PUP today. Autry is no spring chicken at 35, but he should give the Texans some additional inside pass rush ability going forward and make their defense a little harder to work against on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02de-da18-a39a-dadf3c590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints HC Kellen Moore said Spencer Rattler would remain the team’s starter for Week 8 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0304-d651-a9df-6b1563e60000</link>
      <description>When asked to elaborate on whether or not we see rookie Tyler Shough at some point this season, Rattler said who the QB1 is would be determined on a week-to-week basis. Rattler has thrown for 1,450-8-4 in seven starts this season, but tossed three picks in Sunday’s loss to the Bears. For the most part, Rattler was doing a good job at limiting mistakes prior to Week 7’s collapse, but despite this, the Saints still remain one of the least productive offenses in the league. Sitting on a 1-6 record and with little offensive production to speak of, the move to Shough remains a matter of when, not if.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0304-d651-a9df-6b1563e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is not practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030c-d651-a9df-6b1d28420000</link>
      <description>Teams often have practices on Monday after bye weeks, and the NFL does not require them to submit an injury report. Thus, it does not make too much sense to read heavily into this regarding Jackson’s Week 8 availability. He may simply be saving it for Wednesday. But it’s an inauspicious sign that he’s still sidelined in a practice where Roquan Smith, Ronnie Stanley, and Chidobe Awuzie all got into. Jackson’s hamstring will be the number one question about Week 8’s slate, so look for several more updates on it this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030c-d651-a9df-6b1d28420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels’ hamstring injury is not considered long-term, but his uncertain about his Week 8 availability.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030b-da18-a39a-db1b95180000</link>
      <description>Quinn has seldom been clear about the health of his QB1. He beat around the bush for two weeks while Daniels worked through a groin injury, and will likely play the status of his QB1 close to the vest for most of this week. The proof will be in the practice report, which won’t be released until Thursday since the Commanders play on Monday night, but fantasy managers counting on Daniels in Week 8 would be wise to stash backup Marcus Mariota on their bench in case he is ruled out late Sunday or on game day. If he is unable to play in Week 8, it would mark the third game Daniels has missed this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-030b-da18-a39a-db1b95180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said EDGE Dorance Armstrong’s knee injury is season-ending.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-031e-da18-a39a-db1fde580000</link>
      <description>Armstrong signed a three-year, $33 million contract two offseasons ago and the Commanders are not tied to him in 2026, where they’ll be able to save $3.3 million by releasing him or more by using the post-June 1 designation. It’s a devastating injury for the Commanders as Armstrong was by far the best player on the defense this year, with a 77.6 PFF defensive grade in 239 snaps. Entering his age-29 season in 2026, Armstrong is probably playing well enough to stay, but the Commanders will likely look to upgrade the room around him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-031e-da18-a39a-db1fde580000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
