<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants restructured Paulson Adebo’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8dd-db72-a199-fadf6cdc0000</link>
      <description>The team also reworked Jevon Holland’s contract, creating over $4.8 million in cap space, according to ESPN’s Field Yates. Simple restructures are common practice in the NFL and teams typically have the option to do so whenever they want to. The moves could be intended to clear up space for a trade, but NFL trades are rarer than fans want to admit. It’s more likely that they were done to create some freedom for minor free agent moves as the season progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8dd-db72-a199-fadf6cdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said CeeDee Lamb (ankle) is expected to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8e8-dd4c-afb9-efe9d2f20000</link>
      <description>Lamb has missed the past three weeks with a high-ankle sprain. Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said earlier this week that Lamb could play on Sunday. Even a limited practice to start the week is a good sign for his Week 7 availability. If practice goes well this week, Lamb will return to the WR1 ranks for a good matchup versus the Commanders. George Pickens, on the other hand, will tumble back into the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8e8-dd4c-afb9-efe9d2f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) is expected to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8f6-db72-a199-faffb7f80000</link>
      <description>Right guard Tyler Booker is also expected to practice. With CeeDee Lamb looking likely to return this week as well, the Cowboys are getting healthy just as they head into a crucial NFC East matchup against the Commanders. Turpin isn’t on the fantasy radar, but he does bring a level of dynamism to the Cowboys’ offense and special teams that can’t be replicated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8f6-db72-a199-faffb7f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed WR Noah Brown (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fb-db72-a199-fafba4660000</link>
      <description>Brown will miss at least four games now. If Terry McLaurin is back this week, Chris Moore will operate as the team’s No. 3 receiver behind him and Deebo Samuel. He could hold onto the No. 2 role if McLaurin remains sidelined. Moore caught three passes for 46 yards and a score in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fb-db72-a199-fafba4660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard (calf) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fe-dd4c-afb9-efffa8be0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard was spotted on the practice field with the rest of the healthy players as opposed to working individually to the side. That’s a good sign for his Week 7 outlook, though we won’t know his practice status definitively until the Panthers release their official injury report later today. Assuming he is good to go by Sunday, Dave Canales has a tough choice to make. Hubbard is signed long-term and is beloved by the team, but Rico Dowdle is coming off back-to-back games with well over 200 yards from scrimmage. We fully expect a backfield split for Week 7, with Dowdle likely getting slightly more carries as Hubbard is eased back into the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fe-dd4c-afb9-efffa8be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed S Richie Grant, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e90f-def2-abdb-fd6f48fc0000</link>
      <description>Grant briefly spent time with the 49ers this summer following a four-year run with the Falcons, who drafted him in the 2021 NFL Draft’s second round. Grant flashed ball-hawking traits at times, breaking up nine passes and intercepting three in 2022-2023, but his play was ultimately too inconsistent for the Falcons to extend him. He missed 35 tackles during that same span.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e90f-def2-abdb-fd6f48fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said the team plans to put Travis Hunter “in the position to be No. 1 a little bit more often.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e922-dd4c-afb9-efe32d6b0000</link>
      <description>Coen wants to get Hunter more involved on plays where he is the first read or at least earlier in the read progression. Hunter is currently being targeted on 18 percent of his routes. That mark ranks 57th among receivers with more than 50 routes this year. For Hunter to be worth the No. 2 overall pick, that figure has to change, even if he is excelling on defense. Fantasy managers might want to wait one more week before getting Hunter into their lineups, but Coen’s comments should at least make them feel better about holding Hunter despite his lackluster start to the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e922-dd4c-afb9-efe32d6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e92f-dd4c-afb9-efefdbfe0000</link>
      <description>Corum suffered an ankle injury in Week 6. He went down in the first half with an ankle injury but did return for a few snaps after halftime. Sean McVay called him day to day earlier this week. Corum wasn’t providing fantasy value of his own, but he was occasionally stealing work from Kyren Williams. Williams will see as many touches as he can handle if Corum is out for Week 7 against the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e92f-dd4c-afb9-efefdbfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the 49ers consider EDGE Trey Hendrickson “an ideal fit for their defense if the Bengals would part with him for reasonable compensation.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e925-dd4c-afb9-efe5bdde0000</link>
      <description>Reports on the 49ers’ desire to add an impactful EDGE via the trade market continue to roll in, with the injured Hendrickson (hip) being the latest player connected to them. Fowler and his colleague, Dan Graziano, have both been told that the Bengals “remain all-in on this season” despite their 2-4 record. Graziano outlines a scenario where the Bengals, who are set to lose Hendrickson to free agency at the end of the year, could consider recouping value for Hendrickson if they arrive at the November 4th trade deadline with a 2-7 record after facing the Steelers, Jets and Bears over the next three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e925-dd4c-afb9-efe5bdde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said both J.J. McCarthy and Carson Wentz will get work in practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e935-d94a-a79d-e93dfada0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell declined to name a starting quarterback. O’Connell spent the bye week working with McCarthy on his mechanics, although that’s not something you typically see cleaned up in a single week. Wentz almost certainly gives the team a better chance of winning in the short term, but McCarthy is who they drafted to be the starter in the long haul. We suspect O’Connell will side with Wentz for now. He will likely be on a short leash with McCarthy waiting to get his next shot at the starting gig. This is ultimately a situation Superflex fantasy managers will need to watch closely throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e935-d94a-a79d-e93dfada0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
