<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (concussion) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ee6-d8cf-affb-beeeb41c0000</link>
      <description>Lamb was a limited participant on Wednesday. We do not yet know his participation level today, but his continued activity is a good sign. The Cowboys’ No. 1 wide receiver suffered a concussion in last week’s Thursday Night Football game. The extra time off could help him clear the NFL’s concussion protocol without missing any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ee6-d8cf-affb-beeeb41c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR DK Metcalf (abdomen) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0edd-d005-a9bf-defd7bdb0000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin told reporters on Tuesday that Metcalf should be able to play in the team’s Monday Night Football game against the Dolphins this week, but there was a chance Metcalf could miss practice time. Instead, Metcalf took the field for the week’s first practice. Expect him to play on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0edd-d005-a9bf-defd7bdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn (concussion) practiced in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ef3-d8cf-affb-befb21390000</link>
      <description>It seems likely that he’ll clear concussion protocol and play against the Saints in Week 15 after upgrading from a limited session on Wednesday. LB Claudin Cherelus (concussion) also upgraded to a full practice today and figures to be available as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ef3-d8cf-affb-befb21390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs called himself “day-to-day” after his knee “stiffened” in Week 14 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f00-d8cf-affb-bf2a335c0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs told reporters that his “knee stiffened up during the second half last Sunday.” Despite the stiffness, Jacobs played on 16-of-19 backfield snaps and handled 10-of-12 backfield touches in the second half. He underwent “another scan” on Monday, and the knee is reportedly “structurally sound.” We tentatively expect Jacobs to suit up and handle close to his typical workload against the Broncos this weekend. Ideally, he returns to practice tomorrow. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f00-d8cf-affb-bf2a335c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f12-d8cf-affb-bf3a42b50000</link>
      <description>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (calf) was also absent for the portion of practice open to the media. He was limited yesterday. Both players are questionable to play in Week 15 against the Raiders. Hopefully, at least one of them can resume practicing tomorrow. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f12-d8cf-affb-bf3a42b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Mike Evans (collarbone) won’t play “every down” in Week 14.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f16-da9b-a9bf-df1f21ab0000</link>
      <description>He will be on “somewhat of a pitch count” coming back from the collarbone injury. That’s good news for fantasy managers who were relying on Chris Godwin and Emeka Egbuka in Week 15, but it makes Evans a bit of a risky start in his first week off injured reserve. Evans probably belongs on the WR4/FLEX line if you’re going to play him, though the promise that he’ll be out there on “the big downs” is promising.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f16-da9b-a9bf-df1f21ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f19-d8cf-affb-bf3ba3570000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back practices is good news for Odunze even if both of them have been limited sessions. He’s likely to at least find the questionable line ahead of Sunday’s game against the Browns. Olamide Zaccheaus (hamstring) was also limited for a second straight day. If both can return, it will likely lower Luther Burden’s WR4/FLEX stock in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f19-d8cf-affb-bf3ba3570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (toe) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f20-d77b-adfb-cfa38a7b0000</link>
      <description>He was both added to the report on Thursday and seen in the locker room by reporters with a “short walking boot” — this is raising alarm bells that he may not be ready for Week 15’s pivotal game with the Patriots. His status should be updated on Friday, but we’re expecting him to be questionable at best based on this report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f20-d77b-adfb-cfa38a7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Geno Smith (shoulder/back) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f1b-da9b-a9bf-df1fbf540000</link>
      <description>Raiders backup QB Kenny Pickett is extremely likely to be the team’s starter in Week 15 against the Eagles. Even if Smith is able to return in time for Week 16, he would face the Texans’ elite pass-rush unit. Smith does not need to be rostered in re-draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f1b-da9b-a9bf-df1fbf540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Darnell Washington (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f05-d8cf-affb-bf2fc2680000</link>
      <description>The fact that Washington is able to practice is a plus. The Steelers’ jumbo-size tight end suffered a concussion in Week 14 against the Ravens. Players frequently miss at least one game due to concussions, but the Steelers play on Monday night this week, so the added rest day may have increased his odds of playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f05-d8cf-affb-bf2fc2680000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
