<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 21:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived K Lucas Havrisik.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c199-d90e-a9da-df9f646a0000</link>
      <description>In three games with the Packers this season, Havrisik converted 4-of-4 field goals and 7-of-9 extra point attempts. His services are no longer needed with K Brandon McManus (quad) off the injury report. The Packers also signed WR Will Sheppard to the active roster and elevated LB Jamon Johnson and S Jaylin Simpson from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c199-d90e-a9da-df9f646a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (appendicitis) resumed practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a1-d6c4-abfb-d7a376a50000</link>
      <description>Harrison’s return puts him on track to play in Week 13 against the Buccaneers. He is expected to face stiffer target competition from WR Michael Wilson, who OC Drew Petzing said will be put “higher in the progression,” even with Harrison back on the field. Harrison’s productivity has been extremely volatile this season. Consider him a boom-bust WR2/3 in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a1-d6c4-abfb-d7a376a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed Cam Akers, formerly of the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c19b-d6c4-abfb-d79b78e10000</link>
      <description>Seahawks third-string running back George Holani is a candidate for injured reserve after suffering a hamstring injury in Week 12. Assuming he is placed on IR, Akers will take over his role for at least four games. The consummate system-knower, Akers has never directly crossed paths with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak, but has spent most of his career in similar systems via Sean McVay and Kevin O’Connell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c19b-d6c4-abfb-d79b78e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a8-d90e-a9da-dfafcda50000</link>
      <description>Bears LBs Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder) and LB Noah Sewell (elbow) were both sidelined again as well. The team needs these players to get healthy after placing LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) on injured reserve last weekend. The Eagles’ ground game should have a fruitful outing in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a8-d90e-a9da-dfafcda50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1b6-d90e-a9da-dfbfec4c0000</link>
      <description>Dealing with a calf injury in Weeks 7-9, Jacobs banked two RB1 finishes and one RB2 finish. He totaled 14 touches and 16 touches in Weeks 7 and 8, respectively, buoyed by three touchdowns scored in those two games. They are his only outings notching fewer than 20 touches in a game this season. He totaled 21 in Week 9. No. 2 RB Emanuel Wilson played well with Jacobs sidelined by the current knee injury, a bone bruise, last week. It is possible the Packers mildly restrict Jacobs’ touch count a la Weeks 7 and 8, while allowing Wilson to handle 10-12 touches behind him. Jacobs should be in starting lineups against the Lions, though he is perhaps best viewed as a high-end RB2 with RB1 upside, rather than as a locked-in RB1. Wilson is on the RB3/FLEX radar, though his workload admittedly remains tough to project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1b6-d90e-a9da-dfbfec4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 49ers will not open WR Brandon Aiyuk’s (knee) return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c1-d6c4-abfb-d7c368790000</link>
      <description>The goal posts continue to be moved regarding Aiyuk’s return. Unfortunately, the reportedly disgruntled wide receiver would be impossible to trust in his first game back anyway. He can be rostered in injured reserve spots, where available, but he is not guaranteed to return anytime soon, if at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c1-d6c4-abfb-d7c368790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals activated QB Joe Burrow (toe) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c4-db57-afda-d7f6a6050000</link>
      <description>Burrow is set to start against a Ravens defense that has kept lesser opponents in check since returning to good health during their Week 7 bye. Burrow has been a notoriously slow starter in his last three Week 1 appearances, and it is fair to wonder if he will have to shake off rust in-game, following an extended absence. His mobility may also be impacted. Treat Burrow as a borderline QB1/2. Bengals WR Tee Higgins (concussion) has been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c4-db57-afda-d7f6a6050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills QB Josh Allen (right elbow) is practicing fully for Week 13 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1d9-d82c-a79a-f3dddf910000</link>
      <description>The Bills slow-played this one. Allen took a hard fall on Thursday Night Football last week. The next day, Allen told reporters that his left, non-throwing shoulder “went a little numb.” We have no doubt that it did, but he opted not to share any information about his right, throwing arm’s elbow. Allen partially tore the UCL in his right elbow back in 2022, but managed to play through it. The fact that he is already practicing fully is a great sign, and we expect him to play in Week 13 against the Steelers. He can be treated as an elite QB1, as always. This is simply an issue worth monitoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1d9-d82c-a79a-f3dddf910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (knee) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c1-d82c-a79a-f3d58c110000</link>
      <description>Monangai did so yesterday as well, as did backup RB Travis Homer (hamstring/knee). Monangai out-touched and out-snapped RB D’Andre Swift last week and can be treated as a reasonable-floor, limited-ceiling FLEX option against the Eagles on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1c1-d82c-a79a-f3d58c110000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
