<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Michael Penix is seeking a second opinion on what may be a season-ending knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9284-d673-a39e-b6957b470000</link>
      <description>Schefter adds that the initial diagnosis on Penix’s injury “is not encouraging.” It’s a complete 180 from what we heard yesterday when it was reported that the team believed Penix’s injury was similar to the one he suffered in Week 7 that sidelined him for Week 8. Knee injuries followed Penix throughout his college career. He saw his 2018 and 2020 seasons come to an end due to a torn ACL in his left knee, and it was his left knee he injured on Sunday. We’ll likely get an official word on his injury soon, but Kirk Cousins is now poised to take over as the Falcons’ QB1 for the foreseeable future, and perhaps, the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9284-d673-a39e-b6957b470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins CB JuJu Brents suffered a season-ending foot injury in Week 11’s win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-928d-d673-a39e-b69dba9c0000</link>
      <description>It’s a tough end to the season for Brents, who was claimed off waivers before the start of the season after the Colts waived him. The former second-round pick has appeared in seven games for the Dolphins this season but has been used primarily in a backup role, appearing on only 25 percent of the team’s defensive snaps so far. Assuming his recovery goes well, Brents should be good to go for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-928d-d673-a39e-b69dba9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’ Ian Rapoport reports Drake London suffered a sprained PCL in Week 11’s loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9298-d1e7-a1fa-dafaa1d70000</link>
      <description>There’s a good chance London misses more than just one game, but for now, we know he will be sidelined for Week 12 against the Saints. The Falcons will now be without London and quarterback Michael Penix Jr. (knee) next week, further amplifying the struggles for an offense that ranks 27th in scoring and 16th in total yards. Fantasy managers looking for an edge to exploit here are probably better off fading all Falcons receivers. The next man up, Darnell Mooney, has only 16 receptions in eight games this season, and the receivers behind him are unlikely to offer much upside of their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9298-d1e7-a1fa-dafaa1d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Lane Johnson suffered a Lisfranc injury in Week 11’s win over the Lions and will miss 4-6 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92b2-d713-ad9e-fef64dd40000</link>
      <description>It’s a tough blow to one of the league’s best lines and offensive linemen. Johnson is reportedly seeking a second opinion on his injury, but the hope is that this won’t be a season-ender. Johnson, 35, remains one of the premier tackles in the game. He entered Week 11 having played on 435 offensive snaps while earning a PFF pass blocking grade of 81.3. He’s yet to allow a sack this season and has allowed only seven QB pressures on 253 pass blocking snaps. Backup tackle Fred Johnson will presumably start in Johnson’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92b2-d713-ad9e-fef64dd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92c8-d673-a39e-b6d9b80c0000</link>
      <description>Jets HC Aaron Glenn confirmed the report shortly after Russini broke the news. The move to Taylor as the starter felt inevitable after Justin Fields again struggled through the air in Week 11’s loss to the Patriots. It’s a move that probably should have come much sooner, but Taylor is a seasoned vet who, despite his flaws, has proven to be the more capable starter in limited action this season. In three appearances, including one start, Taylor has thrown for 379-3-3 on 69 passes while completing 62.3 percent of his attempts. He’ll have his work cut out for him playing with a depleted receiving corps, but Taylor should provide a little more upside for a passing game in need of help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92c8-d673-a39e-b6d9b80c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs’ knee is “structurally sound” after Week 11’s injury against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ca-d713-ad9e-fede5ab90000</link>
      <description>It’s about the best outcome we could hope for. Testing on Jacobs’ knee revealed no structural damage, and the Packers’ RB1 is not expected to need surgery at this time. While it’s good news overall, Jacobs could still be looking at a short-term absence, although the team hasn’t jumped to rule him out just yet for Week 12 against the Vikings. His status will be one to monitor throughout the week, but if Jacobs is unable to go, backup Emanuel Wilson, who rushed for 11-40-1 against the Giants, would serve as the starter against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ca-d713-ad9e-fede5ab90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn has informed the team that Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92d0-d1e7-a1fa-dafae0430000</link>
      <description>Were it not for an injury to Tyrod Taylor earlier this season, this may have happened much sooner than Week 12. However, the injury to Taylor in Week 8 bought Fields some extra time, and the Jets won back-to-back games in Weeks 8 and 10, generating some hope that the team may be turning a corner. That hope, however, was quickly dashed in Week 11’s loss to the Patriots, when Fields, who struggled mightily in Week 10 despite the victory, threw for 116 yards and one touchdown while also losing a key fumble late in the game. Fields signed a two-year, $40 million contract with the Jets this offseason and carries a $22 million dead cap hit in 2026 if released. The Jets will likely take on that hit as they look to again rebuild their QB room in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92d0-d1e7-a1fa-dafae0430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans HC DeMeco Ryans said C.J. Stroud’s (concussion) status for Week 12 against the Bills is uncertain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92dd-d1e7-a1fa-daff07380000</link>
      <description>Something similar was reported on Sunday morning, but speaking on Monday, Ryans confirmed that Stroud may not return this week. The Texans’ QB1 remains in the league’s concussion protocol, but the Texans playing on Thursday night only adds to the complications. Stroud has missed two straight games due to his concussion, but the Texans have managed to go 2-0 in his absence with Davis Mills under center. Mills has thrown for 566 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in his two starts this season, but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a desperation play in 2QB/superflex leads if he draws the start. Ryans said S Jalen Pitre, who is also in the concussion protocol, is uncertain for Thursday night’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92dd-d1e7-a1fa-daff07380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons placed QB Michael Penix (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92e4-d1e7-a1fa-daee89bb0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Penix aggravated a bone bruise and knee sprain he suffered earlier in the season, but also added, “there has been damage to the ACL, which could mean a full reconstruction.” There’s still some uncertainty regarding Penix’s ACL injury, but we expect a more definitive diagnosis once Penix has had a chance to seek a second opinion — which he is reportedly in the process of doing. Regardless, it sounds like this is shaping up to be a season-ender for Penix, who has thrown for 1,982-9-3 this season while completing 60.1 percent of his passes. For now, Penix is out for a minimum of four games, putting Kirk Cousins in the driver’s seat going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92e4-d1e7-a1fa-daee89bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Jamel Dean is day-to-day with a hip flexor injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ec-d1e7-a1fa-daee72fd0000</link>
      <description>Dean exited Sunday’s game against the Bills and will be evaluated later in the week, according to Bowles. This sounds like a minor injury to Dean, who has already notched a career-high three interceptions this season while also totaling six pass breakups and 28 tackles on the year. The Bucs will hope he’ll have enough time to get right ahead of a big Sunday night matchup against the Rams in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ec-d1e7-a1fa-daee72fd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
