<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Herald’s Barry Jackson believes the Dolphins “almost assuredly” will release Tyreek Hill before mid-March.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec4d-d968-a19b-fcfd41070000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are over the cap before they even get into what it would take to release Tua Tagovailoa off the books. Hill has a $51.1 million cap number for 2026 and the Dolphins can save at least $23 million in cap space depending on what designation they would decide to use to release Hill’s contract. He has a $11 million guarantee set to activate in mid-March as well as a $5 million roster bonus. Hill, entering his age-32 season after tearing a number of ligaments in his knee, would be a fascinating free agent. Perhaps even an affordable one for a contender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec4d-d968-a19b-fcfd41070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune’s Brad Biggs believes the Bears wouldn’t get “a whole lot back in return” in a potential DJ Moore trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec55-d56e-afff-eefd41190000</link>
      <description>The Bears wouldn’t save any real money by releasing Moore because of the way his contract is structured. They could realize $16.5 million in cap space if they traded Moore, but the acquiring team would be taking on a major cap hit to acquire the soon-to-be 29-year-old receiver. It’s possible that the three sides could agree to a new contract before sending Moore out to a new team (our speculation, not Biggs’), but those negotiations always sound easier than they actually are. Moore will be a key domino for the Bears this offseason whether he stays or goes, and it sounds like there’s at least a chance Chicago moves on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec55-d56e-afff-eefd41190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams ruled out RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) for Los Angeles’ NFL Championship Game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec4a-d56e-afff-eeeabdb50000</link>
      <description>Darn. The Rams opened Havenstein’s practice window this week, but he will not play on Sunday in Seattle. Havenstein is a capable run blocker, and the Seahawks allow a league-low 3.8 yards per carry. Fortunately, his backup, OT Warren McClendon, has been playing very well in his stead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec4a-d56e-afff-eeeabdb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with former Titans DC Dennard Wilson for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec5f-dc7a-af9b-efff6f800000</link>
      <description>The Titans, now under head coach Robert Saleh’s leadership, fired Wilson yesterday. Wilson served in his former role for the past two seasons. During the 2025 regular season, Wilson’s squad allowed 5.8 yards per play, tying for the sixth-most in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec5f-dc7a-af9b-efff6f800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec72-d56e-afff-eefa43a90000</link>
      <description>This is Williams’ second interview with the Falcons, though it is his first for this specific role. He previously interviewed for the Falcons’ recently-created president of football position, now occupied by Matt Ryan. Williams is believed to be a “front runner” for the general manager role, as is Bears assistant general manager Ian Cunningham, who interviewed for the same role earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec72-d56e-afff-eefa43a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills completed an interview with former Colts QB Philip Rivers for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec90-d56e-afff-eef8c81c0000</link>
      <description>Rivers, who has no professional head coaching experience, would seem to be a massive longshot to get this job on paper. But you never know. The 44-year-old did complete 63 percent of his passes for four touchdowns and three interceptions in three starts last year, our latest sign yet that anything is possible. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero told Rich Eisen that he “doesn’t get the sense” that we’ll wake up tomorrow and Rivers is the next head coach of the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec90-d56e-afff-eef8c81c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes “if Aaron Rodgers were coming back to play for one coach in 2026, it would be Mike McCarthy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec9e-dc7a-af9b-efbfb3900000</link>
      <description>Pelissero noted that this wouldn’t be the Steelers “trying to lure” Rodgers to come back, but instead frames it as “a bonus” that might not be available if Pittsburgh hired a different head coach with no previous relationship with Rodgers. Given how the Steelers seem locked into a mindset of trying to win games rather than rip it down to the studs, you can squint and understand how they’d come to McCarthy as a good option compared to the more unproven coaches in this hiring class. We will be writing blurbs about Aaron Rodgers until the end of time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec9e-dc7a-af9b-efbfb3900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Cross (foot) is not on Seattle’s final injury report for the NFC Championship game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefa88430000</link>
      <description>Despite not practicing either of the first two sessions of the week, Cross will start against the Rams. Backup T Josh Jones (knee/ankle) is questionable, and third-string left tackle Amari Kight (knee) is doubtful. Cross would appear to be on the spot to play through the pain if neither of his backups were cleared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefa88430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) is not on Seattle’s injury report for the NFC Championship Game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefab41b0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks cleared Darnold for action just as their Friday practice session was beginning, so we do not yet know his participation level. He was limited on Wednesday and Thursday after playing through the injury last weekend. Promisingly, no setbacks have been reported. He will also have LT Charles Cross (foot) active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecb2-d56e-afff-eefab41b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with former defensive coordinator Zach Orr for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecdc-d56e-afff-eefc4fc70000</link>
      <description>Orr had been interviewed by the Cowboys earlier this offseason before they settled on Christian Parker as their defensive coordinator. There’s been some smoke linking him to the Giants with former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh, but that has yet to be realized. Thus, this is Orr’s only live lead for a defensive coordinator role. He had a somewhat disappointing season in 2025, but the 2024 Ravens defense finished highly in several categories, including first in yards per rush attempt allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ecdc-d56e-afff-eefc4fc70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
