<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Emari Demercado suffered a high-ankle sprain and is “unlikely” to play in Week 12 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9782-d45b-affe-d7961fd90000</link>
      <description>Demercado went down in the second quarter against the 49ers. He was listed as questionable to return but never did so. Bam Knight went on to lead the way with five carries for 24 yards and a score. Michael Carter, however, led the backfield in snaps. He operated as the primary back on passing downs and racked up five catches for 22 yards. Expect a similar allocation of reps when the Cardinals take on the Jags this week. Knight will be a low-end RB3 while Carter could have some RB4 value in PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9782-d45b-affe-d7961fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed EDGE Jesse Luketa, formerly of the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97a9-d45b-affe-d7bf25050000</link>
      <description>The news comes from NFL Insider Jordan Schultz. Schultz didn’t specify whether Luketa is joining the team’s practice squad or active roster, but we will assume it’s a practice squad addition for now. Luketa appeared in 10 games for the Cardinals last year and recorded three sacks before suffering a season-ending thigh injury. he also contributed heavily on special teams. Luketa gives them Rams’ some extra depth as they eye a playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97a9-d45b-affe-d7bf25050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Giants EDGE Abdul Carter “vehemently denied Tuesday that he slept through a walk-through practice last week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97ae-d673-a39e-b7bfc8440000</link>
      <description>The No. 3 overall pick was benched for a series on Sunday after reports surfaced that he slept through practice last week. Carter says the Giants changed their practice schedule and he was getting treatment while he was supposed to be at the walk-through. The young defender still owned up to his mistake but wanted to clear the air on exactly what happened. Between the Carter benching and a loss to the Packers in Week 11, it has been a rocky start for interim head coach Mike Kafka. Things won’t be getting any better in Week 12 when the Giants travel to Detroit to take on the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97ae-d673-a39e-b7bfc8440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Aaron Rodgers (wrist) won’t require surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97eb-d45b-affe-d7ffd3cd0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers, after breaking his wrist in Week 11 against the Bengals, is “push to play” this week against the Bears, per Pelissero. He will need to approval of team doctors before he gets the green light for Week 12. If Rodgers can’t suit up, Mason Rudolph would get the start against Chicago. Last week against the Bengals, Rudolph completed 12 of 16 passes for 127 yards and a touchdown. Steelers pass catchers would not see a downgrade if Rudolph gets the nod. He should be rostered in most superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-97eb-d45b-affe-d7ffd3cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan Alexander reports there’s an “extremely low” chance C.J. Stroud (concussion) will play in Week 12 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-980c-d673-a39e-bc9de9140000</link>
      <description>Stroud is expected to return to practice Wednesday but has almost no chance to suit up Thursday night against the Bills, almost three weeks after suffering his head injury. Davis Mills will be in line to get another start for Houston. Over the past two weeks, Mills is fifth among all quarterbacks in passing yards, with three touchdown to one interception. He ranks 19th in accuracy over those two weeks. Mills will remain a decent superflex option in Week 12 against a suspect Buffalo defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-980c-d673-a39e-bc9de9140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982d-d713-ad9e-fc7d2bd40000</link>
      <description>No surprise here after the Monday DNP, Kincaid has not practiced since leaving Week 10’s game against the Dolphins. Perhaps the mini-bye will get him back in the right place, but this is trending towards another DNP and his status for Week 13 should be considered questionable as well at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982d-d713-ad9e-fc7d2bd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Curtis Samuel (elbow/neck) will not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982e-d45b-affe-ddbee9280000</link>
      <description>Neither will Mecole Hardman (calf), and with Buffalo’s wideout depth in trouble for Week 12, it looks like the sort of perfect storm to get Keon Coleman active again for Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982e-d45b-affe-ddbee9280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans K Ka’imi Fairbairn practiced in full on Monday and is “expected back” for Week 12.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-983f-d673-a39e-bcbf31030000</link>
      <description>So long, Matthew Wright. Fairbairn will regain his spot in the K1 conversation this week as the Texans take on the Bills on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-983f-d673-a39e-bcbf31030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Jayden Reed (collarbone) could return to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-984d-d45b-affe-dddf0f410000</link>
      <description>Such a move would involve opening his 21-day window to return from injured reserve. Reed has been on injured reserve since suffering a broken collarbone in Week 2 and apparently also underwent foot surgery to address a Jones fracture. Packers coach Matt LaFleur was less forthcoming about Reed when asked if anyone was coming back this week but “flashed a massive smile while saying, ‘I sure as heck hope so.’” Reed’s return, whenever it officially happens, would probably shake up Green Bay’s wideout pecking order for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-984d-d45b-affe-dddf0f410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said Kenneth Walker is “showing that he’s earning more opportunities to get the ball.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</link>
      <description>Walker out-snapped Zach Charbonnet on Sunday, playing 43 snaps to Charbonnet’s 36. Over the last three weeks, he has 99 snaps to Charbonnet’s 77. Macdonald’s comments create the possibility that there’s more ceiling to Walker going forward this season, perhaps something closer to 70-30 than 60-40 with Charbonnet. “I think you really felt Ken (Sunday),” Macdonald said. “And just, even in the pass game, too, on check-downs, finding him late in the play. Just shows you that he’s such an explosive player with the ball in his hands.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
