<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:02:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750a-d713-ad9e-7d5e35360000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back limited sessions for Boutte are real progress after last week’s three straight DNPs. It remains to be seen if he’s healthy enough to go in this game, but the Jets are a sneaky pass funnel defense and Boutte would be a viable FLEX play if he suits up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750a-d713-ad9e-7d5e35360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (knee) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750b-d673-a39e-f59bc4830000</link>
      <description>He was limited on Monday after tweaking his knee, but this is a good sign that Henderson will carry at least some of the load against the Jets on Thursday night. How the role splits appears to be truly up for grabs given the short week and the fact that Terrell Jennings and Rhamondre Stevenson could both be deemed questionable tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750b-d673-a39e-f59bc4830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Gazette’s Chris Tomasson reports the Broncos are considering placing J.K. Dobbins (foot) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750d-d673-a39e-f59de2c70000</link>
      <description>He apparently picked up the injury during Thursday night’s riveting win over the Raiders, though he played through it at the time while the Broncos closed out the game. If Dobbins is an IR candidate, he’s definitely a candidate to sit this week, which should be a big boost for RJ Harvey and probably make Tyler Badie a FLEX consideration as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-750d-d673-a39e-f59de2c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Austin Hooper (concussion) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7523-d713-ad9e-7d779f500000</link>
      <description>Hooper was diagnosed with a concussion and also did not practice on Monday. The Patriots play on a short week against the Jets on Thursday, making a return to the field unlikely for Hooper in Week 11. Expect more looks for Hunter Henry as practice squad tight end C.J. Dippre may be called up to play a small role this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7523-d713-ad9e-7d779f500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NFL’s Jay Glazer reports Eagles CB Jaire Alexander is stepping away from football.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-756d-d1e7-a1fa-7fef06a40000</link>
      <description>Glazer reports Alexander is stepping away from football “to focus on getting himself right physically and mentally before deciding on his future.” The 28-year-old appeared in two games for the Ravens this season before the Eagles acquired him for a late-round pick swap prior to the trade deadline. Alexander has struggled to stay healthy each of the last three seasons, appearing in a combined 16 games since the start of the 2023 season. He most recently was dealing with a knee issue and could not get fully healthy to contribute to either the Eagles or Ravens this year. Now, it appears he is stepping away from the Eagles and football to determine his physical and mental health before choosing a path for the future. Alexander is not yet retired, but he is unlikely to be a contributor for the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-756d-d1e7-a1fa-7fef06a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports QB Jameis Winston will start in Week 11 if Jaxson Dart (concussion) is out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7856-d713-ad9e-7c56f82c0000</link>
      <description>Winston is being bumped to the QB2 role behind Dart, according to Russini. That means Russell Wilson — a favorite of recently fired head coach Brian Daboll — has been demoted to the emergency QB3 role ahead of the Giants’ Week 11 game against the Packers. Winston’s hair-on-fire play might not be great for real football purposes, but his aggressiveness and willingness to push the ball downfield should benefit Darius Slayton, Theo Johnson, and Wan’Dale Robinson if he gets the start against Green Bay. Dart last week suffered yet another head injury and has a good chance of missing at least one game. Winston should be rostered in all superflex fantasy formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7856-d713-ad9e-7c56f82c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Bucky Irving (shoulder/foot) and Chris Godwin (fibula) are in “rehab mode.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78b0-d1e7-a1fa-7afa7ff40000</link>
      <description>It’s not a great mode to be in as the Bucs head into their Week 11 matchup against the Bills. Stroud said he did not expected Godwin or Irving to practice Wednesday, and both players would seem unlikely to suit up against Buffalo. Look for Rachaad White and Sean Tucker to continue splitting the Bucs’ backfield workload against a weak Buffalo rush defense, and for Tez Johnson to operate as the team’s WR2 with Godwin sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78b0-d1e7-a1fa-7afa7ff40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants QB Jaxson Dart entered the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78d1-d673-a39e-fcd13d530000</link>
      <description>Dart was out cold on the turf in Week 10 against the Bears after slamming his head on the ground in the third quarter. He was checked for a head injury for the fourth time this season before being escorted to the locker room, where he remained for the rest of the contest. Dart is almost certain to miss Week 11 against the Packers. The Giants moved Jameis Winston into the QB2 role ahead of Week 11, meaning Winston would get the starting nod should Dart miss the game. Russell Wilson will serve as New York’s emergency QB3 now that Russ loyalist Brian Daboll is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78d1-d673-a39e-fcd13d530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (shoulder) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78dd-d673-a39e-fcddd83b0000</link>
      <description>Bucs beat writers described Wednesday’s session as a walk-through, meaning Irving wasn’t practicing in full while battling shoulder and foot issues that have plagued him since mid-September. With continued practice participation on Thursday and Friday, Irving could make his return to game action this week against Buffalo. The Bucs could also wait another week to make sure Irving is back to full health before re-installing him as the team’s starting back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-78dd-d673-a39e-fcddd83b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
