<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 04:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons ruled out WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) for Week 6 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d459-def2-abdb-dd791c5d0000</link>
      <description>Mooney was injured in the team’s Week 4 game against the Commanders and did not do enough in practice this week to suit up against the Bills, even following the team’s Week 5 bye. Casey Washington handled 95% of the team’s offensive snaps in Week 1, the last time Mooney was absent, and should step into a featured role alongside Drake London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d459-def2-abdb-dd791c5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions downgraded T Taylor Decker (shoulder) to out for Week 6 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d473-def2-abdb-dd7310a40000</link>
      <description>The Lions will be without one of their premier offensive linemen against an aggressive Kansas City pass rush that currently ranks sixth in blitz rate at over 32%. That could lead to a more ball-out-quick offensive structure, likely benefiting both Amon-Ra St. Brown and Jahmyr Gibbs through the air. The team also downgraded DB Avonte Maddox (hamstring) and OL Giovanni Manu (knee) to out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d473-def2-abdb-dd7310a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons removed CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) from the injury report Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d479-def2-abdb-dd79c7d90000</link>
      <description>That puts Terrell in line to return from a two-game absence against one of the top teams in the AFC on Monday night. The Bills don’t necessarily have a top wide receiver for Terrell to shadow, although he is likely to see the most of second-year standout Keon Coleman on the perimeter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d479-def2-abdb-dd79c7d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears listed TE Colston Loveland (hip) questionable for Monday Night Football against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d47c-db72-a199-fe7f3aaa0000</link>
      <description>Loveland has yet to live up to his offseason hype but is a rookie coming out of his bye, keeping him worthy of a potential deep league stash on the end of fantasy benches. He’ll first need to get on the field, heading into the weekend listed as questionable for the team’s Monday Night Football contest against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d47c-db72-a199-fe7f3aaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills listed TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) as questionable for Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d49e-db72-a199-fedf18510000</link>
      <description>Kincaid managed limited showings in all practices this week but did not do enough to avoid an injury designation for Week 6. We tentatively expect him to play against the Falcons, although fantasy managers could be forced to make alternate plans considering the team plays in the second-to-last game of the weekend on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d49e-db72-a199-fedf18510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Jalen Coker (quad) is out for Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d4e2-dd4c-afb9-f7e306460000</link>
      <description>Coker practiced this week as he attempts to make his season debut following a preseason quadricep injury, marking another week where veteran Hunter Renfrow will handle primary slot duties. It’s a slight hit to the upside of the passing game considering the heavy rates of zone coverage from the Dallas defense, particularly due to the struggles of Bryce Young against zone this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d4e2-dd4c-afb9-f7e306460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d4ee-def2-abdb-ddef94660000</link>
      <description>Kamara remains listed as questionable after three consecutive limited sessions this week. It is unclear when he experienced the ankle injury, although he was seen participating as normal to begin Wednesday’s session before he was unable to finish with the team. Kamara might cede more usage to Kendre Miller if not fully healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d4ee-def2-abdb-ddef94660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cardinals are “preparing for Jacoby Brissett to start” in Week 6 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d653-db72-a199-fe5b99f00000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Murray’s mid-foot sprain is a “version of a Lisfranc injury.” He added that it’s possible Kyler misses more than just Week 6. Murray missed the first two practices of the week before returning on Friday. He was listed as questionable after getting in a limited session. Brissett took the bulk of the reps with the starters in practice this week and Murray’s foot issue could worsen if he tries to play through it. We fully expect to see Brissett under center versus Indy. Brissett is nothing more than a QB2 for fantasy purposes, but he could boost Marvin Harrison Jr.'s fantasy outlook with a more aggressive style as a passer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d653-db72-a199-fe5b99f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Quentin Johnston (hamstring) is “trending toward missing” Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d65f-dd4c-afb9-f7df1b0e0000</link>
      <description>Johnston never progressed past a limited practice this week before being listed as questionable. There is still a chance he suits up on Sunday, but fantasy managers should move forward under the assumption he is out. Keenan Allen will continue to dominate underneath targets in Johnston’s absence. Ladd McConkey will likely see an uptick in intermediate and deep targets. McConkey has been shockingly underwhelming this year, totaling just 213 yards and one score on 21 receptions. He will stick in the WR3 ranks for one more week with a few extra targets up for grabs on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d65f-dd4c-afb9-f7df1b0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Zay Flowers (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d66c-dd4c-afb9-f7edab290000</link>
      <description>Flowers was limited in all three practices this week before being listed as questionable. He will not be joined on the field by Lamar Jackson. Jackson remains out with a hamstring injury, meaning Flowers will be catching passes from Cooper Rush on Sunday. Flowers survived Rush’s first start with five grabs for 72 yards, but the Ravens’ offense imploded and Flowers was targeted just five times. Even as the team’s clear No. 1 receiver, Flowers is barely a WR2 until Jackson returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d66c-dd4c-afb9-f7edab290000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
