<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the 49ers consider EDGE Trey Hendrickson “an ideal fit for their defense if the Bengals would part with him for reasonable compensation.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e925-dd4c-afb9-efe5bdde0000</link>
      <description>Reports on the 49ers’ desire to add an impactful EDGE via the trade market continue to roll in, with the injured Hendrickson (hip) being the latest player connected to them. Fowler and his colleague, Dan Graziano, have both been told that the Bengals “remain all-in on this season” despite their 2-4 record. Graziano outlines a scenario where the Bengals, who are set to lose Hendrickson to free agency at the end of the year, could consider recouping value for Hendrickson if they arrive at the November 4th trade deadline with a 2-7 record after facing the Steelers, Jets and Bears over the next three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e925-dd4c-afb9-efe5bdde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said both J.J. McCarthy and Carson Wentz will get work in practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e935-d94a-a79d-e93dfada0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell declined to name a starting quarterback. O’Connell spent the bye week working with McCarthy on his mechanics, although that’s not something you typically see cleaned up in a single week. Wentz almost certainly gives the team a better chance of winning in the short term, but McCarthy is who they drafted to be the starter in the long haul. We suspect O’Connell will side with Wentz for now. He will likely be on a short leash with McCarthy waiting to get his next shot at the starting gig. This is ultimately a situation Superflex fantasy managers will need to watch closely throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e935-d94a-a79d-e93dfada0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutu Atwell (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e940-dd4c-afb9-efc1a4dc0000</link>
      <description>Atwell suffered an injury in practice last week and was held out of Week 6’s game. Sean McVay told reporters earlier this week he expects Atwell back for the Rams’ upcoming game against the Jags. Atwell should see an uptick in snaps with Puka Nacua out, though Jordan Whittington is also a candidate to take on some of Nacua’s targets. Atwell has a habit of making splash plays when called upon. Fantasy managers could do worse off the waiver wire this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e940-dd4c-afb9-efc1a4dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers ruled out WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) for Week 7 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e93e-d94a-a79d-e93f30180000</link>
      <description>Austin has not yet returned to practice after injuring his shoulder in the Steelers’ Week 4 game against the Vikings. The team had a Week 5 bye and declined to put Austin on short-term injured reserve, which would have required him to sit out until Week 10. The Steelers face the Bengals on Thursday Night Football this week. The short week undoubtedly hurt Austin’s chances of returning in time. The Steelers also ruled out S Miles Killebrew (knee) and listed S DeShon Elliott (personal) and LB Malik Harrison (knee) as questionable. Elliott missed Weeks 3-4 with a knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e93e-d94a-a79d-e93f30180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers opened the 21-day practice window for OLB Khalil Mack (elbow).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e947-dd4c-afb9-efc7818d0000</link>
      <description>Mack will practice today, per Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh. The veteran pass rusher ranks third among Chargers defenders in pass-rush win rate (12.5 percent) while also grading out as the third-best player (69.0 PFF pass-rush grade). Unfortunately, OTs Joe Alt (ankle) and Trey Pipkins III (knee) will not practice today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e947-dd4c-afb9-efc7818d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said he thinks WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e951-d94a-a79d-e95d74df0000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know Johnston’s expected participation level. A limited session seems likely, as the Chargers continue easing Johnston back into action. The 24-year-old wide receiver was limited throughout Week 6 practices before being ruled inactive on Sunday. If he can resume practicing in full by the end of the week, he should be good to go for Week 7 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e951-d94a-a79d-e95d74df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said the plan is for Jalen Coker (quad) to play in Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e95c-def2-abdb-fd7d0d060000</link>
      <description>Coker returned to practice last week after missing the first five games of the year with a quad injury. He was a full participant in all three practices, but the team ultimately ruled him out before Sunday, giving him another week to get back to full strength. He should be good to go after another full week of practices, though Canales noted he needs to make sure Coker can handle the workload before giving him the green light. Coker will immediately step into the Panthers’ starting receiver mix for a great matchup with a struggling Jets defense. He will be a risky start if active this week, but fantasy managers should at least be stashing him in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e95c-def2-abdb-fd7d0d060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e960-db72-a199-fb6b24220000</link>
      <description>Sanders went LP-FP-LP for his three practice sessions last week. It looks like he will get a similar practice regimen this time around, though a full practice on Friday would give him a better shot at suiting up this week. Sanders has been out since Week 3 with a high-ankle sprain. Tommy Tremble and Mitch Evans are splitting the tight end snaps. Neither player is on the fantasy radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e960-db72-a199-fb6b24220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll said he hopes handling 20-plus carries per game is “the norm” for RB Ashton Jeanty moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e95f-d94a-a79d-e95ff1b50000</link>
      <description>Carroll notes that the Raiders have to make sure that they are “managing him right” for the “long haul,” though keeping Jeanty close to the career-high 23 carries he handled in Week 6 is the goal. This is welcome news for fantasy purposes. Jeanty has finished as an RB1 in two of the last three games after finishing as a borderline RB2/3 in Weeks 2-3. Expect Jeanty to handle a hefty rushing workload for as long as the game script allows against the Chiefs this weekend. He is an RB1 for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e95f-d94a-a79d-e95ff1b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said EDGE Patrick Jones (back) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e96a-d94a-a79d-e96fd68e0000</link>
      <description>Per Canales, Jones’ injury requires surgery. He will be placed on injured reserve this week. The Panthers signed Jones to a two-year deal this offseason after his rookie deal in Minnesota came to an end. He appeared in four games with Carolina and logged one sack with 10 pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e96a-d94a-a79d-e96fd68e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
