<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said there was “no way” Lamar Jackson (hamstring) could have returned in Week 4’s loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c6-deb6-a7fd-d7df292f0000</link>
      <description>Knowing this, it’s only fair to assume that Jackson’s Week 5 status against the Texans is somewhat questionable entering the week. Harbaugh said the decision to keep Jackson on the sideline following his injury was strictly due to the nature of the injury and had nothing to do with the fact that the Ravens were facing a multi-possession deficit at the time. Jackson’s status will be one to watch when the team’s first injury report drops on Wednesday. It goes without saying that the fantasy values of Zay Flowers, Mark Andrews, and all other pass catchers would take a hit should Cooper Rush start in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c6-deb6-a7fd-d7df292f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving will undergo an MRI on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c8-dca3-a9fb-bfd915b60000</link>
      <description>What part of Irving was injured in Sunday’s loss to the Eagles was left undisclosed, but Bowles admitted that Irving was one of the injured players he was “concerned” about. This will be a major storyline to follow this week. Rachaad White and Sean Tucker would figure to have much bigger roles if Irving was sidelined in any real way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c8-dca3-a9fb-bfd915b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said Calvin Ridley was “fighting through something” during Week 4’s loss to Houston.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cb-dca3-a9fb-bfdbce940000</link>
      <description>It helps explain his declining usage — Ridley played just 27 of 50 snaps on Sunday. Nobody needs to be holding Ridley in a shallow league at this point either way, but this at least gives you some hope that there could be fantasy volume if you have Ridley in a deep league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cb-dca3-a9fb-bfdbce940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Cesar Ruiz (ankle) is out for Week 5 and is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cd-deb6-a7fd-d7dfc9690000</link>
      <description>Torricelli Simpkins III took Ruiz’s place after he left Week 4’s game against the Bills and played 39 snaps. If Dillon Radunz is unable to get off the injury report this week, Simpkins will likely play guard for the Saints in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cd-deb6-a7fd-d7dfc9690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Foster Moreau (PUP/knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d2-d95b-addb-fed6281f0000</link>
      <description>That will open a 21-day window for Moreau’s return when it happens. It sounds like there’s a chance that both Moreau and Taysom Hill could be back in the near future for the Saints. Is it a cancelling of the Juwan Johnson coming out party? We’ll have to see. Johnson managers are probably going to have at least a few additional weeks of respite, but this seems like it will loom over his rest of season value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d2-d95b-addb-fed6281f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints designate TE Taysom Hill (knee) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d1-deb6-a7fd-d7dfd3a30000</link>
      <description>In his first week eligible to return from the PUP list, Hill is expected to practice with the Saints when they take the field on Wednesday. Hill last saw regular-season action in Week 13 of last season, when he suffered a season-ending knee injury against the Rams. How the veteran gadget player will be used in Kellen Moore’s offense is to be determined, but as always, there could be some fantasy value to be had if he’s still used in the role we’ve grown accustomed to seeing over the years. The Saints have 21 days to officially activate Hill from the PUP list, meaning there’s no guarantee he plays in Week 5 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d1-deb6-a7fd-d7dfd3a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Ravens LB Roquan Smith (hamstring) will miss a few weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96de-d6e9-af9d-9edee8b00000</link>
      <description>Will the last Ravens front seven defender available please turn out the lights at the practice facility? Baltimore will be leaning heavily on its depth against the Texans, making the main starters (Woody Marks, Nico Collins) on one of the league’s worst offenses at least defensible plays. Jake Hummel played linebacker in relief of Smith last week and figures to be one of a few options that could step in against Houston in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96de-d6e9-af9d-9edee8b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Javontae Jean-Baptiste will be out “a while” with a pectoral injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d8-d6e9-af9d-9ed839ac0000</link>
      <description>Jean-Baptiste’s injury was reported after the team’s Week 4 loss to the Falcons. The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala said on Sunday that the team’s fear is that Jean-Baptiste tore his pec, which would likely result in a season-ending injury. We’ll see if Quinn gives us a more definite timeline for Jean-Baptiste’s absence in the coming days, but at the very least, he sounds like a candidate for the IR at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d8-d6e9-af9d-9ed839ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said WR Terry McLaurin (quad) is “trending in the right [direction].”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9707-d6e9-af9d-9f9742820000</link>
      <description>It’s a rather nondescript update for the wideout’s status. We’ll probably have to wait until Wednesday’s injury report to get a real sense of how likely McLaurin is to play, but empty positive words are better than a gutting “not this week.” Deebo Samuel hogged targets in McLaurin’s absence last week and would be a top-tier WR2 play if McLaurin missed again in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9707-d6e9-af9d-9f9742820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed K Riley Patterson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9713-d95b-addb-ff5705380000</link>
      <description>After elevating Patterson from the practice squad the previous three weeks, the Dolphins had no choice but to sign him if they hoped to elevate him again for Week 4 against the Jets. The veteran kicker is 2-for-2 on field goal attempts this season and has made all six of his extra point attempts. He seems like a safe bet to remain the Dolphins’ kicker as long as Jason Sanders (hip) remains sidelined. It’s worth noting that Sanders will be eligible to come off injured reserve after this week, so Patterson’s stay on the 53-man roster could be short-lived.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9713-d95b-addb-ff5705380000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
