<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:30:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 1-of-2 targets for five yards in the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d38f-d968-a19b-dbff296a0000</link>
      <description>One of the Pats’ leading receivers in the Wild Card Round, Henry was a surprising afterthought against the Texans on an afternoon where it was tough sledding for both passing games. Always in the mix on the most important downs, Henry will likely command some critical targets in Sunday’s AFC Championship Game against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d38f-d968-a19b-dbff296a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 2-of-2 targets for 36 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d39e-d56e-afff-f7fe3fcd0000</link>
      <description>Douglas’ 28-yard score on the Patriots’ second series was his first since Nov. 2. He shed a tackle on a 4th-and-1 crosser and was off to the house. Douglas is just a role player in Josh McDaniels’ offense, but one who gets weekly looks. Considering the Broncos’ elite perimeter coverage, Douglas could be something of an AFC Championship Game X-factor over the middle of the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d39e-d56e-afff-f7fe3fcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Stover caught 1-of-3 targets for two yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots before departing with a right knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3a4-d968-a19b-dbf544970000</link>
      <description>Stover, who is the Texans’ primary “tush push” specialist, also added two rushes for six yards. He made some big plays in that department, but appeared to tear up his knee adjusting to an inaccurate fourth quarter C.J. Stroud attempt. It’s a brutal blow for the second-year fourth-rounder, as Dalton Schultz is heading into the final year of his contract, one with no guaranteed money. Now looking at an extended stay on the shelf after being limited to nine games in 2025 by a foot injury, Stover is a 26-year-old (in June) with 27 catches across 24 career games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3a4-d968-a19b-dbf544970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 14 times for 17 yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots, adding two receptions for 19 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3a8-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7e770000</link>
      <description>Playing through a shoulder injury, Marks kept getting stood up on the inside as the Texans’ passing attack disintegrated into a turnover-marred disaster. The No. 116 overall pick of the draft, Marks easily passed veteran Nick Chubb on the depth chart but was slowed by ankle issues down the stretch. Highly inefficient, he churned up just 703 yards on 196 carries (3.6 YPC). He was just as uninspiring by more advanced metrics, finishing in the bottom third in NextGenStats’ “rush yards over expected.” Free agent Chubb will likely be gone for 2026, but 25-year-old Marks didn’t do enough to stave off draft or free agent additions. He will nevertheless be the favorite for lead duties, making him a decent enough RB2/3 in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3a8-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7e770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles requested to interview Dolphins senior passing game coordinator Bobby Slowik for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3ab-d968-a19b-dbfbc7fb0000</link>
      <description>After a two-year stint with the Texans from 2023 to 2024, PFF Bobby spent last season as the Dolphins’ passing game coordinator. Slowik burst on the scene with the Texans in 2023, leading the team to a 13th-ranked finish in points while also finishing 12th in total yards. He was fired following the 2024 season after the offense took a major step back and CJ Stroud regressed in his sophomore season, but Slowik is yet another branch of the Shanahan coaching tree, and should eventually earn another look as an offensive coordinator after some time off. The Eagles are the first team to request an interview, but it wouldn’t be surprising if more teams followed suit in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3ab-d968-a19b-dbfbc7fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb rushed four times for 14 yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3ad-dc7a-af9b-dfbf6c210000</link>
      <description>Making what was likely his final appearance as a Texan, Chubb was a ground-game afterthought despite Woody Marks’ ongoing ineffectiveness. Veteran deference made Chubb the Texans’ lead back to begin the season, but he was easily passed by Marks, who never surrendered No. 1 status despite ineffectiveness of his own. Now on the wrong side of 30 and simply out of gas, free-agent-to-be Chubb probably won’t land guaranteed money on the open market. The main things working in his favor at this point are his experience, leadership and aversion to fumbling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3ad-dc7a-af9b-dfbf6c210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 6-of-10 targets for 59 yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3b3-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9dd80000</link>
      <description>With Nico Collins (concussion) out and Dalton Schultz (calf) soon joining him, Higgins took over as the Texans’ No. 1 pass catcher after playing second fiddle to Christian Kirk in the Wild Card Round. Although it was a disastrous day for the Texans’ passing attack, Higgins was indeed a “rare bright spot.” Although he was much more involved in the second half of the season than the first, Higgins did have a quiet stretch run as the Texans rode their defense to the postseason. The No. 34 overall pick still showed more than enough for fantasy managers to maintain optimism heading into Year 2 in Houston. Collins spends an unfortunate amount of time on the shelf, while Schultz has no guaranteed money remaining on his contract. Kirk is an impending free agent. Already with a 41/525/6 slash to his name, Higgins could end up a “surprising” 2026 WR2 in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3b3-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9dd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylin Noel was held without a catch in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3bc-d968-a19b-dbfd29ff0000</link>
      <description>Nico Collins (concussion) was sidelined and Dalton Schultz (calf) soon joined him, but third-rounder Noel commanded only one target as C.J. Stroud turned his 47 attempts into just 20 completions and an unfathomable four interceptions. Unlike fellow Iowa State rookie Jayden Higgins, fellow 23-year-old Noel never took on a bigger role in the Texans’ offense after popping up for some 4-5 catch performances in late October/early November. He caught six total passes after Thanksgiving, including zero in the playoffs. With fellow slot man Christian Kirk headed to free agency, there’s still plenty of reason to believe Noel could be more involved in 2026, but he is looking like an average at best hold in shallower dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3bc-d968-a19b-dbfd29ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk caught 2-of-6 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c0-d56e-afff-f7e8f1800000</link>
      <description>One of Kirk’s missed connections was a hellacious first quarter drop. A Wild Card hero, Kirk was one of many Divisional Round goats despite his 10-yard touchdown in the second quarter. Mostly a 4-6 target player out of the slot this season, Kirk was able to hold off third-round rookie Jaylin Noel, but only just. Now heading into his age-30 campaign as he prepares for free agency, Kirk could be a victim of the Texans’ receiver youth movement. Wherever he plays in 2026, the best he could hope for in fantasy is low-ceiling WR4 status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c0-d56e-afff-f7e8f1800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Hutchinson caught 4-of-13 targets for 44 yards in the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c6-d968-a19b-dbf723ab0000</link>
      <description>With the Texans in skill corps injury crisis as C.J. Stroud imploded vs. Mike Vrabel’s defense, Hutchinson somehow commanded 10-plus targets for the first time in his three-year corps. Bizarre, and not a harbinger of things to come. Although Christian Kirk is headed to free agency, Nico Collins isn’t going anywhere, while rookies Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel both intrigued in 2025. Hutchinson will probably make the 53-man roster in the final year of his rookie deal, but that’s not locked in. He has 55 catches over 49 career contests. Admittedly, 35 of those came in 2025. This coaching staff probably likes Hutchinson enough to keep him around one more year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d3c6-d968-a19b-dbf723ab0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
