<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports EDGE Dayo Odeyingbo tore his Achilles and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b67-d713-ad9e-6f777abc0000</link>
      <description>Odeyingbo had just one sack this season, accomplished in Week 1, but had 21 tackles and four quarterback hits in his first year with the Bears after signing a big free-agent contract. The 26-year-old will probably be a candidate for the PUP list in training camp based on the timing of this injury. The Bears could conceivably get off his 2026 $20.5 million cap hit without much damage to their cap space. In year two of a three-year deal, the guess is that Odeyingbo will stick with the Bears this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b67-d713-ad9e-6f777abc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said there is “no timetable” for Jayden Daniels’ (elbow) return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b68-d713-ad9e-6f7cef5c0000</link>
      <description>Quinn isn’t placing a timetable on Daniels’ return at the time, but said the team is still working on gathering information on the injury. Quinn, who said the decision to play Daniels in the fourth quarter of a blowout loss was “100 percent on me,” later added that he should be able to provide a clearer update by Wednesday or Thursday. Daniels didn’t suffer a fracture to his non-throwing arm, which is a great sign, but there is still concern about any potential ligament damage, and the option of surgery remains up in the air. A trip to injured reserve seems likely at this point, but we’ll wait for Quinn to provide an update before drawing any conclusions. Marcus Mariota will start as long as Daniels is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b68-d713-ad9e-6f7cef5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said he “doesn’t foresee” Terry McLaurin (quad) playing in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b74-d673-a39e-eff506000000</link>
      <description>“Knowing it’s game-game-bye, that has an affect. But I don’t have a timetable today,” Quinn added. Fantasy managers should be prepared based on this update to be without McLaurin until Week 13. It’s rather inconvenient for fantasy purposes that the Commanders won’t just put him on injured reserve. The star receiver has been dealing with the quad injury since leaving Week 3’s win over the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b74-d673-a39e-eff506000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released S Damontae Kazee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b80-d45b-affe-5f964b530000</link>
      <description>Kazee signed a one-year deal with the Browns this offseason and appeared in only four games. The veteran safety agreed to forfeit $200k in guaranteed money in exchange for his release, and will now hope to land on a team that is at least marginally better than the one he’s leaving. Kazee hasn’t logged a tackle this season, but totaled 92 tackles, three interceptions, and five pass breakups in his previous two seasons with the Steelers. As a veteran with 111 career games under his belt, Kazee should find a new home in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b80-d45b-affe-5f964b530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed LB Jake Hansen to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5beff51e0000</link>
      <description>The special-teams linebacker gets, per Aaron Wilson, an additional year valued at up to a $3 million maximum value. Hansen has played 173 special-teams snaps this year with a career-best 89.6 PFF grade. The Texans are 3-5 and have no offensive line, so it’s good that they’re prioritizing something.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5beff51e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers designated RT Luke Goedeke (foot) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b8a-d45b-affe-5f9e83740000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will have 21 days to activate Goedeke from injured reserve, so he’s not a lock to be rushed back by Week 10 when the Bucs face the Patriots. Goedeke is one of a handful of key players along the Buccaneers’ offensive line who have missed most of this season, but those who have filled in have done so nicely for Baker Mayfield and company. Goedeke allowed five pressures on the 46 pass blocking snaps he appeared on this season and has allowed nine sacks over the last two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b8a-d45b-affe-5f9e83740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals activated DL Walter Nolen (calf) from the reserve/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b92-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa2d9f0000</link>
      <description>The 16th overall selection will plug into Arizona’s defensive line rotation immediately. The Cardinals also activated CB Garrett Williams from injured reserve ahead of tonight’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b92-d1e7-a1fa-5bfa2d9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Matthew Golden (shoulder) will be day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b91-d45b-affe-5f9757a80000</link>
      <description>It’s an encouraging sign for Golden, who was initially thought to be at risk of missing some time. We’ll see if we get more information on his availability before the team releases its first injury report on Thursday, but fantasy managers don’t need to be too concerned about Golden’s availability. The rookie receiver has caught just 23 passes for 262 scoreless yards in eight games this season and can be dropped in all seasonal formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b91-d45b-affe-5f9757a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers announced T Joe Alt (ankle) will undergo surgery and miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b9f-d673-a39e-ef9fb3d30000</link>
      <description>Alt will have season-ending surgery after suffering a second high-ankle sprain to the same leg. We often see NFL players take their time coming back from high-ankle sprains, and rarely do we get the recurrence. This is a brutal blow for the Chargers and puts some governors on their rest of season output. Trey Pipkins and Bobby Hart will do their best to keep Justin Herbert upright, but the Chargers may be susceptible to down games against good pass rushes. Alt will enter year three of his rookie contract in 2026 and he and Rashawn Slater will try to pick up the pieces of what was supposed to be this year in rehab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b9f-d673-a39e-ef9fb3d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Omarion Hampton (ankle) will not have his window to return opened until after the Chargers’ Week 12 bye week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bab-d673-a39e-efbb52b00000</link>
      <description>This has been the tenor of most updates on Hampton, who was placed on IR after Week 5, as he was still spotted in a walking boot after Thursday’s win over the Vikings. Kimani Vidal will continue to be the main back to roster for the Chargers at the moment, though it’s hard to see Hampton not getting the majority of the reps whenever he eventually is activated off injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4bab-d673-a39e-efbb52b00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
