<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kenny Pickett completed 15-of-25 passes for 64 yards and an interception in the Raiders’ 31-0, Week 15 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8f-d005-a9bf-debf24c40000</link>
      <description>It was unclear how things could get worse for the Raiders in Geno Smith’s (shoulder) absence, but they did just that in Philly, with the game taking barely two and a half hours as the Raiders mustered 75 yards of offense. Pickett had 29 yards net passing thanks to taking four sacks for 35 yards. The Eagles rested their starters for nearly the entire fourth quarter. Abysmal, unwatchable stuff that ensures the Raiders will actually try to get Smith back under center if he’s able for Week 16 in Houston. Whomever gets the call will be getting thrown to the wolves vs. perhaps the league’s best overall pass defense. It makes players like Brock Bowers tenuous for the fantasy semifinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8f-d005-a9bf-debf24c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 22 times for 78 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 15 win over the Raiders, adding two receptions for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8c-d77b-adfb-de8f6c660000</link>
      <description>Barkley’s 92 yards on 24 touches, though inefficient, were amassed in just three quarters of play, as the Eagles rested their starters up 31-0 at the 13:17 mark of the fourth quarter. The Raiders didn’t show up, and the Eagles did what you are supposed to do vs. an embarrassing team. Barkley was established early, taking seven carries and drawing two targets on the opening drive. Message received. The hope now is that All-Pro RT Lane Johnson finally returns for next Saturday’s short-week date with a Commanders defense that somehow might be even worse than the one Barkley just faced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8c-d77b-adfb-de8f6c660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Brown has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 15 against the Giants with a rib injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1df8-d8cf-affb-bdfa81c80000</link>
      <description>Brown caught his lone target for 28 yards before leaving with the injury. The 29-year-old had just been activated the previous week from injured reserve with a groin strain, and now could be in danger of missing further time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1df8-d8cf-affb-bdfa81c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 2-of-2 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e96-d1bc-a3fb-9fb6c3ce0000</link>
      <description>With something of a scrimmage atmosphere taking hold as the Eagles toyed with the embarrassing Raiders, Brown provided the final score of 31-0 when he found the soft spot between three Raiders defenders on the first play of the fourth quarter. His 27-yard touchdown was the signal for Philly to rest its starters, which it did for the final 13:17. Embarrassing for Vegas and frustrating for fantasy managers, but fully understandable for the Eagles, who now have a short-week (Saturday) game with the awful Commanders. Despite the bad Philly vibes and his up-and-down season, Brown will be a clear-cut WR1 for the fantasy semis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e96-d1bc-a3fb-9fb6c3ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine returned in the fourth quarter of Week 15’s game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8f-d8cf-affb-beaf3e710000</link>
      <description>It’s not often we see a player carted to the locker room only to return later in the game. That said, Perine did exactly that in the fourth quarter after exiting earlier with a knee injury. Perine didn’t even miss a drive despite the injury, and returned to take more carries from Chase Brown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e8f-d8cf-affb-beaf3e710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans’ DL Mario Edwards (chest) left Houston’s Week 15 game against the Cardinals and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e9e-d77b-adfb-de9f1c850000</link>
      <description>Edwards left late in the fourth quarter. Recent waiver claim Naquan Jones is picking up more snaps on Houston’s early downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1e9e-d77b-adfb-de9f1c850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey (back) is active in Week 15 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea0-d77b-adfb-dea3c8b50000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey popped up on the injury report with a back injury at the end of the week, which is never a great sign, but he will suit up. The 49ers are rather large favorites against the Titans, so the team could limit McCaffrey’s snaps if they get out to a big enough lead. Still, fantasy managers need to play him. The 49ers declared DL Sam Okuayinonu, LB Tatum Bethune, DL Jordan Elliott, WR Jordan Watkin,s RB Jordan James, LB Nick Martin, and DL Sebastian Valdez inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea0-d77b-adfb-dea3c8b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 6-of-8 targets for 28 yards in the Raiders’ Week 15 loss to the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea2-d8cf-affb-beaae7bb0000</link>
      <description>Bowers’ 8.8 PPR points were frankly a miracle as Kenny Pickett produced 29 yards net passing in the Raiders’ second 31-0 loss of the season. He was the only Raider to make any positive box score contribution whatsoever in what was yet another new low in the Raiders’ catastrophic “Pete Carroll year.” As fantasy managers wait for the Raiders’ inevitable next coach and quarterback in 2026, Bowers is a volatile TE1 despite upside that should make him the weekly TE1 overall. You probably can’t bench him for the fantasy quarterfinals against the Texans, but that’s another potential shutout loss on the road for the league’s least competitive team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea2-d8cf-affb-beaae7bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared CB Jalyn Armour-Davis, S Jerrick Reed, OT John Ojukwu, OG Drew Moss, OT Dan Moore, and DT Shy Tuttle inactive for Week 15 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea4-d77b-adfb-dea721b60000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here, and nobody of much fantasy relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ea4-d77b-adfb-dea721b60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
