<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:03:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught his only target for 12 yards in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f87e-d56e-afff-fefeb8e10000</link>
      <description>A free agent this offseason, the 33-year-old tight end certainly didn’t earn many targets for the Rams in 2025 despite 3TE looks being the norm. Some of that is Davante Adams and Puka Nacua, yes. Some of that is also just getting old. We’d bet on Higbee to get sniffs in free agency, but we’d be surprised if the lifelong Ram found a fantasy-favorable role in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f87e-d56e-afff-fefeb8e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konata Mumpfield failed to catch either of his two targets in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f881-d35e-a1bf-fdc3ad0c0000</link>
      <description>Mumpfield had an eight-target game in Davante Adams’ hamstring-related absence and certainly appears to be the main backup wideout on the outside after the Rams picked him in the seventh round of last year’s draft. He finished the year with a 10/92/1 line. There’s not an obvious fantasy vacuum for him to step into even if he managed to be the main third receiver in 2026 — especially given how successful three tight-end looks were for the Rams this year. Still, he’s an interesting dynasty bench stash after making good progress in his rookie year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f881-d35e-a1bf-fdc3ad0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Whittington was not targeted in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f884-d968-a19b-f8f5f06d0000</link>
      <description>From Weeks 1-12, the 2024 sixth-round pick was Los Angeles’ No. 3 receiver and played 52.4 percent of the Rams’ snaps. His fantasy relevancy peaked when the Rams headed to London without Puka Nacua and Whittington managed to reward managers with a 2/9 dud. Over the final five games of the season, dealing with a knee injury, he managed just 44 offensive snaps. Whittington isn’t a must-hold in dynasty leagues at this point, but it’s possible he was simply not himself while trying to play hurt. Either way, it’s hard to imagine much of a 2026 fantasy role for him here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f884-d968-a19b-f8f5f06d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Smith was not targeted in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f888-dc7a-af9b-ffbff0200000</link>
      <description>What Smith did do was lose his footing on a punt return, letting the ball bounce off his chest and arms and right to the Seahawks. It immediately led to a touchdown in what finished as a four-point loss. Kyren Williams replaced Smith afterwards. Smith battled Tutu Atwell for a roster spot all season and eventually won out because of his work on special teams. Welp. An exclusive rights free agent in 2026, Smith was mostly a shot-play weapon and doesn’t figure to have a real fantasy role next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f888-dc7a-af9b-ffbff0200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Mevis made his only field-goal attempt in Los Angeles’ NFC Championship loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f88c-dc7a-af9b-ffbfd3f00000</link>
      <description>Mevis finishes the year 12-of-13 on field goals — missing one against the Seahawks in Week 16 — and hit all 39 of his regular season extra point attempts. He was perfect in the playoffs on five field goals and nine extra-point attempts. The 23-year-old was a find for the Rams and should enter the starting kicker conversation in most fantasy leagues that use kickers in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f88c-dc7a-af9b-ffbfd3f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Philip Rivers has withdrawn his name from consideration for the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa69-d35e-a1bf-ffebedcd0000</link>
      <description>Less than 24 hours ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that the interest between Rivers was“real” and “not a joke.”Now, Rivers is officially out of the search, removing himself from consideration after his first interview. This shouldn’t be an indictment on Rivers or the Bills, but it’s clear he wasn’t ready to move into full-time head-coaching duties just yet. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo notes that a head coaching gig could be in his future but added “now isn’t the right time for him and his family.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa69-d35e-a1bf-ffebedcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Bills are expected to interview Broncos pass game coordinator Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa73-d968-a19b-faf31dae0000</link>
      <description>Webb doesn’t have any experience as an offensive play-caller, but he does have close ties to Buffalo. The former QB turned coach spent three seasons with the Bills from 2019 to 2021, and is a close friend of Josh Allen, which could give him an inside edge on landing the job. Webb got his start in coaching in 2023 with the Broncos as their quarterbacks coach, and added the role of pass game coordinator to his resumé this season. He’s also considered a “prime candidate” for the Raiders head-coaching job, so Webb has multiple suitors. Whether or not he lands a gig is still to be determined, but there’s no denying he’s viewed as an up-and-comer in coaching circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fa73-d968-a19b-faf31dae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed Dolphins OC Frank Smith for the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fab4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf458d0000</link>
      <description>Smith served as the Dolphins’ offensive coordinator from 2022 to 2025 and was named the NFL’s top offensive coordinator in 2023. The longtime coach did not serve as the Dolphins’ primary play-caller under former head coach Mike McDaniel, but his time with the team has earned him multiple interviews over the years. Smith is one of multiple offensive coordinator candidates to meet with the Eagles, who are hoping to improve after ranking 19th in points scored and 24th in total yards last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fab4-dc7a-af9b-ffbf458d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars OC Grant Udinski withdrew his name from consideration for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</link>
      <description>Udinski becomes the third coach to remove his name from consideration for the Browns job, joining Mike McDaniel and Jesse Minter. Udinski was a finalist for the job, but is now eyeing the Bills as a potential landing spot for his first head coaching gig. If he doesn’t join the Bills, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Udinski and the Jaguars already have a new deal in place for him to remain with the team. Udinski, 30, has emerged as one of the hottest names on the market and would become the youngest head coach in NFL history if hired by the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fabb-d968-a19b-fafb86b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans QB coach Jerrod Johnson will interview for the Eagles’ offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</link>
      <description>Johnson interviewed for the Dolphins’ offensive-coordinator vacancy earlier this month but ultimately lost out to Bobby Slowik. Johnson has served as the Texans’ quarterbacks coach since 2023, and worked with the Colts (2020-2021) and Vikings before that. Should he leave for Philly, Johnson, who has never served as an offensive coordinator, would benefit from having proven veterans like Jalen Hurts and Saquon Barkley already in the building.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fac7-d968-a19b-faf7ad330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
