<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 19:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Davis is inactive for Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c7-d087-addf-f1f7e4c70000</link>
      <description>Davis didn’t play an offensive snap in Week 15 and has caught just seven passes for 88 yards this season. There’s no reason to continue stashing Davis in any format during the final three weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c7-d087-addf-f1f7e4c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared WR Rashee Rice (concussion) inactive for Kansas City’s Week 16 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-dc7a-af9b-cfffad830000</link>
      <description>He was declared out on Friday, as were most of the other Chiefs inactives today. Rice has a chance to come back last week, though Gardner Minshew taking over at quarterback significantly reduces his fantasy upside. The rest of the Chiefs inactives are: CB Trent McDuffie (knee), OL CJ Hanson, OT Jaylon Moore (knee), WR Tyquan Thornton (concussion), DT Derrick Nnadi (illness) and RB Dameon Pierce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-dc7a-af9b-cfffad830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts LT Bernhard Raimann (right elbow) will not play in Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41d1-da28-afbb-c5fd1bba0000</link>
      <description>Raimann got in one limited practice this week before being listed as questionable for Monday’s game. Downgrading him to out this early means he wasn’t that close to suiting up. Raimann will eye a Week 17 return. Luke Tenuta took over for Raimann in Week 15 and could be the next man up once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41d1-da28-afbb-c5fd1bba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel “is expected back next season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41f4-d087-addf-f1f45b250000</link>
      <description>As expected, Rapoport notes Tua Tagovailoa is not expected to return in 2026. The Dolphins will either have to eat over $90 million in dead cap to cut Tua or find a trade partner. They would still be on the hook for many millions of dollars if that happens. McDaniel has seemingly gotten the most out of Tagovailoa during their time in Miami. Opposing defenses have simply figured out every adjustment McDaniel made to his offense. Now the experiment is at an end. Quinn Ewers will draw the start this week. Per Rapoport, McDaniel believes Ewers “is what this offense needs to run properly.” We’re skeptical of that, but a strong showing from the rookie would go a long way in keeping McDaniel on the good side of ownership as he looks to keep his job into 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41f4-d087-addf-f1f45b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Woody Marks (ankle) is not expected to play in Week 16 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41fc-d087-addf-f1fc88630000</link>
      <description>As Rapoport notes, expect plenty of Nick Chubb, who is expected to play through a rib injury today. Chubb should indeed lead the backfield, but it wouldn’t be surprising for Jawhar Jordan to see some work as well. Jordan ran for 101 yards on 15 carries with Marks going down early last week. As the top back versus a dead-on-arrival Raiders squad, Chubb is in the RB3 ranks for Week 16. Jordan is a high-risk RB4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41fc-d087-addf-f1fc88630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 16 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-422a-da28-afbb-c67fdfa40000</link>
      <description>Mason went down in the first quarter and was spotted heading into the blue medical tent. He left the medical tent and was immediately carted to the locker room. Aaron Jones is also hurt, meaning Zavier Scott will operate as the team’s lead back if neither Jones nor Mason can return to the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-422a-da28-afbb-c67fdfa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 16 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-422d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcc350000</link>
      <description>Jordan Mason left for the locker room with an ankle injury of his own. That leaves Zavier Scott as the only active running back on the Vikings’ roster. Fullback C.J. will likely see an uptick in snaps as well. Scott will get three quarters of workhorse duties if both Mason and Jones remain out today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-422d-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcc350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaq Thompson (neck) is questionable to return in Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4236-da28-afbb-c67f6b260000</link>
      <description>Thompson went down early in the first quarter and was later spotted on the sideline with his helmet. The veteran linebacker entered the day with 50 tackles, five TFLs, and one sack in 10 games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4236-da28-afbb-c67f6b260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones (ankle) returned to the Vikings’ Week 16 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4240-dc7a-af9b-cfffcbb30000</link>
      <description>Jones left in the first quarter with an ankle issue and was listed as questionable. Jordan Mason also suffered an ankle injury and was taken to the locker room on a cart. Assuming he remains out, Jones and Zavier Scott will split the backfield for the remainder of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4240-dc7a-af9b-cfffcbb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shedeur Sanders (finger) exited for the locker room in the second quarter of Week 16’s game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4242-da28-afbb-c67fa0750000</link>
      <description>Sanders left the field as the Browns were driving in the red zone, but this time it wasn’t by design. The rookie quarterback could be seen with a visible cut on the pinky finger of his throwing hand, and was being escorted from the field by trainers. Dillon Gabriel entered on the following play and immediately took a sack. Will report when we receive more information on Sanders’ status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4242-da28-afbb-c67fa0750000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
