<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed “might need to play extensively” in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-60e0-d713-ad9e-6cf454bf0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks listed WR Cooper Kupp (heel /hamstring) as questionable, WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) as doubtful, while ruling out WRs Jake Bobo (calf) and Dareke Young (hip) on Friday. Fortunately, “Shaheed’s transition to the Seahawks should be streamlined thanks to his familiarity with [OC] Klint Kubiak’s scheme,” and Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the team has “a plan for him” this weekend. Horton also serves as the team’s primary punt returner, while Young is one of the two primary kickoff returners. Shaheed is expected to contribute in both special teams roles as well, having notably earned first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors in 2023 as a punt returner. Shaheed can be started right away as a WR3, regardless of Kupp’s game-day availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-60e0-d713-ad9e-6cf454bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (knee) is questionable for Week 10 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-615d-d673-a39e-e5ddb4270000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also listed LB Tatum Bethune (thigh), DL Alfred Collins (hip), DL Kalia Davis (ankle) and DL Keion White (groin) as questionable and are expected to place DL Mykel Williams (knee) on injured reserve. Williams’ expected injured reserve placement, after suffering a torn ACL, will make him the fourth San Francisco pass rusher to be moved there this season. Williams’ 19 quarterback pressures rank second on the team. 49ers LB Fred Warner was placed on injured reserve after suffering a season-ending dislocated ankle injury in Week 6, yet Warner still accounts for the team’s second-highest tackle total (39). Winters leads the way with 53. Rams QB Matthew Stafford should have comfortable pockets this weekend, and RB Kyren Williams could have fairly easy sledding on runs up the middle, 49ers’ questionable statuses pending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-615d-d673-a39e-e5ddb4270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Cardinals and QB Kyler Murray are expected to have “extensive discussions” about his future with the team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-63c5-d713-ad9e-6fd5284f0000</link>
      <description>Presumably those discussions will take place after the season. Murray was benched in favor of Jacoby Brissett after seven seasons as the starting quarterback with the Cardinals and then placed on injured reserve with a foot injury. Murray is eligible to return from injured reserve in Week 14. The Cardinals will have to act fast this offseason as $19.5 million of Murray’s 2027 base salary becomes guaranteed on the fifth day of the new league year, which will come in mid-March. Schefter passes along that many sources believe Murray will be on a new team next year with one source saying a separation is imminent. Murray won’t turn 29 until next August, but his market could be limited due to a lackluster track record. While head coach Jonathan Gannon and GM Monti Offenfort weren’t part of the Cardinals organization when Murray was drafted and signed to an extension, they’ll incur a dead-cap hit of upwards of $50 million in 2026 if Murray is released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-63c5-d713-ad9e-6fd5284f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 10 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6418-d713-ad9e-6c5c4d390000</link>
      <description>Jones suffered an AC joint sprain at the end of Week 9’s victory over the Lions. The 30-year-old running back missed practice on Wednesday before getting in a pair of limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. Jones told reporters he was in a good spot on Friday and now it’s reported that he’s expected to play. He’s a borderline RB2 this week coming off totaling 98 yards a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6418-d713-ad9e-6c5c4d390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur told reporters Matthew Golden (shoulder) is “fighting to play” in Week 10 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6461-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb0cec0000</link>
      <description>While Golden may be fighting to play, that doesn’t mean he will. LaFleur wouldn’t commit to the 22-year-old receiver practicing Saturday after he was absent from the practice field on Friday. He did say that Golden hasn’t suffered a setback and is day-to-day, but he also said that earlier this week. Golden is a strict avoid for fantasy managers even if he is active in Week 10 as targets will likely condense around Romeo Doubs, Christian Watson and Luke Musgrave anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6461-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb0cec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Commanders QB Jayden Daniels (elbow) could miss 3-6 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-646b-d713-ad9e-6c7f4e920000</link>
      <description>The positives, according to Fowler, are that Daniels doesn’t need surgery and hasn’t been placed on injured reserve yet. The 24-year-old quarterback will be re-evaluated during the Commanders’ bye week, which is in three weeks. According to Fowler, depending on Daniels’ condition and the team’s record going into the bye, a course of action will be charted for his return that will be in the 3-6 week range. Marcus Mariota will continue to start for Washington in the meantime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-646b-d713-ad9e-6c7f4e920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (knee) “unlikely to play” in Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-649a-d673-a39e-e49b90e50000</link>
      <description>Jurgens remained sidelined in practice on Saturday and appears headed for another absence when the Eagles play the Packers on Monday Night Football. Look for Brett Toth to once again be relied upon in the trenches when two top NFC teams meet on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-649a-d673-a39e-e49b90e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns activated WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-64ba-d713-ad9e-6cfeb85b0000</link>
      <description>Tillman returns to a lineup with a new signal caller but had operated as the team’s top option through the air prior to his injury. The second-year receiver’s fantasy ceiling remains relatively low considering the current state of the team, but he should continue to provide consistent production now that he is back in the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-64ba-d713-ad9e-6cfeb85b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley and WR A.J. Brown were removed from the injury report Saturday and will play in Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-64bc-d673-a39e-e4bdef060000</link>
      <description>Both players found themselves on the injury report early in the week coming off the team’s bye week, but both were removed Saturday as the Eagles prepare to face the Packers on Monday Night Football. Center Cam Jurgens was ruled out but his absence didn’t affect Barkley’s rushing output in Week 8. Treat Barkley as a locked-in RB1, even in a difficult matchup, while Brown has fallen slightly to WR2 status of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-64bc-d673-a39e-e4bdef060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) is questionable for Week 10 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6546-d1e7-a1fa-7fee6dbf0000</link>
      <description>Golden started the week off with a limited showing but was unable to retake the practice field for the final two practices this week, indicating a high likelihood he could be looking at an absence for Monday Night Football against the Eagles depsite head coach Matt LaFluer labeling him “day-to-day” earlier in the week. Fantasy managers might want to make alternate plans considering the Packers play in the final game of the week in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6546-d1e7-a1fa-7fee6dbf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
