<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 3-of-5 targets for 43 yards in a Week 7 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe35-d99b-a1dd-fe3d28710000</link>
      <description>Moore spent a night in the hospital over the weekend with a groin injury, so it was great to see him even on the field. He also left this game with an injury at one point, limping to the sideline, so it’s clear that he was not playing at 100 percent. The Bears have also gone far more run-heavy since the bye and only completed 15 passes during this game. The more limited attempts, paired with Moore’s inconsistency, make it hard to trust him in fantasy leagues. Fantasy managers will be hoping for a trade if they want to use Moore with any confidence in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe35-d99b-a1dd-fe3d28710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 3-of-3 targets for 18 yards Philadelphia’s Week 7 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe39-df81-ab9b-feffd9810000</link>
      <description>He had scored in every week since Week 1, but the Kevin Patullo Is Actually My Agent scam had to end some day. Goedert will remain the third option in Philadelphia’s passing game and they’ve proven they’ll look for him in the red zone — the Eagles just only made it to the red zone one time all day. He remains in the TE1 mix in spite of this stinker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe39-df81-ab9b-feffd9810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 3-of-3 targets for 54 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 7 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe35-d99b-a1dd-fe3de7d20000</link>
      <description>Two of Kelce’s three targets came on the Chiefs’ first offensive possession. He ripped off a 44-yard gain on a first-and-twenty to help position the Chiefs for their first of four-straight drives ending in a touchdown, but saw only one target for the remainder of the day. The return of Rashee Rice, who saw 10 targets in the victory, likely ate a bit into Kelce’s workload. The veteran tight end had been averaging 6.2 targets per game through the Chiefs’ first six games of the season, and the three targets he saw on Sunday were his fewest of any game this season. He could become harder to trust going forward with Rice and the rest of the Chiefs receivers healthy, but will remain on the TE1 radar vs. the Commanders in what is a brutal Week 8 bye for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe35-d99b-a1dd-fe3de7d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Reynolds caught 3-of-9 targets for 29 yards in the Jets’ Week 7 loss against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3c-da18-a39b-fe3f195c0000</link>
      <description>With Garrett Wilson (knee) sidelined, Reynolds functioned as the team’s WR1. No other Jets pass catcher saw more than five targets on the day. Reynolds appeared to be a favorite of Tyrod Taylor, who came in for Justin Fields after Fields was benched in the second half. Reynolds would be an interesting deep league option next week against a miserable Bengals defense if Taylor is under center for the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3c-da18-a39b-fe3f195c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 2-of-6 targets for 31 yards in a Week 7 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3b-da18-a39b-fe3b6dc40000</link>
      <description>Odunze led the Bears in targets, but he and Caleb Williams were rarely on the same page. Odzune was also targeted on Williams’ lone interception, and the wide receiver dropped a potential twenty-yard pass when Williams broke from the pocket and hit Odzune down the field. The pass was closely contested, but it hit Odzune in the hands and likely should have been caught. Given that the Bears have done more run-heavy since coming out of the bye, Odzune is becoming more of a high-end WR3 option in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3b-da18-a39b-fe3b6dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 2-of-4 targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 7 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3c-da18-a39b-fe3ffa130000</link>
      <description>Brown has now seen four targets in back-to-back games, but has also found the end zone in consecutive games. With that said, the return of Rashee Rice will undoubtedly eat into his workload after Rice saw 10 targets in his first return to action since Week 4 of last season. The Chiefs spread the ball around to nine different players in Sunday’s win, with four players seeing four or more targets. Brown will be hard to trust as anything more than a deep flex play in Week 8 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe3c-da18-a39b-fe3ffa130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden III caught 1-of-2 targets for 22 yards in a Week 7 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-df81-ab9b-fec7a79c0000</link>
      <description>It seemed like Burden III might be emerging into a bigger role, but he was a distant fourth option in the passing game on Sunday. Ben Johnson and the Bears have also come out of the bye and seem to want to reduce some of their reliance on Caleb Williams’ arm, which means fewer opportunities to go around. If you’re holding Burden in fantasy leagues, you’re doing so just because you hope DJ Moore will be traded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-df81-ab9b-fec7a79c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahan Dotson was not targeted in Philadelphia’s Week 7 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-df81-ab9b-fec7bc640000</link>
      <description>Dotson had 24 snaps of Philadelphia’s team total of 50, so he remains the most-used third receiver for the team. It doesn’t seem like that matters, but we figured we’d tell you in case you were curious. Dotson hasn’t cleared one catch since Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-df81-ab9b-fec7bc640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard had 14 rushes for 31 yards in the Panthers’ Week 7 win against the Jets, adding two catches for 24 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe42-da18-a39b-fe53da060000</link>
      <description>Hubbard returned to the Carolina lineup after missing two games with a calf injury and split the backfield with Rico Dowdle, who had more than 400 total yards from scrimmage over the team’s past two contests. Hubbard wasn’t nearly as efficient as Dowdle, but functioned as the primary back for most of the game. The run-heavy nature of the Carolina offense means the two Panthers backs combined for 34 touches against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe42-da18-a39b-fe53da060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 3-of-4 targets for 35 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 7 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-d651-a9df-ff550fd00000</link>
      <description>This marks the second-straight week that Worthy has seen four targets. The second-year receivers’ volume could only get harder to predict from here after Rashee Rice stepped in for the first time this season and immediately saw 10 targets while finding the end zone twice. Worthy briefly left Sunday’s contest with an apparent shoulder injury but returned after attempting to work through things on the sideline. Assuming the apparent injury doesn’t linger into Week 8, Worthy will be on the WR4 radar in next week’s game against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe41-d651-a9df-ff550fd00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
