<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys released LB Logan Wilson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7cb1-d89c-a1be-ffffe0830000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys acquired Wilson via trade from the Bengals in early November and played his first game with the team in Week 11. During his time with the Cowboys, Wilson totaled 20 tackles, one pressure and one pass breakup. Wilson, 29, has decent odds of landing on a new team in free agency, though he may be best suited to a rotational role as a run defender. The Cowboys save $6.5 million by releasing him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7cb1-d89c-a1be-ffffe0830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Tanzel Smart as their new assistant defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7cbf-d89c-a1be-ffffba320000</link>
      <description>Smart’s hiring reunites him with Titans head coach Robert Saleh. The two spent three seasons together with the Jets from 2021-2023. Smart won over Hard Knocks viewers in his final NFL season, vying for a roster spot during the Jets’ 2023 training camp. He entered the NFL’s coaching ranks last season, signing on as a defensive quality control assistant with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7cbf-d89c-a1be-ffffba320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid said QB Patrick Mahomes (knee) is “making progress every day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7d04-d042-afbc-7dd6bbc10000</link>
      <description>Per Reid, Mahomes is spending seven hours per day with Chiefs assistant athletic trainer and physical therapist Julie Frymyer. Reid notes that although rehab following a significant knee injury is “not going to be a pleasant thing,” Mahomes keeps showing up and Frymyer continues to challenge him and keeps him “on task.” The positive reports continue to trickle in for the veteran quarterback, who has a chance to be ready for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7d04-d042-afbc-7dd6bbc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that Titans QB Cam Ward (shoulder) is “recovering well.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dc8-d042-afbc-7dda60560000</link>
      <description>Ward suffered an AC joint sprain in his right, throwing shoulder late in the year. Ward has been doing “lower-body work” and is expected to resume throwing the football in March, roughly two-to-three weeks from now. Titans coaches are reportedly focused on correcting “some of the bad habits” Ward picked up last year by improving his “base.” We should have another update on Ward’s recovery in the next couple of weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dc8-d042-afbc-7dda60560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe believes the Browns could pursue Packers LT Rasheed Walker in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7d00-d042-afbc-7dd271e70000</link>
      <description>Last week, The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman said he believes Jordan Morgan will be the Packers’ starting left tackle next season, so today’s report makes sense. All five members of the Browns’ starting offensive line are set to enter free agency this offseason. Starting anew with Walker, a talented 26-year-old left tackle, could be a smart move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7d00-d042-afbc-7dd271e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Dolphins do not want to trade away RB De’Von Achane and WR Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dd0-d042-afbc-7dd28bf40000</link>
      <description>This comes as no surprise. Achane, 24, and Waddle, 27, are core offensive players. The Dolphins recently released WRs Tyreek Hill and Nick Westbrook-Ikhine and LB Bradley Chubb as they enter a youth-oriented rebuild. Wolfe echoed recent reports indicating that trade talks regarding QB Tua Tagovailoa and S Minkah Fitzpatrick could heat up at the NFL Scouting Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dd0-d042-afbc-7dd28bf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Dolphins do not want to trade away WR Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dd8-d990-a1de-7dde3c140000</link>
      <description>This does not mean that other teams will not try to acquire him and RB De’Von Achane, but Waddle is currently valued as a core player. The Dolphins’ new front office has already begun releasing veterans and hopes to trade others, as they begin an organizational reset. Waddle, 27, is still a quality No. 1 wide receiver who can help develop a new, young quarterback. Keeping him makes sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7dd8-d990-a1de-7dde3c140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kansas City Star’s Pete Sweeney reports that Jaguars RB Travis Etienne has “legitimate interest” in signing with the Chiefs in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7e2a-d990-a1de-7e6e2d340000</link>
      <description>Etienne will become an unrestricted free agent when free agency officially begins. This would be quite the fun pairing. The Chiefs’ offense, featuring RBs Kareem Hunt and Isiah Pacheco, averaged just 4.2 yards per carry during the regular season, ranking 20th in the NFL. Adding an explosive player like Etienne would be a significant upgrade. Both Hunt and Pacheco are set to become free agents as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7e2a-d990-a1de-7e6e2d340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appearing on the Pat McAfee Show, Steelers correspondent Mark Kaboly said to “keep an eye on” Pittsburgh potentially trading for WR Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-80b0-d89c-a1be-afff4d000000</link>
      <description>Kaboly went as far as saying the Steelers believed they had a deal done for Waddle before last season’s trade deadline. While adding another wide receiver to go along with D.K. Metcalf seems to be a priority for the Steelers, it ultimately takes two teams to make a trade. Pittsburgh’s pursuit of Waddle before last year’s trade deadline came up short and NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reported on Friday that the Dolphins aren’t interested in trading Waddle this offseason. That could also be posturing by the Dolphins to get better trade offers. If truly available, Waddle will be one of the big names to watch at the NFL Combine next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-80b0-d89c-a1be-afff4d000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Daniel Jeremiah told reporters the Lions have “been sniffing around” free agent tackles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-80c7-d042-afbc-fdd76ec40000</link>
      <description>With Taylor Decker considering retirement after 10 seasons with the Lions, it’s no surprise the team is preparing in case the 31-year-old indeed decides to call it quits. While the Lions could address their long-term need at tackle with their first round pick, which is 17th overall, the organization will certainly sign a free agent tackle before then if Decker retires. The Lions are approaching this situation proactively after center Frank Ragnow retired late last offseason, which left the team unprepared. Braden Smith, Rasheed Walker, Trent Brown and Jermaine Eluemunor are some of the free agent tackles that could make sense for the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-80c7-d042-afbc-fdd76ec40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
