<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) is questionable for Buffalo’s Wild Card game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44a-dc7a-af9b-efffc4ce0000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited Friday practice to hit the questionable line after a pair of missed sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. Even if Johnson is active, the Bills could lean a little more on Ray Davis if they don’t trust what the saw on Friday. Johnson’s hard to trust in DFS and Playoff Best Ball lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44a-dc7a-af9b-efffc4ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Terrel Bernard (calf) won’t play in Buffalo’s Wild Card game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44c-d56e-afff-e6ec669e0000</link>
      <description>Bernard injured the calf in Week 17 and has not practiced yet while earning a pair of rule-outs. Dorian Williams and Joe Andreessen saw all the linebacker snaps against the Jets in a meaningless Week 18, while we’d expect to see Shaq Thompson and Matt Milano out there for the Bills on Sunday against the Jaguars. Buffalo also ruled out 2025 first-round CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle), who injured himself late in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a44c-d56e-afff-e6ec669e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed their interview with 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams for their president of football vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a450-d56e-afff-e6f8fd7c0000</link>
      <description>Williams was reported as a finalist for the Dolphins’ general manager position, alongside Jon-Eric Sullivan, who ultimately got the job. Ironically, the Falcons’ president of football operations role could be a step up. Whoever assumes the Falcons’ newly created position will lead the interview process for the head coach and general manager searches. Both figures will then report to the president of football operations, who reports directly to team owner Arthur Blank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a450-d56e-afff-e6f8fd7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons will interview Matt Ryan for their new president of football role that “many believe was created for him.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a454-dc7a-af9b-efff5f6f0000</link>
      <description>The president of football will lead the interview process as the Falcons search for their new head coach and general manager. Once those three roles are filled, the president of football will then hold the head coach and general manager “accountable and report directly to [team owner Arthur] Blank himself.” Blank reportedly acknowledged that the head coach and general manager candidates “would not be keen on ceding authority” to the new position, “so those positions will remain the primary decision-makers in their respective roles.” The Falcons have interviewed other candidates and will continue to do so, but Blank has effusively praised Ryan throughout the process. He is seemingly the favorite to secure the gig at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a454-dc7a-af9b-efff5f6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders completed an interview with Chiefs DL coach Joe Cullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a465-dc7a-af9b-efffe8bc0000</link>
      <description>Jacksonville’s defensive coordinator for one disastrous 2021 season with Urban Meyer, Cullen is a long-time NFL defensive line coach. If the Commanders went forward with him, it would likely be a nod to Dan Quinn continuing to call plays. Cullen has been Kansas City’s defensive line coach since 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a465-dc7a-af9b-efffe8bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) was downgraded to out for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against Chicago.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a469-d968-a19b-fcf9c3170000</link>
      <description>Initially questionable, Wicks did not clear concussion protocol today and has been downgraded to out. It’s a small silver of hope for Matthew Golden to be involved in the game plan against the Bears, though he certainly isn’t a recommended play given how his season went.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a469-d968-a19b-fcf9c3170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed their interview with former Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a460-d968-a19b-fcf1a5940000</link>
      <description>Varying explanations have been offered as to why the Ravens fired head coach John Harbaugh. Pairing QB Lamar Jackson with a creative, offensively-minded head coach, who is widely viewed as a quarterback guru, could make for a very fun match. Stefanski served as the Browns’ head coach from 2020-2025 after a successful 2019 season serving as the Vikings’ offensive coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a460-d968-a19b-fcf1a5940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s John Keim reports Dan Quinn “wanted a different offensive identity and spoke often with his staff of wanting a better run-pass balance.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a47d-d56e-afff-e6fd80d70000</link>
      <description>‘Bill’ Croskey-Merritt and restricted free agent Chris Rodriguez would stand to gain fantasy value if the Commanders focused on a more run-focused approach, as they seem like a team that has limited resources to dedicate to the running back position this offseason. It’s hard to speculate on who the Commanders could bring in to install a scheme that’s akin to what Quinn desires just based on the idea of more run-pass balance, but the search to replace Kliff Kingsbury looks destined to bring in someone with a more buttoned-up run game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a47d-d56e-afff-e6fd80d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Johnson (foot) is questionable for Philadelphia’s Wild Card game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a48c-d968-a19b-fcfd62b10000</link>
      <description>The veteran got in three limited sessions in his return from a midseason Lisfranc injury. We’d be surprised if he didn’t at least give it a go despite the questionable status. It would have been good to have seen a full practice at any time this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a48c-d968-a19b-fcfd62b10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
