<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (knee) is questionable to play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fad-d294-a19b-fffda5390000</link>
      <description>Williams briefly exited the 49ers’ Week 1 game against the Seahawks and exhibited a slight limp as he left the field. The 37-year-old blindside protector plays through injury whenever he can, so he seemingly has decent odds of suiting up. The Saints’ pushover pass rush will be without top EDGE Chase Young (calf), though, so the 49ers may be able to sneak past this opponent without Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fad-d294-a19b-fffda5390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fcd-dc44-a9d9-3fef924e0000</link>
      <description>The Rams entered the Week 2 practice week with their right tackle, RG Kevin Dotson and LG Steve Avila nursing ankle sprains. Good news for Matthew Stafford: Havenstein and Dotson have been cleared to play. The Titans’ pass rush is hardly a game-wrecker but it’s still nice to know that Stafford will have at least four-of-five starters in front of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fcd-dc44-a9d9-3fef924e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) has been removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fe7-dc44-a9d9-3fe757d50000</link>
      <description>Before injuring his ankle in mid-August, Watkins was competing for one of the team’s top-four wide receiver roles. Training camp reports indicated that the rookie looked good. Watkins is unlikely to meaningfully contribute this week but wide receiver-needy fantasy managers can stash him on benches to see how things shake out in the short term. 49ers RB Jordan James (finger) and will also make his 2025 debut this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fe7-dc44-a9d9-3fe757d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts worked out free agent LB Duke Riley on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4005-d86f-abdd-45bd9a500000</link>
      <description>Riley briefly signed on with the Commanders this summer but his time with them was short-lived. The Colts also worked out CB Shemar Bartholomew, LB Milo Eifler, LB David Long, LB Raekwon McMillan and LB Ty Summers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4005-d86f-abdd-45bd9a500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB Tyler Badie could have a featured role in the passing game due to the “amount of pressure looks” expected from Colts DC Lou Anarumo in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-400b-da67-a99f-ccffd1620000</link>
      <description>Badie took 7-of-16 third-down snaps and 6-of-9 two-minute drill snaps against the Titans in Week 1. The usage reduces both J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey’s fantasy-scoring potential, and unfortunately for fantasy managers, it appears as though that usage will hold in Week 2. Broncos head coach Sean Payton believes Badie is “good in the [blitz] pickups” and in the passing game overall. Payton spent “quite a bit of time” preparing for Anarumo’s “exotic looks” on second and particularly third down. Apparently, both Payton and OC Joe Lombardi think Badie is the man for the exotic job, rather than Dobbins, who is known for his pass-pro chops, and Harvey, who was heralded as one of the 2025 rookie class’ top receiving backs. Dobbins can be treated as a high-end RB3/FLEX while Harvey can be viewed as a borderline RB3/4. Badie is only a floor-based FLEX option in very deep PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-400b-da67-a99f-ccffd1620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-402c-d86f-abdd-45bdefbd0000</link>
      <description>Bobo and WR Dareke Young (hamstring) will both be available this weekend. Jaxon Smith-Njigba was the only Seahawk to earn more than three targets in Week 1, returning anyone even mildly capable to the lineup is a plus. Bobo will likely compete with rookie WR Tory Horton for WR3 duties. S Julian Love (groin) and DT Jarran Reed (back) are good to go as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-402c-d86f-abdd-45bdefbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Commanders RB Jacory Croskey-Merritt is “expected to be the starting running back” moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4024-d294-a19b-e4f48c2a0000</link>
      <description>Austin Ekeler suffered a non-contact lower-leg injury on Thursday that is believed to be a season-ending Achilles tendon rupture. He has not yet undergone an MRI, but as Rapoport notes, “it feels like everyone knows the results.” Croskey-Merritt has minimal experience in the passing game, so journeyman RB Jeremy McNichols will likely get the first shot at handling passing down duties. As evidenced by his first two NFL games, Croskey-Merritt’s weekly performance can be impacted by game script, operating largely in an early-down role. That said, he should at least see more opportunities on those downs with Ekeler sidelined, and Croskey-Merritt notably converted a third-and-short carry on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4024-d294-a19b-e4f48c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Packers believe WR Jayden Reed (collarbone) will return in early November.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-408e-d294-a19b-e4fe26df0000</link>
      <description>Reed will undergo surgery to repair his broken collarbone early next week, likely on Tuesday. The Packers’ star slot receiver will then rehab the injury for 6-8 weeks. It’s a lengthy absence, and one that is likely only navigable for fantasy managers possessing an open injured reserve spot. Unfortunately, the Packers will likely still be running their fantasy-unfriendly wide receiver rotation when he returns, and their established field-stretcher, WR Christian Watson (knee), could return from the reserve/physically unable to perform list before then, keeping Reed in the efficiency-based WR3/FLEX territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-408e-d294-a19b-e4fe26df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Browns RB Quinshon Judkins is expected to play in Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4372-da67-a99f-cff7999f0000</link>
      <description>Judkins is still officially listed as questionable, though it’s not injury-related. The 21-year-old running back from Ohio State missed all of training camp, but was able to practice on Thursday and Friday ahead of Week 2’s matchup with the Ravens. Judkins being active is significant for his season-long value, but it’s unclear how much work he might receive in his first game alongside Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford in the backfield. Sampson and Ford combined for 37 rushing yards on 18 carries against the Bengals in Week 1 and the Browns’ backfield has another difficult matchup on the ground against the Ravens on Sunday. Judkins or any Browns running back is likely best left on the bench this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4372-da67-a99f-cff7999f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Dolphins have no plans to trade WR Tyreek Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-437e-dc44-a9d9-477ee8720000</link>
      <description>Schefter goes as far as to say that the Dolphins haven’t received calls from any teams interested in Hill. His report flies in the face of a Pro Football Talk report earlier this week that said the Chiefs and Steelers were interested in the 31-year-old wide receiver. With Hill wearing out his welcome in Miami and the Dolphins season already nosediving, he’s an obvious trade candidate. The Chiefs make logical sense as a landing spot given that he’s played there before and the team has a need at wide receiver until Rashee Rice returns from suspension. Still, no trade appears imminent at this time and his value could be complicated by his recent domestic violence allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-437e-dc44-a9d9-477ee8720000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
