<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:07:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Vikings are “optimistic” about WR Jalen Nailor’s (hand) availability for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings recently brought back Adam Thielen via trade, with Jordan Addison set to serve a three-game suspension, and immediately listed Thielen as the fill-in No. 2 wide receiver. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that “Minnesota envisions a key role for Nailor, especially with Jordan Addison out via suspension,” but that’s tough to trust given his injury and the recent personnel development. Nailor is best-suited to single-game DFS lineups and should really only be considered for flex duties in 14-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Perrion Winfrey left practice early on Sunday after suffering a “low back” injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0160-d332-a1fd-9776e1290000</link>
      <description>Winfrey, 25, has had a bumpy ride in professional football, playing both in the NFL and UFL. He made it through final cuts, listed as a third-string defensive tackle. The Cowboys, now organizationally committed to stopping the run, need all the help they can get on the defensive line. Hopefully, Winfrey is available in Week 1, even if only for a handful of snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0160-d332-a1fd-9776e1290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed OG Kenyon Green to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-019b-d332-a1fd-97bf23e60000</link>
      <description>Green’s promotion coincides with OG/C Willie Lampkin being placed on injured reserve. Lampkin was waived by the Rams with an injury designation after suffering a preseason knee injury. Lampkin will be eligible to return after four games missed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-019b-d332-a1fd-97bf23e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles S Andrew Mukuba (groin) was seen in pads and is “ready to practice in some form today.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0131-db7b-a5dd-a13583db0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles drafted Mukuba in the second round this year. He was competing with Sydney Brown for one of the starting safety roles when he suffered a shoulder injury in late July. He later picked up a groin injury upon returning. Mukuba is likely slated for a backup role early in the year, but his draft capital should get him more opportunities to take over as a starter as the year progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0131-db7b-a5dd-a13583db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane reports that Eagles OG Landon Dickerson (knee) is “trending toward playing” in Week 1 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01a2-de13-afdd-47eb0df80000</link>
      <description>Dickerson recently underwent surgery to address a meniscus injury. It appears as though his rehab has gone very well. The three-time-defending Pro Bowl blocker should play a pivotal role as the Eagles likely attempt to ground-and-pound their way to victory in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01a2-de13-afdd-47eb0df80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bengals are utilizing RB Chase Brown “more split out wide versus linebackers” and have “restructured the run game specifically around his skill set.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01b7-dbe3-a9bb-31f7a17b0000</link>
      <description>Beat writers suggesting that a starting running back could line up as a receiver more often is a common theme among summer puff pieces. We should not fully expect Brown to suddenly be treated as a part-time wide receiver pre-snap, but it’s reasonable to believe that he could see increased passing game usage this season. Over the last three years, the Bengals have led the league in neutral game passing rates twice. Reports continue to suggest Brown will maintain a featured role while receiving RB Samaje Perine takes on a “lesser version” of his prior 3rd-down role. The Bengals’ ground game restructure also bodes positively for his rushing efficiency. Brown profiles as a high-upside RB1 available at the Rounds 2-3 turn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01b7-dbe3-a9bb-31f7a17b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee) said he is “unsure” of his availability for Week 1 but will play “no later than Week 4.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01f4-db7b-a5dd-a1f4dd470000</link>
      <description>That is a very wide range of potential outcomes, Mr. Diggs. For what it’s worth, the Cowboys’ cornerback is currently practicing in full. It’s anyone’s guess as to whether he will be cleared to play four days from now. The Cowboys’ defense sure could use reliable coverage defenders, with its pass rush now profiling as a potential liability on the front end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01f4-db7b-a5dd-a1f4dd470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT DeWayne Carter will miss the 2025 season after rupturing his Achilles tendon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01d7-db7b-a5dd-a1d706770000</link>
      <description>Carter missed multiple games with a wrist injury during his 2024 rookie season. He totaled 10 tackles and eight quarterback pressures while active. It’s a brutal blow for the former third-round pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01d7-db7b-a5dd-a1d706770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown (hamstring) said he will play in the Eagles’ Thursday Night Football game against the Cowboys in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0227-db7b-a5dd-a2278f450000</link>
      <description>The Eagles handled Brown’s hamstring rehab conservatively, and he’s been able to continue practicing without issue since last Wednesday. Barring a setback, Brown can be started as a safe WR1 against a Cowboys defense that will struggle to rush the passer. If the Cowboys’ offense can keep things competitive, Brown could have quite the busy night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0227-db7b-a5dd-a2278f450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers DE Derrick Brown “has continued to impress this summer and should be a force” in his return from last year’s season-ending knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0210-db7b-a5dd-a214dca80000</link>
      <description>Brown was sidelined for the entirety of the 2024 season after undergoing surgery to repair a meniscus tear that he suffered in Week 1. Brown has been a “high-impact player” for years, notably setting the defensive linemen record for tackles in a single season (103) in 2023. The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports, “judging by conversations with those around him this season, it doesn’t sound like there’s any dropoff in sight.” Brown was held out of preseason play due to a separaterib/obliqueissue, but there are no indications that Brown’s Week 1 availability is in question. The Panthers’ defensive leader will have a busy day, attempting to contain the Jaguars’ three-deep rushing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0210-db7b-a5dd-a214dca80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
