<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers released WR Mecole Hardman.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6f9-de13-afdc-e6fbebbc0000</link>
      <description>Hardman was a long shot to make the Packers even as a quality special teams player, as there are too many bodies in the Green Bay receiving room. It’s possible he could be a target for the practice squad, but it’s likely someone will give Hardman a chance to return kicks on the active roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6f9-de13-afdc-e6fbebbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed LB Jaylon Carlies (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e702-de13-afdc-e7cb2bf00000</link>
      <description>He was expected to be the other starting Colts linebacker next to Zaire Franklin, but Carlies did not play a single preseason snap while dealing with recovery from an offseason shoulder surgery. Carlies will miss at least the first four weeks of the season. Longtime Bengal Joe Bachie might be the favorite to step in as Indy’s LB2 at the start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e702-de13-afdc-e7cb2bf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released S Jalen Mills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e702-de13-afdc-e7cb3dd10000</link>
      <description>Mills logged two tackles and one interception through two preseason games with the Texans. He spent 2024 with the Jets. The veteran safety has decent odds of finding a spot on a final roster at some point this year, though a practice squad spot is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e702-de13-afdc-e7cb3dd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released QB Kedon Slovis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e700-d332-a1fd-f7365d1b0000</link>
      <description>Slovis was unable to make the Texans to the surprise of absolutely no one. The 24-year-old is a candidate for the practice squad of Houston or another team looking for signal-caller depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e700-d332-a1fd-f7365d1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived WR A.T. Perry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e708-db7b-a5dd-e70c9e160000</link>
      <description>Perry, 25, has been unavailable this summer due to an undisclosed injury. The former sixth-round selection is certainly a candidate for the Broncos’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e708-db7b-a5dd-e70c9e160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released RB Pierre Strong Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e707-db7b-a5dd-e707e5030000</link>
      <description>This move is a bit surprising with Quinshon Judkins still unsigned. Perhaps that signing is just around the corner, or the team just feels good about Jerome Ford and Dylan Sampson. In two preseason games, Strong rushed 18 times for 18 yards and caught 5-of-6 targets for 28 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e707-db7b-a5dd-e707e5030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints released RB Clyde Edwards-Helaire</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e70a-de13-afdc-e7cb446b0000</link>
      <description>It’s possible that this is just a short-term move the Saints have made knowing that nobody else is going to pick up Edwards-Helaire, and that they’ll sign him back to the practice squad or 53-man roster. CE-H played 33 snaps for the Saints in the preseason and is a logical third-down back fit behind Alvin Kamara, with the only problem being Kamara doesn’t really need to be taken off the field on third down. If the Saints decline to bring Edwards-Helaire back, Kendre Miller and Devin Neal will likely back up Kamara.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e70a-de13-afdc-e7cb446b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans released TE Josh Whyle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e710-dbe3-a9bb-f75331ca0000</link>
      <description>Whyle got quite a bit of run in Week 18’s loss to the Texans, leading Tennessee with seven targets as they helped clinch the pick that delivered Cam Ward. The Titans then blocked him with fourth-rounder Gunnar Helm and decided Whyle was expendable. Entering his age-26 season, Whyle will be a candidate to catch on elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e710-dbe3-a9bb-f75331ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Asante Samuel Jr. (neck) will undergo a CT scan in October to ensure “successful spinal fusion.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e715-dbe3-a9bb-f757e3e90000</link>
      <description>Samuel Jr. won’t attempt to sign with a team until the second half of the season. The former Chargers standout has been stellar on the field, but missed most of last season with this injury and looks poised to try to rebuild his value for 2026 free agency with a small cameo in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e715-dbe3-a9bb-f757e3e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
