<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Ravens are blocking special teams coordinator Chris Horton from accepting a lateral position with another team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddd2-d35e-a1bf-ddd26e170000</link>
      <description>Horton has been the Ravens’ special teams coordinator for the past six seasons and the team would like to have the option of retaining him under the impending head coaching hire. He can only leave for roles that are promotions from his current job. Garafolo reports “Assistant Anthony Levine Sr. and senior ST coach Randy Brown might also be retained, pending the new HC hire.” As Baltimore gets closer to a head coaching hire, decisions are being made about the surrounding staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddd2-d35e-a1bf-ddd26e170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Networks’ Mike Garafolo reports the Packers will interview former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddf9-dc7a-af9b-dfffd4e70000</link>
      <description>Gannon let go by the Cardinals after three underwhelming seasons as head coach. He previously spent two seasons as the Eagles’ defensive coordinator, making the Super Bowl in that time. The Cowboys have already interviewed Gannon, who will talk to Green Bay for the potential to work with Micah Parsons and the Packer defense. With Jeff Hafley leaving to coach the Dolphins, the Packers have a vacancy that could be filled by Gannon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddf9-dc7a-af9b-dfffd4e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel is “expected to become” the Chargers’ new offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de4a-dc7a-af9b-dfff82cb0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers have won the Mike McDaniel sweepstakes, expecting to hire the former Dolphins head coach to their open offensive coordinator role. Several teams were in on the 42-year-old, who was interviewing for both head coaching and offensive coordinator roles. According to Schefter, McDaniel is informing teams they are out and staying in Los Angeles for the evening with the expectation he is the next Chargers’ offensive coordinator. For fantasy purposes, we are in for a faster-paced offense under Justin Herbert. Omarion Hampton is in line for more opportunity in the passing game while the wide receiver room gets better opportunities in McDaniel’s offense when compared to former offensive coordinator Greg Roman’s passing game concepts. Fantasy managers can expect to be more bullish on Herbert and the Chargers offense for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de4a-dc7a-af9b-dfff82cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers beat writer Mark Kaboly reports the Falcons will interview Steelers assistant general manager Andy Weidl for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de9f-d968-a19b-deff8d2a0000</link>
      <description>Weidl spent the last four seasons as the Steelers’ assistant general manager. According to Kaboly, he “is a well-respected personnel evaluator around league circles.” Having spent 27 years in the NFL, Weidl brings experience to a Falcons front office led by President of Football Matt Ryan. The Falcons will interview Weidl for general manager after the team hired Kevin Stefanski as its new head coach. With that role filled, the general manager candidate interviews will come quicker for a potential hire soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de9f-d968-a19b-deff8d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Falcons are interviewing Buccaneers wide receivers coach Bryan McClendon for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-deb4-d56e-afff-fefcc0370000</link>
      <description>McClendon has been with the Bucs for the past two seasons, helping develop the likes of Jalen McMillan and Emeka Egbuka in the wide receiver room, alongside vets Mike Evans and Chris Godwin. The Falcons are conducting offensive coordinator interviews under new head coach Kevin Stefanski. McClendon will interview with the chance to develop Drake London and Bijan Robinson’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-deb4-d56e-afff-fefcc0370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested an interview with Colts defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0b8-dc7a-af9b-efbfa3c10000</link>
      <description>Anarumo, 59, is once again a popular head coaching candidate, landing interviews with the Titans and Giants before those teams filled their head coaching spots with Robert Saleh and John Harbaugh, respectively. Buffalo is seeking a new head coach after firing Sean McDernmott, one of the league’s winningest coaches over the past decade. The Colts under Anarumo in 2025 finished 23rd in yards allowed and 21st in points allowed, with their best finish in any category being allowing only 3.9 rushing yards per attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0b8-dc7a-af9b-efbfa3c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan said he wants build a team that can win in cold weather.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0dc-d56e-afff-e6fcafb20000</link>
      <description>Sullivan said the goal in the coming years is to put together a roster of players who can win in Buffalo, New York, and New England in the second half of the season. The Dolphins, practicing and living in Miami, have traditionally been a miserable cold-weather team, leading to a number of late-season collapses going back to the Marino era. Sullivan’s comments echo newly hired head coach Jeff Sullivan, who reportedly wants to ditch the team’s emphasis on speed for size and physicality. “Our division runs through Buffalo and New England and New York, cold-weather places,” Sullivan said. “There’s a saying in our business, fast gets slow but big doesn’t get small. We’re not going to sacrifice speed and explosion and skill for a bunch of big stiff guys, but we’re going to have substance to us at all levels of our team. At corner, at receiver, at running back, and certainly up front. It starts with the quarterback, and then we’ll build this team from the inside out. We’ve got to be dominant on the offensive line, dominant on the defensive line.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0dc-d56e-afff-e6fcafb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested an interview with Jaguars offensive coordinator Grant Udinski for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0e2-dc7a-af9b-efff7a2a0000</link>
      <description>Udinski, 30, is just a few months older than Bills QB Josh Allen and would represent a massive shift for Buffalo after the team fired longtime defense-oriented head coach Sean McDermott, one of the most successful coaches in the NFL over the past decade. Udinski has interviewed for the Browns head coaching job after a 2025 season in which he helped make Jacksonville’s offense one of the most productive in football. Udinski would make for an interesting hire if the Bills are ready to get back to the pass-first approach that made them lethal in 2020 and 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0e2-dc7a-af9b-efff7a2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested an interview with former Giants head coach Brian Daboll for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0e8-d35e-a1bf-e5ea8b010000</link>
      <description>Daboll served as Buffalo’s offensive coordinator from 2018 to 2021 before landing the Giants head coaching job. Daboll’s Bills offense was top-five in both yards and points in both 2020 and 2021 as the team shifted to a more pass-first offense with Josh Allen under center. Daboll’s success with Allen could land him the top job in the coming days and weeks as the Bills interview potential replacements for Sean McDermott. That includes 30-year-old Jacksonville OC Grant Udinski and Colts DC Lou Anarumo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e0e8-d35e-a1bf-e5ea8b010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested an interview with Dolphins defensive coordinator Anthony Weaver for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e10d-d968-a19b-f9fd976c0000</link>
      <description>Weaver is suddenly a popular name among teams looking to fill head coaching jobs in the coming days and weeks. Weaver, Miami’s defensive coordinator over the past two seasons, has talked to the Ravens and Steelers about their head coaching vacancies and will now enter the fray as Buffalo’s potential top guy after the team fired Sean McDermott. The Bills are also interviewing former Giants head coach Brian Daboll and Jaguars OC Grant Udinsky. Weaver’s Miami defense over the past two seasons has given up the league’s ninth highest EPA per play and seventh highest offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e10d-d968-a19b-f9fd976c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
