<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets waived QB Adrian Martinez.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</link>
      <description>Martinez is a practice squad candidate, but the Jets may choose to go with Brady Cook as the third quarterback behind Josh Fields and Tyrod Taylor. New York also waived LB Jamin Davis, DE Michael Fletcher, T Liam Forandel, T Samuel Jackson, TE Zach Kuntz, DB Tanner McCalister and RB Lawrance Toafili.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s John Shipley believes “the Jaguars will look to unload” either Travis Etienne Jr. or Tank Bigsby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</link>
      <description>Shipley adds that if the Jaguars’ trade efforts are unsuccessful, he thinks they will carry Etienne, Bigsby and rookies Bhayshul Tuten and LeQuint Allen Jr. on the final roster and make “one of the two rookies inactive on game day.” Etienne regularly took passing down snaps during preseason play. While Tuten’s explosive traits make him an all-around breakout candidate, it’s possible Allen could sneak into a specialized passing down role if Etienne ends up being traded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Archer of ESPN reports that the Cowboys are releasing OT La’el Collins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</link>
      <description>Collins was signed at the start of August to add depth, but the 32-year-old didn’t do enough in his limited time with Dallas to make the 53-man roster. Collins could be of interest for a team in need of depth, but is unlikely to be more than one of the last few players on the roster as long as he’s still playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers waived CB Tre Avery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dde4-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7658a0000</link>
      <description>Avery signed with the Buccaneers just two days ago and racked up seven tackles in the team’s preseason Week 3 game against the Bills on Saturday. He spent the first two preseason games on the Patriots’ roster, totaling five tackles and one forced incompletion with them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dde4-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7658a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that the Bills are expected to re-sign DT Jordan Phillips later this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</link>
      <description>Phillips worked out with the Bills today, and evidently, it went well. The 32-year-old previously played for the Bills in 2019 and from 2022-2023. He spent the 2024 season with the Cowboys. He can be expected to serve as a rotational player on the Bills’ interior defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Tomasson of the Denver Gazette reports that the Broncos waived WR Joaquin Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</link>
      <description>Davis caught one pass for 14 yards after being added as an undrafted free agent by the Broncos. The 6-foot-4 wideout is likely to hang around on the practice squad. Denver also waived linebacker Andrew Farmer according to Tomasson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Patriots are “shopping” S Kyle Dugger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de1f-de13-afdc-dedf3fb00000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s report backs up what Jordan Schultz reported on August 20th. The Patriots’ new coaching staff is hoping to move on from Dugger. Earlier today, ESPN’s Mike Reissreportedthat it has been a “challenging year” for Dugger, who underwent offseason ankle surgery and has played “deep into preseason games” this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de1f-de13-afdc-dedf3fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions released CB Dicaprio Bootle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de17-d332-a1fd-de37c7200000</link>
      <description>Bootle, 27, was signed in the middle of July, and didn’t stick around past the summer. The speedy corner will now be free to sign with another team, but is likely just roster-fodder at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de17-d332-a1fd-de37c7200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived CB Micah Abraham.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de44-dbe3-a9bb-fe57c8830000</link>
      <description>Abraham suited up for two Broncos preseason games this year, allowing one catch for nine yards on two targets. He recorded zero tackles. The 2024 sixth-round pick will now look to make a final roster elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de44-dbe3-a9bb-fe57c8830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars traded T Fred Johnson to the Eagles in exchange for for a 2026 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de5b-d332-a1fd-de7ff04b0000</link>
      <description>Johnson returns to the Eagles after signing with the Jaguars in March. The 28-year-old will likely be a backup bookend for Philadelphia; a role that he served for the majority of the 2024 season with the club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-de5b-d332-a1fd-de7ff04b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
