<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:11:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders CB Mike Sainristil (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1df-d6e9-af9d-abdf430e0000</link>
      <description>Sainristil was a new addition to the injury report this week, nursing a knee issue. The 24-year-old intercepted a pass last week and is one of the team’s starting cornerbacks. If he cannot go in Week 5, the Commanders will turn to Noah Igbinoghene for help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1df-d6e9-af9d-abdf430e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavien Howard retired after nine seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1ef-dca3-a9fb-bdfffe3e0000</link>
      <description>The Colts placed CB Xavien Howard on the reserve/retired list after a subpar four game start from the 32-year-old veteran. Howard spent last season unsigned, but had an illustrious eight seasons with the Dolphins before. He made four Pro Bowls throughout his career, tallying 95 passes defended, 29 interceptions, and 342 combined tackles through nine seasons. Howard was once one of the best cornerbacks in the league, getting a first-team All-Pro selection in 2020. He ends his NFL career after attempting to jumpstart it with the Colts, but having made a significant impact to the Dolphins teams of the late 2010s and early 2020s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a1ef-dca3-a9fb-bdfffe3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a200-dca3-a9fb-bf99e8ef0000</link>
      <description>Dissly has missed the last two weeks due to a knee issue. He starts out Week 5 practicing, putting him on track to return against the Commanders this week, or against the Dolphins next week. Dissly’s absence has led to an uptick in opportunities for Oronde Gadsden, but a potential Dissly return would decrease those looks for Gadsden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a200-dca3-a9fb-bf99e8ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders opened the 21-day practice window for OL Sam Cosmi (knee).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a20f-d95b-addb-ea4fb26a0000</link>
      <description>Cosmi suffered a torn ACL in the Divisional Round last season and began this season on the PUP list. He was a full participant in practice on Wednesday as the Commanders opened his 21-day practice window. Cosmi may not return immediately in Week 5, but should be back in the offensive line rotation within the next three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a20f-d95b-addb-ea4fb26a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Michael Carter said he will be starting for the team when speaking to reporters Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a212-deb6-a7fd-f3df6edb0000</link>
      <description>When asked about his journey to signing with the active Cardinals roster, Carter said, “It’s been a lot...go from Pat Tillman one week to starting the next.” The Cardinals’ “Pat Tillman” designation is for the Scout Player of the Week. Carter may have let slip about the Cardinals’ backfield rotation for Week 5, saying he will be “starting the next.” We don’t know how an Emari Demercado - Michael Carter backfield will look like, but Carter certainly believes he will be starting. Head coach Jonathan Gannon said there is a chance we see all three backs, adding Bam Knight into the mix. This is a messy situation for fantasy managers, but it seems Demercado will take passing-down work while Carter has more of the early-down work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a212-deb6-a7fd-f3df6edb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (knee/biceps) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a21f-deb6-a7fd-f3dfd5d20000</link>
      <description>Mayfield starts out the week not practicing, a downgrade from last week when he started out the week as a limited participant. He played through a right biceps injury last week, but now has a knee injury added to his practice designation. Mayfield has gritted out injuries before, but having two separate body parts listed on the injury report and starting out the week not practicing is a concerning sign. Head coach Todd Bowles made Wednesday a walkthrough practice, citing lack of healthy players. Full-speed practices from later in the week will tell if Mayfield’s injuries are truly a concern or not for Week 5 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a21f-deb6-a7fd-f3dfd5d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers Sterling Shepard (foot) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a226-dca3-a9fb-bfbfb5910000</link>
      <description>Shepard joined a long list of Bucs players not practicing on Wednesday with a foot issue. The veteran has been a small cog in the Bucs’ offense, though with Mike Evans’ hamstring injury keeping him sidelined, Shepard was in line for more snaps. A potential Shepard absence could mean even more opportunities for Emeka Egbuka and Chris Godwin come Sunday against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a226-dca3-a9fb-bfbfb5910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers CB Jamel Dean (hip) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a22d-deb6-a7fd-f3ffcacc0000</link>
      <description>Dean left the Bucs’ Week 4 loss to the Eagles with a groin injury that now seems to be more of a hip issue. Also not practicing were CB Benjamin Morrison (hamstring) and DB Christian Izien (quad). If none of the trio can practice the rest of the week, the Bucs’ secondary will look depleted against the Seahawks for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a22d-deb6-a7fd-f3ffcacc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a23c-d95b-addb-ea7e7b790000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon played last Thursday after recovering from the knee injury, so his non-participation may be more precautionary than a concern. Practice reports later in the week will tell if he is in jeopardy to miss Week 5 against the Bucs. S Julian Love (hamstring) and DE Demarcus Lawrence (quad) were also both non-participants and the Seahawks defense enters the week a little banged up. On the positive side, S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) was a full participant after missing each of the last three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a23c-d95b-addb-ea7e7b790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a248-d6e9-af9d-aad8c09a0000</link>
      <description>Bowers has been nursing his knee injury since Week 1 and starts out this week as a limited practice participant. He likely felt soreness between the Raiders’ 4 loss to the Bears and Wednesday, causing him to be limited, compared to last week when he started out as a full practice participant. Bowers’ knee injury still seems to be hampering him as his usage has not been high volume. Fellow TE Michael Mayer (concussion) was a limited participant in practice after missing Week 4. Between Mayer’s potential return and middling usage amid the knee injury, there is reason to be concerned about Bowers’ fantasy outlook, though he is still a fantasy TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a248-d6e9-af9d-aad8c09a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
