<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts ruled out RT Braden Smith (concussion/neck) for Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13b2-d77b-adfb-dbb3e3400000</link>
      <description>The Colts will be without their starting right tackle for Sunday’s road game against a stout Seahawks defense. Backup Jalen Travis is expected to draw the start in his place and will be tasked with keeping one of either Riley Leonard or Philip Rivers upright. In addition to Smith, the Colts also ruled out WR Anthony Gould (ankle) and CB Sauce Gardner (calf).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13b2-d77b-adfb-dbb3e3400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said there’s “no quarterback decision just yet” when asked who will start Week 15’s game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13ba-d8cf-affb-bfba81670000</link>
      <description>Riley Leonard (knee) has practiced in full all week, so it sure seems like he’d be available to go if the Colts wanted him to. Of course, if they really wanted him to go, they probably would not have signed a 44-year-old grandfather in the first place. So there’s that. We’ll likely get a report that Rivers will start at some point in the next 36 hours. He’s not to be trusted in superflex leagues in his first start in five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13ba-d8cf-affb-bfba81670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeForest Buckner (neck) will not play in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13bc-d1bc-a3fb-97bc6dbc0000</link>
      <description>Bucker’s 21-day return window was opened earlier this week, but the veteran lineman will miss at least one more game before being activated. Buckner hasn’t played since Week 9 but can be activated any time over the next three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13bc-d1bc-a3fb-97bc6dbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Denzel Ward (calf) won’t play in Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13be-d77b-adfb-dbbf92a30000</link>
      <description>Ward did not practice at any point this week since suffering the injury in Week 14. He certainly could be a candidate for an IR shut down with the Browns eliminated from the playoffs. Ward has had the worst PFF coverage grade of his career so far in 2025, at 54.4 in 701 defensive snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13be-d77b-adfb-dbbf92a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) will not play in Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c0-d8cf-affb-bfeaebda0000</link>
      <description>Njoku did not practice all week after re-aggravating the injury in Week 14’s game against the Titans. He had played through the knee listing for a few weeks. It’s possible that Njoku gets shut down for the season with Cleveland eliminated from the playoffs. This rule out is great news for Harold Fannin’s Week 15 prospects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c0-d8cf-affb-bfeaebda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (calf/hand) will not play in Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c3-d005-a9bf-dbf7d3e60000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week after having the “hand” listing added to his injury on Wednesday. Raheim Sanders and Trayveon Williams will back up Quinshon Judkins in Week 15, with neither player approaching the FLEX conversation at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c3-d005-a9bf-dbf7d3e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (concussion) will not play in Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c6-d005-a9bf-dbf60ccc0000</link>
      <description>That makes two weeks in a row where Conklin will sit with a concussion, and he didn’t practice all week. Joel Bitonio (knee/back) is questionable after not practicing either of the first two days, while Wyatt Teller (calf) remains out. Cleveland’s OL injuries are dire enough that we must point out that Zak Zinter (back) is also questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c6-d005-a9bf-dbf60ccc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Cedric Tillman (concussion/rib) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c8-d005-a9bf-dbfc72fb0000</link>
      <description>Tillman didn’t practice either of the first two sessions of the week, but has a chance to play. He doesn’t have much of a fantasy role at this point, as the Browns can only reliably count on Harold Fannin and Jerry Jeudy to deliver actual production. Tillman has not scored since September 14 and hasn’t cracked 55 yards all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c8-d005-a9bf-dbfc72fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ J.J. Watt reports T.J. Watt “had successful surgery to stabilize and repair a partially collapsed lung” on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c2-d1bc-a3fb-97e65c890000</link>
      <description>According to Watt, the Steelers’ pass-rusher suffered a collapsed lung during a “dry needling treatment session at the facility.” Watt’s recovery time is unknown, but it’s safe to assume he will miss the Week 15 game against the Dolphins. Watt isexpected to returnat some point this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13c2-d1bc-a3fb-97e65c890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) won’t play in New England’s Week 15 game against Buffalo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13cb-d77b-adfb-dbcbade60000</link>
      <description>D’Ernest Johnson will be the name that neither Rhamondre Stevenson nor Treyveon Henderson-reliant managers want to see on the field on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13cb-d77b-adfb-dbcbade60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
