<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Baker Mayfield (shoulder) is trending toward playing in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cb98-d90e-a9da-df9f33360000</link>
      <description>Mayfield took the field on back-to-back days to close out the week of practice, and looked good in his final session, per Bowles. The Buccaneers’ signal-caller exited in the first half of last week’s loss to the Rams due to a sprained AC joint, but the fact that the injury is to his non-throwing shoulder was an obvious good sign. We’ll get his Week 13 game status soon, but Mayfield being active would be a good sign for his fantasy managers, and anybody rostering Emeka Egbuka.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cb98-d90e-a9da-df9f33360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interim HC Mike Kafka confirmed Jaxson Dart will start in Week 13 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cba1-d82c-a79a-fbb5d63c0000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after it was announced on Thursday that Dart cleared the league’s concussion protocol. The rookie signal-caller is expected to take first-team reps with the offense for the remainder of the week in the days leading up to Monday night’s tilt with the Patriots. Dart finished as a top-12 fantasy QB in four of his last five starts and will profile as a high-end QB2 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cba1-d82c-a79a-fbb5d63c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn (concussion) won’t play in Carolina’s Week 13 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cba5-db57-afda-dfb7c75c0000</link>
      <description>Not that life was going to be hard for Puka Nacua and Davante Adams, but this would seem to make it even easier. Carolina’s highly-paid corner did not practice at any point this week and will need to clear concussion protocol by next Friday to get on the field for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cba5-db57-afda-dfb7c75c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said he expects Terry McLaurin (quad) to play in Week 13 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbab-d6c4-abfb-dfabb5ce0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin has practiced all week and is in line to make his return since last appearing in Week 8’s loss to the Chiefs. It’s already a lost season for the Commanders and McLaurin, who has caught just 13 passes for 203 yards and one touchdown in the four games he’s appeared in this season. Assuming he’s active, he’ll profile as a WR3 against a stout Broncos defense with Marcus Mariota under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbab-d6c4-abfb-dfabb5ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said WR Jermaine Burton (ankle) is “week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbaa-db57-afda-dfba143e0000</link>
      <description>The 80th overall pick of the 2024 draft class has fallen behind Mitchell Tinsley in the pecking order and has not received a snap yet this season after spending most of last year as the guy the coaching staff was willing to call out for showing up late and not working hard enough. This has little fantasy impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbaa-db57-afda-dfba143e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen confirmed Daniel Jones (fibula) will start in Week 13 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbbb-d82c-a79a-fbbfc8b60000</link>
      <description>This comes a day after it was reported that Jones would attempt to play through the injury, so this news doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Jones reported “looked good” in practice, although it’s worth noting that some reps we saw in videos that surfaced online looked questionable at best. Jones will need to be at the top of his game against a Texans defense that ranks sixth in the league in sacks and brought down Josh Allen a season-high five times in Week 12. Jones will be a risky QB2 for fantasy this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbbb-d82c-a79a-fbbfc8b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers HC Mike Tomlin said Aaron Rodgers (wrist) will start in Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc2-d90e-a9da-dfcf10f70000</link>
      <description>He’ll be on the superflex QB2 line against the Bills, but the Steelers will probably run the ball plenty on Buffalo’s diminshed front seven. Rodgers has become a checkdown and screen merchant with Arthur Smith’s offense and we don’t expect him to suddenly start pushing the ball more now that he’s playing through a fractured wrist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc2-d90e-a9da-dfcf10f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared CB Tyrique Stevenson, LB Ruben Hyppolite, DL Dominique Robinson, WR Jahdae Walker, LB Noah Sewell, LB T.J. Edwards and QB Case Keenum inactive for Chicago’s Week 13 game against the Eagles</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc1-db57-afda-dff3d8b60000</link>
      <description>Kyler Gordon and Jaylon Johnson were both activated from injured reserve and will play, but the Bears are still down Stevenson after a hip injury and light their three linebackers who were all ruled out on Thursday. Robinson is dealing with a concussion. The other two players are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc1-db57-afda-dff3d8b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Sam Howell, LB Joshua Uche, DT Ty Robinson, CB Mac McWilliams, OT Lane Johnson, WR Xavier Gipson, and RB A.J. Dillon inactive for Week 13 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc3-db57-afda-dff343e70000</link>
      <description>Johnson is the only notable player on this list, and he was ruled out on Thursday. The Eagles are operating at near full strength as they prepare to host the 8-3 Bears in a clash of division leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc3-db57-afda-dff343e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lane Johnson (foot) is targeting Philadelphia’s Week 15 game against the Raiders for a return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbd2-d6c4-abfb-dfd3560a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson left Week 11’s game against the Lions with the injury and this would set him up to miss three games before returning. The Eagles have struggled on offense without Johnson, though they’ve really struggled with consistency all year so that’s not a major surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbd2-d6c4-abfb-dfd3560a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
