<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 22:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said he’s “optimistic” about Terry McLaurin (quad) for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb13-d94a-a79d-bb1f446f0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders do have an extra day of rest ahead of Monday Night Football. It is worth pointing out that Quinn said McLaurin was “trending in the right direction” last week before a DNP-DNP-Ruleout, so the optimism doesn’t exactly mean much until we see McLaurin in practice. Still, it doesn’t sound like this will drag on too much longer based on reports from ESPN last week and we’d anticipate McLaurin showing up in Week 6 or Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb13-d94a-a79d-bb1f446f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said Carson Wentz (shoulder) is “being further evaluated.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb1c-d94a-a79d-bb1d78690000</link>
      <description>Wentz briefly left Week 5’s game in England with the shoulder injury, but it happened close enough to halftime that the Vikings didn’t actually do much without Wentz on the field. The Vikings are on bye, and the fact that he was able to play through it in Week 5 is encouraging, but there’s no such thing as a good “further evaluation” in the NFL. Wentz being hurt would make turning the keys back over to J.J. McCarthy easier after Wentz went 2-1 over three games, assuming McCarthy comes back healed from his high-ankle sprain, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb1c-d94a-a79d-bb1d78690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said Tyjae Spears’ role will see an increased role going forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baf8-d94a-a79d-bbfdd98a0000</link>
      <description>This is a true “take it with a grain of salt” statement from Callahan. Spears played on 17 snaps in his Week 5 return and saw exactly zero targets. If his role didn’t increase beyond what we saw in Week 5, then Spears would have no role. With that in mind, it’s worth keeping in mind what Spears’ role looked like under Callahan last season. He averaged just 9.5 opportunities per game in 2024 which made him nearly impossible to trust for fantasy, but averaged 16.3 opportunities per game in the final three weeks of a lost season. Spears is a worthwhile stash in deeper leagues, but still faces competition for touches from Tony Pollard and plays in one of the worst offenses in the league. It’s hard to imagine there being much, if any, weekly upside here as long as Pollard is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baf8-d94a-a79d-bbfdd98a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Matt Milano (pectoral) aggravated his injury in Week 5 and is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb28-db72-a199-fb6bbfaf0000</link>
      <description>That almost assures we won’t see any Milano this week. Milano has just a 34.2 PFF grade while struggling through three games on injury and wasn’t much better last year — he simply hasn’t been the same player he was in 2022 in a long time at this point. The Bills should probably consider an IR stint to just get him as healthy as he can be for a playoff run, so McDermott naturally said that IR is not a consideration at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb28-db72-a199-fb6bbfaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (ankle) will practice following the team’s Week 6 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2b-db72-a199-fb6bd6cb0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy was expected to practice late last week, but some inclement weather on Friday kept the QB sidelined out of precaution. In addition to McCarthy, O’Connell also said LG Donovan Jackson, C Michael Jurgens, and LB Blake Cashman are also expected to practice after the team’s Week 6 bye. With a Week 7 game against the Eagles on the horizon, the hope is that the Vikings will have several key players back in a pivotal NFC matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2b-db72-a199-fb6bd6cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Omarion Hampton (ankle) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-d94a-a79d-bb2f3f600000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games. It’s devastating fantasy news as Hampton had just taken on a more-or-less full-time role in Los Angeles’ backfield. Without him, they’ll form a committee with Hassan Haskins and Kimani Vidal leading the way. Haskins is probably the better bet for fantasy managers since he has actually spent some of this year on the roster. We would not expect miracles out of either player, but a Week 6 matchup with the team that brought you “Rico Dowdle, 200-yard rusher” should make Haskins a borderline RB2/FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-d94a-a79d-bb2f3f600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles listed Saquon Barkley (knee) as DNP on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-db72-a199-fb6f999c0000</link>
      <description>It’s only an estimated report, but an estimated DNP is still concerning for Barkley, who has struggled on the ground to start the season. We’ll see if things change come Tuesday when the Eagles actually hold a practice, but this is clearly something worth monitoring until we receive word that Barkley is in the clear for Thursday night’s game against the Giants. If Barkley is unable to go, A.J. Dillon could be in line to handle early-down touches while Will Shipley mixes in on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-db72-a199-fb6f999c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nakobe Dean (knee) was listed as a full participant on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb5c-dd4c-afb9-ffddb43d0000</link>
      <description>Dean returned to practice last week in a limited capacity but was upgraded to full by the end of the week. The fact that he was limited as a full participant to start this week is an encouraging sign for his Week 6 availability, but the Eagles still have time to delay his return if they don’t think he’ll be ready to play on a short week. Dean totaled 128 tackles and three sacks in a breakout 2024 performance. When he returns, he should slot in as the Eagles’ No. 1 inside linebacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb5c-dd4c-afb9-ffddb43d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Saquon Barkley (knee) “had general soreness” after Week 5’s loss to the Broncos but expects to play in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb64-dd4c-afb9-ffe5ca300000</link>
      <description>The Eagles had fans and fantasy managers buzzing on Monday when they listed Barkley as a DNP due to a knee injury. That said, this appears to be a very minor issue, and any decision to sit Barkley early in practice is out of precaution. We’ll be sure to monitor his status throughout the week, but we’d expect Barkley to be ready to go come Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb64-dd4c-afb9-ffe5ca300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
