<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Omarion Hampton (ankle) will undergo more testing to determine the severity of his injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9ea-dd4c-afb9-ffebb5200000</link>
      <description>Hampton is at risk of missing some time after being spotted in a walking boot following Week 5’s loss to the Commanders, but we could have a better sense of his return timeline once we know more about the severity of his injury. Any length of absence would be tough for a Chargers team that has been dealt long-term injuries to several key offensive players already, including Najee Harris, whose season ended in Week 3 due to a torn Achilles. We’ll hopefully have more information on Hampton soon, but if he were to miss any time, the Chargers would be looking at Kimani Vidal and Hassan Haskins as their top two backs heading into Week 6 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9ea-dd4c-afb9-ffebb5200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports it’s “more likely than not” that Travon Walker (wrist) will miss Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba22-d94a-a79d-bb2fe8920000</link>
      <description>Walker underwent surgery on his wrist last week. While the star pass rusher is not expected to be out long-term, a one-game absence was always the most likely outcome. According to Rapoport, the Jaguars will allow Walker to decide how he feels before game time, but added that Walker seems like a “long shot” to play at this point. Walker has totaled 12 tackles, two TFLs, and two sacks in four games this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba22-d94a-a79d-bb2fe8920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers designated WR Christian Watson (knee) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba2d-def2-abdb-bf6d4c980000</link>
      <description>Watson was on the practice field Monday, marking his first practice since tearing his ACL in Week 18 of last season. The Packers now have 21 days to activate Watson from injured reserve, and given the nature of his injury and his extended time away, it wouldn’t be surprising if they used every day available to them to ramp Watson up before his return. The fourth-year receiver caught 29 passes for 620 yards and two touchdowns in 15 games last season while seeing just 53 targets. He’ll help add another deep element to Green Bay’s passing attack, but Watson has been very boom-or-bust for fantasy managers for much of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba2d-def2-abdb-bf6d4c980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Tom (oblique) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba40-def2-abdb-bf6154ea0000</link>
      <description>We don’t know the capacity in which Tom practiced, but after two weeks off, it’s possible Tom could be in line to return for Week 6 against the Bengals. The Packers don’t need to release an official injury report until Wednesday, but his return following a Week 5 bye is a good sign to start the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba40-def2-abdb-bf6154ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts K Spencer Shrader (knee) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba5d-db72-a199-fa5f5e4d0000</link>
      <description>The first report of Shrader’s season-ending injury came from The Pat McAfee Show. Shrader, who has made 13-of-14 field goals for the Colts this season, exited Week 5’s game against the Raiders after a defender collided with his knee. It didn’t look good the moment it happened, so the season-ending report doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Shrader reportedly tore multiple ligaments in his knee, but will hopefully be able to return in time for the 2026 season. The Colts will bring in a new kicker later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba5d-db72-a199-fa5f5e4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said Chuba Hubbard (calf) will be day-to-day this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba7a-dd4c-afb9-fffbb08d0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard’s absence in Week 5 paved the way for Rico Dowdle to have a career day against the Dolphins, which understandably raised questions about where Hubbard stands entering Week 6. Canales said on Monday that the team having “two good backs” is “a good problem,” but it’s hard to imagine Dowdle’s emergence not coming at the expense of Hubbard’s fantasy managers. Hubbard has struggled out of the gate this season, totaling 53-217-0 on the ground while adding another 13 receptions for 94 yards and two scores. It sounds like Hubbard is trending toward a return this week, which will make for an interesting Week 6 matchup against the Cowboys with Dowdle putting himself on the map.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba7a-dd4c-afb9-fffbb08d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (shoulder) said he’s not sure if a stint on injured reserve will be possible for him.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baac-def2-abdb-bfedc64e0000</link>
      <description>Austin was injured in Week 4, and the Steelers had a bye in Week 5, so any trip to the injured reserve list would likely be decided on later this week. Austin has caught 10 passes for 139 yards and two touchdowns this season, with most of his production coming in Week 1 against the Jets. Regardless of when he returns, fantasy managers should be looking to Austin for any kind of production any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baac-def2-abdb-bfedc64e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders released LB Germaine Pratt.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bab3-def2-abdb-bff347bf0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Pete Carroll said during the Raiders’ Monday presser that Pratt has been let go. The veteran linebacker joined the Raiders on a one-year deal this offseason after spending the first six years of his career with the Bengals. Pratt totaled 25 tackles and one TFL in four starts with the Raiders this season, but didn’t join the team in Indy for Week 5 due to non-injury reasons. Carroll declined to get into why the Raiders released Pratt, opting to leave it at the team deciding to go in another direction. Pratt is 29 and has 92 career starts under his belt. He will likely catch on with another team in the coming days/weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bab3-def2-abdb-bff347bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Antonio Gibson suffered a torn ACL in Week 5’s win over the Bills, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bacf-db72-a199-facfefae0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots wasted little time ruling Gibson out for the remainder of Sunday’s game after he exited in the second quarter following a hard hit to his legs. Gibson is in the second year of a three-year contract he signed with the Patriots last offseason. Serving as the Patriots’ primary kick returner, the sixth-year back also rushed 25 times for 106 yards and a touchdown this season, and will hopefully be back in time for training camp next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bacf-db72-a199-facfefae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said the Ravens will “consider everything” when asked if Tyler Huntley could get snaps if Lamar Jackson (hamstring) can’t go in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae2-d94a-a79d-bbefc0960000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly a glowing endorsement of Cooper Rush after one week. Huntley was rumored to be in some goal-line packages for his ability to be a run threat, but never actually took a snap in the game. If Rush and Huntley split the load in any way in Week 6, it would be hard to recommend either of them in even the deepest fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae2-d94a-a79d-bbefc0960000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
