<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (ankle) will be limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</link>
      <description>While we would prefer to see Kittle begin the week with a full practice, we cannot complain about this outcome. Kittle made it through Week 18 without suffering any reported setbacks. His early-week participation puts him on track to play in the 49ers’ Wild Card Weekend game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks designated TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</link>
      <description>Arroyo missed the last four games after suffering a knee injury. The 22-year-old notably fell in the 2025 NFL Draft due to concerns over knee-related issues, but Arroyo is not yet being relied upon as a featured pass catcher. The Seahawks should be able to bring him along slowly, given starting TE AJ Barner’s presence and their first-round playoff bye. Thus far, Arroyo has caught 15-of-24 targets for 179 yards and one touchdown. The Seahawks have 21 days to evaluate him in practice before officially activating him from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles designated OLB Azeez Ojulari (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles have 21 days to observe Ojulari in practice before making a decision on whether they will officially activate him from injured reserve. They face the 49ers on Sunday, though. Ojulari would likely operate as an infrequently used situational pass rusher if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a06-d56e-afff-feee8eb30000</link>
      <description>The shifty pass catcher and change-of-pace player has been a valuable contributor this season. He still has a few days to get back on track for Sunday, but if Johnson were to sit out the Bills’ Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars, it would likely add passing down work to RB James Cook’s workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a06-d56e-afff-feee8eb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh said that Hampton is “working through it” and “doing everything he can” to get the ankle better. Hampton neither practiced nor played last week, as the Chargers shut down multiple key starters, giving off the impression that Hampton’s absence was more of a precautionary move than anything else. Harbaugh’s comments, coupled with Hampton’s absence, suggest he is still working his way back from the ankle fracture he suffered in Week 5. Hampton’s per-game touch counts increased each week after the talented rookie resumed playing in Week 14, culminating in a 22-touch outing in Week 17. It was his second-largest workload of the year. We still think Hampton has strong odds of suiting up for the Chargers’ Wild Card Round game against the Patriots, though his practice participation should be followed closely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said he will remain the team’s head coach for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</link>
      <description>Per the Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Bowles “met with the Glazer family, which owns the team, Tuesday.” He met with his coaching staff on Wednesday and informed the Tampa Bay Times that “there will be some changes to his coaching staff.” The Glazer family reportedly took the offensive line’s myriad injuries into account before they made their decision. While no information was shared about the potential coaching staff changes, Stroud did note that “the offense did not produce under first-year coordinator Josh Grizzard.” Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2b-dc7a-af9b-dfbf38a20000</link>
      <description>Moore is on track to play, having logged two limited sessions thus far. The Bears face the Packers on Saturday evening, and it would be great to see Moore upgrade to full participation on Thursday. Moore has played through multiple injuries already this season, while delivering both high- and low-end fantasy results. We expect him to be active this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2b-dc7a-af9b-dfbf38a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2c-dc7a-af9b-dfbf51b90000</link>
      <description>Odunze has now logged three straight limited practices dating back to last week. Rest was prescribed as the fix for his stress fracture, but an aggravation occurred during pre-game warmups in Week 15, when he hurried back after taking just one week off. Odunze sat out of practices and games until he resumed practicing late last week. After practice today, Odunze told reporters he plans on “playing” against the Packers on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2c-dc7a-af9b-dfbf51b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a63-d56e-afff-feeb21480000</link>
      <description>Wicks remains limited through two practices as he attempts to return from a concussion he suffered in Week 17. His availability for the Packers’ Wild Card Round game against the Bears remains up in the air. Having him on the field would provide QB Jordan Love with another capable pass catcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a63-d56e-afff-feeb21480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (Achilles) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a64-dc7a-af9b-dfff4cd20000</link>
      <description>Golden has been a full participant in both practices this week despite the unsettling injury listing. The rookie wide receiver has been unable to carve out a role in the offense and played extensively in Week 18 while the coaching staff rested its key starters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a64-dc7a-af9b-dfff4cd20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
