<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Commanders S Darnell Savage has requested his release.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e9a2-da9b-a9bf-ffafdcd80000</link>
      <description>As expected, Wilson reports Savage will be granted his release. Savage began the year with the Jags but was released and eventually joined the Commanders. He has 16 combined tackles and two pass breakups in total this season. Savage will hit waivers once his release is made official. Expect a contending team to take a shot on him as a depth option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e9a2-da9b-a9bf-ffafdcd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The San Francisco Standard’s David Lombardi reports the 49ers wanted George Pickens “in return for Brandon Aiyuk during those 2024 trade discussions.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea2c-d77b-adfa-eaafac940000</link>
      <description>The Steelers actively pursued Aiyuk last year, but, as Lombardi notes, Pickens was not on the trade block until the 2025 offseason. Aiyuk ultimately stayed in San Francisco on a new contract and the Steelers moved Pickens to Dallas ahead of the 2025 season. The move worked out terrifically for Pickens, who is putting up top-five receiving numbers with the Cowboys. Everyone else involved likely wishes they had handled things differently. Aiyuk has since had guarantees in his contract voided, meaning he and the 49ers are headed for an ugly split after the season. It wouldn’t be surprising to see the Steelers pursue him again next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea2c-d77b-adfa-eaafac940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Justin Herbert (hand) is expected to return to practice today or tomorrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea3a-d005-a9bf-fa3e85750000</link>
      <description>Herbert fractured a finger on his non-throwing hand. He wasn’t on the practice field yesterday, but both Herbert and head coach Jim Harbaugh have told reporters he plans on playing this week. Even a limited practice in the next day or two would bode well for his odds of suiting up. If he can’t go, the Chargers will turn to Trey Lance. Either way, expect a run-heavy approach as Harbaugh attempts to protect his quarterback versus a stout Philly pass-rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea3a-d005-a9bf-fa3e85750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer believes the Cowboys are “not afraid of the franchise tag number” for George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea5c-d005-a9bf-fa7c29510000</link>
      <description>A source inside the building put it as bluntly as possible, telling Archer, “He ain’t leaving.” The franchise tag would cost Dallas just over $27 million, which could actually be a discount on his services. According to Archer and Jeremy Fowler, Pickens could be looking for more than $30 million per year. It’s a steep price, but one that Dallas will almost certainly pay or delay via the franchise tag. Pickens is currently second in the league in receiving yards (1,142) and third in touchdowns (eight). Dak Prescott is playing near an MVP level, supported by the best receiver duo in the NFL. It’s hard to imagine the Cowboys letting this level of production hit the open market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea5c-d005-a9bf-fa7c29510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Darius Slay is “contemplating retirement and will not report” to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea72-dce4-a1da-fa762cdd0000</link>
      <description>Slay was released by the Steelers earlier this week in a mutual parting of ways. At the time, it looked like Slay simply wanted a fresh start elsewhere. After turning down a chance in Buffalo, it’s possible he simply wanted to rejoin the Eagles, who were just behind the Bills in the waiver priority. The Bills still hold Slay’s rights, so his options are to retire or negotiate another release.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea72-dce4-a1da-fa762cdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (hip) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea77-d77b-adfa-eaf7822c0000</link>
      <description>Washington sustained a hip injury in week 13 and did not return versus the Titans. A DNP for Wednesday’s practice put him on the wrong side of questionable to open the week. His return today gives him a shot at suiting up for Week 14. Washington will retain his slot duties if active, but the Jags’ receiver room is a bit crowded now with Brian Thomas Jr. healthy and Jakobi Meyers in the fold. Washington will sit in the WR5 ranks if he suits up versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea77-d77b-adfa-eaf7822c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter is considered week-to-week after undergoing procedures on both shoulders on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea91-d005-a9bf-fab5bbde0000</link>
      <description>Carter has been listed with a shoulder injury on the Eagles’ injury report this season. Evidently, both shoulders were hurt. Carter has already been ruled out for the Eagles’ Week 14 game against the Chargers on Monday night, and his goal is “to be as close to 100 percent as possible for the playoff run.” The game-wrecking defensive tackle experienced a slight dip in his pass-rush win rate from 2024 to 2025, dropping from 12.9 percent to 11.5 percent. Despite the injuries, he ties for third on the team with 36 quarterback pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ea91-d005-a9bf-fab5bbde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-d77b-adfa-eaa79b6a0000</link>
      <description>Harrison is on the wrong side of questionable at this point. The young X-receiver returned from an appendicitis-induced absence last week, only to injure his heel in-game. It is an unfortunate turn of events. He played well in his first game back, catching 6-of-7 targets for 69 yards. Harrison still has a chance to suit up in Week 14 against the Rams, but backup plans should be made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-d77b-adfa-eaa79b6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa8-dce4-a1da-fabe4e190000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are giving Jackson a day off fairly often at this point, though this typically occurs on Wednesday. Today’s absence could simply be standard rest and rehab, but it is hardly reassuring given Jackson’s recent streak of performances. Jackson is barely on the QB1 radar for Week 14. Hopefully, he practices fully tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa8-dce4-a1da-fabe4e190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-dce4-a1da-fab7b7570000</link>
      <description>Benson has been sidelined since Wednesday of last week. Whether he suffered a setback or his surgically repaired knee is simply responding poorly to his ramp-up period remains unknown. At this point, Cardinals RB Bam Knight appears to be heading toward another week operating as the team’s No. 1 running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-dce4-a1da-fab7b7570000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
