<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c61c-db72-a199-fe5f04e70000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon missed Week 5 with his knee injury. The Seahawks were also missing S Julian Love (hamstring), LB Derick Hall (oblique), LB Ernest Jones (shoulder), EDGE Demarcus Lawrence (quad) on the defensive side of the ball. If they cannot practice the rest of the week, the Jaguars offense will have an easier matchup in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c61c-db72-a199-fe5f04e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip/rest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c621-d94a-a79d-cf2ddef30000</link>
      <description>Waller has started out hot with three touchdowns in his first two games with the Dolphins. He sits out Wednesday’s practice with the hip injury that kept him out for the start of the season. This is likely just a precautionary absence as he was also listed out with rest on the injury report. Waller is a low-end TE1 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c621-d94a-a79d-cf2ddef30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c627-dd4c-afb9-e7e70ba70000</link>
      <description>Godwin was dealing with some soreness in Week 5 and now starts out Week 6 not practicing due to a fibula issue. The 29-year-old returned from his major October 2024 ankle injury in Week 4, but is clearly not 100 percent yet. The possibility of Godwin missing Week 6 is on the table as his back-to-back weeks of three receptions for 26 yards show he is not at full speed for the Bucs’ receiving corps. Mike Evans (hamstring) remains out, which leaves Sterling Shepard as possibly the No. 2 Bucs wideout next to Emeka Egbuka should Godwin miss this week against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c627-dd4c-afb9-e7e70ba70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins QB Tua Tagovailoa (hip/thumb) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c644-def2-abdb-df65bf640000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa seemingly suffered the injuries in the Dolphins’ Week 5 loss to the Panthers. Though he was limited, the thumb injury was to his throwing hand, and his mobility will be impacted by the hip issue. Tagovailoa has been banged up frequently throughout his career, so playing through injuries won’t be a first for him. He is a low-end QB2 for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c644-def2-abdb-df65bf640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Zay Flowers (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c64d-def2-abdb-df6dcade0000</link>
      <description>Add Flowers to the pile of Ravens injuries to monitor. He was limited with a shoulder injury and though it could be a precautionary practice limitation, it is important to note the Ravens have a Week 7 bye and players that are truly questionable may be held out against the Rams this week. Flowers is still trending to play, but fantasy managers should stay tuned to his situation, likely heading into another week without Lamar Jackson for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c64d-def2-abdb-df6dcade0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c665-dd4c-afb9-e7e5d9460000</link>
      <description>Mayer has been sidelined with a concussion each of the last three weeks. He starts out Week 6 as a full participant in practice, indicating he is ready to return this week against the Titans. With Brock Bowers (knee) still hurting, Mayer is worth an add as a fill-in for fantasy managers with Bowers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c665-dd4c-afb9-e7e5d9460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c66a-d94a-a79d-cf6f4b9e0000</link>
      <description>Hamilton practiced for the first time since getting in a limited session last Wednesday. The versatile 24-year-old safety is a key piece on the back end of the struggling Ravens’ secondary and would be a vital addition back to the defense if he returns against the Rams in Week 6. Also practicing was LT Ronnie Stanley (ankle). Both Hamilton and Stanley are cornerstone starters at their respective positions and their potential returns would boost a Ravens team that is off to a disappointing 1-4 start this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c66a-d94a-a79d-cf6f4b9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns acquired CB Tyson Campbell and the Eagles’ 2026 seventh-round pick from the Jaguars in exchange for CB Greg Newsome and the Jets’ 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c6c9-def2-abdb-dfe9fc5d0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns and Jaguars will be swapping late-round picks in addition to the cornerbacks. Campbell signed a four-year, $76.5 million extension in the 2024 offseason with the Jaguars and is now under contract through 2028 for Cleveland. He has six interceptions and 42 passes defended through his five-year career, but has missed 11 games over the last two seasons. The Jaguars swap him out for Greg Newsome, who is in the last season of his rookie deal. Newsome held a top-45 PFF coverage grade each of his first three seasons and has three interceptions and 37 passes defended through four total seasons. The Jags have flexibility at corner with Travis Hunter mixing in for snaps; his usage won’t decrease with Newsome joining him on the outside. Meanwhile, the Browns opt for Campbell’s long-term deal over negotiating a Newsome extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c6c9-def2-abdb-dfe9fc5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan believes Cam Skattebo is “the Giants’ future and present at running back.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c8fd-db72-a199-faffeb300000</link>
      <description>It’s quite the departure from Raanan’s August report that named Tyrone Tracy the unquestioned lead back after Skattebo sustained a hamstring injury in training camp. Skattebo has established himself as New York’s RB1 over the past few weeks with Tracy sidelined with a shoulder injury. Though Tracy is set to return to game action on Thursday night against the Eagles, Skattebo is expected to remain the team’s primary back. He has 48 touches over the past two games in a massively run-heavy Giants offense. He could go down as one of the most important fantasy selections in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c8fd-db72-a199-faffeb300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
