<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts T Bernhard Raimann (elbow) did not practice Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3851-dc7a-af9b-ffffc1a10000</link>
      <description>He hasn’t practiced on either Thursday or Friday ahead of Monday Night’s game against the 49ers. Raimann left Week 15’s game against the Seahawks, giving way to Luke Tenuta at left tackle. Indianapolis worked out several offensive linemen this week. It would not be surprising if Raimann were placed on IR ahead of Monday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3851-dc7a-af9b-ffffc1a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (Achilles) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3858-d087-addf-b9f8e5830000</link>
      <description>He should be good to go for Week 16’s Monday affair against the 49ers. However, it’s hard to project much in terms of passing volume for the downfield threat with Philip Rivers under center. Expectations should be managed, pushing Pierce into the WR4/WR5 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3858-d087-addf-b9f8e5830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs (personal) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385a-d087-addf-b9fa36ca0000</link>
      <description>He’ll be in line for a real role on Monday night, though with Philip Rivers under center the best fantasy managers can realistically hope for is a PPR scam with some touchdown equity. Downs is probably best thought of as a WR4/WR5 in Week 16’s slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385a-d087-addf-b9fa36ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Seahawks CB Riq Woolen’s knee injury is “not considered serious.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3852-da28-afbb-fc7ffbb30000</link>
      <description>Seahawks S Coby Bryant (knee) is expected to miss “some time.” Woolen has broken up seven passes and intercepted one pass this season. Fowler describes him as being only “banged up.” Bryant has broken up two passes and ranks second on the team with four interceptions. Losing either player hurts. Hopefully, Woolen can play in Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3852-da28-afbb-fc7ffbb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (groin/knee) is questionable for Week 16’s game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385c-d35e-a1bf-7dde57380000</link>
      <description>Taylor told reporters that he “feels good enough to play” on Sunday earlier today, but with Brady Cook already named the starter, Taylor will be in a reserve role if active. Still, it’s possible Taylor could wind up drawing real snaps in Week 17 or Week 18, and it’s a good sign for the Jets passing game FLEX scams that he’d be healthy enough to do it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385c-d35e-a1bf-7dde57380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Justin Fields (knee) is questionable for New York’s Week 16 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385f-d087-addf-b9ffaf0f0000</link>
      <description>Fields talked to reporters on Friday and said he is “week to week” and “trying to get back before the end of the season.” Those don’t read like the quotes of someone who will be active in Week 16, but here he is on the questionable line, daring the Saints to prepare for him or something like that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385f-d087-addf-b9ffaf0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt (lung) will not play in Pittsburgh’s Week 16 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3861-d35e-a1bf-7de36ca90000</link>
      <description>Watt didn’t practice all week, but was spotted in the facility today. Perhaps we’ll get more clarity from him before the end of the day on the timeline for his recovery, he obviously wasn’t close to playing after not practicing all week. Fellow EDGE Nick Herbig (hamstring) is doubtful after a limited session on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3861-d35e-a1bf-7de36ca90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder/rest) is questionable to play in Week 16 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3853-da28-afbb-fc7fe0a20000</link>
      <description>Decker has been gutting it out on game day for months now. Lions C Graham Glasgow missed Thursday and Friday’s practices with a knee injury. Lions OG Christian Mahogany practiced fully twice before downgrading to limited on Friday. He is attempting to return from injured reserve after fracturing a fibula in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3853-da28-afbb-fc7fe0a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers G Isaac Seumalo (triceps) will not play in Pittsburgh’s Week 16 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3864-d35e-a1bf-7de64b610000</link>
      <description>Seumalo didn’t practice all week after leaving Week 15’s game with the injury. Spencer Anderson and Ryan McCollum both filled in off the bench for the Steelers on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3864-d35e-a1bf-7de64b610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions ruled out S Kerby Joseph (knee) for Week 16 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385f-d087-addf-b9ff49450000</link>
      <description>Joseph will, unfortunately, will yet another game. Lions head coach Dan Campbell told reporters last week that the talented safety suffered a setback at some point. Landing on injured reserve was said to be a possibility, though, the team did not place him on it last week. He totaled one pass breakup and three interceptions in just six games played this season. Lions CB Amik Robertson (hand) and S Thomas Harper (concussion) are questionable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-385f-d087-addf-b9ff49450000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
