<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LT Laremy Tunsil (oblique) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2992-d1bc-a3fb-adb6475e0000</link>
      <description>Tunsil suffered an oblique injury in Week 15 and his status for Week 16 is in flux. Commanders head coach Dan Quinn on Monday that Tunsil will play “if he can”, but the left tackle starts out the week not practicing. Practice reports later in the week will tell if Tunsil is good to go for Saturday against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2992-d1bc-a3fb-adb6475e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (stinger) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2995-d1bc-a3fb-adb5f9e10000</link>
      <description>Barkley popped up with a new listing on the injury report, getting a DNP designation due to a stinger. It is unclear yet how serious the injury is, as stingers indicate some kind of head/shoulder nerve pain. He starts out the week with a DNP and practice reports later in the week will tell how serious the issue is. Should Barkley miss Week 16 against the Commanders, Tank Bigsby would be next man up. Bigsby was limited on Tuesday with an illness, but is still tracking to play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2995-d1bc-a3fb-adb5f9e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulders) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-299e-d8cf-affb-bdbee14d0000</link>
      <description>Carter remains sidelined after undergoing surgery on both shoulders two weeks ago. His timetable was week-to-week, but he is not back practicing yet. The Commanders’ running game will have an easier time attacking the middle of the Eagles’ defense if Carter cannot return for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-299e-d8cf-affb-bdbee14d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29a0-d005-a9bf-f9b4b1e80000</link>
      <description>In addition to Johnson, LG Landon Dickerson (calf) also was listed as DNP. Dickerson was at least able to play in Week 15, meaning the designation could just be out of precaution for Tuesday’s walkthrough ahead of a Saturday game. As for Johnson, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reportedlast week he was going to practice this week, but he remains out to start Week 16. Johnson has a few more days to practice before the Eagles play the Commanders on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29a0-d005-a9bf-f9b4b1e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Daniel Oyefusi reports Browns LB Devin Bush was found not guilty of assault and harassment charges stemming from a May incident.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29ca-d8cf-affb-bdeabb5b0000</link>
      <description>Bush was arrested in May on charges of simple assault and harassment. The 27-year-old linebacker has been available for the Browns this season with his trial set for December, snagging two interceptions and making 93 combined tackles in 14 games so far. Oyefusi reports that court documents show Bush was found not guilty of the simple assault and harassment chargers on Tuesday. Bush is now clear to play the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29ca-d8cf-affb-bdeabb5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame RB Jeremiyah Love has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29cf-d005-a9bf-f9ffaf8b0000</link>
      <description>Love is one of the nations’ top running back prospects, finishing his junior year at Notre Dame with 199 carries for 1,372 rushing yards and 18 touchdowns, adding 27 receptions for 280 yards and three touchdowns. He finished as a finalist for the Heisman Trophy award and won the Doak Walker award for the top running back in college football. Teams in the first round of the draft will already be circling Love’s name at the top of their running back big boards; he is certainly a candidate to go in the top 10 picks, similar to Ashton Jeanty in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-29cf-d005-a9bf-f9ffaf8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</link>
      <description>As expected, Adams was listed with a DNP for the Rams’ Tuesday walkthrough. Sean McVay did not rule Adams out for Thursday’s game against the Seahawks and said he could be a game-time decision. Adams re-aggravated his hamstring injury in Week 15 and getting healthy on a short week will be difficult. Colby Parkinson emerges as a red zone target for the Rams if Adams is out for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2a17-d005-a9bf-fa37ce800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes Giants QB Jaxson Dart “has a target on his back as a runner.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28e6-d8cf-affb-bceeb9880000</link>
      <description>Duggan pointed to comments from Commanders head coach Dan Quinn ahead of Washington’s Week 15 game against Dart and the Giants as evidence that New York opponents are targeting Dart based on his willingness to take big hits, even to the head. “The quarterback is a very competitive dual-threat guy. He will try to run the ball like a running back,” Quinn told his defense last week. “He will try to run you over. He will try to stiff-arm. He doesn’t really run out of bounds. He doesn’t slide a whole bunch. We can get the ball off of him.” Dart took yet another shot to the head in the Giants’ Week 15 loss to the Commanders and was checked for a concussion before re-entering the ballgame. Dart has missed time with brain injuries this season and continues to lower his head as a rusher in the open field. It’s something he’ll need to change if he wants to have a long NFL career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-28e6-d8cf-affb-bceeb9880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed TE Jeremy Ruckert to a two-year contract extension worth $10 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2cb3-d77b-adfb-eeb3ad890000</link>
      <description>The new deal includes a maximum of $11 over the 2026 and 2027 seasons. Ruckert, drafted by the Jets in 2022, has 55 receptions on 75 targets over four NFL seasons, including 20 catches for 163 yards and a touchdown in 2025. Ruckert has seen some more involvement in the Jets offense of late, recording two receptions in each of the past three contests. The team’s commitment to Ruckert could raise questions about how the Jets see TE Mason Taylor, a rookie with 44 receptions for 369 yards and a score this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2cb3-d77b-adfb-eeb3ad890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
