<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving rushed 16 times for 60 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1092-d77b-adfb-da93fd540000</link>
      <description>Irving also caught one of his three targets and picked up 11 yards. The 23-year-old had some decent runs, but outside of a 16-yard burst he wasn’t able to get into the Atlanta secondary, and he saw Sean Tucker vulture a touchdown from him early in the contest. Irving should see a similar amount of touches in Week 16 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1092-d77b-adfb-da93fd540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed four times for seven yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f2-d1bc-a3fb-95f675340000</link>
      <description>Tucker got the scoring started by volturing a touchdown early in the contest. That makes back-to-back games with a trip to paydirt, but it’s also three straight games he hasn’t cleared 30 yards. He’s as touchdown-dependent as you’ll find in the league right now, in terms of offering potential fantasy value. It’s potentially worth noting that Tucker did receive more carries than Rachaad White, as White carried the rock just one time for 20 yards in the loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f2-d1bc-a3fb-95f675340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-7 targets for 64 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f6-d1bc-a3fb-95f634c00000</link>
      <description>Well, it’s better than the previous two weeks. Egbuka wasn’t great, but he was involved even with Mike Evans and Jalen McMillan returning from injury Thursday. Still, it’s another statline that pales in comparison to what his early success looked like, and it’s fair to wonder if those numbers are going to come again in 2025. The next chance to do so comes in a massive matchup for the Bucs against the Panthers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f6-d1bc-a3fb-95f634c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin caught 4-of-5 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f9-d8cf-affb-bcfbd4570000</link>
      <description>it was a very quiet day for Godwin, but he was able to not only get into the end zone on a connection with Baker Mayfield, but he also picked up the two-point conversion a play later on a pass from Mayfield. Godwin now has added competition with both Mike Evans and Jalen McMillan back, but he he’s in the WR3 conversation for Week 16 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10f9-d8cf-affb-bcfbd4570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen McMillan caught 2-of-2 targets for 38 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10fc-d8cf-affb-bcfe3aeb0000</link>
      <description>McMillan came mere inches short of turning his first catch of 2025 into a touchdown, but instant replay deemed him to be down inside of the one yard line. The second-year wideout has missed the entirety of the campaign prior to Thursday due to a neck issue, and while there are a lot of bodies to feed in the Tampa Bay offense, it’s worth keeping in mind that McMillan was a significant part of the passing attack in 2025 as a rookie. Still, it’s hard to see him being a fantasy option for the remainder of 2025, and there’s more risk than reward for Week 16 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10fc-d8cf-affb-bcfe3aeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Culp caught his lone targets for a six-yard touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 15 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10ff-d8cf-affb-bcff8ab70000</link>
      <description>With Cade Otton (knee) unavailable, it was Culp who scored the first touchdown of the season for a Tampa Bay tight end. It’s reasonable to wonder if it’ll be the last. Culp has impressive athleticism, but is miles and miles away from fantasy relevancy at this stage of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10ff-d8cf-affb-bcff8ab70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zane Gonzalez converted a 43-yard field goal with no time remaining in the Falcons’ Week 15 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1105-d8cf-affb-bd2f72c30000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez also connected on all of of his extra-point attempts. His 43-yarder with no time remaining just snuck inside of the post to give Atlanta the win. On the year, Gonzalez has made 11 of his 13 attempts, and he’s perfect on all 11 PATs. He’ll square off against the Cardinals in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1105-d8cf-affb-bd2f72c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes “it seems to be trending toward T.J. Watt (lung) missing” Week 15’s game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12c7-d1bc-a3fb-97e7722b0000</link>
      <description>Watt was hospitalized with a lung issue on Wednesday and was unsurprisingly listed as a DNP on Thursday. He’ll have some extra time to get ready ahead of Monday night’s matchup against the Dolphins, but given the nature of the injury, this may not be something Watt can “tough it out” to play through. With two days of practice left to go, we’ll continue to monitor his status throughout the week, but the Steelers could be down their top defensive player in a pivotal Week 15 matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12c7-d1bc-a3fb-97e7722b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed C Josh Myers to a two-year, $11 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12db-d77b-adfb-dadbeb760000</link>
      <description>Myers signed a one-year deal with the Jets this offseason and has started all 13 games for them. Myers has played on 803 offensive snaps while earning a PFF offensive grade of 53.6. With Myers’ extension, the Jets now have four of their five offensive starters under contract for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12db-d77b-adfb-dadbeb760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb has cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 15 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12e7-d005-a9bf-daf7d7630000</link>
      <description>With extra time to heal up after getting concussed in a Thursday night matchup against the Lions, Lamb is now good to go in a pivotal Week 15 game against the Vikings. Lamb turned in arguably his best performance of the season before going down last week, totaling six catches for a season-high 121 yards in just one half of play. He can be trusted as a WR1 in this week’s fantasy playoff matchups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-12e7-d005-a9bf-daf7d7630000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
