<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed WR Brenden Rice, formerly of the Chargers, to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50cd-d713-ad9e-7cddb2380000</link>
      <description>The son of NFL legend Jerry Rice, Brenden was drafted by the Chargers in the seventh round of the 2024 NFL Draft. He made the Chargers’ 53-man roster but only appeared in three games as a rookie and did not record any stats. Rice was then cut ahead of his second season. With Kayshon Boutte banged up, Rice gives the Chargers some extra depth at wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50cd-d713-ad9e-7cddb2380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (concussion) returned to practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50d4-d673-a39e-f4d5ceae0000</link>
      <description>It’s a big step in the right direction for the speedy wideout. Mims missed Week 9 because of the concussion and wasn’t able to practice on Monday. After looking like a safe bet to miss Week 10 as of 24 hours ago, Mims now has a shot to suit up for Denver’s Thursday date with the Raiders. Mims still has some hurdles to clear in the league’s concussion protocol, so keep an eye out for his practice status tomorrow. If he is back in the lineup for Week 10, Mims will be a boom/bust WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50d4-d673-a39e-f4d5ceae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cardinals are naming Jacoby Brissett as their starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50dc-d1e7-a1fa-5afeb6920000</link>
      <description>It’s a move that sounds shocking but felt completely inevitable after Brissett toppled the Cowboys on Monday Night Football. Brissett made three starts in place of an injured Kyler Murray. He threw for 860 yards and six touchdowns while Murray nursed his foot injury. His lowest yardage total was 261, coming against Dallas. That would have been Murray’s highest total of the year by over 40 yards. Brissett was also getting more out of both Trey McBride and Marvin Harrison Jr. McBride has four touchdowns in three Brissett starts. He has five career touchdown receptions from Murray. MHJ is coming off a career-high in receptions at seven. In the short-term, Brissett is a mid-range QB2 for fantasy purposes and both of his top pass-catchers will get a boost in the ranks for Week 10 against the Seahawks. In the long-term, the Cardinals are now headed toward an ugly breakup with Murray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50dc-d1e7-a1fa-5afeb6920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyler Murray has been benched as Cardinals starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ffd-d45b-affe-5fff0db00000</link>
      <description>For what it’s worth, Murray’s foot injury is supposedly “still a factor.” Although this had begun to feel inevitable, it’s still stunning when a team benches its seventh-year starter in the middle of a massive contract extension. It’s even more surprising considering the alternative is Jacoby Brissett. The veteran journeyman, of course, had out-played Murray this season to the extent that it would have become awkward had Murray kept his job for Week 10 against the Seahawks. The No. 1 overall pick of the 2019 draft, Murray appeared polished and almost fully formed as a rookie. The problem is that he was fully formed, turning in variations of the same season since without leveling up. Still only 28 years old, Murray is signed through 2028 with guaranteed salary through 2026. He will obviously be traded this offseason. A year in McVay and or Shanahan finishing school would probably do him well, but Murray’s long track record of static play could limit his market more than expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ffd-d45b-affe-5fff0db00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired CB Ja’Sir Taylor from the Chargers in exchange for a 2028 conditional seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50e3-d713-ad9e-7cf7ae360000</link>
      <description>The Chargers announced the move on social media a full hour after the trade deadline had passed, but who’s counting? Taylor played 16 defensive snaps in Week 8. He has otherwise been relegated to special teams duties this year. Taylor will give the Jets some extra depth at corner after they traded away Michael Carter and Sauce Gardner in the past week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50e3-d713-ad9e-7cf7ae360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears hosted RB Raheem Blackshear for a tryout on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-511d-d673-a39e-f59d48cb0000</link>
      <description>In addition to Blackshear, the Bears also hosted Israel Abanikanda, Montrell Johnson, and ShunDerrick Powell. Starting running back D’Andre Swift did not play in Week 9 due to a groin injury, leading to Kyle Monangai having a monstrous 29-touch workload in a win over the Bengals. The Bears may be evaluating their options should Swift miss more time, looking to add depth. None of the four backs were signed, but a situation to watch as the week of practices unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-511d-d673-a39e-f59d48cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans K Ka’imi Fairbairn is dealing with a lower body injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5136-d673-a39e-f5b702780000</link>
      <description>Wilson adds that Fairbairn’s status for Week 10 is “still being determined” and the 31-year-old is receiving treatment for a lower body injury. He knocked down five kicks in the Texans’ Week 9 loss to the Broncos and is averaging 11.5 fantasy points per game this season, best among kickers. If Fairbairn misses times, fantasy managers will have a legitimate hole in their roster with his production matching that of a low-end RB2. The Texans signed Matthew Wright to the practice squad; Wright is likely to kick in place of Fairbairn if he is out Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5136-d673-a39e-f5b702780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos K Wil Lutz (illness) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5141-d1e7-a1fa-5bebfee90000</link>
      <description>Lutz was a new addition to the practice report with an illness Tuesday. The Broncos play on a short week with a Thursday game against the Raiders, so Lutz’ addition is notable as he has two days to get ready. We often see players not miss time with an illness, so expect Lutz to play barring any setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5141-d1e7-a1fa-5bebfee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived RB Malik Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5169-d45b-affe-55ff0ae00000</link>
      <description>Davis was active as the backup to Javonte Williams in Week 9 over rookie Jaydon Blue and saw just one carry for three yards. He has played in three games this season, totaling three carries for six yards. The Cowboys jettisoning Davis either indicates rookie seventh-rounder Phil Mafah (shoulder) is nearing a return from injured reserve or a renewed confidence in Blue. Either way, Williams will continues to dominate backfield touches for the Cowboys. Davis is also a candidate to return via practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5169-d45b-affe-55ff0ae00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Derrick Brooks reduced Commanders LB Frankie Luvu’s one-game suspension to a $100,000 fine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5206-d45b-affe-5796e4060000</link>
      <description>Brooks, jointly appointed by the NFL and the NFLPA, reduced Luvu’s one-game suspension to a $100,000 fine. Luvu was initially suspended for “repeated violations of playing rules” after committing his third hip-drop tackle of the season in Week 9. The 29-year-old has now been fined for all three tackles, but will no longer serve a suspension. Luvu is eligible to play Week 10 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5206-d45b-affe-5796e4060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
