<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9eef-dc7a-af9b-dfff74620000</link>
      <description>The Bills could simply be giving Johnson, their reliable passing down back, an extra day of rest. Thursday absences are often bad signs, though. If he can resume practicing tomorrow, he should be good to go for his team’s Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars. With QB Josh Allen nursing a foot injury, having Johnson available for checkdown passes would be beneficial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9eef-dc7a-af9b-dfff74620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed their interview with Broncos DC Vance Joseph.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef2-dc7a-af9b-dfffe30c0000</link>
      <description>That was fast. Just yesterday, Josina Anderson broke the news that Joseph was set to interview with the Ravens. Prior reports indicate that the Giants, Raiders, Titans, and Cardinals had requested to interview Joseph for their head-coaching vacancies as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef2-dc7a-af9b-dfffe30c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers fired DL coach Charlie Strong.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef9-dc7a-af9b-dfff53240000</link>
      <description>Buccaneers CB coach Kevin Ross has also been let go, and S coach Nick Rapone, 69, is retiring. Offensive consultant Tom Moore retired as well. The Buccaneers released two staffers on the offensive side of the ball, OC Josh Grizzard and QB coach Thad Lewis, plus ST coordinator Thomas McGaughey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef9-dc7a-af9b-dfff53240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will interview DC Jim Schwartz for their head-coaching vacancy on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f03-d968-a19b-dff356a20000</link>
      <description>Schwartz has regularly churned out formidable defenses since being hired by the Browns in his current role in 2023. Elevating him to the head coach role makes sense if ownership wishes to double down on an old school brand of football. Browns OC Tommy Rees will also interview for the team’s head-coaching vacancy today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f03-d968-a19b-dff356a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will interview OC Tommy Rees for their head-coaching vacancy on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f03-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9bec0000</link>
      <description>Rees was hired as the Browns’ passing game specialist and TE coach in 2024. He was promoted to offensive coordinator in January 2025 and took over play-calling duties in Week 10. The “rookie-led unit” averaged just 4.6 yards per play, ranking 28th in the NFL, after that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f03-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9bec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) is not on Chicago’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f17-d968-a19b-dff750360000</link>
      <description>Odunze got in his first full practice on Friday and was removed from the injury report — his return figures to be key as the Bears try to take two of three games against the Packers. Chicago’s star receiver finished his season with a 44/661/6 line in 12 games and has not played since November 28. Lowered expectations make sense in a DFS setting, but the full practice gives us a little optimism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f17-d968-a19b-dff750360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams ruled out RG Kevin Dotson (ankle) for the Wild Card Round against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f11-d35e-a1bf-dfd36bc30000</link>
      <description>Seahawks LB Derick Hall was suspended for one game after injuring Dotson in Week 16. Rams head coach Sean McVay said Dotson “is making good progress.” One hopes he can return next week, if the Rams beat the Panthers and advance to the next round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f11-d35e-a1bf-dfd36bc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore is not on Chicago’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f1a-d56e-afff-fffadc080000</link>
      <description>As expected, Moore managed to clear a new knee listing ahead of this game quickly. He practiced in full today. With Rome Odunze back, Moore probably figures to slide into a smaller role as he did earlier in the season. Especially with Luther Burden also having shown worthy of more usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f1a-d56e-afff-fffadc080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) is questionable to play in the Wild Card Round against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f12-d968-a19b-dff33b380000</link>
      <description>Rams WR Jordan Whittington (knee) is also questionable. Ferguson earned four targets in each of his last two games, catching five for 87 yards and two touchdowns. Having him on the field would be great for the Rams’ creative tight end usage. Whittington serves only as a rotational weapon at wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f12-d968-a19b-dff33b380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) is questionable for Chicago’s Wild Card game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f1c-dc7a-af9b-dfbff7040000</link>
      <description>Gordon got in a full session — everybody but Chicago’s three concussed rule-outs got in a full session today — and appears likely to give it a go against the Packers. Gordon has played just three games this year and would have to be considered at least a slight re-injury risk. If healthy, though, his return would be huge for Chicago. Fellow designated-to-return-from-IR-on-Tuesday pal OT Braxton Jones is also officially questionable for Saturday, but wouldn’t figure to have as big of a role as Gordon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9f1c-dc7a-af9b-dfbff7040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
