<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini believes the Vikings will look to acquire a veteran quarterback this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3883-d355-a5bd-bfd700710000</link>
      <description>Russini threw cold water on Vikings’ fans wildest dreams, reporting that the Bengals have no intention of trading Joe Burrow. Still, she believes the organization will bring in a veteran quarterback this offseason. That shouldn’t come as earth-shattering news given J.J. McCarthy’s struggles last season. Teammates Justin Jefferson and Aaron Jones went on a media blitz during Super Bowl week that included both of them essentially saying the team should’ve kept Sam Darnold. The Vikings can’t go back in time, but they can be proactive about next season. Kirk Cousins, Aaron Rodgers and Mac Jones come to mind as veteran options that could be available this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3883-d355-a5bd-bfd700710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the 49ers aren’t looking to trade QB Mac Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3891-d629-a1bc-b89de0310000</link>
      <description>This report comes on the heels of 49ers coach Kyle Shanahan telling reporters last month he’d be very surprised if Jones wasn’t on the team in 2026. With quarterback options limited in the draft and free agency, Jones, who has one year left on the two-year deal he signed in San Francisco, could be attractive to quarterback-needy teams this offseason. While the team doesn’t appear interested in the slightest in moving off of the backup QB that went 5-3 as a starter in 2025, that could change once other teams start making offers for the 27-year-old signal caller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3891-d629-a1bc-b89de0310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Eagles WR A.J. Brown’s relationship with the organization remains somewhat tenuous.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-389a-d629-a1bc-b89f2c000000</link>
      <description>From what Russini is hearing, substantial conversations about Brown’s future with the organization haven’t taken place yet, but will ramp up around the NFL combine in two weeks. This jives with a previous report from the Athletic’s Zach Berman where the beat writer guessed Brown would seek a trade this offseason. While Eagles general manager Howie Roseman has previously mentioned that it’s hard to find great players like Brown, it could also be difficult to move forward with him as his relationship with QB Jalen Hurts seems to have deteriorated. Unless his contract is reworked, though, Philadelphia would be on the hook for $72.5 million in dead cap if Brown is moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-389a-d629-a1bc-b89f2c000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown said in an interview that he’s excited for next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-38c1-d355-a5bd-bfd598cb0000</link>
      <description>Brown appeared on Micah Parsons’ The Edge podcast, saying he’s excited for next season. Amid reports from various outlets that Brown could be on the move this offseason, the receiver, who turns 29-years-old in June, was talking like he expects to be back with the Eagles. Brown said he’s looking forward to reviewing tape of the offense from this season and the offense rediscovering itself. Keeping him in the fold for next season makes complete financial sense for the Eagles, who would be hit with a $72.5 million dead cap charge if Brown is moved on his current contract. The out in Brown’s contract comes after the 2026 season, when he’ll have just $27.1 million in dead cap remaining on his deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-38c1-d355-a5bd-bfd598cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RB David Montgomery told NBC Sports new Lions OC Drew Petzing “knows exactly what needs to happen” next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-38ce-d355-a5bd-bfde08c10000</link>
      <description>Montgomery joined the Fantasy Football Happy Hour at Super Bowl week and expressed optimism when discussing new Lions OC Drew Petzing. The 28-year-old running back said Petzing knows exactly what needs to happen next season, possibly alluding to more touches for himself. Montgomery had 185 carries and 38 targets in 2024, but those numbers dipped to 158 carries and 29 targets in 2025. Lions general manager Brad Holmes said the team would discuss Montgomery’s future this offseason at his season-ending press conference and it seems like the former Bears third-round pick is on board with the Lions’ plan for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-38ce-d355-a5bd-bfde08c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens will not retain former senior defensive assistant-secondary coach Chuck Pagano under HC Jesse Minter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-395e-d355-a5bd-bf5e1fe70000</link>
      <description>Pagano unretired in 2025 to coach for John Harbaugh’s Ravens but will not be retained by new head coach Jesse Minter. Minter appears to have a firm hand in the trajectory of team decisions after being hired away from the Chargers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-395e-d355-a5bd-bf5e1fe70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets hired former Lions assistant tight ends coach Seth Ryan as their new offensive pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3962-d629-a1bc-b97f3cd60000</link>
      <description>The hire marks the third generation of Ryans coaching for the Jets in New York, following in the footsteps of his grandfather, Buddy, and father, Rex. The passing game coordinator role is a solid stepping stone towards future offensive coaching positions considering recent trends around the league, potentially setting up Seth well for potential coordinator positions in the near future if all goes well with the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3962-d629-a1bc-b97f3cd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Falcons are expected to release QB Kirk Cousins ahead of the new league year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-39ef-d629-a1bc-b9ff8d280000</link>
      <description>The expected move will allow the veteran quarterback options as he decides on his next move. ESPN’s Kevin Seifert adds that Cousins is also weighing the opportunity to turn his attentions to broadcasting after dipping his toes in the discipline earlier this year. According to Seifert, Cousins “will be fully open to finding the right opportunity with another NFL team in need of quarterback help.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-39ef-d629-a1bc-b9ff8d280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports reports the Cowboys are expected to franchise tag impending free agent George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ad8-d629-a1bc-badd30bc0000</link>
      <description>This has been our lean for a while, too, but it’s interesting Schefter’s sources are already confirming so at this early stage of the offseason. The tag window opens Feb. 17 and closes March 3. The sides would then have until mid-July to negotiate a long-term deal. The tag would guarantee Pickens roughly $28 million. Although the 25-year-old (next month) surely won’t mind the monster one-year payday, he will undoubtedly view this as his best chance at a mega long-term deal. Cowboys owner Jerry Jones has claimed he desires the same outcome, but Dallas has become as bad as any team at negotiating long-term deals. A mercurial player like Pickens playing on a one-year pact would have the potential to end poorly for both parties. It’s definitely one of the offseason’s top early storylines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ad8-d629-a1bc-badd30bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce was arrested on Saturday in Miami after crashing his car at the end of a police chase.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3b22-d042-afbc-7ff219b80000</link>
      <description>Pearce is alleged to have been fleeing a domestic dispute. Not good, to put it mildly. It somehow gets worse when you factor in the charges Pearce is facing following the chase and subsequent crash, including two counts of aggravated battery with a deadly weapon and aggravated stalking. That’s in addition to “fleeing or eluding police with lights or siren.” Social media footage shows what appears to be Pearce in a struggle with police following the chase. The 22-year-old had a sensational rookie season following the Falcons’ aggressive move up to get him late in the first round, but this has him in danger of a massive suspension, perhaps missing all of 2026. There’s also the very real possibility of a jail sentence. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3b22-d042-afbc-7ff219b80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
