<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Royce Lewis is not in the lineup Wednesday against the Athletics.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/baseball/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deff222a0000</link>
      <description>Lewis will get the day off — something that doesn’t happen often all that often — so Ryan Fitzgerald will start at third base and hit ninth against JT Ginn and the A’s bullpen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/baseball/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deff222a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR DeVonta Smith (groin) missed practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deffafe10000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are likely being conservative with both Smith and A.J. Brown (hamstring), with neither suiting up in recent practices. Smith has also dealt with a back injury in training camp. We don’t expect these injuries to spiral into Week 1 at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deffafe10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jesse Newell believes Brashard Smith could see first-team reps in Kansas City’s preseason finale.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d0-db7b-a5dd-e8d41d880000</link>
      <description>Newell describes Smith as fit in “a gadget-type role for Kansas City, which would showcase him as both a runner and receiver.” It sounds like the seventh-round pick has an inside track to a roster spot over Elijah Mitchell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d0-db7b-a5dd-e8d41d880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Tashan Reed believes WR Jack Bech is “firmly the fourth receiver in the rotation” for the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d5-dbe3-a9bb-f8d73ee70000</link>
      <description>It appears that Bech is the backup slot option behind Jakobi Meyers at this point, with fellow rookie Dont’e Thornton ahead of him on outside sets because Bech “lacks noteworthy long speed and is still learning how to beat press coverage at the line of scrimmage.” Oof. Bech appears to lack standalone value in dynasty drafts at this point, though with Meyers a pending free agent, it’s possible Bech could have some value in his sophomore season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d5-dbe3-a9bb-f8d73ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired Jowon Briggs and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Browns for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8e7-d332-a1fd-def7e2940000</link>
      <description>A blockbuster. Briggs, who turns 24 in September, played 133 snaps for the Browns last year from Weeks 13 to 18, compiling a 66.5 PFF run defense grade. He’ll try to provide a boost for the Jets interior line. The 2024 seventh-rounder has three cost-controlled years left on his rookie deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8e7-d332-a1fd-def7e2940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Denzel Ward (shoulder) will be back “pretty soon.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f7-de13-afdc-ceff18810000</link>
      <description>Ward missed another practice on Wednesday, but it doesn’t seem like he’s in any real danger of missing Week 1 for the Browns. Cedric Tillman (thumb) wore a brace at today’s practice but it is another injury that is not considered serious, per Stefanski.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f7-de13-afdc-ceff18810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Kenny Pickett (hamstring) won’t play in Cleveland’s third preseason game on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f9-db7b-a5dd-e8fd91080000</link>
      <description>It seems that preseason Week 3 will set up as a split between Shedeur Sanders and Dillon Gabriel, with Sanders back throwing in individual drills. Pickett has not attempted a pass in any preseason game this year and that might make him a tough trade target for teams across the league, perhaps increasing the chances the Browns carry four quarterbacks at the start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f9-db7b-a5dd-e8fd91080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WRs Jordan Addison and Tai Felton left practice early on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c925-de13-afdc-cfefbb800000</link>
      <description>We don’t have confirmed status updates from the team yet, but The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes Addison jammed “something” and that Felton “looked like he dinged his arm.” Felton, per ESPN’s Kevin Seifert, walked off the field with a wrap on his left hand. If there’s one thing that would accelerate trade talks for wideouts ahead of last cuts, it’s more injuries to this room. The Vikings should update Addison’s (and Felton’s) status in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c925-de13-afdc-cfefbb800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said both Tyler Shough and Spencer Rattler will play in New Orleans’ preseason finale.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c937-de13-afdc-cfff07150000</link>
      <description>He declined to give an order of play, though it seemed like Rattler was up first in practice today. The last starting quarterback should be announced in the next week or so — whether it’s Rattler or Shough, it’s hard to believe either player will remain the starter all season based on how tight the process has been. Neither of them qualify as desirable options even in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c937-de13-afdc-cfff07150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala reports Terry McLaurin asked for “more than DK Metcalf.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c973-dbe3-a9bb-f9734a010000</link>
      <description>Metcalf got a four-year, $132 million extension with the Steelers this offseason, but is also both younger than McLaurin and had more leverage after the Steelers surrendered a second-round pick to acquire him. The contract that the Commanders point to is Courtland Sutton, who signed a four-year, $92 million deal earlier in training camp. There’s a canyon between Metcalf’s $33 million a year and Sutton’s $23 million — it’s likely that McLaurin will have to settle for something closer to the midpoint of those two numbers than what Metcalf got. Unless of course he’d like his holdout to continue into the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c973-dbe3-a9bb-f9734a010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
