<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers DC Jeff Hafley will have a second interview with the Dolphins about the team’s open head coaching position next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc8e-d56e-afff-eeee183e0000</link>
      <description>Hafley is interviewing with the Steelers on Saturday and has fielded requests from the Raiders, Titans, Cardinals and Falcons as well. The 46-year-old coach has led a top-12 defense in each of his two seasons as the Packers’ defensive coordinator. Hafley is a natural fit with the Dolphins given his relationship with new Dolphins GM Jon-Eric Sullivan, who worked in the Packers’ front office for many years. Before joining the Packers, Hafley had a 22-26 record in four season as the head coach at Boston College.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc8e-d56e-afff-eeee183e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports John Morton joined the Broncos this week as a consultant for the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc96-d35e-a1bf-cdd6eecf0000</link>
      <description>Morton was fired as offensive coordinator of the Lions after the season, though he was stripped of play-calling duties midyear. The 56-year-old coach has coached under Sean Payton in New Orleans and Denver before, so his arrival with the Broncos this week isn’t a big surprise. Morton could find himself on Payton’s staff again next year as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc96-d35e-a1bf-cdd6eecf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Raiders will interview Panthers DC Ejiro Evero for a second time regarding its open head coaching position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cca0-d56e-afff-eee88a4f0000</link>
      <description>Evero met virtually with the Raiders this week and will have an in-person interview sometime next week. The 45-year-old defensive coordinator also has an interview with the Steelers coming up. Evero has been a defensive coordinator for the last four years (three with the Panthers, one with the Broncos) with mixed results, though he remains respected around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cca0-d56e-afff-eee88a4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports QB Aaron Rodgers isn’t expected to return to the Steelers next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ccd1-d56e-afff-eef9cb4c0000</link>
      <description>While Rodgers’ future in the NFL remains uncertain, it’s become clear he’s unlikely to continue quarterbacking the Steelers next season. Rapoport’s report that the 42-year-old signal caller isn’t expected to return to Pittsburgh comes on the heels of Steelers owner Art Rooney II saying as much at his press conference earlier this week. Rooney made it clear that Rodgers joined the Steelers last year to play for Mike Tomlin, who stepped down immediately following the team’s loss in the Wild Card round of the playoffs. Without Tomlin, there’s almost no chance of the Rodgers-Steelers partnership continuing. If Rodgers does ultimately decide to keep playing, there should be plenty of openings this offseason with the draft and free agency light on starting options. He’s still one final stop in Minnesota away from completing the Full Favre, though he engaged in discussions with the Vikings last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ccd1-d56e-afff-eef9cb4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Bills DT Ed Oliver (biceps) is less than 100 percent and will play limited snaps in the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd03-d35e-a1bf-cdc3fd0b0000</link>
      <description>The Bills activated Oliver along with WR Curtis Samuel (elbow, neck) from injured reserve earlier this week. While Oliver has missed all but three games this year, he recorded a sack in all three of those contests. Even in limited snaps, he should provide run-stuffing ability and pass rush juice while he’s out there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd03-d35e-a1bf-cdc3fd0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed former Giants interim HC Mike Kafka for their vacant offensive coordinator position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd29-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7a9d0000</link>
      <description>The team completed the interview Saturday following the parting of ways with former offensive coordinator Kevin Patullo, who was fired earlier in the week. The change comes in the wake of a 6.9 points per game decrease in scoring compared to their Super Bowl-winning season in 2024, meaning quarterback Jalen Hurts will operate with a sixth offensive coordinator in his seventh professional season when the new league year begins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd29-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7a9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) is inactive for the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd57-dc7a-af9b-cfffb8b10000</link>
      <description>Johnson came into the weekend listed as questionable after a single limited session in practice this week, ultimately deemed inactive for the second consecutive playoff contest. Expect Ray Davis to once again fill in as the primary change of pace and clear passing situation back, as he did in the Wild Card win over the Jaguars. Also inactive for the Bills are LB Terrel Bernard, S Jordan Poyer, CB Maxwell Hairston, OT Tylan Grable, DT Phidarian Mathis, and TE Keleki Latu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd57-dc7a-af9b-cfffb8b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared QB Sam Ehlinger, TE Caleb Lohner, WR Elijah Moore, ILB Karene Reid, CB Reese Taylor, OLB Que Robinson, and DL Sai’Vion Jones inactive for the Divisional Round against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd8f-d968-a19b-ddff76060000</link>
      <description>The Broncos begin their path to the Super Bowl as one of the healthier teams in the league after their Wild Card bye as the No. 1 seed in the AFC, enough so that they appear to have elevated two practice squad members, Elijah Moore and Caleb Lohner, to receive a small roster bonus as thanks for their time on the practice squad this season. The home-favorite Broncos face a difficult challenge against the Josh Allen-led Bills as they aim to avoid the same postseason outcome as in 2024 when the Bills bounced the Broncos in a blowout loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd8f-d968-a19b-ddff76060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers will interview former Giants HC Brian Daboll for their vacant offensive coordinator position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd9e-dc7a-af9b-cfbfeb670000</link>
      <description>Daboll has drawn significant interest for numerous vacant offensive coordinator positions around the league in recent weeks and could land on his feet with a change of scenery after a turbulent head coaching stint with the Giants. He also interviewed with the Titans on Friday for their vacant head coaching position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cd9e-dc7a-af9b-cfbfeb670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed former Ravens HC John Harbaugh to a five-year contract to be their next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cda1-d56e-afff-efe9a71e0000</link>
      <description>And... it’s done. After numerous delays amidst contract minutiae, the two sides have agreed on a five-year contract to make Harbaugh the team’s next head coach. The former Ravens head coach was one of the longest tenured head coaches in the league before being fired last week, quickly landing on his feet with one of the more desirable head coaching vacancies in the league. He’ll be tasked with turning around a franchise that has had little success in the post-Eli era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cda1-d56e-afff-efe9a71e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
