<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 2-of-8 targets for 40 yards in the Lions’ Week 4 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-920c-dca3-a9fb-bf9d49ba0000</link>
      <description>Williams has been a feast or famine fantasy bet this year, and managers were left starving after this one. Williams committed multiple drops and was the intended target on Jared Goff’s only interception of the day. Without a healthy diet of underneath targets, Williams’ doesn’t have much of a floor for fantasy purposes. He has been held to two catches in three consecutive games and has topped 50 yards once this year. Better days will be ahead for Williams, but predicting the next one grows more difficult by the week. He remains a boom/bust WR3 heading into Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-920c-dca3-a9fb-bf9d49ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 1-of-2 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in a Week 4 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9212-d6e9-af9d-9a928bfa0000</link>
      <description>The Bills didn’t use their tight ends much in this one, so Kincaid wasn’t asked to do much; however, he hauled in a crucial touchdown late in this game to allow the Bills to pull away from the Saints. Kincaid’s usage is going to make it hard for fantasy managers to rely on him every week, but he’s playing well this season now that he has recovered from his knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9212-d6e9-af9d-9a928bfa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 5-of-5 targets for 70 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 4 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9212-d95b-addb-fa56d7e80000</link>
      <description>It was the type of performance that was foretold in 2021 when the Falcons drafted Pitts No. 4 overall. The 70 yards Pitts totaled in Week 4 were his most since Week 8 of last season, and were buoyed by two gains of 20-plus yards. He broke free for a short seven-yard score early in the third quarter to give the Falcons a double-digit lead, and came up big late in the fourth quarter to help put the game on ice. Pitts has now caught four or more passes in every game this season and has gone for 50 or more yards twice. The Falcons now enter their Week 5 bye, but he should have some fantasy upside in Week 6 when they return to face the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9212-d95b-addb-fa56d7e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Palmer caught 2-of-3 targets for 25 yards in a Week 4 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9218-deb6-a7fd-d3df697b0000</link>
      <description>Palmer caught the first pass of the game for 14 yards but was relatively quiet after that. The 26-year-old continues to be on the field often for the Bills, but they have so many pass-catchers that they are willing to throw to, including their three tight ends, which makes it hard to count on him for fantasy production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9218-deb6-a7fd-d3df697b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 3-of-6 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in a Week 4 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-921a-d6e9-af9d-9a9a1dc10000</link>
      <description>Olave also threw an interception on a botched “Philly Special” play when the Saints were about to score to take the lead late in the second quarter. Olave also had a really bad drop on a potential first-down catch in the first half, but the New Orleans passing attack just seems dysfunctional right now. Olave is the main target in the passing game, but with Spencer Rattler under center, it’s really hard to think of him as anything more than a boom-or-bust WR3 in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-921a-d6e9-af9d-9a9a1dc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught 4-of-5 targets for 47 yards in a Week 4 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-921c-deb6-a7fd-d3df72a70000</link>
      <description>Shaheed led the Saints in catches and yards and had just one fewer target than Chris Olave. Still, it didn’t amount to much. Shaheed is a tremendous big-play threat, but this Saints offense doesn’t have to time or effectiveness to hit on deep plays with Spencer Rattler under center. That makes it hard to roster Shaheed in shallower fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-921c-deb6-a7fd-d3df72a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed seven times for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 4 win over the Panthers, adding two</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9217-d95b-addb-fa5778060000</link>
      <description>Rhamondre Stevenson “started,” but Henderson was on the field for snap No. 2. They ended up in an even rotation while again ceding work to Antonio Gibson, who also found the end zone. Henderson’s score was a rugged five-yarder in the second quarter where he really pushed the pile. It was undoubtedly something the Pats’ coaching staff had been wanting to see. We doubt anything really changes heading into Week 5 against the Bills, but Henderson at least held serve this afternoon. He remains a volatile FLEX option as New England sorts through a committee that has gone from two backs to three.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9217-d95b-addb-fa5778060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed seven times for 59 yards in the Commanders’ Week 4 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9219-deb6-a7fd-d3df22b20000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez saw 48 of his rushing yards come on a long run in the first quarter. Outside of that, it was a forgettable day for the third-year back, who again drew the start in the Commanders’ backfield. Rodriguez hasn’t seen a target through two games and has struggled to find any room to run outside of Sunday’s 48-yard run and last week’s 14-yard gain. Fantasy managers shouldn’t count on him in Week 5 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9219-deb6-a7fd-d3df22b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 3-of-4 targets for 39 yards in the Lions’ Week 4 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9216-d6e9-af9d-9a96e7b20000</link>
      <description>LaPorta has been held to four targets and fewer than 40 yards in each of the past three weeks. To be fair to LaPorta, the Lions have barely passed the ball during that stretch. Jared Goff has not attempted more than 28 passes since their blowout loss in Week 1. The bad news for LaPorta is that he and the Lions will be heavy favorites over the Bengals in Week 5. LaPorta will be stuck as a touchdown-dependent TE1 next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9216-d6e9-af9d-9a96e7b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
