<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans K Joey Slye (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5dd-db72-a199-ffdf27340000</link>
      <description>Slye is listed with a right calf injury for Wednesday. It is unclear when he suffered the injury as the 29-year-old kicked the game-winner in the Titans’ win over the Cardinals in Week 5. The Titans may look to add a kicker to the practice squad should Slye not practice the rest of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5dd-db72-a199-ffdf27340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5e8-d94a-a79d-cded652b0000</link>
      <description>Spears just returned from injured reserve due to an ankle injury he suffered before the season. He saw limited usage in his Week 5 return, but head coach Brian Callahan said on Monday his role will expand. Take this as a precautionary limited practice as the Titans ramp up Spears’ workload, but monitor his status throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5e8-d94a-a79d-cded652b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Van Jefferson (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ea-d94a-a79d-cdef816a0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson is seldom-used in the Titans’ passing game, getting just 12 snaps in Week 5. He did not practice Wednesday with an ankle injury. If Jefferson misses time, it could lead to increased snaps for Chimere Dike and Tyler Lockett, though no Titans receiver outside of Calvin Ridley or Elic Ayomanor should be considered for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ea-d94a-a79d-cdef816a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (ankle) did not participate Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5f6-db72-a199-ffffe08c0000</link>
      <description>Simmons did not participate in Wednesday’s practice while nursing an ankle injury. The 28-year-old is the Titans’ top defensive tackle and an important anchor for the defense. If he cannot go this week, Ashton Jeanty will have be in line for an even-better matchup against the Titans in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5f6-db72-a199-ffffe08c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOF Network’s Nick Underhill reports Saints RB Alvin Kamara is “day-to-day” with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5fb-d94a-a79d-cdffc2ef0000</link>
      <description>We have an update on the severity of Kamara’s ankle injury. Though initial reporting had his injury occurring on Wednesday, Underhill reports Kamara actually suffered the injury in the first half of the Saints’ Week 5 win against Giants and it “isn’t anything serious.” The veteran experienced soreness in practice and backed off of it. Should Kamara miss time, Kendre Miller is in the fantasy RB2 range. Regardless, Miller has been cutting into Kamara’s workload and needs to be rostered, while Kamara has fallen to the low-end RB2 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5fb-d94a-a79d-cdffc2ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c604-d94a-a79d-cf0d9e440000</link>
      <description>Johnston popped up on the injury report with a hamstring issue Wednesday. The 24-year-old is experiencing an electric start to the season but fumbled in a four-catch, 40-yard game in Week 5. The Chargers’ high usage of Johnston has frustrated Ladd McConkey owners so far this season. Should Johnston miss any time or be limited in Week 6, McConkey and Keenan Allen could see an uptick in targets, while rookies KeAndre Lambert-Smith and Tre Harris would compete for deep routes. Fantasy managers should stay tuned for Johnston’s practice status throughout the week. Meanwhile, WR Derius Davis (knee) was a non-participant in the Chargers’ receiving corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c604-d94a-a79d-cf0d9e440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald’s Doug Kyed reports Patriots practice squad RB Terrell Jennings “could have a gameday role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c611-db72-a199-fe5bcece0000</link>
      <description>Jennings has been on the Pats’ practice squad this season and could be next in line to rotate into the backfield with Antonio Gibson’s ACL injury. Head coach Mike Vrabel said, “He’s got a toughness to him. I think he’s improved.” Between Rhamondre Stevenson’s fumble issues and TreVeyon Henderson’s pass-protection struggles seemingly keeping him off the field, Jennings could carve out a meaningful role in the Patriots backfield with Gibson out for the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c611-db72-a199-fe5bcece0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c61c-db72-a199-fe5f04e70000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon missed Week 5 with his knee injury. The Seahawks were also missing S Julian Love (hamstring), LB Derick Hall (oblique), LB Ernest Jones (shoulder), EDGE Demarcus Lawrence (quad) on the defensive side of the ball. If they cannot practice the rest of the week, the Jaguars offense will have an easier matchup in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c61c-db72-a199-fe5f04e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip/rest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c621-d94a-a79d-cf2ddef30000</link>
      <description>Waller has started out hot with three touchdowns in his first two games with the Dolphins. He sits out Wednesday’s practice with the hip injury that kept him out for the start of the season. This is likely just a precautionary absence as he was also listed out with rest on the injury report. Waller is a low-end TE1 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c621-d94a-a79d-cf2ddef30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c627-dd4c-afb9-e7e70ba70000</link>
      <description>Godwin was dealing with some soreness in Week 5 and now starts out Week 6 not practicing due to a fibula issue. The 29-year-old returned from his major October 2024 ankle injury in Week 4, but is clearly not 100 percent yet. The possibility of Godwin missing Week 6 is on the table as his back-to-back weeks of three receptions for 26 yards show he is not at full speed for the Bucs’ receiving corps. Mike Evans (hamstring) remains out, which leaves Sterling Shepard as possibly the No. 2 Bucs wideout next to Emeka Egbuka for Week 6 should Godwin miss this week against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c627-dd4c-afb9-e7e70ba70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
