<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:03:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d39-d8cf-affb-bd3b1fb60000</link>
      <description>It’s a positive sign for London’s Week 16 availability against the Cardinals, though head coach Raheem Morris cautioned against assuming London will play Sunday. “Looking forward to seeing how much he’ll be able to give us this week,” Morris told reporters Wednesday. London has bee sidelined with a knee injury since the middle of November. The Falcons, eliminated from postseason contention, don’t have much reason to rush back (or play) their star receiver in the season’s final weeks. If London suits up in Week 16, he will be an elite option against an Arizona secondary that has been shredded of late. London’s return would put something of a damper on Kyle Pitts’ emergence and would make David Sills V unplayable in most formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d39-d8cf-affb-bd3b1fb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said WR Christian Watson (chest) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5b-d77b-adfb-efdb457d0000</link>
      <description>Three days after Watson was transported to a nearby hospital for evaluation of an upper body injury he sustained against the Broncos, he’ll practice in a limited capacity. “He’s improving. We’ll just see how he’s feeling out there,” LaFleur said. It’s a good sign for his Week 16 availability against the Bears. Watson has emerged as Green Bay’s WR1 over the past month, seeing 20 percent of the team’s targets for 35 percent of the air yards over that stretch. If Watson is sidelined in Week 16, Matthew Golden would have some intrigue as a volatile WR4 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5b-d77b-adfb-efdb457d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison, Jr. (heel) will practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5f-d1bc-a3fb-ad7f26480000</link>
      <description>Harrison, who sat out in Week 15 with the heel issue, could make yet another return to the Arizona lineup in time for a good matchup against a burnable Atlanta secondary dealing with myriad injuries going into Week 16. Harrison, who has 40 receptions over ten games this season, would profile as a WR3 play if he suits up and plays a full complement of snaps against the Falcons. The dominant Michael Wilson would go from a locked-in WR1 to an iffy WR3/4 with MHJ back in the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d5f-d1bc-a3fb-ad7f26480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes began rehab following surgery to repair his injured knee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d72-d77b-adfb-eff3bc8c0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs said Mahomes, who went down in Week 15’s loss to the Chargers, underwent surgery on Monday to repair the LCL part of his ACL/LCL ligament and immediately started his rehab. Mahomes has a shot to be under center for Kansas City to start the 2026 season, though it will be a close call considering he suffered the ACL injury in mid-December. ESPN’s Adam Schefter has said “it will be a surprise” if Mahomes is not ready for Week 1 in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d72-d77b-adfb-eff3bc8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (ankle/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d86-d1bc-a3fb-ada61c850000</link>
      <description>Head coach Matt LaFleur praised Jacobs’ toughness yesterday as he continues to battle through injuries to close out the regular season. Jacobs has been dealing with the knee issue for a while, though the ankle issue appears to be new. He played through the knee injury last week after logging a lone limited practice on Friday. Jacobs is likely headed for a similar practice routine this week. Fantasy managers may want to keep Emanuel Wilson on their bench in case Jacobs doesn’t play this week, which remains a possibility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d86-d1bc-a3fb-ada61c850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said S Josh Metellus (shoulder) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d8d-d8cf-affb-bdafbc8d0000</link>
      <description>Metellus will undergo surgery on his shoulder, sidelining him for the remainder of the season. He has been playing through the injury as of late, but there isn’t much point in that anymore with the Vikings out of the playoff hunt. His season ends with six pass breakups, two interceptions, and .5 sacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d8d-d8cf-affb-bdafbc8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d96-d8cf-affb-bdbe47d20000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw has been in and out of the lineup because of the knee issue this year. With the Vikings officially eliminated from the playoff hunt, he may have played his last snap of the season. Head coach Kevin O’Connell said both Justin Skule and Blake Brandel will get reps at left tackle in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d96-d8cf-affb-bdbe47d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d9a-d1bc-a3fb-adbe87870000</link>
      <description>Bateman was a late addition to the injury report last week. He was added to the report on Thursday and then downgraded to a DNP on Friday before being listed as questionable. Bateman was ultimately among the team’s inactives ahead of kickoff. A return to practice today is a step in the right direction, but fantasy managers will get more clarity later in the week. Either way, Bateman is not a particularly appealing fantasy option to close out the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2d9a-d1bc-a3fb-adbe87870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Quinnen Williams (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2da3-d005-a9bf-fdb754bd0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Brian Schottenheimer said Williams is doing better but remains in the league’s concussion protocol. A DNP to open the week will make it hard for him to clear the protocol ahead of Sunday’s game. As expected, Williams has been a massive upgrade for the Dallas defense. He has 1.5 sacks with the team and picked off J.J. McCarthy in Week 15. Losing him would likely send the Cowboys’ defense back to their early-season form.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2da3-d005-a9bf-fdb754bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dad-d005-a9bf-fdbd9f120000</link>
      <description>Wicks was listed as a DNP for Tuesday’s walkthrough. He will likely be limited in today’s practice, but that still puts him on track to suit up on Saturday. With Christian Watson banged up, Wicks could play a larger role than usual this week. He would be a high-risk WR5 if Watson is out for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dad-d005-a9bf-fdbd9f120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
