<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said CB Corey Thornton (fibula) is out for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bce0-d6c4-abfb-fee355bf0000</link>
      <description>He broke his fibula against the 49ers in Week 12’s Monday night game. The 2025 UDFA had been decent in spot duty for the Panthers, notching a 67.6 PFF coverage grade in 127 defensive snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bce0-d6c4-abfb-fee355bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed WR Brandin Cooks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bce4-db57-afda-fef605710000</link>
      <description>Cooks has just 1,081 yards over his last 36 games and will need to prove to us that he’ll be a fantasy factor before we recommend adding him in anything but the deepest leagues. He did have a lower-rung role with the Saints early in the season, with 15 targets in his first four weeks, but his work eventually dwindled. It’s a big-name add, but not necessarily one that shakes up the fantasy landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bce4-db57-afda-fef605710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (shoulder/illness) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcef-d90e-a9da-bfef26380000</link>
      <description>Turpin was a DNP on Monday. The shifty slot receiver/returner looks to be trending towards playing on a short week after taking three touches for a combined 52 yards on Sunday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcef-d90e-a9da-bfef26380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs TE Noah Gray (concussion) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf0-d82c-a79a-bff4bf410000</link>
      <description>Gray has slowly seen his role in the passing game grow over the past month, accumulating 12 targets in Kansas City’s last four games. It looks very unlikely he’ll be up for Thursday’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf0-d82c-a79a-bff4bf410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs G Trey Smith (ankle) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf3-d82c-a79a-bff7167f0000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back DNPs have the star guard looking unlikely to play against the Cowboys on Thanksgiving. He’s reportedly dealing with both “high- and low-ankle sprains,” per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. It wouldn’t be surprising if he missed multiple weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf3-d82c-a79a-bff7167f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (ankle) participated in full during Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf4-db57-afda-fef6a9410000</link>
      <description>If you were ever going to start Worthy again, you’d have to figure it would be against the Cowboys, right? But they’ve improved enough on defense over the last few games that Worthy is probably still just a questionable FLEX play in Week 13 with no teams on bye. Worthy upgraded from a limited practice on Monday and continues to have his ankle injury managed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf4-db57-afda-fef6a9410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd03-db57-afda-ff33ebac0000</link>
      <description>Neither did Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder), LB Noah Sewell (elbow), or CB Tyrique Stevenson (hip) on the estimated report. The good news is that Kyler Gordon and Jaylon Johnson, both on IR, practiced in full on Tuesday. Still, down several linebackers, this could be a smash spot for the struggling Saquon Barkley on Black Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd03-db57-afda-ff33ebac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said he “doesn’t see” S Kerby Joseph (knee) playing this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd08-d90e-a9da-bf0f7c3d0000</link>
      <description>Joseph hasn’t played since October 12. We appreciate how good Joseph is and understand that the Lions would rather have him out there if at all possible, but there’s literally an injured reserve for this sort of thing. Brian Branch (toe/ankle) got in a full session today to upgrade over a Monday limited, and Terrion Arnold (concussion) remained limited and may be trying to clear protocol tomorrow to make the active line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd08-d90e-a9da-bf0f7c3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Isaac TeSlaa (hand) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd0b-d90e-a9da-bf0f873e0000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa would seem to be the beneficiary if Kalif Raymond (ankle, DNP for second day in a row) can’t go on Thursday. No need to rush the rookie wideout into your lineups as he has yet to do better than one catch in a game this year, but perhaps he’ll be a worthwhile monitor on Thursday with an eye towards the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd0b-d90e-a9da-bf0f873e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd38-d6c4-abfb-ff3b97b30000</link>
      <description>We haven’t heard anything concerning about Jacobs’ chances of playing in Week 13 to this point. He certainly seems to be trending towards playing, though Wednesday’s status report will tell the full tale. Jacobs has practiced on a limited basis for four consecutive days dating back towards last week, and as long as he has his full range of motion, we expect to see him out there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd38-d6c4-abfb-ff3b97b30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
