<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak “could be of interest” if the Buccaneers were to move on from head coach Todd Bowles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80f5-d968-a19b-d8f525f50000</link>
      <description>Breer notes that the Buccaneers “just signed Todd Bowles to an extension through 2028 in June,” so moving on from him is an unlikely outcome. That said, the team suddenly finds itself “in the midst of a 1–7 slide, with a chance to miss the playoffs even with a win over the Panthers this weekend.” Ironically, Breer adds that “if a change comes,” he expects the Buccaneers to “look at young offensive coaches, like the ones they lost (Liam Coen, Dave Canales)” in recent seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80f5-d968-a19b-d8f525f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed OL Cole Van Lanen to a three-year, $51 million extension through 2028.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8110-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb0c10000</link>
      <description>Van Lanen, a fifth-year NFL veteran, is having a career year in his fourth season with the Jaguars. The versatile blocker has played all over the offensive line this season, taking snaps at left tackle (300), left guard (72), right guard (46) and right tackle (133). His 75.9 PFF pass-blocking grade and 78.9 PFF run-blocking grade both lead the team. The deal includes $32.5 million in guarantees and keeps Van Lanen in Jacksonville through his age-30 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8110-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb0c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “the general sense” is Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon will return next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-823e-d968-a19b-daff79e10000</link>
      <description>Something has to change with the Cardinals losing 13 of their last 14 games in Gannon’s third year on the job, just don’t expect it to be the 42-year-old former defensive coordinator’s job status. Despite Kyler Murray being injured for much of the season, the offseason focus will be on how they can get rid of Murray rather than Gannon, according to Rapoport. Gannon, who inherited Murray, will also have a say along with GM Monti Ossenfort in selecting the next Cardinals QB. With Murray’s years of failure in Arizona outnumbering Gannon’s, it seems he was destined to lose this power struggle. At some point, though, the results have to turn around for Gannon to remain in place past next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-823e-d968-a19b-daff79e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Raiders head coach Pete Carroll returning for a second season “would be a major surprise.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8476-dc7a-af9b-cfff59f50000</link>
      <description>One loss away from clinching the No. 1 overall pick in the 2026 NFL Draft, the Raiders seem ready to head into a full rebuild this offseason. Last offseason’s plan to bring in Carroll along with former Seahawks QB Geno Smith failed spectacularly. Carroll was brought in as a stabilizer after Antonio Pierce was fired after just one season, but the Raiders were arguably even more in disarray this year and it’s likely the 74-year-old coach will suffer the same fate. While the decision on Carroll will be made by Mark Davis, expect Raiders minority owner Tom Brady to have input on the next coach once the job presumably becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8476-dc7a-af9b-cfff59f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports signs continue to point towards Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel returning next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-847f-d968-a19b-dcffd9e60000</link>
      <description>McDaniel, whose contract runs through 2028, has rebounded nicely this season. After a 1-6 start, the Dolphins have gone 6-3. The 42-year-old coach sacked quarterback Tua Tagoovailoa, who’s unlikely to play again for the Dolphins, according to Rapoport. Quinn Ewers showed some promise in his limited action. With McDaniel likely safe, the team is still looking for a new GM and has enlisted the services of Troy Aikman as a consultant. Coaching staff changes are also possible and the Dolphins will probably looking for a new quarterback as well, but have some stability with their head coach expected back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-847f-d968-a19b-dcffd9e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports 49ers LT Trent Williams’ (hamstring) status is “up in the air” for Week 18’s game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-848b-d56e-afff-e6eb75000000</link>
      <description>Williams hasn’t practiced this week, but head coach Kyle Shanahan left the door open for him to play. Fowler reports Williams should be good for the playoffs, but his status is up in the air for Saturday night’s battle for the No. 1 seed in the NFC Playoffs. The 49ers will see how Williams feels pregame, but they also don’t want him to make the injury he originally suffered just last week worse, according to Fowler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-848b-d56e-afff-e6eb75000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports 49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (back/knee) is hopeful to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8491-d35e-a1bf-c5d356280000</link>
      <description>Pearsall played through his various ailments last week against the Bears and managed to haul in five receptions for 85 yards. After practicing in a limited fashion all week, it seems like the 25-year-old wide receiver is prepared to play through pain once again. Pearsall is an upside WR3 despite the difficult matchup against the Seahawks in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8491-d35e-a1bf-c5d356280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals head coach Zac Taylor “is not going anywhere.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8495-d968-a19b-dcf504f20000</link>
      <description>Since going to the Super Bowl and Conference Championship Game in back-to-back years, the Bengals have now missed the playoffs for the third straight year. While Joe Burrow missed significant time in two of the last three seasons, Taylor has overseen the Bengals defense get progressively worse over that time. This year’s version has already allowed 472 points, which is the most in franchise history with one game still to go. Still, it’s really no surprise that Taylor is being brought back considering the devotion the Bengals ownership has already shown him as well as previous coaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8495-d968-a19b-dcf504f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lions head coach Dan Campbell will search for a new offensive coordinator this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-849d-d35e-a1bf-c5dfb85f0000</link>
      <description>Campbell took over play-calling duties in Week 10 after a disastrous loss at home to the Vikings where offensive coordinator John Morton’s lack of adjustments seemed to cost the Lions offense. Morton was blunt in his assessment of that game, putting the blame on the players, specifically the offensive line. Whether Campbell or Morton was calling plays this year, the Lions lost all seven games where they failed to rush for 100 yards after only rushing for less than 100 yards twice in the previous season. Fixing the run game will likely take new personnel along the offensive line, as Morton seemed to suggest, but after losing Ben Johnson and bringing in Morton last offseason, Campbell is still on the lookout for a new offensive coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-849d-d35e-a1bf-c5dfb85f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers added WR Chris Godwin (illness) to the injury report Saturday but he is expected to play in Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-851f-d35e-a1bf-c5df58660000</link>
      <description>Godwin is caught up in the sickness sweeping the league, with the team adding him to the injury report Saturday. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the veteran receiver is expected to play as the Buccaneers fight to keep their season alive against the Panthers later today, giving quarterback Baker Mayfield his full compliment of pass-catching weapons in the must-win game. We’ll get final word when the team releases inactives 90 minutes prior to first kick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-851f-d35e-a1bf-c5df58660000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
