<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Sam Howell, LB Joshua Uche, DT Ty Robinson, CB Mac McWilliams, OT Lane Johnson, WR Xavier Gipson, and RB A.J. Dillon inactive for Week 13 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc3-db57-afda-dff343e70000</link>
      <description>Johnson is the only notable player on this list, and he was ruled out on Thursday. The Eagles are operating at near full strength as they prepare to host the 8-3 Bears in a clash of division leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbc3-db57-afda-dff343e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lane Johnson (foot) is targeting Philadelphia’s Week 15 game against the Raiders for a return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbd2-d6c4-abfb-dfd3560a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson left Week 11’s game against the Lions with the injury and this would set him up to miss three games before returning. The Eagles have struggled on offense without Johnson, though they’ve really struggled with consistency all year so that’s not a major surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbd2-d6c4-abfb-dfd3560a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans ruled out C Lloyd Cushenberry (foot) for Week 13 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbdb-d82c-a79a-fbdf59c80000</link>
      <description>Cushenberry’s absence is unfortunate. The Jaguars’ pass rush has played well in recent weeks. The Titans also ruled out DT Shy Tuttle (concussion), S Xavier Woods (hamstring), S Kendell Brooks (concussion) and CB Jalyn Armour-Davis (Achilles). Armour-Davis’ injury is a bit concerning. He was downgraded to a DNP on Thursday. Hopefully, it is only a short-term issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbdb-d82c-a79a-fbdf59c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans confirmed C.J. Stroud (concussion) cleared protocol and will start against the Colts on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbe3-d82c-a79a-fbf7b4600000</link>
      <description>Jalen Pitre, too, cleared protocol and will take on the current AFC South leaders. Stroud will be on the QB2 line after a long layoff, but has done reasonably well against the Colts over his two NFL seasons to date. Indianapolis’ defense, while improved with the return of Charvarius Ward and Sauce Gardner, isn’t a bad matchup from a fantasy perspective.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbe3-d82c-a79a-fbf7b4600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR DK Metcalf (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbea-db57-afda-dffaa0980000</link>
      <description>Metcalf took the day off on Wednesday before practicing fully from there on out. The Bills’ run defense is a fantasy-friendly unit and the cornerback corps is solid. Metcalf remains a borderline WR2/3, though, based on talent and target share. He will have QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) back in the lineup this weekend as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbea-db57-afda-dffaa0980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (pectoral) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbf1-db57-afda-dff39e2f0000</link>
      <description>Highsmith has not played since Week 10. Getting him back provides the Steelers’ pass rush with a big boost. The Steelers will also have CB Joey Porter Jr. (hip) on the field when they take on the Bills this weekend. Both Highsmith and Porter practiced full on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbf1-db57-afda-dff39e2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) will get a chance to establish the “hot hand” in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbf5-d82c-a79a-fbf578020000</link>
      <description>Speaking with reporters on Friday, Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said that once Irving “gets in, we’ll see how he is rolling, and then between him, Rachaad [White] and Sean [Tucker], we’ll kind of go with the hot hand.” Bowles’ phrasing suggests Irving will be given the first chance to establish the hot hand. The team had already made clear that Irving would be eased into action, so the hot hand approach makes sense. It is never what we want to hear for fantasy purposes, though. Irving is the most talented player of the bunch. If he can get going early, he has a chance to return RB2 value or better, but his floor is lower than it typically would be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbf5-d82c-a79a-fbf578020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (concussion) won’t play in Minnesota’s Week 13 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbec-db57-afda-dffe3b3b0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy got in limited sessions all week and should be a possibility to play in Week 14, if the Vikings actually want to do that to themselves. Max Brosmer will start in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cbec-db57-afda-dffe3b3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (back) is questionable to play in Week 13 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc07-db57-afda-de3763730000</link>
      <description>New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill reported yesterday that Olave is dealing with back spasms and is considered day-to-day with the issue. His return to practice today is a good sign, though unfortunately, we will have to track his status this weekend. If active, he remains a WR2 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc07-db57-afda-de3763730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said Max Brosmer will start Minnesota’s Week 13 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc0a-d6c4-abfb-de0b34780000</link>
      <description>Brosmer will walk into a tough situation for a first start against a top-5 DVOA defense on the road in Seattle. Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison should keep it from being downright unbearable, and it’s hard to imagine he’ll do as poorly as J.J. McCarthy did against the Packers last week, but the floor could still be quite low for the rookie UDFA. It would be a victory for the Vikings if Brosmer can escape the bottom of the superflex ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc0a-d6c4-abfb-de0b34780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
