<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:09:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver reports that the Eagles “might draft a quarterback this spring.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84b-dc7a-af9b-cfffa81b0000</link>
      <description>Silver adds that Eagles backup QB Tanner McKee “is also highly regarded within the building.” Hurts reportedly “fashions himself” as the NFL’s Michael Jordan, chasing excellence with a “hyper-focus that can come off as aloofness.” He has reportedly “been the source of much internal frustration, including from teammates other than” WR A.J. Brown. That said, Hurts “likely isn’t going anywhere anytime soon.” There is “a sense inside the locker room” that head coach Nick Sirianni, general manager Howie Roseman and owner Jeffrey Lurie “are reluctant to criticize Hurts,” and Lurie “remains confident that an offseason reset can thrust Philly back into Super Bowl contention.” Hurts, 27, did not have a good year, but he led the team to a Super Bowl victory one year ago and has three years left on the five-year, $255 million extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84b-dc7a-af9b-cfffa81b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers completed an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8ea-dc7a-af9b-cfffd3950000</link>
      <description>Yesterday, ESPN’s Jeff Darlington reported that the Buccaneers’ offensive coordinator could appeal to McDaniel because it gives him “full autonomy of the offense,” with head coach Todd Bowles focused on the defensive side of the football. The Eagles, Lions and Chargers are also reportedly interested in hiring McDaniel as their next offensive coordinator, though all three teams possess offensive-minded head coaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8ea-dc7a-af9b-cfffd3950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders will interview Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8f6-dc7a-af9b-cfff0d5e0000</link>
      <description>This is Brady’s first reported connection to the Raiders. He and the Bills notably take on the Broncos on Saturday. If things go well, he will have yet another positive mark on his resume as he heads into the interview. His offense is averaging 5.9 yards per play, ranking fourth among Divisional Round competitors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8f6-dc7a-af9b-cfff0d5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders will interview with 49ers OC Klay Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8fa-d56e-afff-eefa0c200000</link>
      <description>Only two days ago, Kubiak had zero reported interview invites. Now he is slated to interview for both the Steelers and Raiders’ head-coaching vacancies. Good for him. Kubiak’s offense has helped propel the 49ers into the Divisional Round, with the defense’s front-seven being hampered by injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8fa-d56e-afff-eefa0c200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver believes it is “untenable” for the Eagles to “stay the course” with WR A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff56bb0000</link>
      <description>Silver notes that Brown’s talents are not being maximized. After this season, we tend to agree. Were the Eagles to trade him, though, it would create more than $72 million in dead money. Silver believes that “the team and potential suitors might need to find a more creative solution, such as a preemptively reworked contract.” Of course, hiring a brilliant offensive coordinator could always fix things. Brown’s discontent is well documented, but revamping roles may simply be the best and easiest fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff56bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c926-d35e-a1bf-cde639e70000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that Gannon had interviewed with the Cowboys earlier this week, ostensibly via video. The Cowboys are reportedly set to host two more in-person meetings, one with Eagles DB coach and pass game coordinator Christian Parker and the other with Vikings DB coach and pass game coordinator and Daronte Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c926-d35e-a1bf-cde639e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Giants are still expected to sign former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh to a five-year contract to be their next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c929-d35e-a1bf-cdeb63530000</link>
      <description>Over the last few hours, multiple reports have indicated that the two sides are still expected to come to an agreement. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “seems like something was lost in translation” during early negotiations, specifically regarding the “reporting structure” and decision-making powers. He adds that the Titans are still “interested and waiting” to find out what happens, while noting that former Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski could be “the one” for the Giants if things fall through with Harbaugh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c929-d35e-a1bf-cdeb63530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers will interview former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c971-d35e-a1bf-cdf3eb620000</link>
      <description>This would be a fun pairing. The Chargers’ offense stagnated this season, with veteran WR Keenan Allen operating as the No. 1 target earner. One imagines McDaniel would draw up some fantasy-friendly concepts for QB Justin Herbert and WR Ladd McConkey if he were to be offered and accept the role. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the interview “will likely happen early next week.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c971-d35e-a1bf-cdf3eb620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “remains to be seen” whether the Eagles want to keep WR A.J. Brown on the roster for the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c916-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0370000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, there are questions as to whether Brown and QB Jalen Hurts “can be together for another season.” He also states bluntly that if the team wishes to trade him away, they will take a cap hit to do so. Earlier today, The Athletic’s Mike Silver reported something similar, though he believes the Eagles and a potential trade partner “might need to find a more creative solution, such as a preemptively reworked contract.” Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c916-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c975-d56e-afff-effd47980000</link>
      <description>Shula, 39, will also interview for the Titans, Steelers, Giants, Cardinals and Raiders’ head-coaching vacancies. The Rams face the Bears’ explosive offense on Sunday, in a contest that will determine one of the two representatives in the NFC Championship Game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c975-d56e-afff-effd47980000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
