<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the 49ers are still “expecting” WR Brandon Aiyuk (knee) to return later this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5604-d673-a39e-f695411e0000</link>
      <description>In early August, 49ers GM John Lynch said he did not “think” Aiyuk would be able to return for the team’s Week 1 game against the Seahawks. Roughly one week later, 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said Aiyuk was “on track to be back around Week 6.” His latest supposition has been that Aiyuk could return in Week 10. Despite Schefter’s report, the team has not yet activated Aiyuk’s 21-day practice window, suggesting he is more than three weeks away from returning. He still has time to return before the season’s end, but one wonders how many games he can reasonably be expected to appear in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5604-d673-a39e-f695411e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (concussion) will not play in Week 10 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5610-d1e7-a1fa-5efa1d940000</link>
      <description>Mims returned to practice this week but failed to clear the league’s concussion protocol ahead of Thursday’s game. He should be back for a pivotal game against the Chiefs in Week 11. Troy Franklin and Courtland Sutton will continue to dominate the Broncos’ targets in his absence. RJ Harvey could also see a few more designed touches once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5610-d1e7-a1fa-5efa1d940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Surtain (pec) will not play in Week 10 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5612-d1e7-a1fa-5efab7fc0000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as the Broncos are expected to be without Surtain for a few weeks. He suffered a pec strain in Week 8 and has yet to return to practice. His absence will make things a bit easier for Geno Smith and company on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5612-d1e7-a1fa-5efab7fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones (shoulder/toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5614-d673-a39e-f695b5090000</link>
      <description>Jones suffered an AC joint sprain in Week 9. The injury is believed to be minor, but a DNP to open the week suggests it could sideline him for at least one game. As if things couldn’t get worse, Jones is also dealing with a toe injury, though it doesn’t sound like that would be the reason for him to miss Week 10. If he is ruled out, Jordan Mason will take over the backfield once again, putting him on the RB2/3 border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5614-d673-a39e-f695b5090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5617-d713-ad9e-7e57e4620000</link>
      <description>Highsmith missed two games earlier this year because of an ankle issue. It’s unclear if this is related or something new. Either way, his odds of playing in Week 10 are 50/50 at best right now. With Pittsburgh’s defense already struggling this year, the last thing they needed was to lose one of their best pass-rushers. Highsmith has 3.5 sacks and a forced fumble in six games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5617-d713-ad9e-7e57e4620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-561d-d45b-affe-579ff7630000</link>
      <description>Brown left Week 9’s game against the Raiders with a concussion and did not return. A limited session puts him on track to play in Week 10, but he still has a few hurdles to clear in the league’s concussion protocol. With Brian Thomas Jr. unlikely to play, Brown will start alongside Parker Washington and Jakobi Meyers in three-receiver sets. He will have some low-end WR4 value if he is ready to go by Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-561d-d45b-affe-579ff7630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars LB Devin Lloyd (calf) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5620-d1e7-a1fa-5eeac5960000</link>
      <description>Lloyd returned to practice last week and was listed as questionable on Friday. He only practiced in a limited capacity, however, and the Jags ultimately ruled him out on Sunday. A full practice today means he should be good to go for Week 10. Lloyd had four interceptions, one of which was a pick-six, before going down in Week 6. His return will be a big boost for a Jags defense facing off against Davis Mills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5620-d1e7-a1fa-5eeac5960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Long (hip/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5623-d45b-affe-57b7c4830000</link>
      <description>Long had been filling in for Brenton Strange, who remains on injured reserve with quad and hip injuries. Johnny Mundt would be the next man up if Long is out for Week 10. We don’t expect Long’s absence to create any fantasy value for Mundt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5623-d45b-affe-57b7c4830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt (tooth) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562a-d45b-affe-57bea0540000</link>
      <description>JCM apparently had some dental work done recently. That is not a joke. The Commanders put him in a non-contact jersey for Wednesday’s practice. There’s no reason to believe he will miss Sunday’s game against the Lions. Bill doesn’t have a role in the passing game, making him entirely dependant on game script. As a massive underdog to the Lions, he is stuck in the RB3 ranks for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562a-d45b-affe-57bea0540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562f-d45b-affe-57bf1d260000</link>
      <description>Fellow starting tackle Taylor Decker also missed Wednesday’s practice with a shoulder issue. He has been dealing with the issue for a while but has played through it for the past two weeks. Sewell’s shoulder injury is new, though it is not believed to be a long-term issue. Left guard Christian Mahogany, however, is expected to miss extended time because of a leg injury. All in, the Lions are either going to be slightly undermanned in the trenches this week or drastically undermanned. The hope will be that both tackles can suit up, but this is a situation to monitor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-562f-d45b-affe-57bf1d260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
