<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 20:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs TE Travis Kelce “plans to play in each of the final three games this season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e0-d087-addf-b9f08d460000</link>
      <description>We assumed this would be the case, but it is good to know nonetheless. The Chiefs are eliminated from playoff contention and Kelce’s “best friend on the roster,” QB Patrick Mahomes (knee),” is out for the year. The 36-year-old tight end needs just 203 receiving yards to “become the oldest tight end in the NFL’s history to record 1,000 yards in a season.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e0-d087-addf-b9f08d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee) is likely to be activated for Week 16’s game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c6e-da28-afbb-fc7f57b30000</link>
      <description>This report comes on the heels of Diggs himself telling reporters earlier this week that he was healthy. The 27-year-old cornerback seemed miffed about not being activated from injured reserve earlier. If Diggs isn’t activated Saturday, he’ll be ineligible to return at all this year. While Rapoport reports an activation is likely, the final decision will come Saturday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c6e-da28-afbb-fc7f57b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) is expected to play in Week 16’s game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c73-d35e-a1bf-7df3a6d20000</link>
      <description>Swift popped up on the injury report Wednesday with a groin injury and practiced in a limited fashion on Thursday and Friday. While the 26-year-old running back is still listed as questionable, Fowler reports that he’s expected to play. Swift, coming off his best game of the season, is an RB2 against the Packers in Week 16. He could also see additional pass game usage with the Bears down multiple receivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c73-d35e-a1bf-7df3a6d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts DT DeForest Buckner (neck) will play in Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce4-d35e-a1bf-7de6a8a10000</link>
      <description>Buckner hasn’t played since Week 9 due to a neck injury. The 31-year-old defensive tackle began practicing again last week. Colts coach Shane Steichen told reporters Saturday that Buckner will play. His return could be important for the Colts’ defensive line as they look to get after Brock Purdy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce4-d35e-a1bf-7de6a8a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts ruled out CB Sauce Gardner (calf) for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce8-dc7a-af9b-ffff546e0000</link>
      <description>Colts coach Shane Steichen answered in the affirmative when asked Saturday if Gardner would play again this season. That bodes well for the 25-year-old cornerback, who so far has avoided injured reserve despite a calf injury. Gardner will be out for Week 16’s matchup with the 49ers, but the Colts clearly believe he’ll return for at least one of the last two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3ce8-dc7a-af9b-ffff546e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed RB Dameon Pierce to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cf8-d35e-a1bf-7dfa64b10000</link>
      <description>The team waived running back Elijah Mitchell in an associated move. Mitchell had been active in only once game this season, whereas Pierce can contribute to special teams on game day. The Chiefs enter “evaluation mode” for the first time in over a decade after being eliminated from postseason contention in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cf8-d35e-a1bf-7dfa64b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns placed T Jack Conklin (concussion) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cfe-d35e-a1bf-7dfeaff80000</link>
      <description>The move ends the veteran tackle’s season in what amounts to an evaluation year. The Browns continue to experience multiple injuries along an aging offensive line, something they could look to address in the coming offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3cfe-d35e-a1bf-7dfeaff80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports TE Gunnar Helm (toe) and WR Van Jefferson (back) are expected to play in Week 16 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d07-d35e-a1bf-7dc71af40000</link>
      <description>Both entered the weekend listed as questionable but it appears as if rookie quarterback Cam Ward will have his normal supporting cast available for a marquee matchup with the Chiefs on Sunday. Neither player is overly enticing in a fantasy setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d07-d35e-a1bf-7dc71af40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed K Charlie Smyth to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d11-d35e-a1bf-7dd3ea360000</link>
      <description>The kicker from Northern Ireland made his NFL debut just last month and now sticks with the Saints for the next three seasons. Smyth is 4-fo-5 in field goal attempts and has hit all five point after tries. The specifics of the contract are not yet available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d11-d35e-a1bf-7dd3ea360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated CB Trevon Diggs (knee) ahead of Week 16 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</link>
      <description>The team also placed fellow cornerback DaRon Bland (foot) on injured reserve in an associated move. As has been the case for most of the season, the Cowboys continue forward without pieces from their secondary. Diggs pushed his return up to the limit, meaning we might not see him play a full allotment of snaps in his first game in over two months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
