<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns won’t open Deshaun Watson’s 21-day practice window ahead of Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7346-d673-a39e-f7d719300000</link>
      <description>Watson, according to Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot, has made “excellent progress” in recovering from his re-ruptured Achilles tendon but won’t start practicing this week. Cabot said Watson “must first pass his medical exams before being permitted to practice. Once he’s cleared, the Browns must be reasonably sure he’ll be ready for action before they open the window.” Browns QBs coach Bill Musgrave said Watson, 29, is determined to return to game action one day. “I know he wants to play a lot of football again,” Musgrave said. “He feels like he’s got a lot of tread left on his tires.” There remains very little chance Watson, who has played 19 games since the start of the 2022 season, will suit up for Cleveland in 2025. Dillon Gabriel will be under center in Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7346-d673-a39e-f7d719300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow (toe) said he’s targeting a Week 13 return to game action.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73af-d1e7-a1fa-7bef78600000</link>
      <description>The oft-injured Burrow, who suffered his toe injury in Week 2, said the Bengals’ record and postseason hopes could factor into whether he returns this season. “We’ll see how these next couple weeks go,” Burrow said in his first news conference since the injury. “There’s a lot that goes into it. There’s a lot of variables that you have to consider.” Burrow on Monday practiced for the first time since September, “throwing passes to receivers not facing any defenders,” according to ESPN’s Ben Baby. Burrow, Baby said, “sported a different pair of shoes during his limited practice and acknowledged there is additional hardware in his cleats.” Joe Flacco is set to start Week 11 against the Steelers. Burrow should be rostered in all fantasy formats in case he returns in the season’s final month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73af-d1e7-a1fa-7bef78600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said RB Jaylen Warren could see more touches in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73ee-d1e7-a1fa-7bee11500000</link>
      <description>Tomlin said the only thing that stopped Warren from exceeding the 18 touches he saw in Week 10 against the Chargers was game script and the Steelers’ inability to convert third downs. With shortened drives, Warren’s workload was not nearly as big as it could have been, Tomlin suggested in his Tuesday press conference. “We win more third downs, Jaylen [Warren] will get more touches,” he said. Warren accounted for 41 percent of the Steelers’ offensive production in Week 10’s loss while losing out to Kenneth Gainwell on third down opportunities. That, Tomlin said, would continue. Warren will be a top-12 fantasy play in Week 11 against an abysmal Bengals front seven.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73ee-d1e7-a1fa-7bee11500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders placed G Jackson Powers-Johnson (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73ff-d673-a39e-f7ffe6000000</link>
      <description>It’s a blow to the Vegas offensive line. Powers-Johnson suffered his ankle injury in Week 10 against the Broncos and did not return to the game. Pro Football Focus has graded Powers-Johnson as the NFL’s 44th best pass blocking guard this season and the league’s 24th best run blocking guard. The Raiders have the fourth worst rushing success rate this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73ff-d673-a39e-f7ffe6000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed K Greg Joseph to the team’s practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7405-d45b-affe-7597a11e0000</link>
      <description>The move comes after Daniel Carlson missed a critical field goal in Week 10’s narrow loss to the Broncos. Carlson has made just 12 of his 16 field goal tries this season while missing one extra point. It looks like the Raiders could be ready to move on from Carlson if he misses a kick in Week 11 against the Cowboys. Joseph appeared in eight games in 2024, attempting 20 field goals and converting 16 of them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7405-d45b-affe-7597a11e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rob Demovsky reports Packers C Elgton Jenkins (leg) suffered a fracture in Week 10’s loss to Philadelphia.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7439-d1e7-a1fa-7efbb4020000</link>
      <description>Packers coach Matt LaFleur is on record saying that the injury “doesn’t sound promising.” Jenkins sounds like a candidate to spend some time on injured reserve. Sean Rhyan replaced Jenkins at center and figures to be the replacement in the short term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7439-d1e7-a1fa-7efbb4020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes believes Browns HC Kevin Stefanski is “a name to watch” for the Giants head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-745d-d673-a39e-f4dd91730000</link>
      <description>Stefanski certainly couldn’t be blamed for wanting to exit Cleveland after another season spent coordinating a dead-on-arrival offense hamstrung by Deshaun Watson’s contract. Especially after he didn’t appear to be on Andrew Berry’s page about giving up Joe Flacco to the Bengals in a midseason trade. As we hit silly season, Stefanski’s status will be one of the more important dominoes to watch. Hughes also mentions as names to watch for the job: Packers DC Jeff Hafley, Rams OC Mike LaFleur, Eagles OC Kevin Patullo (??), Chiefs DC Steve Spagnuolo, Vikings DC Brian Flores, Former Raiders HC Antonio Pierce, and Texans DC Matt Burke.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-745d-d673-a39e-f4dd91730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ian Rapoport reports Travis Hunter (knee/IR) underwent season-ending surgery to repair a torn LCL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-748e-d673-a39e-f49f145b0000</link>
      <description>Hunter is going to be ready for full football activities in six months, so he should be fully ready for training camp. What to make of this rookie year? It was a year of waiting for something to launch. There were no touchdowns until (what would become) his final game of the season, where the Jaguars forced balls to him with aplomb in garbage time against the Rams. The target rate was there, and then it wasn’t, and then it was again. The two major elephants in the room for him this offseason will be what happens (or doesn’t) with Brian Thomas Jr., and whether or not he’ll continue to be a two-way player following the injury. We expect the status quo to rule this situation — mostly because of what the Jags invested in Hunter and Thomas — and for Hunter to roll into the 2026 season as WR3 in fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-748e-d673-a39e-f49f145b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed CB Asante Samuel Jr. to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-74bc-d673-a39e-f4bd15520000</link>
      <description>The Asante Samuel tour of America ends early, as he had been threatening to keep it rolling in other towns later this week. Samuel had spinal-fusion surgery after heading to IR early in the 2024 season. A once-promising high second-round pick, he’s still only 26 years old. If he can play anything like his old form, the Steelers did well to roster him. The fact that he’s signed with the practice squad shows an NFL that is pretty skeptical he’ll return to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-74bc-d673-a39e-f4bd15520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL suspended Buccaneers RB Josh Williams six games for violating the league’s performance-enhancing substances policy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-74c1-d673-a39e-f4d113ca0000</link>
      <description>Williams is mainly a special teamer, so this carries little in the way of fantasy implications. Perhaps one of Tampa’s practice squad backs, Owen Wright or Michael Wiley, will be more involved with the offense — we doubt it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-74c1-d673-a39e-f4d113ca0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
