<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</link>
      <description>Not one of Hopkins’ four catches was routine as the veteran receiver made several spectacular grabs throughout. Arguably the most impressive was a ball down the sideline that deflected off the defenders hands, which he corralled in time to drag the trailing foot as he headed to the ground. Hopkins doesn’t play enough snaps for the low volume Ravens to warrant weekly fantasy consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are never a high pass volume offense, but things got worse in this one following the departure of starting quarterback Lamar Jackson in the second quarter. The team shifted to a heavier emphasis on Derrick Henry in the second half, which appeared to be working until they allowed the Patriots to overcome an 11-point fourth quarter deficit to steal the win. Now at the tail end of his career, Andrews rarely returns fantasy utility if he is held out of the end zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lamar Jackson is day-to-day with a back bruise.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-462e-d35e-a1bf-47ee7b190000</link>
      <description>The back injury Jackson suffered in the second quarter of Sunday’s loss to the Patriots ended up sidelining him for the remainder of the game, but it sounds like he’ll have a chance to return in Week 17 against the Packers. The Ravens are hanging onto their playoff hopes by a thread, needing to win out over the final two weeks of the season while also needing the Steelers to lose their final two games. Facing a true do-or-die scenario next week, the Ravens will hope Jackson can return under center come Saturday. If he’s unable to go, Tyler Huntley would draw the start in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-462e-d35e-a1bf-47ee7b190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Little converted both of his field goal attempts in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4448-d35e-a1bf-45ca0ce90000</link>
      <description>The big-footed Little continues to be one of the NFL’s most reliable kickers. He’s missed just four kicks this season — making 88 percent of his kicks — while making 43 of 44 extra point tries. Little has benefited from the neutral and positive game script created by a red hot Jacksonville offense. He’ll be a solid option in Week 17 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4448-d35e-a1bf-45ca0ce90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) was discharged from the hospital on Sunday night.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4638-d968-a19b-5ef9869c0000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Jeff Legwold, Bryant was diagnosed with a concussion “but cleared of other major injuries” after leaving on a stretcher in Week 16’s loss to the Jaguars. Bryant was also tested for a neck injury, but those tests came back negative, per Legwold. Bryant is probably a long shot to clear concussion protocol in time to be ready for Week 17’s game against the Chiefs, but it sounds like he avoided all serious injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4638-d968-a19b-5ef9869c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the league will review the situation between DK Metcalf and a fan in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4642-dc7a-af9b-cfffd1fa0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was seen jawing with a Lions fan in the first half of Sunday’s game, and appeared to throw a punch in the direction of the fan. The fan involved in the incident spoke with a member of theDetroit Free Pressafter the game, and said Metcalf came over to him after he called him by his full name. Metcalf will almost certainly be fined for his involvement with the fan, but a suspension could also be on the table. We would expect to hear a final decision on this later in the day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4642-dc7a-af9b-cfffd1fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Malik Willis (shoulder) is “pretty sore” after Week 16’s loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-464b-d968-a19b-5efbef110000</link>
      <description>Speaking with the media on Sunday, LaFleur discussed the health of both his quarterbacks and said Willis’ injury is “a legitimate deal that he’s dealing with.” While Willis is dealing with a shoulder injury, Jordan Love suffered a concussion in Saturday’s win and will be in concussion protocol to start the week. If both quarterbacks are unable to go this week, 2023 fifth-rounder Clayton Tune would draw the start against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-464b-d968-a19b-5efbef110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Jordan Love is in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-467c-d968-a19b-5efd57820000</link>
      <description>Love suffered a head injury in the second quarter of the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears. He took a hard helmet-to-helmet shot on the play and was visibly shaken up afterward, and was ruled out shortly after leaving the field. Love will have to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to play in Saturday’s game against the Ravens. If he is unable to go, Malik Willis (shoulder) would be next in line to draw the start, with Clayton Tune being the third man up if both players are sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-467c-d968-a19b-5efd57820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports J.J. McCarthy will undergo an MRI on his hand.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4686-d35e-a1bf-47c6603b0000</link>
      <description>X-rays on McCarthy’s hand reportedly came back negative for a broken bone. McCarthy will undergo an MRI to determine the exact nature of the injury that knocked him out of Week 16’s game against the Giants, but if the MRI doesn’t reveal anything severe, we would expect him to have a chance to suit up in Week 17 against the Lions. If McCarthy is unable to go, Max Brosmer would make his second career start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4686-d35e-a1bf-47c6603b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Brady Cook will start in Week 17 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46bc-d56e-afff-e6fc64150000</link>
      <description>The Jets continue to evaluate their quarterback position ahead of the offseason. Cook took a whopping eight sacks in Week 16’s loss to the Saints and will have a chance to take eight more in next week’s game against the Patriots. Cook can be avoided in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46bc-d56e-afff-e6fc64150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
