<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colby Parkinson suffered a sprained AC join in the Rams’ Week 1 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b22-dbe3-a9bb-3b73d5f20000</link>
      <description>This injury doesn’t bear any weight on the fantasy community, but Parkinson, who did play through the injury, appeared on 29 offensive snaps for the Rams last season and has been a key player on their offense since joining them last offseason. It’s possible he’ll play in Week 2 against the Titans, but if not, Davis Allen would appear next in line to play in 2TE sets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b22-dbe3-a9bb-3b73d5f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Eagles are hosting free agent WR Quez Watkins for a workout on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b2a-de13-afdd-6feb50410000</link>
      <description>Watkins was a sixth-round pick of the Eagles back in 2020 and caught 98 passes for 1,249 yards and six touchdowns during his four-year tenure with the team. He hasn’t played a regular season snap since 2023 and has also bounced around between the Steelers and Cardinals over the last two years. If signed, Watkins wouldn’t be any more than added depth to a receiver room that is currently five players deep. In addition to Watkins, the Eagles also hosted WR K.J. Osborn and DE Isaiah Foskey for workouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b2a-de13-afdd-6feb50410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said OG Kevin Dotson is week-to-week with a sprained ankle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b3b-d332-a1fd-bf3f8a430000</link>
      <description>Dotson suffered what is being called a lateral ankle sprain in the Rams’ Week 1 win over the Texans. The sixth-year pro is in his third year with the Rams and has started every game he’s appeared in since 2023. Whether or not Dotson lands on injured reserve will likely be determined in the coming days. For now, he’ll likely be replaced by backup guard Justin Dedich.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b3b-d332-a1fd-bf3f8a430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said “the number of snaps you can get Keaton (Mitchell) on offense are pretty limited” when asked about the decision to scratch him in Week 1 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b57aa630000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal quote for anybody stashing Mitchell in hopes of an eventual role emerging. Harbaugh highlighted the fact that Mitchell taking the field would be on “designer plays” that could tip off the defense as to who the ball is going to. For obvious reasons, Harbaugh has no interest in taking Derrick Henry or Justice Hill off the field to work in these plays, and said Mitchell also needs to improve on special teams if he hopes to see the field. There’s nothing to get excited about here as far as Mitchell is concerned. We’ll see if anything changes as the season progresses, but he holds no fantasy value at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b57aa630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) is out for Week 1 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b67-db7b-a5dd-ab6717c30000</link>
      <description>Johnson went through warmups but reportedly “needs another week” before healthy enough to take the field. It’s a sizable blow to a secondary tasked with slowing down Justin Jefferson on Monday Night Football, which will now be forced to so without their All-Pro cornerback. Expect Nahshon Wright and Jaylon Jones to soak up his vacated snaps opposite Tyrique Stevenson. Also inactive for the Bears are DB Kyler Gordon, QB Case Keenum, RB Roschon Johnson, LB T.J. Edwards, and DL Shemar Turner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b67-db7b-a5dd-ab6717c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports 49ers QB Brock Purdy (shoulder/toe) is uncertain for Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b7b-d332-a1fd-bf7f6cb60000</link>
      <description>The 49ers emerged from their Week 1 victory over the Seahawks with three significant injuries, losing George Kittle for multiple weeks with a hamstring injury, Jauan Jennings to a shoulder injury, and Purdy to multiple ailments. Purdy’s status for Week 2 remains up in the air, with Schefter saying the team will “see how the week goes.” Mac Jones would be in line to start against the Saints if Purdy can’t go and would be charged with leading an offense decimated by injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b7b-d332-a1fd-bf7f6cb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (hamstring) will miss multiple games.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b7e-dbe3-a9bb-3b7fac510000</link>
      <description>The 49ers emerged from Week 1 with multiple key injuries, including Kittle, quarterback Brock Purdy, and wide receiver Jauan Jennings. Kittle’s absence is especially damning considering his role in the offense, something that could completely change the team’s preparations for the Saints when taken in conjunction with a potential absence from Purdy. Fantasy managers will want to make other plans at tight end for the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b7e-dbe3-a9bb-3b7fac510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings OT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is inactive for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b83-db7b-a5dd-ab87347b0000</link>
      <description>The veteran tackles’s absence is a massive blow to a Vikings team already without Jordan Addison due to suspension. The Vikings do get some good news as Jaylon Johnson is inactive for the Bears, lessening the matchup on the perimeter for Justin Jefferson. Darrisaw was reportedly close to suiting up but will require at least one more week before returning to the field to protect J.J. McCarthy. Also inactive for the Vikings are S Harrison Smith, RB Zavier Scott, G Joe Huber, DL Elijah Williams, and QB Max Brosmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b83-db7b-a5dd-ab87347b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) candidate for Injured Reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b87-de13-afdd-6fcf75ff0000</link>
      <description>Saehawks head coach Mike Macdonald went back on his post game presser, saying that rookie safety Nick Emmanwori did have a high ankle sprain and that the team was considering injured reserve. Emmanwori was injured on the fifth play in his professional debut on a tackle of Christian McCaffrey in the backfield for a two-yard loss. The team should know more on his situation as the week progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b87-de13-afdd-6fcf75ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaguars traded RB Tank Bigsby to the Eagles for 2026 fifth and sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ba7-de13-afdd-6fef8bd20000</link>
      <description>Jaguars head coach Liam Coen was quoted saying that it would be “difficult” to carry four running backs on the active game day roster on 21 August, prompting rumors of a trade at the position at some point in 2025. The team made good on those rumors by moving Bigsby to the Eagles, where he is likely to battle Will Shipley for the change of pace role behind Saquon Barkley. Eagles general manager Howie Roseman continues to leverage late picks to bolster his team as they look to repeat as Super Bowl champions. The move paves the way for Bhayshul Tuten to step into the primary change of pace role in Jacksonville, while Etienne has a clear runway for primary duties the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ba7-de13-afdd-6fef8bd20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
