<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:29:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived RB Blake Watson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ backfield is taking shape with Audric Estime and Watson being waived today. Watson had just four carries for 10 yards last season and suffered a PCL strain last week. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports there was some trade interest in him, so he is a candidate to be claimed. If not, the Broncos likely want him back on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles released EDGE Ochaun Mathis, S Andre’ Sam, and CB A.J. Woods.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e373-dbe3-a9bb-f373a4790000</link>
      <description>The Eagles continue to make cuts ahead of Tuesday’s deadline on the defensive side of the ball. Mathis and Sam each played in one game for the Eagles last season while Woods has only appeared in preseason games for the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e373-dbe3-a9bb-f373a4790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released WR DeAndre Carter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e384-db7b-a5dd-e384c6580000</link>
      <description>Carter was brought in by the Browns in March with a chance to be a special teams contributor, but Cleveland will go elsewhere for their returner to open 2025. His speed makes him likely to find a new club at some point this fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e384-db7b-a5dd-e384c6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevon Diggs (knee) was a full participant in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-de13-afdc-e7cfa53b0000</link>
      <description>Diggs was activated Sunday off the PUP (Physically Unable to Perform) list, and all signs point to the stellar 26-year-old cornerback being available for next Thursday’s Week 1 opener against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-de13-afdc-e7cfa53b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived QB Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</link>
      <description>Buechele is a strong candidate to end up on the Bills’ practice squad. He’s the second quarterback Buffalo has dropped Tuesday, as they also waived Mike White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e38c-dbe3-a9bb-f3df06cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers waived WR Brenden Rice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-d332-a1fd-f7b650fa0000</link>
      <description>Rice appeared in three games for the Chargers last season, playing just three snaps on offense. Getting fanfare as Jerry Rice’s son coming out of USC in the seventh round last year, he earned a spot on the 53-man roster. However, he dealt with a shoulder injury and is now out after the Chargers added Keenan Allen and Tre Harris to the receiving group this offseason. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo mentions Rice is a candidate for the team’s practice squad if he clears waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e386-d332-a1fd-f7b650fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders acquired QB Kenny Pickett from the Browns in exchange for a 2026 fifth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b4-de13-afdc-e7ff6ca20000</link>
      <description>The Raiders add Pickett to the quarterback room, needing a backup quarterback after Aidan O’Connell fractured his wrist in the preseason. Browns GM Andrew Berry had expressed his intent to keep four quarterbacks on the roster, it was always going to be tough to justify the roster spots. Instead, opportunity came knocking from the Raiders and the Browns get a fifth-rounder for their troubles. Pickett had been dealing with a hamstring injury in the preseason, but the Raiders seem to believe he will be ready for Week 1. Meanwhile, this all but guarantees the Browns will be keeping Joe Flacco as the starting quarterback with rookies Dillon Gabriel and Shedeur Sanders as backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b4-de13-afdc-e7ff6ca20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings traded CB Mekhi Blackmon to the Colts for a 2026 sixth-round selection.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b6-dbe3-a9bb-f3f7d6890000</link>
      <description>Blackmon will give the Colts some needed depth in the secondary. The 26-year-old missed all of 2024 with a torn ACL, but showed promise in his rookie campaign the previous year after being selected with the 102nd pick out of USC. Assuming good health, Blackmon should contribute in packages and also on special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3b6-dbe3-a9bb-f3f7d6890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3c3-dbe3-a9bb-f3d3e2400000</link>
      <description>Head coach Mike Macdonald announced Bobo is in concussion protocol after suffering a head injury in preseason Week 3. The Seahawks’ receiving depth behind Jaxon Smith-Njigba and Cooper Kupp is banged up heading into Week 1, with Tory Horton (ankle) aiming for a return to full practice next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3c3-dbe3-a9bb-f3d3e2400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the team will “have plays for Jalen [Milroe] in game plans.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3d9-db7b-a5dd-e3ddd5ed0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald said, “we’re going to have plays for Jalen in game plans and he’s going to rep those with the 1s.” It seems the Seahawks have a plan to use Milroe offensively despite Sam Darnold still being the starter. We can expect to see the 22-year-old rookie have a package of plays, likely in the run game, for the Seahawks to utilize his rushing skillset. For fantasy purposes, this won’t make Milroe fantasy-relevant, but might take high-value rushing touches away from Kenneth Walker in the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e3d9-db7b-a5dd-e3ddd5ed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
