<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (knee/PUP) said he anticipates returning to practice “in some capacity” when his window to do so opens up in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53bf-dfa0-a9bb-dbbfa9490000</link>
      <description>“I feel like if it was the NFC Championship Game tomorrow, I would be able to go out there and feel confident, for sure,” Watson told The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman. Watson’s window to return, whenever it opens, would be 21 days long. So reading between the lines, it sounds like Watson could be ready for a return sometime before Week 10. That’d be great news for the Packers, who are now sans Jayden Reed for the short-term future and haven’t gotten much from first-round pick Matthew Golden in the early going.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53bf-dfa0-a9bb-dbbfa9490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes Tyrone Tracy’s involvement as a kick returner “suggests a reduced offensive role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53c7-d606-a5db-5fd741dd0000</link>
      <description>“Tracy returned three kickoffs as a rookie, but that role ceased once he became the No. 1 running back in Week 5,” Duggan writes. Cam Skattebo appears to have taken over the top spot on the depth chart in Week 2. It’s hard to call Skattebo a sure fantasy weapon given how poorly the Giants are run blocking, but he sure seems like he’s at the head of a committee already. Skattebo should be a popular waiver wire target in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53c7-d606-a5db-5fd741dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars released S Darnell Savage.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5405-d654-a19b-d465a47f0000</link>
      <description>Savage played a reduced role in Weeks 1 and 2 of this season, one where he was almost entirely a deep safety in 48 passing-downs snaps. Savage had a $4.6 million cap figure and was one of Trent Baalke’s latest busts, accumulating a 46.9 PFF grade in 764 snaps for the 2024 Jaguars. He’ll look to catch on elsewhere as a swing safety. Andrew Wingard appears to have the trust of the coaching staff at strong safety. 2025 sixth-rounder Rayuan Lane III and Antonio Johnson are the current depth options for Jacksonville at safety.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5405-d654-a19b-d465a47f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB Desmond Ridder.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5427-dfa0-a9bb-dfa7d27b0000</link>
      <description>Apparently they aren’t ready to thrust Max Brosmer into the fire as the main backup despite carrying him as an UDFA. The team will carry four quarterbacks on their 53-man roster while dealing with J.J. McCarthy’s high-ankle sprain. Ridder was terrible with the Raiders last year, turning six appearances and one start into a 458/2/2 line while getting sacked on 10.5 percent of his dropbacks. He’s still only 26, and now he’s in a Kevin O’Connell offense so we may have to care about him, but you’d think we would have seen a real sign of life from Ridder at some point over the last three years if he was going to be a solid NFL backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5427-dfa0-a9bb-dfa7d27b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers RT Luke Goedeke (foot) is expected to miss “multiple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-542e-d051-a3df-7eef56910000</link>
      <description>Goedeke came into Week 2’s game with a foot injury that he had barely practiced on, then aggravated it in-game and Charlie Heck took over at right tackle. Heck would appear to be the backup plan for the Buccaneers for the forseeable future while Goedeke is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-542e-d051-a3df-7eef56910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed RB Cam Akers to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-543d-d654-a19b-d47db7600000</link>
      <description>We’re surprised nobody thought to sign Akers so that they could squeeze a draft pick out of the Vikings this time. Akers has now been acquired midseason by the Vikings three years in a row. He’ll help fill in for Aaron Jones’ absence and could see a small share of carries if he’s in playing shape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-543d-d654-a19b-d47db7600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Jaylen Wright (knee) was “real close” to playing last week and that Mike McDaniel is “most optimistic” about Wright playing in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5443-d654-a19b-d463e3570000</link>
      <description>Of course, most optimistic is in relation to Darren Waller, who nobody should be optimistic about playing. It’s relative. But Wright did get in a limited practice on Monday and would seem to be in line to assume backup duties behind De’Von Achane if healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5443-d654-a19b-d463e3570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) is unlikely to play in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-544b-d051-a3df-7eeb1fc90000</link>
      <description>Waller did get in a limited practice on Monday but after being ruled out for Week 2, it was never exceedingly likely that he was going to make it back for Thursday Night Football. Week 4 is a more reasonable timeline for Waller after a mini-bye for the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-544b-d051-a3df-7eeb1fc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed Aaron Jones (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5457-d654-a19b-d477c0cd0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games and be eligible to return in Week 7, after Minnesota’s Week 6 bye. Jones is a worthwhile hold if your league has injured reserve spots, but you likely can’t expect him to do better than being co-head of a committee whenever he does return, and that’s assuming Jordan Mason doesn’t take advantage of this opportunity in a big way. Now in his age-31 season, Jones is firmly on the back nine of his fantasy relevance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5457-d654-a19b-d477c0cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Malik Washington (thumb) said he’d play in Miami’s Week 3 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5469-d606-a5db-5cf92fae0000</link>
      <description>Washington popped up on the report with a limited practice on Monday, but it sounds like the issue isn’t all that serious. If Tyreek Hill were ever to be moved, Washington would be an intriguing fantasy add. He led the team in targets in Week 1 and contributed a 74-yard punt return touchdown in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5469-d606-a5db-5cf92fae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
