<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Malik Willis (shoulder) is “pretty sore” after Week 16’s loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-464b-d968-a19b-5efbef110000</link>
      <description>Speaking with the media on Sunday, LaFleur discussed the health of both his quarterbacks and said Willis’ injury is “a legitimate deal that he’s dealing with.” While Willis is dealing with a shoulder injury, Jordan Love suffered a concussion in Saturday’s win and will be in concussion protocol to start the week. If both quarterbacks are unable to go this week, 2023 fifth-rounder Clayton Tune would draw the start against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-464b-d968-a19b-5efbef110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Jordan Love is in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-467c-d968-a19b-5efd57820000</link>
      <description>Love suffered a head injury in the second quarter of the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears. He took a hard helmet-to-helmet shot on the play and was visibly shaken up afterward. He was ruled out shortly after leaving the field. Love will have to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to play in Saturday’s game against the Ravens. If he is unable to go, Malik Willis (shoulder) would be next in line to draw the start, with Clayton Tune being the third man up if both players are sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-467c-d968-a19b-5efd57820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports J.J. McCarthy will undergo an MRI on his hand.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4686-d35e-a1bf-47c6603b0000</link>
      <description>X-rays on McCarthy’s hand reportedly came back negative for a broken bone. McCarthy will undergo an MRI to determine the exact nature of the injury that knocked him out of Week 16’s game against the Giants, but if the MRI doesn’t reveal anything severe, we would expect him to have a chance to suit up in Week 17 against the Lions. If McCarthy is unable to go, Max Brosmer would make his second career start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4686-d35e-a1bf-47c6603b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Brady Cook will start in Week 17 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46bc-d56e-afff-e6fc64150000</link>
      <description>The Jets continue to evaluate their quarterback position ahead of the offseason. Cook took a whopping eight sacks in Week 16’s loss to the Saints and will have a chance to take eight more in next week’s game against the Patriots. Cook can be avoided in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46bc-d56e-afff-e6fc64150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed QB Jeff Driskel, formerly of the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46f3-d35e-a1bf-47f375c20000</link>
      <description>Commanders beat writer Ben Standig was the first to report the move. The move to sign Driskel to the 53-man roster suggests Marcus Mariota (hand) is unlikely to play in Week 17 against the Cowboys. Driskel spent all of last season with the Commanders and should have plenty of familiarity with Kliff Kingsbury’s playbook. That said, Josh Johnson is still considered the favorite to start after taking over for Mariota in Week 16’s loss to the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-46f3-d35e-a1bf-47f375c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts activated DT DeForest Buckner from injured reserve for Week 16’s game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4708-d968-a19b-5ff96e320000</link>
      <description>As a procedural move to activate Buckner, the Colts also waived QB Brett Rypien. It was reported before the weekend that Buckner was expected to play in Week 16’s game, but the Colts made it official on Monday with his activation. Buckner has been sidelined with a neck injury since Week 9 and should provide an immediate boost to a defense that ranks 22nd in total yards allowed but has been a top-10 run-stopping unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4708-d968-a19b-5ff96e320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL upheld Derick Hall’s one-game suspension for Week 17 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-470d-d56e-afff-e7edac1a0000</link>
      <description>Hall was suspended following Week 16’s game against the Rams, in which he could be seen blatantly stepping on RG Kevin Dotson’s leg, which resulted in Dotson being carted from the field. Hall will miss Week 17’s game against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-470d-d56e-afff-e7edac1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said the team has not ruled out the possibility of Marcus Mariota (hand/quad) playing in Week 17 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4711-d56e-afff-e7f9e9ce0000</link>
      <description>Quinn said the team is still evaluating the injuries to Mariota’s throwing hand and quad. While that may be the case, we also can’t overlook the fact that the Commanders signed QB Jeff Driskel off the Cardinals’ practice squad earlier today, a move that suggests they are preparing to be a man down at QB this week. We’ll see where things go from here, but with a short week to prep for Thursday’s game against the Cowboys, it wouldn’t be surprising if Josh Johnson made the start while Driskel served as his backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4711-d56e-afff-e7f9e9ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed OG Sam Cosmi (concussion) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4720-d56e-afff-e7e85fb50000</link>
      <description>Cosmi’s season will come to an end following this move. The veteran right guard appeared in nine games for the Commanders this season after rehabbing from a torn ACL he suffered in last year’s NFC Divisional Round. One of the better guards in the league since being drafted in 2021, Cosmi earned a PFF grade of 76.3 this season while playing on 545 offensive snaps. He is expected to be replaced by Andrew Wylie for the final two weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4720-d56e-afff-e7e85fb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cardinals fear CB Garrett Williams suffered a torn Achilles in Week 16’s loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4734-d56e-afff-e7fc95200000</link>
      <description>Williams exited Sunday’s game against the Falcons with a non-contact Achilles injury and had to be carted from the field. The third-year vet will undergo an MRI to confirm, but the injury had the look of a season-ender long before this report. Williams has started 21 of the 26 games he’s appeared in over the last two seasons for the Cardinals and has tallied five pass breakups and one interception this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4734-d56e-afff-e7fc95200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
