<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught 2-of-2 targets for 46 yards in Baltimore’s Week 5 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f85350000</link>
      <description>He Mossed a ball over a Texans defender and rumbled 29 yards on Baltimore’s first drive. The Ravens’ passing attack was simply too inconsistent to deliver a second fantasy contributor behind Zay Flowers. Despite how good he’s looked in his limited sample this year, Hopkins won’t be a Week 6 play. Neither will Rashod Bateman after a bagel on three targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f85350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 6-of-7 targets for 33 yards and two touchdowns in a Week 5 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fe0140000</link>
      <description>Johnson figured to step into a larger role without Malik Nabers (knee) and certainly did that, catching touchdowns on both of the Giants’ first two drives of the game. Even if fellow tight end Daniel Bellinger was more involved in the offense early on, Johnson was clearly Jaxson Dart’s top target when the Giants got into the red zone. Johnson was also peppered with targets late in the game in garbage time. Since the Giants figure to be in garbage time often, Johnson is a solid TE2 option the rest of the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fe0140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed six times for 30 yards in the Eagles’ Week 5 loss to the Broncos, adding three receptions for 58 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9ff66e0000</link>
      <description>Despite his season-worst effort on the ground — he hasn’t cleared 50 yards rushing since Week 2 — Barkley finally provided a chunk gain, catching a 47-yard touchdown pass on a third quarter wheel route. That put the Birds up 17-3 with 28 minutes remaining, but they stunningly blew the game to Bo Nix and company. There was a big first half development when LG Landon Dickerson departed with a likely high-ankle sprain. Not the news Barkley needed ahead of a short-week Thursday night date with the Giants. At some point, Barkley is going to bust out on the ground, and it could be as easily as this week, as the G-Men are far more vulnerable on the ground than through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9ff66e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely caught his only target for 12 yards in Baltimore’s Week 5 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b622-deb6-a7fd-f7ff122b0000</link>
      <description>He finished fourth on the team in receiving yards, so at least that’s something. Likely actually saw a small decrease in snaps — from 25 to 23 — as Charlie Kollar has proven himself unable to be banished from the rotation so far. Likely isn’t worth holding on to at this snap share and target rate, especially with Lamar Jackson still expected to be out in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b622-deb6-a7fd-f7ff122b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 5-of-7 targets for 30 yards in a Week 5 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b623-dca3-a9fb-bfbb37f10000</link>
      <description>Even with Malik Nabers (knee) out, Robinson didn’t step into a much more impactful role. Both Darius Slayton and Jalin Hyatt are more suited to downfield roles, which kept Robinson closer to the line of scrimmage. The Giants’ offensive line also struggled to protect Jaxson Dart, which led to a lot of scrambles and off-script throws. Robinson is going to see plenty of snaps and targets, which will keep him on fantasy radars, but he’s more of a WR3/FLEX play in PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b623-dca3-a9fb-bfbb37f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 5-of-8 targets for 43 yards in the Eagles’ Week 5 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b625-d95b-addb-fe67fd640000</link>
      <description>To the point where he was basically publicly pleading for the ball, Brown reached eight targets for the fourth consecutive contest, but he still failed to make a box score impact. To underscore just how disappointing his season has been, today was Brown’s second best yardage total. Stunning stuff, especially with the Eagles finally opening up the passing attack a little bit this afternoon. DeVonta Smith posted 8/114 on 10 looks. Brown got a deep target near the end of the third quarter, but curiously slowed up after executing a double move. It also wasn’t an amazing throw from Jalen Hurts. Brown’s final look was a 29-yard end zone heave as time expired. Fittingly, he and Smith both fought for the ball and it fell incomplete. Brown now has a short-week Thursday night date with Giants defense that covers the pass better than the run. The misery could easily continue for both the wideout and fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b625-d95b-addb-fe67fd640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 7-of-9 targets for 49 yards and two touchdowns in the Cowboys’ Week 5 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f18fd0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson continues to put up numbers. He tied with Ryan Flournoy for the team lead in targets on the day and found the end zone twice in the first half. His first score came on a 26-yard gain from a tight end screen, where he ran untouched into the end zone. His second was on a one-yard strike in the end zone just seconds before halftime. The fourth-year tight end has now caught 27 passes for 171 yards and three touchdowns over the last three weeks, and has seen 30 targets over that span. He’s an easy must-start in Week 6 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b61f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f18fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Caroll said Brock Bowers (knee) is “day to day” after missing Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b622-d6e9-af9d-beb262ac0000</link>
      <description>Bowers is dealing with a PCL injury and a bone bruise in his knee that simply need rest to heal. Bowers tried to gut it out through the injuries for a few weeks but reached a breaking point ahead of today’s game. Caroll said the Raiders hoped some rest days during the week would be enough for Bowers to get on the field today. The team seemingly knew by Saturday that it wasn’t going to happen. ESPN’s Adam Schefter called Bowers “week to week,” so consider us slightly skeptical of Caroll’s day to day designation. Michael Mayer missed Week 5 with a concussion, but will be an interesting add off the waiver wire assuming he is able to return for Week 6 versus Tennessee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b622-d6e9-af9d-beb262ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beaux Collins caught 1-of-3 targets for seven yards in a Week 5 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b626-deb6-a7fd-f7ff8a1b0000</link>
      <description>With Darius Slayton struggling and then leaving the game with a hamstring injury, it was the rookie UDFA Collins who stepped into a larger role for the Giants. That wasn’t actually a good thing since Collins and Jaxson Dart didn’t seem to be on the same page at all, which led to one interception and little production. Collins wasn’t a dynamic prospect out of college, so he figures to remain off the fantasy radar even if he steps into a larger role if Slayton misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b626-deb6-a7fd-f7ff8a1b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
