<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:03:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Bengals won’t entertain trade offers for QB Joe Burrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dfd-d042-afbc-7dff77bb0000</link>
      <description>“I do expect teams to call the Cincinnati Bengals,” Rapoport said. There was a brief groundswell of the idea of a Burrow trade towards the end of the season when he let loose on how bad he was feeling at a press conference, but even if he had wanted out, the Bengals have always played hardball with their players that they want to keep. The Bengals, per Rapoport, will instead channel Burrow’s belief that things need to change into spending and getting better on defense. We’ll believe that when we see it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3dfd-d042-afbc-7dff77bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Eagles have not had trade talks with other teams yet about A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e04-d89c-a1be-bfdf815f0000</link>
      <description>They also, per Garafolo, have only briefly broached with Brown’s “camp” the idea of a trade. Talks are expected to pick up near the scouting combine. Brown told Garafolo that “a lot of this is out of my control at this point.” We’re not entirely sure what to make of that, but the best guess probably remains that there will be trade talks with Brown at some point. It might come down to what kind of price the Eagles have set on the star wideout and how close other teams are willing to get to it. There’s certainly no way Howie Roseman is letting Brown walk without getting a first-round pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e04-d89c-a1be-bfdf815f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports “many league sources” think the Vikings will pursue Broncos GM George Paton for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e09-d355-a5bd-bf5dbc810000</link>
      <description>Paton would presumably require compensation to acquire. And while he has done an admirable job rebounding from it over the past few years with Sean Payton, our first taste of Paton is always going to be the disastrous Russell Wilson trade. However, as the long-time lieutenant to Rick Spielman in Minnesota, it is not surprising that the Vikings would have some interest in bringing Paton back. This will probably be one to watch after the draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e09-d355-a5bd-bf5dbc810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports “all bets are off” on the Vikings plans for J.J. McCarthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e10-d89c-a1be-bfdff5b90000</link>
      <description>“If anything, [firing Adofo-Mensah] increase the chances that the Vikings will take a big swing at finding a veteran quarterback who could start in 2026,” Seifert writes. With the GM who believed in him gone, it’s likely that McCarthy will enter training camp in a competition for his job in the best-case scenario. His dynasty stock has gone full Anthony Richardson over the last year and he should not be treated as a sure-fire starter in best ball drafts this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e10-d89c-a1be-bfdff5b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Seahawks quarterbacks coach Andrew Janocko is a “natural candidate” to be the Raiders offensive coordinator under Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e14-d89c-a1be-bfdf2ff50000</link>
      <description>Janocko has followed Kubiak as he’s had stints in Minnesota, New Orleans, and now Seattle. Fowler also notes that Seahawks passing game coordinator Jake Peetz could get an in-house look as Seattle’s offensive coordinator when Kubiak leaving is officially finalized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e14-d89c-a1be-bfdf2ff50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports “several people in the league” think Broncos coach Sean Payton will eventually relinquish playcalling to OC Davis Webb.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e1f-d355-a5bd-bf5f8ee20000</link>
      <description>We’ll believe it when we see it, of course, but it could be a way for the Broncos to continue to hold on to Webb while paying him as if he were a head coach. We have no mathematical data for how a Webb offense would run differently than a Payton one, and would likely be relying on quotes and beat-writer reports until we saw how it would play out on the field. It was already clear the Broncos really didn’t want Webb to get away, but giving him playcalling duties would be another level of dedication to that idea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e1f-d355-a5bd-bf5f8ee20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes the Cowboys could trade George Pickens this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e24-d042-afbc-7ff63df60000</link>
      <description>“A tag-and-trade scenario is considered to be a possibility for Dallas” this offseason, Rapoport reports. It makes all the sense in the world for Dallas given how they rehabilitated Pickens’ value this offseason and how the current state of their salary cap is. It would be much easier to do the work on the defensive side of the ball with extra money from not keeping Pickens. Of course, that relies on the Cowboys to be excited about a young receiver in the draft, or perhaps with elevating Ryan Flournoy to a bigger role. We wouldn’t count on this to happen, but a Pickens tag-and-trade definitely is a plausible scenario for how this unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e24-d042-afbc-7ff63df60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt believes Eagles QB Tanner McKee could be a logical trade target for the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e32-d89c-a1be-bfff547c0000</link>
      <description>New Jets OC Frank Reich “has a close relationship with Eagles coach Nick Sirianni” and McKee “fits the physical mold of a Reich QB” per Rosenblatt. Rosenblatt also links the Jets to Geno Smith (if released), Jacoby Brissett and Kirk Cousins. McKee would be an interesting trade target after a couple of spot starts in Week 18 the past few years. He’s entering the final year of his rookie contract in 2026 and would probably cost the Jets at least a Day 2 pick, but it would undoubtedly be a higher-upside play than relying on Smith or Cousins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e32-d89c-a1be-bfff547c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns interviewed safeties coach Ephraim Banda and linebackers coach Jason Tarver for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e36-d629-a1bc-be3f77c70000</link>
      <description>Banda was requested for the Jets and Cowboys defensive coordinator vacancies, so he at least has some outside buzz as a real candidate. This is the first interview we can record for Tarver. The other name remaining for the Browns appears to be Texans assistant Cory Undlin. It’s an underwhelming group in the wake of Jim Schwartz’s resignation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e36-d629-a1bc-be3f77c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Colts will begin contract talks with Daniel Jones soon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e56-d042-afbc-7fd6c7fd0000</link>
      <description>It was no surprise to hear this as both Jones and the Colts had mutual interest in a re-signing after their regular season ended, and Jones’ Achilles tear had a lot to do with them tumbling out of the playoffs. We’re extremely curious who is compromising on value here as Jones has been an almost-Kirk Cousinsesque money maker over his early career, and it would seem that his mobility being compromised would make him tough to trust in 2026 as a starter since a real chunk of his value is tied to that. The Colts, of course, don’t have any better options after dealing their 2026 and 2027 first-round picks away for Sauce Gardner. It wouldn’t be surprising if this got to the stage of franchise or transition tags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3e56-d042-afbc-7fd6c7fd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
