<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Kaleb Johnson is listed behind Jaylen Warren and Kenneth Gainwell on the team’s official depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b6f-de13-afdd-4fefe0bc0000</link>
      <description>We’d expect Johnson to be mixed in and play a bigger part at some point this season, but for now at least it appears he’ll have only a minor role in the rushing attack. With Warren recently signed to an extension and Johnson off to a relatively slow start in taking a share of the backfield, Johnson’s fantasy stock has declined precipitously since the draft. He’s still the best between-the-tackles fit the team has, so we’d bet he creates a role for himself eventually in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b6f-de13-afdd-4fefe0bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes DeVonta Smith could “near” his 2022 totals of 95 catches for 1,196 yards and seven touchdowns in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b8f-d332-a1fd-9fbf02460000</link>
      <description>“Look for an uptick in production from Smith,” Berman writes. It certainly would make some sense for the Eagles to throw more in 2025 so long as Saquon Barkley actually takes a regression step somewhere along the line, though that obviously is not guaranteed. Smith’s lengthy injury history causes fantasy football managers their own pains, but it’s hard to deny that there’s a path for him to improve on last year’s numbers — at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b8f-d332-a1fd-9fbf02460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Buscaglia believes “it’s fair to expect more of the same from [Dalton] Kincaid’s early 2024 role to begin 2025.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b96-de13-afdd-4fdf99670000</link>
      <description>In fact, Buscaglia believes it is “possibly complicated even more for Kincaid, as fifth-round rookie Jackson Hawes has had an impressive camp as a blocker, and if active, could get more playing time than former third tight end Quintin Morris” did in 2024. We’d put Kincaid firmly on the TE1 borderline at this point. You can probably do better than starting him against the Ravens in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b96-de13-afdd-4fdf99670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Stefon Diggs (knee) will play in Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b9c-de13-afdd-4fdfd4ea0000</link>
      <description>Diggs never really looked like he’d be sidelined as he participated heavily in training camp, but after a summer of optimistic updates, we now have confirmation that he’ll play in Week 1. He should be fired up as a WR2/WR3 in Week 1 against the Raiders, who have one of the barest cornerback cupboards in the NFL. A big game wouldn’t be surprising.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b9c-de13-afdd-4fdfd4ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Rosenblatt believes the Jets might “need” Arian Smith to have “a significant role ... quickly.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bb6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7e8ac0000</link>
      <description>“It’s a tall order to bank on a fourth-round rookie,” Rosenblatt writes, then notes that unless the Jets make a trade or acquire some outside help, they probably don’t have much upside at the position beyond Smith. Smith has enough speed to hit a huge play here or there, but we’d be surprised given the run-heavy direction of the offense if the Jets found a significant fantasy contributor at receiver outside of Garrett Wilson. Still, we can’t completely dismiss Smith’s chances if he creates a big role for himself early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bb6-dbe3-a9bb-3bf7e8ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor is listed as a first-team wideout on Tennessee’s unofficial depth chart ahead of Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bcc-db7b-a5dd-abcc88730000</link>
      <description>He’s ahead of Van Jefferson, in other words. It’s going to be hard to fully understand the Titans’ offensive potential until we see how Cam Ward plays — and even then we might give him a mulligan if he performs poorly against the Broncos in Week 1 — but it’s certainly in the realm of possibility that Ayomanor winds up being a fantasy starter at some point in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bcc-db7b-a5dd-abcc88730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Hollywood Brown (ankle) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0be2-de13-afdd-4feb78f40000</link>
      <description>There doesn’t appear to have been much question about his status for Week 1, but practicing in full certainly erases whatever doubt was remaining. Brown will walk into Sao Paolo as a FLEX dart with Rashee Rice out for the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0be2-de13-afdd-4feb78f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed QB Davis Mills to a one-year, $7 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bf7-db7b-a5dd-abf723c50000</link>
      <description>Big news for fans of the 2022 Texans. Mills played extensively in the team’s Week 18 win over the Titans last year, culminating in a second-and-goal dive where Mills landed helmet mask first short of the goal line and a narrow win. Mills hasn’t exactly played poorly when given a chance, but he’s probably not one of the best 10 backups in the league either.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bf7-db7b-a5dd-abf723c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders listed Jacory Croskey-Merritt fourth on their unofficial depth chart at running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c11-d332-a1fd-9e37a0170000</link>
      <description>Sure, whatever you say guys. Austin Ekeler is the starter in name on this depth chart. We tentatively expect Croskey-Merritt and Chris Rodriguez to have major roles on the early downs while Ekeler is in charge of passing downs this year. We’re sure this will generate questions for Dan Quinn and Kliff Kingsbury later. For now, let’s enjoy being engaged by some bait.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c11-d332-a1fd-9e37a0170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne Jr. and Tank Bigsby are listed as co-starters on Jacksonville’s unofficial depth chart for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c22-de13-afdd-4eebad8f0000</link>
      <description>A confusing situation remains confusing. Worst of all, correctly figuring out which Jaguars running back will get the majority of the run against a Panthers defense coming off one of the worst seasons defending the run in NFL history could mean a lot for fantasy football in Week 1. We’re going to have to hit the press conference tape hard to figure this one out. Either player is startable in Week 1 as a FLEX play until we hear something stronger from the coaching staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c22-de13-afdd-4eebad8f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
