<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:05:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker had two carries for zero yards in the Bucs’ Week 13 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d722-db57-afda-d732838a0000</link>
      <description>With Bucky Irving active for the first time since Week 4, Tucker received only one chance to establish the supposed “hot hand,” and he flunked miserably. A distant third in both touches and snaps behind Irving and Rachaad White, Tucker seems to again be on the outside looking in of the Bucs’ backfield rotation. Perhaps that changes if there is Week 14 garbage time against the Saints, but Tucker isn’t looking worth a 12-team league roster spot with the playoffs about to begin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d722-db57-afda-d732838a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 1-of-5 targets for five yards in the Titans’ Week 13 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d71a-d6c4-abfb-d71be0de0000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor returned from a one-game absence due to his hamstring injury and led all Titans receivers in snaps. He and Cam Ward had very little chemistry this game as Ayomanor caught just one of his five targets. Chimere Dike and Van Jefferson were the only other wideouts to get over three targets; Jefferson caught 3-of-4 targets for 20 yards. No Titans receivers should be in fantasy lineups for Week 14 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d71a-d6c4-abfb-d71be0de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson had four rushes for 23 yards in the Browns’ Week 13 loss against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d725-d82c-a79a-f7b5dfce0000</link>
      <description>Quinshon Judkins led the backfield as usual, this time with 20 rushing attempts to go along with four targets. Sampson was the only Cleveland back to log a carry besides Judkins in another run-heavy game plan for the Browns. Jerome Ford led the Browns backfield in pass routes, meanwhile, Sampson is a smart bench stash for now in case Judkins misses time down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d725-d82c-a79a-f7b5dfce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 23 times for 142 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 13 loss to the Jets, adding five receptions for 51 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d726-db57-afda-d7363a6f0000</link>
      <description>Robinson’s 193 yards from scrimmage were his most since Week 6, and second most of the season. This being the Falcons, he did manage to get vultured by Tyler Allgeier for a score, but Robinson actually returned the favor when Allgeier got the Falcons to the Jets’ eight-yard line in the third quarter. Approaching 200 yards from scrimmage in this offensive environment is a major accomplishment, but it probably requires a hapless opponent like the Jets. The Falcons don’t have that for Week 14 in the Seahawks, though the game is at least at home at 1PM ET. That’s one long plane ride for Seattle and company. Hopefully 120-plus yards remain on the menu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d726-db57-afda-d7363a6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson caught 5-of-9 targets for 39 yards in the Saints’ Week 13 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d724-d82c-a79a-f7b4fb9a0000</link>
      <description>It was business as usual for Johnson, who has at least four catches in three-of-four Tyler Shough starts. He scored in Shough’s first two starts but has since run dry in that department. That is to be expected with Shough taking his lumps on a week-to-week basis. Johnson led the Saints in targets this week, though Devaughn Vele paced the team in catches and yards. Johnson will remain a low-end TE1 for his Week 14 matchup with the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d724-d82c-a79a-f7b4fb9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders declared QB Jayden Daniels, S Darnell Savage, LB Ale Kaho, LS Tyler Ott, T Trent Scott, T George Fant, and DE Jalyn Holmes inactive for Week 13 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72c-db57-afda-d73e1e730000</link>
      <description>That means wide receiver Terry McLaurin is officially active after appearing in just one of the team’s previous eight games, although the Commanders will have to wait until Week 14 before they get their starting quarterback back under center. Marcus Mariota will start for the fourth time in the previous five games for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72c-db57-afda-d73e1e730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared TE Nate Adkins, OLB Jonah Elliss, T Geron Christian, DL Jordan Jackson, and DE Sai’vion Jones inactive for Week 13 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72e-d82c-a79a-f7be05380000</link>
      <description>That means standout corner Pat Surtain makes his return to the active roster after missing the previous three games, making the Broncos one of the healthier teams in the league as they enter Week 13. They’ll take on an injury ravaged Commanders team without its starting quarterback as Jayden Daniels was ruled out earlier in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72e-d82c-a79a-f7be05380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed eight times for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 13 loss to the Jets, adding two receptions for 35 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72b-d6c4-abfb-d72b4e760000</link>
      <description>Allgeier’s score was a one-yarder after Bijan Robinson failed to punch it in the previous play, but Robinson got Allgeier back in the third quarter after his backup brought the Falcons to the Jets’ eight-yard line. Having eclipsed 50 yards rushing one time since September, Allgeier is a low-floor, zero-ceiling second FLEX option in 12-team leagues with the fantasy playoffs only two weeks away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d72b-d6c4-abfb-d72b4e760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adonai Mitchell caught 8-of-12 targets for 102 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 13 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d730-d90e-a9da-df3ff2140000</link>
      <description>Well alrighty then. So far only known in New York for his drops transferring from Indy, Mitchell displayed sure hands as he erupted for the first 100-yard receiving day of his short career. The highlight was a 52-yard touchdown where he simply ran by CB Mike Hughes, only to have to come back to the ball and make an excellent catch near the goal line. It was proof of concept that if the Jets kept giving Mitchell opportunities, he would eventually reward them with big plays. You don’t need us to tell you Mitchell will remain inconsistent down the stretch, but the fact he has finally established spiked week potential makes him much more lively as a WR4. The Dolphins are another plus matchup for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d730-d90e-a9da-df3ff2140000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
