<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:03:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said it’s “more than likely” Josh Jacobs (knee) will not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e57-d005-a9bf-de77e97c0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur told reporters, “We’ll see how he’s feeling tomorrow &amp; go from there.” He isn’t ruling Jacobs out yet, but it’s safe to say the veteran back is on the wrong side of questionable after missing the first two practices of the week. Jacobs previousy missed Week 12 with the knee issue. Backup Emanuel Wilson racked up 28 carries, which he turned into 107 yards and a pair of touchdowns. Wilson would push for an RB1 ranking if Jacobs sits in Week 15 versus the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e57-d005-a9bf-de77e97c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt is “currently in a local hospital for further medical evaluation of his lung after experiencing discomfort at the practice facility on Wednesday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e7e-d005-a9bf-de7e182d0000</link>
      <description>This news comes directly from the team. Steelers spokesman Burt Lauden added that Watt will not practice on Thursday and his status for Monday’s game is in question. Head coach Mike Tomlin will provide more updates at the appropriate time. It’s a scary update for one of the best defenders in the league. The hope will be that this is a short-term issue, but it’s too early to say anything definitively. We don’t expect Watt to suit up versus the Dolphins on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e7e-d005-a9bf-de7e182d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (knee) was not seen at Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e88-da9b-a9bf-de8de11c0000</link>
      <description>Tyrod Taylor was also absent during the portion of practice open to the media. All signs point to Brady Cook making his starting NFL debut on Sunday. Cooks took over for Taylor mid-game last week and was a disaster. He completed fewer than half of his attempts and was intercepted twice. Cook also took six sacks. Cook being named the starter would take Aondai Mitchell and John Metchie off the fantasy radar for Week 15. Cook himself won’t be a fantasy option, even in Superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e88-da9b-a9bf-de8de11c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall (knee) was seen participating in individual drills during Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e8c-d8cf-affb-beaed1400000</link>
      <description>This will likely go down as a limited session for Hall. That is a step in the right direction after the team held him out of Wednesday’s practice entirely. This is likely just maintenance for a workhorse back who has been dealing with a knee issue for over a month. Hall should be good to go by Sunday, though the absence of Justin Fields and Tyrod Taylor could tank the Jets’ offense. Brady Cook appears to be in line to start versus the Jags. The Jets will undoubtedly ride Hall, keeping him in the RB2 ranks even if the offensive environment is a disaster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e8c-d8cf-affb-beaed1400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (knee) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e93-d77b-adfb-ce931d210000</link>
      <description>Outstanding. The Texans’ featured rookie running back, once viewed as simply a pass-catching specialist, is tentatively on track to play in Week 15 against the Cardinals. Marks’ 84 touches over the last four weeks tie for the position’s fourth-largest workload during that span. He should handle another hefty workload with Chubb (ribs) on the wrong side of questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e93-d77b-adfb-ce931d210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e9e-da9b-a9bf-de9f31c40000</link>
      <description>Chubb is now on the wrong side of questionable for the Texans’ Week 15 game against the Cardinals. The veteran running back was forced from his team’s Week 14 victory over the Chiefs on Sunday night after injuring his ribs. Rookie running back Woody Marks (knee) should be viewed as a borderline RB1/2 at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0e9e-da9b-a9bf-de9f31c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (personal) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ea6-d77b-adfb-cea790f90000</link>
      <description>Knox should be good to go for the Bills’ Week 15 game against the Patriots. He is not worth starting in re-draft formats, though he warrants minimal consideration in DFS, given the expectedly fantasy-friendly game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ea6-d77b-adfb-cea790f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts designated DT DeForest Buckner (neck) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0eb1-d77b-adfb-ceb3c1d70000</link>
      <description>The Colts officially opened Buckner’s 21-day practice window on Wednesday. He kicked the week off with a limited session and continued practicing today, though his participation level is unknown. The talented defensive tackle was placed on injured reserve in November after suffering a herniated disc in his neck that was pressing on a nerve, resulting in a loss of strength on the left side of his body.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0eb1-d77b-adfb-ceb3c1d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson resumed practicing on Thursday after resting on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ebc-d77b-adfb-cebf95e80000</link>
      <description>Last week, Jackson banked his first QB1 finish since Week 9. He gets an extra soft matchup against the Bengals’ fantasy-friendly defense in Week 15, giving him strong odds of repeating the once-routine feat. This is a must-win game for both teams. The Ravens (6-7) and Bengals (4-9) are still attempting to claw their way toward a playoff spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0ebc-d77b-adfb-cebf95e80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
