<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 27-of-50 attempts for 279 yards and two touchdowns in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants, adding four rushes for 44 yards and two touchdowns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe93-df81-ab9b-fed7014f0000</link>
      <description>Nix led a remarkable comeback after the Broncos found themselves down 18 points midway through the fourth quarter against the underdog Giants. Nix and the Denver offense were lifeless through three and a half quarters, but came to life when it counted. Nix’s check downs turned into intermediate and deep throws as the Broncos climbed back from a deficit against the upstart Giants, led by Jaxson Dart and Cam Skattebo. Nix hit two late passes down the middle to set up the game winning field goal by Wil Lutz. He showed off his rushing ability throughout, gaining almost 10 yards per rush and finding pay dirt twice on the ground. Nix will get a plus matchup in Week 8 against a soft Dallas defense that has bled fantasy production to opposing QBs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fe93-df81-ab9b-fed7014f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota completed 4-of-10 passes for 63 yards and an interception in the Commanders’ 44-22, Week 7 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fedc-d651-a9df-ffdd41e20000</link>
      <description>By the time Mariota came in, it was too late to change where this game was headed. He hung a ball to the sideline under pressure and was pick-sixed by DaRon Bland, though he did at least lead a late touchdown drive that capped with a Chris Rodriguez rushing touchdown. Should Jayden Daniels be unable to go in Week 8, Mariota would be a reasonable superflex starter against the Chiefs, though he certainly would be closer to a middle-pack QB2 than someone you’d definitely want to fire up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fedc-d651-a9df-ffdd41e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams rushed 19 times for 116 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 7 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fedf-d99b-a1dd-fedfa4a90000</link>
      <description>The 13/29 abomination line against the Panthers was an outlier as Williams flat-out embarrassed the Commanders defense, breaking tackles left and right and creating (per early PFF data) 95 yards after contact. It’s almost a little surprising he didn’t find a second touchdown in this game given how long the Cowboys led, but they opted to give Jayden Blue some garbage time run. Williams will remain on the RB2 line against the Broncos in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fedf-d99b-a1dd-fedfa4a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman Jr. caught 7-of-9 targets for 58 yards, one touchdown and one two-point conversion in the Colts’ Week 7 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee0-d651-a9df-fff575b80000</link>
      <description>Pittman dominated the short-to-intermediate field depths, regularly getting open and picking up chunk gains whenever Colts QB Daniel Jones needed him. The Colts faced a fourth-and-two situation from the Chargers’ four-yard line at the end of their second drive, and head coach Shane Steichen smartly kept his offense on the field and dialed up a play-action pass play for Pittman, who caught it in the flats and sped into the end zone. He later made a play in the end zone via a two-point conversion on the Colts’ sixth drive. Pittman is a high-end WR2 against the Titans in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee0-d651-a9df-fff575b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 13 times for 33 yards in Washington’s Week 7 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee1-d99b-a1dd-feedae5f0000</link>
      <description>Ugly. The Commanders simply faced a much different Cowboys pass defense than most teams have this season by virtue of strolling into the game without their top three wideouts. “Bill” never had a chance to get untracked, ultimately losing a lot of playing time in a blowout to Chris Rodriguez, who actually managed a touchdown in garbage time. We don’t have major concerns about Croskey-Merritt’s workload, and he did manage to avoid fumbling, but he’ll be more of a low-end RB2 play against the Chiefs in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee1-d99b-a1dd-feedae5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacoby Brissett completed 25-of-36 passes for 279 yards, two touchdowns and a fumble in the Cardinals’ 27-23, Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fead-da18-a39b-febf22a50000</link>
      <description>Brissett started his second straight game with Kyler Murray (foot) continuing to sit. He displayed mobility and kept the offense on-schedule for 279 passing yards, adding 26 yards on six carries. Brissett tossed both of his touchdowns to Trey McBride, who has been his No. 1 target the last couple weeks. He notably got up wincing after a Micah Parsons hip drop tackle that resulted in a penalty in the second quarter, but did not miss any plays. Keisean Nixon forced a strip sack fumble in the third quarter, after which Brissett played relatively mistake-free football. He completed 13 straight passes in the second half and had the Cardinals driving down one score in the two-minute drill in the fourth quarter. The game ended in a failed Hail Mary as Arizona stayed in a close game up until the end. Brissett has been a good fantasy quarterback, with back-to-back games of two touchdowns and a turnover and holding the Cardinals’ top-two highest passing totals of the season. Murray is expected to return after the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye, but Brissett is a fantasy QB2 if he starts again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fead-da18-a39b-febf22a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaydon Blue rushed seven times for 29 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 7 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee3-d99b-a1dd-feefd8e50000</link>
      <description>He had a first-down run called back for holding in the first half, but most of this work came with the Cowboys up 44-22 and trying to run the clock out in the second half. Blue only had 15 snaps and won’t have standalone value next week against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee3-d99b-a1dd-feefd8e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed three times for 12 yards and a touchdown in Washington’s Week 7 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee5-d99b-a1dd-feed22110000</link>
      <description>He only played nine snaps to Jeremy McNichols’ 24, but managed to plunge in on a Marcus Mariota-led third quarter drive to get a touchdown. Rodriguez remains off the fantasy radar until he actually makes a move on “Bill” for more of the early-down duties, but he’s run well in limited samples this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee5-d99b-a1dd-feed22110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 4-of-5 targets for 69 yards and one touchdown in the Colts’ Week 7 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdca-df81-ab9b-ffcfba420000</link>
      <description>Warren once again thrived as a post-catch producer, catching multiple passes in the flats before sprinting down the sideline for explosive gains. He produced two 29-yard gains by catching a pass off to the right side of the field before sprinting down the sideline en route to an explosive gain. He found the end zone on the Colts’ third drive and nearly scored on the prior drive as well, but he and QB Daniel Jones were unable to connect on an end zone target from the Chargers’ 12-yard line. Warren remains a locked-in TE1 against the Titans next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdca-df81-ab9b-ffcfba420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 19-of-29 passes for 179 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ 27-23, Week 7 win over the Cardinals, adding four rushes for 22 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee4-d99b-a1dd-feec0c950000</link>
      <description>Love and the Packers offense had a relatively mediocre showing in the team’s win over the Cardinals. The first and only passing touchdown came in the fourth quarter, with Love connecting with Tucker Kraft for a seven-yard score. The Cardinals defense kept Love in check for the most part as most of his throws were in the shallow and intermediate ranges. He just missed Romeo Doubs for a long score on fourth down in the first quarter and did not have many other deep balls the rest of the game. Despite a non-exciting game, Love moved the ball enough with Doubs, Kraft, and Matthew Golden. He is a low-end QB1 for Week 8 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fee4-d99b-a1dd-feec0c950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
