<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:04:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the Bengals “are still considering” using the franchise tag on Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ec2-d355-a5bd-bfd6bf8a0000</link>
      <description>Does this mean that Hendrickson will be on the Bengals’ roster in 2026? Garafolo answered that question by saying, “maybe, maybe not,” noting that a tag-and-trade scenario may be the goal. The two sides slapped a band-aid on Hendrickson’s offseason trade request last year by agreeing to a one-year deal that gave Hendrickson a $14 million raise for the 2025 season. Unfortunately, a core muscle injury, apparently suffered in Week 6, limited him to just seven games played. Hopefully, things will be resolved quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ec2-d355-a5bd-bfd6bf8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Marc Raimondi reports that court records show Falcons EDGE James Pearce is “facing five felonies” after being arrested on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ec1-d89c-a1be-bfdff42e0000</link>
      <description>Pearce is reportedly being held in Miami-Dade County on a $20,500 bond. The case “was assigned to the felony domestic crimes intake unit,” and Pearce was “given a pre-trial conditional stay-away order” regarding WNBA player Rickea Jackson. We expect more updates in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ec1-d89c-a1be-bfdff42e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans’ agent, Deryk Gilmore, told The Insiders that he thinks Evans’ “competitive nature leads to more football.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3eea-d355-a5bd-bffe64920000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo paraphrased Gilmore’s messaging by saying Evans “has more football in him.” Evans, 32, is coming off his 12th NFL season. It is the first time in which Evans finished with fewer than 1,000 receiving yards, though he missed time with a hamstring strain, a broken collarbone and a concussion. He is scheduled to enter free agency this offseason. After this segment, we expect Evans to touch base with his agent soon, if he hasn’t already.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3eea-d355-a5bd-bffe64920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Goodell said that if the NFL’s “international growth continues,” international teams “are very possible someday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ef4-d629-a1bc-befdd5830000</link>
      <description>In an interview with Westwood One, Goodell discussed the NFL’s expansion into international markets, with games scheduled to take place in Mexico, France, Brazil, Spain and Australia next season. Goodell was, of course, noncommittal, but took the time to note that there are currently “cities out there that could support an NFL team.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ef4-d629-a1bc-befdd5830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that it is “not out of the question” for Kirk Cousins to be on the Falcons’ roster in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f0d-d629-a1bc-bf1dca730000</link>
      <description>Garafolo’s report is somewhat tough to parse. It sounds like he believes the Falcons could release Cousins, and then attempt to re-sign him to a more affordable contract. Renegotiating the contact before releasing him makes more sense. The Browns notably attempted to trade for Cousins last year, with new Falcons head coach Kevin Stefanki then serving as the Browns’ head coach. One wonders if Stefanski might make a push to avoid releasing Cousins in the first place. Garafolo notes that there is expected to be “a lot of interest” in Cousins if he hits free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f0d-d629-a1bc-bf1dca730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes that the Cardinals are “likely” to move on from QB Kyler Murray.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f2a-d629-a1bc-bf3fc5010000</link>
      <description>This seems to be the consensus opinion regarding the Cardinals’ looming decision. Murray has a fully guaranteed $36,800,000 salary in 2025. If he is on the Cardinals’ roster at the beginning of the new league year, on March 11th, it will trigger a $20 million guarantee for the following season. A release is possible, and could help Murray find a new starting role, albeit for less money than he may desire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f2a-d629-a1bc-bf3fc5010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared WR Efton Chism, CB Kobee Minor, OLB Bradyn Swinson, OT Marcus Bryant, G Caedan Wallace, TE C.J. Dippre and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f3f-d629-a1bc-bf3fe4480000</link>
      <description>Chism, an undrafted free agent rookie, was active in the Divisional Round and Wild Card Round but did not play in the AFC Championship Game. He caught 3-of-3 targets for 75 yards and one touchdown in the regular season and caught his lone postseason target for a 20-yard gain. DeVito will serve as the Patriots’ emergency third quarterback today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f3f-d629-a1bc-bf3fe4480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) is active for Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f48-d355-a5bd-bf5c39f50000</link>
      <description>Spillane and LB Harold Landry (knee) are both good to go. This was the expected outcome, but it is great news for the Patriots’ defense nonetheless. ESPN’s Mike Reiss reported earlier today that both players could be limited to some sort of snap count, but those types of plans are sometimes cast aside once the game begins. Regardless, LB Jack Gibbens has proven himself as a capable backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f48-d355-a5bd-bf5c39f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared TE Nick Kallerup, FB Robbie Ouzts, QB Jalen Milroe, LB Chazz Surratt, OLB Jared Ivey, OL Mason Richman and NT Brandon Pili inactive for Super Bowl LX against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f4c-d355-a5bd-bf5c570c0000</link>
      <description>With Kallerup out of the lineup, Seahawks second-round rookie TE Elijah Arroyo will make his postseason debut. Arroyo has been impacted by a late-season knee injury. He will likely operate as the team’s No. 3 tight end today. Ouzts, a fan favorite, is sidelined by a neck injury. Milroe is inactive, but will serve as the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3f4c-d355-a5bd-bf5c570c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that Seahawks run game specialist and assistant OL coach Justin Outten has “come up in league circles as a potential candidate” to replace OC Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ee0-d042-afbc-7ff26aac0000</link>
      <description>Kubiak is set to assume the Raiders’ head-coaching role once the season concludes. Outten has evidently impressed in his lone season with the team. Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker has run for 178 yards and four touchdowns in postseason play, and the Seahawks’ offensive line has played well despite experiencing a few injuries late in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3ee0-d042-afbc-7ff26aac0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
