<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:29:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 2-of-2 targets for 24 yards and one touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa1-da67-a99f-cef54f0b0000</link>
      <description>Mims was seemingly headed toward a big outing when he dusted Colts CB Xavien Howard for a diving 23-yard touchdown on the Broncos’ first drive. He earned just one target after that and was not heard from again, aside from two kick returns that he brought back for 52 yards. Mims is just a boom-bust FLEX option against the Chargers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa1-da67-a99f-cef54f0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Joe Burrow (toe) could miss up to three months if he is required to undergo surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4adc-d86f-abdd-4ffd01e40000</link>
      <description>Schefter reports that images of Burrow’s toe are being sent to foot specialist Dr. Robert Anderson, who will review them and determine if surgery is necessary. It would be about the worst possible outcome for the Bengals’ QB1, who was seen in a walking boot and on crutches after the game. NFL Insider Jordan Schultz later reported that the team “expects to have full details tomorrow,” so we should have a good understanding of where things stand soon. A three month absence would put Burrow on track for a return around mid-December, but will likely also depend on where the Bengals’ record sits by the time he’s ready to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4adc-d86f-abdd-4ffd01e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Conner had 11 rushes for 34 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 2 win against the Panthers, adding one catch for 18 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ad8-d86f-abdd-4ffdcb310000</link>
      <description>What’s clear after two weeks of regular season play is that Conners’ weekly upside will be capped by Trey Benson’s involvement in the Arizona backfield. Benson on Sunday three carries and four receptions and ran one more pass route than Conner. Conner saw much of the goal line work and punched in a one-yard rush for a touchdown in the first half. He underwhelmed overall against a Carolina defense that was bludgeoned on the ground by the Jaguars in Week 1. Conner should still be a decent RB2 play in Week 3 against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ad8-d86f-abdd-4ffdcb310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 1-of-2 targets for 11 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 2 win against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae0-d294-a19b-eef0098e0000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s lone reception went for a touchdown. He continued operating as Arizona’s WR2 behind Marvin Harrison, Jr. He used his big frame to box out a Panthers defender on his touchdown grab, his first since Week 14 of last season and only his fifth since the start of the 2024 season. Wilson won’t be fantasy viable unless MHJ misses time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae0-d294-a19b-eef0098e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 8-of-9 targets for 89 yards and one touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts, rushing once for 11 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4adb-d86f-abdd-4fff99640000</link>
      <description>Franklin looked like an ascending star on the Broncos’ third drive. In the a seven-play sequence, Franklin secured four of his eight receptions, ripped off a 42-yard gain and punched in Bo Nix’s second touchdown of the evening after catching a pass in the flats. He’s worth adding in re-draft formats and can be deployed in the FLEX next week against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4adb-d86f-abdd-4fff99640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Dobbins rushed 14 times for 76 yards and one touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts, adding one reception for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae4-dc44-a9d9-4fe6456e0000</link>
      <description>Dobbins got the requisite workload to return RB2 value despite Broncos head coach Sean Payton employing a three-play rotation at the position. Passing down specialist Tyler Badie was a factor in the high-value two-minute drill, which hurts the other two Broncos backs. Dobbins faces his former team, the Chargers, next week and can be started as a low-end RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae4-dc44-a9d9-4fe6456e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed five times for eight yards in the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts, adding one reception for 16 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae8-dc44-a9d9-4fee39de0000</link>
      <description>Harvey earned two targets on the day, and had a similar workload in Week 1, but unfortunately, he was unable to rip off a 50-yard gain to buoy his box score. The rookie RB also returned three kicks for 70 yards. Harvey is stuck in bench-stash land until head coach Sean Payton removes RB Tyler Badie from the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae8-dc44-a9d9-4fee39de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 1-of-2 targets for 12 yards in the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aec-d294-a19b-eefc2d440000</link>
      <description>Engram is over the hill, at age 31, and simply does not need to be on re-draft rosters. The fact that head coach Sean Payton’s second-favorite tight end, Adam Trautman, is on the roster does not help. Trautman caught 3-of-3 targets for 10 yards and one touchdown, doing nothing to shake Payton’s faith in him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aec-d294-a19b-eefc2d440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Bengals DE Shemar Stewart (ankle/knee) “is believed to have avoided anything major” and will likely be week-to-week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae9-d86f-abdd-4ffdb8ce0000</link>
      <description>Stewart was seen on crutches after Sunday’s win over the Jaguars, but the rookie pass rusher seems to have avoided any kind of serious injury. Stewart had a highly documented holdout earlier this offseason and eventually signed and reported to camp in late July. He has recorded one tackle in two games played this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ae9-d86f-abdd-4ffdb8ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Giddens caught 0-of-1 targets in the Colts’ Week 2 win over the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4af3-d86f-abdd-4fff28880000</link>
      <description>This game remained close from start to finish, so the Colts never had a clear opportunity to get their backup rookie running back a few touches. Giddens did not rush the ball even once. On the plus side, fellow backup Tyler Goodson (elbow) was inactive for this one, suggesting Giddens is ahead of him on the depth chart at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4af3-d86f-abdd-4fff28880000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
