<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Raider will name QB coach Greg Olson as interim OC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</link>
      <description>Olson was born to be a Raider. Literally. The 62-year-old coach is in his third stint with the team since first being hired as offensive coordinator in 2013, and also spent three years as their OC from 2018-2021 under Jon Gruden. Now, instead of having to get better play out of Derek Carr, Olson will take on the task of fixing Geno Smith, who took an unprecedented 10 sacks in Week 12’s loss to the Browns. The Raiders currently ranked 31st in points scored and are 30th in yards. Running back Ashton Jeanty has had his moments, but is also underwhelming to the tune of 166-604-4 on the ground while averaging 3.6 YPC. While it’s hard to imagine the Raiders doing a complete 180 midseason, it’s also hard to imagine things will continue as they have. We’ll get our first look at the Olson-led offense in Week 13 when the Raiders face the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</link>
      <description>Officially fired on his day off, Gabriel will spend Week 13 backing up Shedeur Sanders after missing Week 12’s game due to his brain injury. Gabriel’s lack of a vertical passing game, as evidenced by a 6.4 ADOT and eight deep throw attempts over eight games, may have proven to be his downfall. Gabriel topped 200 passing yards just once in the six starts he made this season while ranking near the bottom of the league in both dropback success rate and EPA per dropback. Barring injury or a complete implosion by Sanders, there’s a good chance this is the last we have seen of Gabriel in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders designated WR Noah Brown (groin) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b73e-db57-afda-f73e23bc0000</link>
      <description>Browns’ 21-day practice window has now been opened, meaning the Commanders can officially activate him off injured reserve whenever they believe he’s ready to go. Brown hasn’t played since Week 2 and has just three catches for 36 yards this season. He caught just 35 passes for 453 yards and one touchdown last season, and has little to no fantasy upside whenever he’s activated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b73e-db57-afda-f73e23bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayen Daniels (elbow) is unlikely to play in Week 13 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b74a-d413-ad9f-b7df182d0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, a source familiar with the situation believes Daniels playing in Week 13 is “a long-shot.” That said, the second-year quarterback is expected to practice this week, meaning a return could be near. Daniels, who has yet to be cleared for contact, per head coach Dan Quinn, has missed five games this season due to a mixed bag of injuries, but has thrown for 1,183-8-2 in his six starts. Fantasy managers looking for a boost at quarterback ahead of the fantasy playoffs should consider stashing Daniels where available, as he remains a strong QB1 candidate any week when he is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b74a-d413-ad9f-b7df182d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders HC Pete Carroll said Ashton Jeanty’s ankle injury is not considered serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b755-db57-afda-f777c67b0000</link>
      <description>When asked whether the injury could limit Jeanty in practice this week, Carroll said he hasn’t “heard that it would yet.” The Raiders’ RB1 totaled 108 yards from scrimmage and a touchdown in Week 12’s loss to the Browns and is one of the very few bright spots for the offense. It doesn’t sound like Carroll is overly concerned about Jeanty’s injury sidelining him for Week 13 against the Chargers. If he were to miss this week’s game, Zamir White would figure to step in on early downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b755-db57-afda-f777c67b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles S Andrew Mukuba suffered a fractured leg in Week 12’s loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b76d-d413-ad9f-b7fd647d0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo, Mukuba’s injury will most likely require surgery. The timeline for his return is unclear at this point, but Mukuba has made an immediate impact for the Eagles this season. The rookie second-rounder has started 10 of the 11 games he’s appeared in while notching two interceptions, three pass breakups, and 46 tackles. Mukuba will land on injured reserve, while backup Sydney Brown is expected to takeover for him as the starter opposite Reed Blankenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b76d-d413-ad9f-b7fd647d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said WR Ashton Dulin (hamstring) will “miss some time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b779-d90e-a9da-bf7f37280000</link>
      <description>He should be considered week-to-week. Dulin’s major fantasy football impact this year was mainly keeping Adonai Mitchell on the bench in Week 5, but this leaves the Colts thin behind their top three receivers and should keep their snap counts high in Week 13 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b779-d90e-a9da-bf7f37280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said “the plan” is to ramp up Chris Godwin’s usage.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b795-d413-ad9f-b7ddc5960000</link>
      <description>Godwin only played 25 of 70 snaps and was limited by a stifling Rams defense that also managed to knock out Baker Mayfield at halftime. There’s a wide range of possible outcomes for Godwin this week depending on his health, how much his usage increases, and if Mayfield is actually able to play (and play effectively) on Sunday. He’s worth considering in Week 13 lineups, but probably won’t have enough upside juice to pass the FLEX line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b795-d413-ad9f-b7ddc5960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) was practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b799-d82c-a79a-b79de1e30000</link>
      <description>It’s a light walkthrough practice, the sort we’d normally ignore at this point in the season. But it marks a step on McLaurin’s return from a quad injury that has derailed his season and possibly points at him getting back this week. If McLaurin is able to suit up against the Broncos this week, he’d probably start out as a FLEX option given the long layoff, a good Broncos defense, and the Commanders likely going with Marcus Mariota at quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b799-d82c-a79a-b79de1e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (ankle) suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12’s win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7a2-d90e-a9da-bfaf5d170000</link>
      <description>Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports Nate Thomas will likely start Thursday against the Chiefs. Most high-ankle sprains are multi-week absences, so it’s possible Guyton winds up on injured reserve ahead of Thanksgiving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7a2-d90e-a9da-bfaf5d170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
