<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Mercury News’ Jerry McDonald reports 49ers TE Jake Tonges will see an increase in playing time if George Kittle (ankle) is out in Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-510c-d968-a19b-59fd49f60000</link>
      <description>Tonges operated as the Niners’ primary pass-catching tight end earlier this season when Kittle was sidelined with an injury, and could find himself in that role again this week against the Bears if Kittle — who sustained a “low to mid” ankle sprain on Monday night — is sidelined. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said he’s confident Tonges can take on the role and be a productive part of the team’s red-hot passing offense. Tonges had 22 receptions over five games with Kittle out in the first half of the season. He would be a viable 14-team league option against the Bears if Kittle can’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-510c-d968-a19b-59fd49f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts head coach Shane Steichen said Anthony Richardson (eye) won’t be activated from IR for Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-511e-d35e-a1bf-55dee7d70000</link>
      <description>Richardson will remained sidelined with an eye injury he suffered in October in a freak pre-game warmup accident. Richardson was seen on the Colts sideline on Monday night against the 49ers wearing dark sunglasses. It’s possible he’s played his final snap with the Colts after a disastrous three-year run in which he had 11 touchdown passes and 13 interceptions over 17 regular season games. He could be a backup or third stringer for another team in 2026 if anyone is willing to take a chance on the 23-year-old QB.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-511e-d35e-a1bf-55dee7d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders placed Brock Bowers (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5130-d35e-a1bf-55f2a8d10000</link>
      <description>It comes out of nowhere but makes sense considering Bowers has dealt with a knee injury all season and the Raiders were long ago eliminated from postseason contention. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said “the decision was made to get it taken care of now and focus on being 100% in 2026.” That could mean Bowers will undergo surgery in the offseason after playing through the knee ailment for four months. Bowers ends 2025 with 64 receptions for 680 yards and seven touchdowns on 84 targets over 12 games. All of his metrics remained similar to his outstanding rookie campaign in 2024. He’ll be an elite fantasy producer in 2026, hopefully with a different quarterback and coaching staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5130-d35e-a1bf-55f2a8d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (concussion) practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5149-d35e-a1bf-55cb6e440000</link>
      <description>Love remains in the NFL’s concussion protocol, however. He suffered the head injury last week against the Bears and did not return to the game. If he’s able to clear the protocol today, he could suit up on Saturday against the Ravens. Malik Willis, who is struggling with a shoulder injury he picked up against the Bears, would presumably get the starting nod if Love is out for Week 17. Willis said he believes he can play through the injury. He would make for an interesting superflex option if he starts against Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5149-d35e-a1bf-55cb6e440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said WR Drake London (knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-515b-dc7a-af9b-dfffafb80000</link>
      <description>Morris added that London’s practice participation would be modified in the coming days. London returned to action in Week 16 against the Cardinals and caught three of his eight targets for 27 yards. London was seen limping on the sideline in the second half, obviously in some discomfort. London should be in lineups in Week 17 against the Rams, whose secondary has shown signs of weakness over the past month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-515b-dc7a-af9b-dfffafb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said Josh Johnson will start Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-516e-d35e-a1bf-55ee7cf40000</link>
      <description>The well-traveled journeyman quarterback will get the nod against Dallas after Marcus Mariota sustained quad and hand injuries in Week 16 against the Eagles. Johnson represents a big-time downgrade for Terry McLaurin, Deebo Samuel, and the rest of the Washington pass catchers, even in a matchup against the burnable Cowboys secondary. Look for the Commanders to go run heavy in Week 17, making Chris Rodriguez viable as a flex option in 12-team formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-516e-d35e-a1bf-55ee7cf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philip Rivers said he expects to start in Week 17 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5180-dc7a-af9b-dfbf22740000</link>
      <description>Colts head coach Shane Steichen has said Rivers would draw his third straight start in Week 17, as the team still has an outside shot to sneak into the postseason if they win their final two games following a Week 16 blowout loss against the 49ers. Rivers displayed better arm strength and a willingness to throw it downfield on Monday night against the Niners, throwing for 277 yards and two touchdowns. If he remains aggressive this week, Michael Pittman, Josh Downs, Tyler Warren, and Alec Pierce could be viable in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5180-dc7a-af9b-dfbf22740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals S Budda Baker entered the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5183-d35e-a1bf-55c3de500000</link>
      <description>Baker was evaluated for a brain injury in Week 16 against the Falcons but re-entered the game, only to report concussion-like symptoms on Wednesday. Baker is likely to sit out this week against the Bengals, creating an even better matchup for Joe Burrow and the Bengals pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5183-d35e-a1bf-55c3de500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Willis (illness) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5188-d968-a19b-59f92bbf0000</link>
      <description>This initially looked like a step in the wrong direction for Willis, who was limited for Tuesday’s practice. However, it was later reported that Willis missed today’s session because of an illness, not his shoulder injury. He still appears to be on track to be available for Saturday’s game. Jordan Love was at practice today, giving him a good chance of suiting up for Week 17 against the Ravens. If he doesn’t clear concussion protocol, the Packers will be down to Willis or Clayton Tune. Willis would have some low-end QB2 juice if he gets the start. Tune, on the other hand, would not be on the fantasy radar as the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5188-d968-a19b-59f92bbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51a4-d56e-afff-f7ec8f710000</link>
      <description>Jackson has now missed the first two practices of the week because of the back contusion he suffered in Baltimore’s Week 16 loss to the Patriots. He is likely on the wrong side of questionable with one practice left to go. If he can’t suit up, Tyler Huntley will draw the start in a must-win game versus the Packers. Huntley would barely register as a fantasy QB2 for a road game versus a solid Green Bay defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51a4-d56e-afff-f7ec8f710000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
