<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes the Titans are “firmly in the mix” for former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3e5-d56e-afff-f7ed4c520000</link>
      <description>A source tells Garafolo that Harbaugh likes “Cam Ward, $100m+ in cap space, high picks, new stadium, GM Mike Borgonzi.” The rest of the Titans roster, which feels downright barren, somehow is not mentioned in this rundown. But the fact that the sources are coming out on the timeline leads us to believe that when the Harbaugh interview roses go out, the Titans may still be in contention to grab one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3e5-d56e-afff-f7ed4c520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ec-d56e-afff-f7ec996f0000</link>
      <description>It’s the first known interview for Harbaugh, who apparently did not leak his schedule to the entire insider crew at NFL Network. It would make sense for him to view this as one of the most appealing jobs out there despite the unsettled nature of the quarterback position, as the Falcons tied for the NFC South “lead” at 8-9 this year and have stars like Bijan Robinson and Drake London on tap along with a rising defense. ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes Harbaugh is still in touch with the Giants, Titans, Browns, Raiders, and Cardinals. We suspect we’ll be blurbing a lot more about this Harbaugh character over the next few days. He seems to be the first domino for most coaching searches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ec-d56e-afff-f7ec996f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman writes that Tucker Kraft (knee) “anticipates” starting training camp on the PUP list but “sounded confident he’ll play in the season opener.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b406-d35e-a1bf-f5c614030000</link>
      <description>“By the time Week 1 rolls around, I’ll be 10 months post-surgery and hopefully bulletproofed by then,” Kraft told reporters. Green Bay’s TE1 had seemed to be becoming their main weapon as the middle of the season came around before his Week 9 ACL tear. The Packers passcatchers will remain a headache for fantasy managers to figure out if Matt LaFleur remains head coach, but at least Kraft will offer a TE1 floor even if the weekly target volume fluctuates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b406-d35e-a1bf-f5c614030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Gabe Davis (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b419-d35e-a1bf-f5db502c0000</link>
      <description>It’s absolutely brutal timing for Davis, who will have his rehab stretch far into the 2026 season as a free agent. His age-27 season will likely hinge on when he can come back from injury, just as his age-26 season did after injuring his knee as a Jaguar. The Bills will go forward with Khalil Shakir, Brandin Cooks, Tyrell Shavers and Keon Coleman as their wideouts against Denver on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b419-d35e-a1bf-f5db502c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) is “week to week” and will not play against the Broncos on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b41d-d56e-afff-f6fdc9330000</link>
      <description>2025 fifth-round pick Jordan Hancock replaced Poyer at safety and will likely be asked to do so going forward. The Bills don’t have much star-level talent on defense this year, so they’re asking a lot out of McDermott’s coaching to help them spring a road upset of the No. 1 seeded Broncos on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b41d-d56e-afff-f6fdc9330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Dalton Kincaid being in a walking boot after the game was “precautionary.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b420-dc7a-af9b-ffbf33030000</link>
      <description>Kincaid appeared to struggle to get up after his fourth-quarter touchdown catch and will likely be spotted on the injury report this week. That’s nothing unusual for Kincaid, who has been on it with a knee for weeks now. It’s possible Dawson Knox becomes a bigger part of the game plan this week, though practice reports will tell more of that story than we know right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b420-dc7a-af9b-ffbf33030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Ed Oliver (biceps) will be designated to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b422-d35e-a1bf-f5e26c0c0000</link>
      <description>The Bills will see if they can get him healthy enough to play against the Broncos in the divisional round. The 21-day window will open for Oliver when Buffalo next practices. McDermott gave the same update for Curtis Samuel, who somehow feels desperately needed with Gabe Davis lost to a torn ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b422-d35e-a1bf-f5e26c0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys scheduled an interview with former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b425-d35e-a1bf-f5e7df930000</link>
      <description>Finally a big name in this search. Gannon was more quirky than good as Eagles defensive coordinator, something he carried over with him in the desert as the unit spit out a 21st-place finish in defensive DVOA in 2025 after a ton of offseason investments in players like Josh Sweat and Will Johnson. Gannon would at least have more time to focus on calling a defense as a coordinator again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b425-d35e-a1bf-f5e7df930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview former Ravens DC Zach Orr for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b429-d35e-a1bf-f5ebda8e0000</link>
      <description>Orr’s defining trait as a defensive coordinator in his two seasons in Baltimore was figuring out where Kyle Hamilton would play after a poor month, then letting him do that. With John Harbaugh fired, Orr’s job is obviously up in the air while the Ravens wait for a new head coach. Orr wouldn’t necessarily be a superb pivot for the Cowboys, but as we have often noted, it would be hard to do worse than Matt Eberflus did last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b429-d35e-a1bf-f5ebda8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed K Lucas Havrisik, OT Brant Banks, DL Dante Barnett, OG Karsen Barnhart, DL Anthony Campbell, TE McCallan Castles, OT Dalton Cooper, TE Drake Dabney, DL James Ester, CB Tyron Herring, LB Jamon Johnson, RB Damien Martinez, S Mark Perry, WR Will Sheppard, RB Pierre Strong Jr. and TE Messiah Swinson to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b42d-d35e-a1bf-f5ef65e00000</link>
      <description>Havrisik hit 4-of-4 field goals and 7-of-9 extra points this year, and the Packers seemed to be developing him as kicker of the future — whatever that means in the NFL — while letting him stay on the practice squad. With Brandon McManus’ job officially under scrutiny, it’s possible he eventually gets the Packers kicker gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b42d-d35e-a1bf-f5ef65e00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
