<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught all five of his targets for 30 yards in the Bills’ 13-12, Week 17 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6798-d968-a19b-7ff9e2770000</link>
      <description>With Dalton Kincaid out, Knox was the featured tight end in Buffalo and was third on the team in targets. He also had a touchdown catch late in the fourth quarter that was overturned and changed to him being down on the half-yard line. With Dalton Kincaid battling a knee injury, and the Bills having very little to play for next week against the Jets, you could see Knox as the primary tight end again in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6798-d968-a19b-7ff9e2770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenny Pickett completed 2-of-2 passes for 16 yards in the Raiders’ Week 17 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6796-dc7a-af9b-efbf32530000</link>
      <description>Pickett connected with rookie WR Dont’e Thornton for a five-yard gain and later linked up with his old pal, WR Shedrick Jackson, Bo Jackson’s nephew, for an 11-yard gain. Unfortunately, on the latter play, it was 4th-and-16 from the Giants’ 47-yard line. Pickett will likely start against the Chiefs next week. He is a borderline QB2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6796-dc7a-af9b-efbf32530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 6-of-7 targets for 35 yards in the Bills’ 13-12, Week 17 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679a-dc7a-af9b-efbf9aa10000</link>
      <description>Once again, Shakir led the Bills in targets and catches but had little to show for it with a long gain of just 13 yards. Essentially, everything the Bills throw to Shakir this season is a screen behind the line of scrimmage or a short crosser, and then they ask him to make defenders miss. He also got himself wide open on a two-point conversion that would have won the game, but Josh Allen simply missed him. The 25-year-old is a talented receiver, but he’ll have to hope the Bills bring in some weapons around him next season so that he can go back to being more than a short-yardage safety blanket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679a-dc7a-af9b-efbf9aa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Lockett caught 2-of-3 targets for nine yards and one touchdown in the Raiders’ Week 17 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6791-d56e-afff-e7f9f7ae0000</link>
      <description>Lockett scored the Raiders’ only touchdown in Week 17. Late in the third quarter, from the Giants’ four-yard line, the veteran wide receiver faked a route into the flats before turning upfield and getting open in the back of the end zone. Raiders QB Geno Smith spotted him and got it to him for the score. Lockett should not be in re-draft lineups against the Chiefs next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6791-d56e-afff-e7f9f7ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 5-of-6 targets for 49 yards in the Raiders’ Week 17 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679d-d35e-a1bf-67df9d030000</link>
      <description>Tucker got involved on the Raiders’ second drive, first picking up five yards through the air. A few plays later, he banked four yards on an end-around before notching a 26-yard reception by running up the seam and breaking outward on a corner route, bringing the football to the Giants’ 15-yard line. Unfortunately, QB Geno Smith (ankle) threw an interception two plays later. Tucker is a shaky WR5 against the Chiefs next week, likely catching passes from Kenny Pickett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679d-d35e-a1bf-67df9d030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandin Cooks caught 4-of-6 passes for 101 yards in the Bills’ 13-12, Week 17 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679e-d56e-afff-e7fed2780000</link>
      <description>Cooks came into this game with just one catch and two drops in his two games with the Bills. However, Josh Allen kept firing deep shots to him and, in the first quarter, Cooks finally hauled in a huge 50-yard completion. Later in the game, on the Bills’ final offensive possession, Cooks converted on a key third-down catch and then made a ridiculous 36-yard grab with a defender draped all over him. At 32 years old, Cooks is not the receiver he used to be, but he can still make some plays down the field, and the Bills are clearly relying on him to do so. If Josh Allen plays in Week 18 against the Jets, we’d expect to see more deep shots to Cooks in an offense that is dying for big plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-679e-d56e-afff-e7fed2780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 19 times for 68 yards in the Eagles’ Week 17 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a2-d56e-afff-e7ea67570000</link>
      <description>The Bills’ defense sold out to stop the run in the pouring rain, and they had defenders in the backfield multiple times throughout the game. Barkley looked healthy and ripped off a solid 16-yard run to the boundary at one point; however, there simply wasn’t a lot of running room for him this week. Things should be a bit easier next week against the Commanders if the Eagles play their starters, which they seem inclined to do with the two-seed on the line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a2-d56e-afff-e7ea67570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 5-of-7 targets for 68 yards in the Eagles’ Week 17 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a4-d56e-afff-e7eca5500000</link>
      <description>Brown made a few tough catches in the first half with defenders in close coverage and put up his fourth-straight 1,000-yard receiving season. However, the Eagles’ offense gained just 19 total yards in the second half, so there was not much for Brown after his early drives. We’d expect more production next week against a Commanders team that Brown just posted 95 yards against a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a4-d56e-afff-e7eca5500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 2-of-5 targets for 25 yards in the Eagles’ Week 17 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a7-d56e-afff-e7ef66ed0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles only threw for 110 yards, so there wasn’t much happening in the passing game on a day when the rain was pouring down. Smith was third on the team in targets and receptions, so we guess there’s that. He did have a touchdown against the Commanders last week, so perhaps he can repeat that when the two teams play in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a7-d56e-afff-e7ef66ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 3-of-6 targets for eight yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 17 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a9-d35e-a1bf-67eb093a0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles had only 190 total yards of offense, so there weren’t many productive players in the rain; however, Goedert converted on a short touchdown pass to put the Eagles up 7-0 after a crucial Josh Allen fumble. This passing game looked uninspired, and the playcalling was highly questionable, but Goedert is clearly a big part of the game plan, which keeps him on the TE1 radar for next week against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-67a9-d35e-a1bf-67eb093a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
