<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Daniel Ekuale suffered a torn ACL in Week 8’s loss to the Packers and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-273f-d5d8-a3ff-ff7f777e0000</link>
      <description>Ekuale exited in Sunday night’s loss to the Packers and did not return to the field. The 31-year-old vet who signed a one-year contract with the Steelers this offseason will now miss the remainder of the year due to his knee injury. Ekuale totaled a career-high 24 tackles last season with the Patriots as a full-time starter, but has tallied just four tackles for the Steelers this season while playing in a reduced role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-273f-d5d8-a3ff-ff7f777e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders elevated K Matthew Wright from the practice squad ahead of Week 8’s game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2748-d245-adfb-b75fa07b0000</link>
      <description>Matt Gay was a late addition to the Commanders’ injury report after suffering a back injury on Friday. The decision to elevate Wright ahead of Monday night’s game against the Chiefs suggests Gay could be sidelined for Week 8, putting any fantasy managers who may be counting on him in a tough spot. If Gay is unable to go, Wright becomes the plug-and-play option you can rely on in a pinch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2748-d245-adfb-b75fa07b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Ed Oliver (bicep) will undergo surgery and be out indefinitely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274b-dab4-a3fb-bf7b25960000</link>
      <description>It’s almost certain to be an IR stint for Oliver. Buffalo has brought in plenty of depth behind him — Larry Ogunjobi stepped up into a bigger role — but there’s no replacing what Oliver does at his best. It’s a major blow for Buffalo’s defensive ceiling ahead of their Week 9 matchup with the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274b-dab4-a3fb-bf7b25960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gay (back) will not play in Week 8 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274e-dab4-a3fb-bf7e885b0000</link>
      <description>This move was expected after the Commanders signed K Matthew Wright to the practice squad and then elevated him to the roster for Monday night’s game. Any fantasy managers who have Gay in their lineup can pivot to Wright in hopes of avoiding a goose egg in the kicker slot. Wright has converted 87.5 percent of his field goals in his career and is 42-of-44 on extra points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274e-dab4-a3fb-bf7e885b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams placed WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f43f50000</link>
      <description>Even though he played through the hamstring injury in Week 8, Atwell only played 10 snaps. Jordan Whittington will be the Rams’ main No. 3 receiver going forward, but won’t have fantasy value unless Davante Adams or Puka Nacua are hurt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-274f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f43f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said DT Shemar Turner (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2752-d5d8-a3ff-ff73fd330000</link>
      <description>Turner ends his rookie year with six tackles, two TFLs, and a 34.4 PFF defensive grade. He was essentially being treated as a rotational player, maxing out at 23 snaps in Week 3. Depending on rehab, Turner may be ready for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2752-d5d8-a3ff-ff73fd330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints HC Kellen Moore said he still hasn’t decided on who will start at QB in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-d5d8-a3ff-ff7753e30000</link>
      <description>Moore pulled Spencer Rattler after a disastrous first half in Sunday’s loss to the Buccaneers and replaced him with rookie Tyler Shough. Shough didn’t fare much better in the 23-3 defeat, but speaking on Monday, Moore said the offensive failures were on the whole unit and not just Rattler. Perhaps he’ll consider going back to Rattler again despite his struggles all season, but we’ve seen coaches downplay a QB change early on only to inevitably show their hand later in the week. It would not be at all surprising if Shough was under center in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-d5d8-a3ff-ff7753e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said Olamide Zaccheaus (knee) is day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-dab4-a3fb-bf775d540000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus caught a season-high seven balls against the Ravens in Week 8 with Luther Burden ruled out early in concussion protocol. Zaccheaus is a pro’s pro, but has not cleared 42 yards receiving all year and does not need to be in fantasy consideration outside of deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2757-dab4-a3fb-bf775d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said Luther Burden is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2759-deb1-a39b-275fd5320000</link>
      <description>The potential absence of both Burden and Olamide Zaccheaus (knee, day-to-day) might drive the Bears to use more Colston Loveland next week against the Bengals. FLEX-hungry fantasy managers should keep in touch with Chicago’s injury report later this week to see what comes of these wideout injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2759-deb1-a39b-275fd5320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz will undergo surgery on his left shoulder, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2773-dab4-a3fb-bf73a8af0000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini was the first to report the news. Wentz’s injury is to his non-throwing shoulder, but after further evaluation of his injury, it was decided that surgery would be the best option to correct things. Wentz stepped up to start in five games for the Vikings this season after J.J. McCarthy suffered an ankle injury in Week 2. Wentz’s season ends with a 1,216-6-5 line through the air, with four of his touchdowns coming in Weeks 3 and 4. The veteran quarterback signed a one-year deal with the Vikings this offseason and will likely have a chance to earn a backup role somewhere in 2026 once he is back to full strength.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2773-dab4-a3fb-bf73a8af0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
