<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 04:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 5-of-8 targets for 24 yards and a touchdown in the Titans’ Week 14 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc03-d005-a9bf-fc3774e50000</link>
      <description>That’s a highly disappointing yardage total considering Dike’s catches and targets, but the looks matched a season high. The score was also his second in three weeks. The Titans have followed through on their pledge to get Dike more involved down the stretch. It has been difficult for it to translate to real fantasy value because of Cam Ward’s ongoing struggles, but Dike is still looking like someone who could be an eventual fantasy WR3. That will not include for Week 15 against the 49ers. Fantasy managers simply have too many other higher-ceiling options with the playoffs beginning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc03-d005-a9bf-fc3774e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) is out for the remainder of Week 14 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb48-d8cf-affb-ff6a9ee40000</link>
      <description>McDuffie departed in the first quarter after landing hard while defending a deep pass to Texans alpha wide receiver Nico Collins. He would remain on the field before being helped off by trainers, who would check the knee for stability. McDuffie spent the remainder of the first quarter testing his knee on the sideline before being ruled out near the half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb48-d8cf-affb-ff6a9ee40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 2-of-3 targets for nine yards in the Steelers’ Week 14 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc02-d8cf-affb-fc2a085b0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth ran a pass route on 22 of the Steelers’ 36 drop backs, leading all tight ends and seeing a small bump in playing time with Darnell Washington sidelined with a concussion he sustained in the first quarter. Jonnu Smith, meanwhile, ran just 13 routes and saw one target. Freiermuth, who doesn’t have more than three receptions in the game since Week 6, could have some deep-league fantasy relevance in Week 15 against the Dolphins if Washington enters the league’s concussion protocol and misses a game or two.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc02-d8cf-affb-fc2a085b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 1-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Titans’ Week 14 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc08-d005-a9bf-fc3c35d60000</link>
      <description>Today snapped a streak of three straight four-catch performances for the rookie fourth-rounder. There just wasn’t any volume in the Titans’ passing attack with Tony Pollard going bonkers on the ground. Cam Ward completed 14 passes, generating 117 yards in the process. Helm has showed enough that he can be considered a potential future TE1 — emphasis on “potential” — but even TE2 status will be difficult to come by during the fantasy playoffs with Chig Okonkwo still successfully vying for looks down the seam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc08-d005-a9bf-fc3c35d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 2-of-2 targets for 20 yards in the Titans’ Week 14 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc0c-d005-a9bf-fc3c21000000</link>
      <description>Still yet to score this season, Okonkwo continues to pair the most modest of floors with the most nonexistent of ceilings. That will not change during the fantasy playoffs, leaving Okonkwo out of sight, out of mind in both re-draft and DFS fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc0c-d005-a9bf-fc3c21000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Thielen caught his lone target for four yards in the Steelers’ Week 14 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc06-da9b-a9bf-fe0f12b50000</link>
      <description>It was Thielen’s first game as a Steeler after parting ways with the Vikings last week. He started the game for Pittsburgh — with Roman Wilson a healthy scratch — but ran just 12 pass routes on 36 Aaron Rodgers drop backs against Baltimore. Marques Valdes-Scantling and Calvin Austin ran ahead of Thielen. Though Mike Tomlin has made some noise about involving Thielen in the Steelers offense, there’s little chance the fading veteran will see much usage in the coming weeks. He should remain on waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc06-da9b-a9bf-fe0f12b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Carter had three rushes for 13 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams, adding two catches for 18 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc10-d8cf-affb-fc3a616b0000</link>
      <description>The Arizona backfield didn’t have much going on in a blowout loss that saw Jacoby Brissett drop back to pass 50 times. Bam Knight led the backfield with seven rushes for just 16 yards, but it was Carter who ran 25 pass routes to 17 routes for Knight. Carter, who had 47 yards on five receptions last week against the Bucs, appears to be the Cards’ primary pass-catching running back. He’s only relevant in the deepest fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc10-d8cf-affb-fc3a616b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Knight had seven rushes for 16 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams, adding three catches for 18 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc15-da9b-a9bf-fe1d3f080000</link>
      <description>Michael Carter, meanwhile, had three carries for 13 yards and caught two balls for 18 yards in the loss. While Carter ran more pass routes than Knight, it was Knight who led the backfield with six targets on the day. Knight in Week 13 totaled 98 yards on 14 touches as the de facto lead back for Arizona. Knight will be flex worthy in deep leagues next week against a tough Texans defense that has shut down opposing ground games in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc15-da9b-a9bf-fe1d3f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andre Baccellia caught 1-of-3 targets for three yards in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc19-d005-a9bf-fc3dc55c0000</link>
      <description>Baccellia, with Greg Dortch (chest) on injured reserve and Xavier Weaver dealing with an ankle injury, operated as the Cardinals’ WR2 in Week 14. He logged a pass route on 39 of Jacoby Brissett’s 50 drop backs. Weaver would likely take on the WR2 role if he’s able to suit up in Week 15 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc19-d005-a9bf-fc3dc55c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) will not return to Week 14 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc05-d77b-adfa-fe8728120000</link>
      <description>Chubb departed in the second quarter and did not return following the half, with the team ruling him out for the remainder of the game. It’ll be the Woody Marks show in the Houston backfield for the remainder of the game. Chubb managed just three yards on one carry prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc05-d77b-adfa-fe8728120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
