<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson had six rushes for 25 yards in the Packers’ Week 3 loss against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e67-d93f-ad9d-7ee7b48a0000</link>
      <description>Wilson handled six carries while Josh Jacobs saw 16 rushing attempts for just 34 yards against a stout Cleveland defense. Wilson has established himself for now as the Packers’ No. 2 running back who would likely take over the backfield should Jacobs miss any time in 2025. Wilson should be rostered in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e67-d93f-ad9d-7ee7b48a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 4-of-6 targets for 39 yards in the Falcons’ Week 3 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e63-dfde-a1bd-7eef56390000</link>
      <description>Pitts saw most of his usage come in the shallow-yardage area, catching dump-offs and checkdowns for 39 yards on the day. He is a clear top-four pass-catching option in the Falcons’ offense, sharing shallow-yardage routes with Bijan Robinson. Michael Penix had a brutal day throwing the ball against the Panthers, and better days are ideally ahead for the entire offense. Pitts is the beneficiary of intermediate throws over the middle of the field, a role no other tight end on the roster has the skills to take from him this season. He will be a fantasy TE2 for Week 4 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e63-dfde-a1bd-7eef56390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 1-of-3 targets for six yards in the Steelers’ Week 3 win over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e69-d6a5-adff-feed39840000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth hadn’t done much through two weeks entering this game, but he at least had three catches in both outings. Even the PPR floor fell out versus New England with a 14 percent target share and just one grab. Freiermuth is behind Jonnu Smith in the pecking order for targets, making him the backup tight end on a low-volume passing attack. He is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e69-d6a5-adff-feed39840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman Jr. caught 6-of-6 targets for 73 yards and a touchdown in the Colts’ Week 3 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e5f-d6a5-adff-fedf43560000</link>
      <description>Pittman has now bookended a 4/40/0 Week 2 with nearly identical statlines. Although he’s competing with Tyler Warren to be the No. 1 “weapon,” Pittman has been firmly re-established as the Colts’ No. 1 receiver. Never known for ceiling, Pittman at least appears to have brought back his WR3 floor. A Week 4 Los Angeles road trip to face the Rams will be a stiff test for a team that’s had two non-competitive contests and a Week 2 dog fight with the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e5f-d6a5-adff-fedf43560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught 4-of-4 targets for 52 yards in the Packers’ Week 3 loss against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e6e-d6a5-adff-feef4c0e0000</link>
      <description>Golden led the Packers in receiving yards on another low-volume day for Jordan Love, who had just 25 attempts on the day. Golden had the team’s biggest play of the day with a 34-yard grab in the second half after getting good separation from a Browns defender. The rookie has struggled to start his NFL career. He had just two catches for 16 scoreless yards coming into Week 3. With Jayden Reed (shoulder, foot) sidelined, Golden should see more snaps and routes in the run-first Packers offense. Golden might have some flex appeal in Week 4 against the Dallas secondary, one of the worst NFL coverage units in living memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e6e-d6a5-adff-feef4c0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 3-of-5 targets for 38 yards in the Colts’ Week 3 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e78-d1b3-a5dd-6f7984a60000</link>
      <description>Warren’s box scores have now declined in back-to-back weeks after his 7/76 Week 1, but he’s remained heavily involved in every aspect of the Colts’ offense. Today that included throwing a hellacious lead block on a Jonathan Taylor touchdown. This is probably Warren’s absolute floor, and it’s doubtful we have seen his ceiling. He remains an intriguing top-five tight end option for Week 4 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e78-d1b3-a5dd-6f7984a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 2-of-3 targets for 24 yards in the Colts’ Week 3 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7a-d93f-ad9d-7effbb7b0000</link>
      <description>Downs now has 10 catches for 97 yards through the Colts’ 3-0 start. Not awful. Also not moving the needle as a WR4 in fantasy. With a robust rushing attack and deep skill corps, the Colts’ passing volume is going to be all over the map. It’s difficult to see Downs commanding consistent enough looks to really be worth it in 12-team leagues for the time being, though the receiver waiver wire is barren as usual. With injuries being what they are, we would probably still hold onto Downs until injuries or byes force us to cut him loose.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7a-d93f-ad9d-7effbb7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared WR Xavier Worthy, CB Kristian Fulton, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, DE Michael Danna, and C Hunter Nourzad inactive for Week 3 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7d-d6a5-adff-fefd73c90000</link>
      <description>Worthy had previously been ruled out so his game status comes as little surprise. The speedy second-year receiver is looking to return from a shoulder injury sustained in a collision with teammate Travis Kelce early in the team’s Week 1 win. Kelce is sorely needed after numerous mental lapses to begin the 2025 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7d-d6a5-adff-fefd73c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley caught 1-of-7 targets for 27 yards in the Titans’ Week 3 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7e-dfde-a1bd-7effda780000</link>
      <description>Weeks 1 and 2 were already disappointing, but this was Ridley’s worst statline yet. He was missed for a potential deep score in the fourth quarter, but Ridley has mostly been getting in cardio as a struggling Cam Ward tries to strike up a connection with fellow rookie Elic Ayomanor. Ridley is still profiling as the Titans’ No. 1 wideout. It’s just unclear what that means in this dreadful attack. Definitely more of a WR4 than WR3 for the time being, Ridley has a lamentable Week 4 matchup in the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7e-dfde-a1bd-7effda780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared LB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles, LB Darius Muasau, DL Chauncey Golston, OL Evan Neal, TE Thomas Fidone II, DL Rakeem Nuñez-Roches Sr, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 3 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7f-dfde-a1bd-7eff47d80000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here as the Giants prepare for an upset bid over the Chiefs. The New York offense remains heavily built around standout wide receiver Malik Nabers, although Wan’Dale Robinson saw his route tree extended slightly in their Week 2 loss to the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e7f-dfde-a1bd-7eff47d80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
