<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released WR KJ Hamler.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72b-de13-afdc-e7eb7e490000</link>
      <description>Hamler, 26, was unable to stick as one of the backend wideouts for the active roster. It won’t be a surprise at all if he’s added to the practice squad if/when he doesn’t find another opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72b-de13-afdc-e7eb7e490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks released RB Damien Martinez.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72d-dbe3-a9bb-f77f9e2a0000</link>
      <description>Despite Martinez’ college record of success rushing for 1,000 yards and 10 touchdowns at Miami last year, the seventh-round pick was outplayed in preseason by George Holani, who appears to be the Seahawks’ RB3 to start the year. Martinez is still a name to watch as he could catch on with another team’s 53-man roster via waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72d-dbe3-a9bb-f77f9e2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jourdan Rodrigue believes Matthew Stafford’s back injury “is going to be a thing” that may have to be managed “throughout the entire season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e710-de13-afdc-e7dbf47d0000</link>
      <description>Rodrigue is encouraged by Stafford’s return to practice, but expressed concern regarding his ability to stay healthy if he takes “a bad hit.” She also notes that the Rams have built in “backstops” by constructing a deep roster, with the hopes of staying in the Super Bowl hunt even if Stafford misses time. When on the field, Stafford can be expected to facilitate high-end performances for Puka Nacua, Davante Adams and Kyren Williams. He makes for a shaky QB2 option, himself, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e710-de13-afdc-e7dbf47d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans waived WR Xavier Restrepo.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72e-dbe3-a9bb-f77fb9930000</link>
      <description>Restrepo is a candidate for the Titans practice squad per Adam Schefter and will almost certainly head there if he doesn’t get a 53-man roster spot elsewhere. Restrepo played 44 offensive snaps in the preseason per PFF and finished with a solid 68.7 offensive grade. He may eventually be fantasy-relevant in Tennessee if the receivers in front of him wash out just based on his connection with former college teammate Cam Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e72e-dbe3-a9bb-f77fb9930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Archer of ESPN reports that the Cowboys have released G Saahdiq Charles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e730-db7b-a5dd-e734a0aa0000</link>
      <description>Charles was signed to a one-year deal by the Cowboys in April, but the 26-year-old former fourth-round pick was unable to secure one of the backup offensive line stops. He’s now free to sign with a new team, but also could be a practice squad candidate for Dallas if he doesn’t find a new home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e730-db7b-a5dd-e734a0aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released DE Clelin Ferrell.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6fc-de13-afdc-e6ff81130000</link>
      <description>The former first-round defensive end started 10 games for the Commanders in 2024, notching 26 tackles and 3.5 sacks across 14 appearances. Ferrell is well traveled at this point in his career but has mostly settled for a rotational role the previous three seasons with the Raiders, 49ers, and Commanders. His veteran status and continued production on the field could land him a new home via waivers over the coming 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6fc-de13-afdc-e6ff81130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans released QB Trevor Siemian.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73b-db7b-a5dd-e73fb4f10000</link>
      <description>Siemian played in Tennessee’s final two preseason games after signing with the team late in the 2024 season. He had a 74.1 PFF passing grade in 34 snaps. Paul Kurharsky reports the Titans want him on their practice squad. This means Brandon Allen has won the job to be Cam Ward’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73b-db7b-a5dd-e73fb4f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released LB Eugene Asante.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73a-de13-afdc-e7fb7ca00000</link>
      <description>Asante gets an injury settlement from the Dolphins after being injured in the third preseason game. The undrafted free agent reportedly had a strong camp and was pushing to make the final 53 in Miami before the injury. He likely faces an uphill battle to crack an NFL roster this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73a-de13-afdc-e7fb7ca00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived QB Sean Clifford.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e734-de13-afdc-e7ff98d20000</link>
      <description>The Packers also waived rookie QB Taylor Elgersma. This leaves just Jordan Love (thumb) and Malik Willis on the active roster. We take it as a good sign for Love’s health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e734-de13-afdc-e7ff98d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins worked out K Eddy Pineiro, formerly of the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73e-de13-afdc-e7ff25590000</link>
      <description>Jason Sanders will be sidelined to start the regular season, prompting the Dolphins to explore their options at kicker for the first few games. Pineiro has a career 88.1% field goal conversion rate but ended his 2024 season with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e73e-de13-afdc-e7ff25590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
