<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 4-of-4 targets for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Titans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Falcons on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b341-d45c-a7fc-b35b87910000</link>
      <description>While Chig Okonkwo is still the top tight end with the Titans, he seems to have legitimate rookie competition in the form of Helm. Okonkwo didn’t suit up Friday, but played every snap with the first team in the Titans’ first preseason game. Helm made the most of his opportunity Friday by catching every pass that came his way and hitting pay dirt. While it’s difficult to get excited about Helm’s fantasy prospects in 2025, he could be relevant enough to negatively impact Okonkwo’s fantasy stock this year. In the long term, Helm could be part of the Titans’ succession plan at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b341-d45c-a7fc-b35b87910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold completed 4-of-4 passes for 34 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 2 preseason game against the Chiefs on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b348-d90d-a5bd-b35b45c20000</link>
      <description>Darnold and the Seahawks offense went through the Chiefs’ defense like a hot knife through butter. The 28-year-old quarterback hit a series of short roll-out passes when the Seahawks running game took a break from gashing the Chiefs. If this drive was any indication of what the regular season will be like, the Seahawks won’t have any trouble putting up points this year with Darnold at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b348-d90d-a5bd-b35b45c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet ran five times for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ preseason Week 2 game against the Chiefs on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b353-d90d-a5bd-b35b634b0000</link>
      <description>Kenneth Walker III didn’t play, but Charbonnet was excellent in the lead back role Friday while averaging nine yards per carry and capping the opening drive for Seattle with a 15-yard touchdown run. Heading into the season behind Walker on the depth chart, Charbonnet is a premium backup given the Seahawks’ commitment to the running game under Klint Kubiak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b353-d90d-a5bd-b35b634b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith ran three times for 22 yards and caught 2-of-2 targets for 16 yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 2 game against the Seahawks on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b35b-df63-a199-fb7b9bea0000</link>
      <description>Smith only had five touches, but showed he has some juice against the Seahawks. The 22-year-old running back made a defender miss in the backfield before bouncing the run outside and gaining 10 yards. Smith also caught both of his targets for 16 yards. He certainly looked better than Elijah Mitchell, who had just nine yards on four carries. Smith figures to mix in as one of a few backs behind Isiah Pacheco this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b35b-df63-a199-fb7b9bea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel (hamstring) is expected to start against the Eagles in Week 2 of the preseason on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b366-d45c-a7fc-b37efa1b0000</link>
      <description>Gabriel is dealing with a hamstring injury, but is well enough to play against the Eagles on Saturday. Shedeur Sanders (oblique) and Kenny Pickett (hamstring) won’t play while also dealing with injuries while Joe Flacco will be held out as the likely starter for Week 1. Tyler Huntley figures to come off the bench for Gabriel and play a good amount of reps in reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b366-d45c-a7fc-b37efa1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton left Friday’s Week 2 preseason win over the Chiefs with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3b1-d45c-a7fc-b3bbc6d40000</link>
      <description>Horton made one catch for 12 yards before exiting. Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters that Horton could have reentered if needed, but obviously wasn’t going to take those chances in an exhibition bout. Horton has impressed this summer, and has a chance to be the third wide receiver when the season opens in September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3b1-d45c-a7fc-b3bbc6d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 4-of-7 passes for 46 yards in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f1-d45c-a7fc-b3fb98360000</link>
      <description>Maye and most of the starters played two series for the Patriots against the Vikings. The first drive stalled due to a delay of game penalty which placed them behind the sticks while the second was largely focused on the run game with TreVeyon Henderson and Antonio Gibson, resulting in an eight-yard touchdown scamper from the electric rookie. Maye was without Stefon Diggs in this one, which left Kayshon Boutte as a starter alongside Mack Hollins and DeMario Douglas. Maye connected with Hollins on three of his pass attempts, something this team could need once the regular season roles around considering his deep threat ability. It remains uncertain if Maye and the starters will see action in the final preseason tune-up next week against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f1-d45c-a7fc-b3fb98360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed four times for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f7-d90d-a5bd-b3ff00c70000</link>
      <description>Rhamondre Stevenson was held out in this one, leaving the backfield to Henderson and Antonio Gibson for the team’s first two drives with the starters. It was a mixed bag for Henderson, who got stuffed on his first two carries before ripping off carries of 11 yards and eight yards to cap off his final drive, the last of which resulted in his touchdown. Henderson brings elite play-making ability and plus vision and burst but his end-of-year production likely relies heavily on an offensive line currently ranked as a bottom five unit. Fantasy managers will want to monitor Stevenson’s injury after the veteran missed the previous week of practice in camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3f7-d90d-a5bd-b3ff00c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas failed to catch his only target in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fb-df63-a199-fbfbb7050000</link>
      <description>Douglas predictably drew the start but failed to haul in his lone target on two drives worth of action against the Vikings. He is locked into a starting role alongside veterans Stefon Diggs and Mack Hollins, the latter of whom will likely cede snaps to Kayshon Boutte this season. Douglas is clearly more beneficial to rosters in full PPR formats but brings enough to the table as a viable late-round bye week fill in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fb-df63-a199-fbfbb7050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught all three targets for 38 yards in the Patriots’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fe-d45c-a7fc-b3fe38810000</link>
      <description>Hollins operated as Drake Maye’s top target with fellow veteran Stefon Diggs out of action. The highlight of his day was a solid 20-yard snag on the second possession on a ball down the sideline. Hollins should operate as the starting X-type receiver but could cede snaps to Kayshon Boutte as the team looks to introduce packages designed to open up the middle of the field for their primary pass-catchers. That leaves his fantasy value in questionable territory despite the plus showing Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b3fe-d45c-a7fc-b3fe38810000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
