<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins QB Tua Tagovailoa (hip/left thumb) is not on Miami’s final injury report for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf94-dd4c-afb9-efd5d9fe0000</link>
      <description>As expected, Tagovailoa practiced in full the final two sessions of the week after a limited practice on Wednesday. He’ll be on the QB2 line against a Chargers defense that has been decent against the pass this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf94-dd4c-afb9-efd5d9fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Curtis Samuel (neck/ribs) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf98-d94a-a79d-cf9db70d0000</link>
      <description>It’s a downgrade from a limited session on Wednesday.So dawn goes down to dayNo Curtis Samuel active status can stay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf98-d94a-a79d-cf9db70d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Jalen Ramsey (hamstring) is questionable for Pittsburgh’s Week 6 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf9c-def2-abdb-dffd4a850000</link>
      <description>He got in a full session after a pair of DNPs and talked shop with the media, two signs that strongly point to him being available for Week 6. Pittsburgh also has a game next Thursday night so it was likely that Ramsey would miss that game as well if he wasn’t up for Sunday. It seems like the star defensive back will be ready to go on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf9c-def2-abdb-dffd4a850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers LB Alex Highsmith (ankle) and CB Joey Porter (hamstring) are off Pittsburgh’s final Week 6 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf9e-dd4c-afb9-efdf0e380000</link>
      <description>Mike Tomlin said on Tuesday that he felt good about having both players available this week and after five full practices between them, both will be back in the fold. Porter has not played since Week 1, while Highsmith has been out since Week 2. The Steelers defense looks to be at almost full strength on Sunday against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf9e-dd4c-afb9-efdf0e380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf7d-dd4c-afb9-effdafd70000</link>
      <description>The Bills are dutifully managing the oft-injured tight end’s reps this week. His continued limited participation suggests he will play on Monday night against the Falcons, though he may be prone to re-injury. On the plus side, Kincaid has been playing very efficiently in his limited game-day role. Unlike many TE1s, he ranks just second in his position group in offensive snaps (171). If active, he can be started as an elite TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf7d-dd4c-afb9-effdafd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) is out for Week 6’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa0-dd4c-afb9-efe130210000</link>
      <description>He did not practice all week, said he wasn’t sure if he’d be an injured reserve candidate or not, and exited Week 4’s game in an ambulance. We’d be unsurprised if Austin was placed on IR over the weekend. Given how run-happy they’ve been and how involved the tight ends are in this offense, we’d hold off on trying to figure out who Pittsburgh’s No. 2 receiver is while speculating for fantasy value this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa0-dd4c-afb9-efe130210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) was limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa3-d94a-a79d-cfaf1f9a0000</link>
      <description>It seems like Loveland is still on track to play in Week 6, but the fact that we haven’t seen a full session yet makes us feel uncomfortable with the idea of holding on until MNF to play him as a TE2. He might need an acclimation week. Loveland is probably on pace to wind up on the questionable line on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa3-d94a-a79d-cfaf1f9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (thigh) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa5-dd4c-afb9-efe55a6d0000</link>
      <description>It’s a big turnaround from Thursday’s DNP, which now feels a lot like just a rest session. Monangai should slot in as Chicago’s backup running back for Monday Night’s game against the Commanders assuming we don’t get a negative update on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa5-dd4c-afb9-efe55a6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) is not on Tennessee’s final injury report for Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa8-dd4c-afb9-efe94cfb0000</link>
      <description>He got in a full session on Friday to get removed from the report entirely. Spears should be in line for a modest workload increase in Week 6 and profiles as a desperation FLEX play against a Raiders defense that has held up well against the run but can be had through the air. Perhaps Spears’ ability to earn targets will come in to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa8-dd4c-afb9-efe94cfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa9-db72-a199-ffebed4b0000</link>
      <description>Simmons is operating as a one-man wrecking crew along the Titans’ defensive line. He is the only Titans defender who has double-digit quarterback pressures (24) and his four sacks are double that of the next closest player. Titans OLB Arden Key is, unfortunately, sidelined by a quad injury and WR Van Jefferson (ankle) is questionable to play despite practicing in full on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfa9-db72-a199-ffebed4b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
