<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (shoulder) was limited in practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ed8-d673-a39e-fed9d55a0000</link>
      <description>That’s a big upgrade for Moore, who left Week 10’s game with the shoulder injury. Now it looks like he has a chance to be questionable at worst, and perhaps get cleared off the report as has been the usual thing before this shoulder injury. It would also likely crush the streaming value of Luther Burden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ed8-d673-a39e-fed9d55a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7edc-d1e7-a1fa-7efe32f50000</link>
      <description>He’ll almost certainly be up and the Bears will again divvy up carries between Swift and Kyle Monangai. Swift is the better bet of the two, and given how often the Vikings have been run on this year, this could qualify as a plus matchup that leaves Swift a high-end RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7edc-d1e7-a1fa-7efe32f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ec8-d673-a39e-fed989a50000</link>
      <description>Last week, listed with heel and ankle injuries, Odunze sat out on Wednesday, practiced in a limited capacity on Thursday and practiced fully on Friday. He is on track to do the same this week. Assuming he indeed upgrades to full participation tomorrow, Odunze can be started as a borderline WR1/2 against the Vikings this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ec8-d673-a39e-fed989a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee/hamstring) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ede-d1e7-a1fa-7efe86c10000</link>
      <description>Watson told reporters he plans to play and this is just the team being precautious. The big quote of the session was “I like being football sore not ACL/knee sore.” It doesn’t sound like this is anything to worry about, and Watson figures to be a FLEX option in Week 11 against a rough Giants defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ede-d1e7-a1fa-7efe86c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (back) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7edd-d45b-affe-7fdf8b230000</link>
      <description>The Bears’ veteran tight end is on track to play in Week 11 against the Vikings, though he will only warrant TE2 consideration with rookie TE Colston Loveland establishing himself as the team’s starter. The youngster has out-targeted Kmet 11-4 over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7edd-d45b-affe-7fdf8b230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Khalil Shakir (ankle/ribs) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ee1-d713-ad9e-7ef5453e0000</link>
      <description>Shakir continues to practice in a limited capacity while sporting a non-contact jersey. It would be great to see him feel well enough to shed it on Friday, but that may not happen. Protecting the injured ribs for as long as is needed is the smart move. For now, we expect Shakir to play in his typical No. 1 wide receiver role against the Buccaneers this weekend. He is a WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ee1-d713-ad9e-7ef5453e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Rico Dowdle (quad) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ee3-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb745e0000</link>
      <description>It’s the same pattern the Panthers used with Dowdle last week, with an off-day on Wednesday and a limited session on Thursday. It would be surprising if Dowdle wasn’t cleared off the injury report tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ee3-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb745e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ede-d713-ad9e-7edecc330000</link>
      <description>Kincaid remains sidelined, as expected, after being labeled “week-to-week” on Monday. The Bills’ top receiving tight end is highly unlikely to play this weekend, expectedly elevating veteran TE Dawson Knox to the starting role. Youngster, TE Jackson Hawes, should be monitored though. Hawes has already established himself as a talented blocker and is averaging 2.17 yards per route run, albeit on a very small sample.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7ede-d713-ad9e-7edecc330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7efd-d713-ad9e-7efd5ee10000</link>
      <description>With such a lengthy layoff, we probably shouldn’t assume that Godwin will return for sure this week, but back-to-back limited sessions is usually a good sign that a player will give it a go on Sunday. Godwin would make for a WR3/FLEX play against the Bills if he suited up. We’d bet he at least makes the questionable line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7efd-d713-ad9e-7efd5ee10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (shoulder) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7eff-d45b-affe-7fff2b7b0000</link>
      <description>This is promising, though we wouldn’t go as far as to say that we’re 100 percent convinced Irving will play in Week 11 given the long layoff. Back-to-back limited sessions augur well for Irving’s return though — most players who practice on Wednesday and Thursday make it to game day. We’d bet he’ll get a questionable tag on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7eff-d45b-affe-7fff2b7b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
