<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6359-d1b3-a5dd-637939a60000</link>
      <description>Andy Reid was non-committal on Worthy when asked by reporters on Friday, so Worthy may be an annoying late-game game-time decision for fantasy managers. Worthy got in three limited practices this week while managing his shoulder that he dislocated in Week 1. Hollywood Brown and Tyquan Thornton would have more appeal as fantasy options if Worthy did not play. If Worthy does play, he’ll likely be a boom-bust WR3, as he possibly deals with snap count/decoy issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6359-d1b3-a5dd-637939a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out CB Jaylon Johnson (groin) for Week 3 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6354-d6a5-adff-f7d552da0000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear why the Bears have not yet placed Johnson on injured reserve, but that could occur on Saturday. The star cornerback is expected to undergo surgery after suffering what is believed to be a season-ending groin injury. Bears slot CB Kyler Gordon, LB T.J. Edwards and backup CB Jaylon Jones are all sidelined by hamstring injuries. Bears DL Grady Jarrett (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 3, but the Cowboys should be able to pass and run as they please against this depleted unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6354-d6a5-adff-f7d552da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-635c-dfde-a1bd-7fdd8c440000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Thursday and Friday and would seemingly be on the optimistic side of questionable. Royals hasn’t played yet this season and it would be a surprise if he were fantasy-relevant right away even with the current state of the Chiefs wideout room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-635c-dfde-a1bd-7fdd8c440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) for Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6363-d93f-ad9d-7be738120000</link>
      <description>Journeyman QB Carson Wentz starts in McCarthy’s stead. He is a boom-bust QB2 option against a soft Bengals defense. Vikings C Ryan Kelly and backup LT Justin Skule both suffered concussions in Week 2. Neither player cleared the protocol. On the plus side, LT Christian Darrisaw (knee), S Harrison Smith (illness) and LB Andrew Van Ginkel (concussion) are questionable to play in Week 3 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6363-d93f-ad9d-7be738120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) will not play in Week 3’s game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6371-dfde-a1bd-7ffd44b40000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week for the second-straight week and could be an IR candidate over the weekend as the Steelers set their roster. His absence should help make fantasy managers more than comfortable firing up fantasy-relevant members of the Patriots passing game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6371-dfde-a1bd-7ffd44b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6372-d6a5-adff-f7f7e6930000</link>
      <description>He got in a full session on Friday after two limited sessions on Wednesday and Thursday and looks to be on the optimistic side of questionable to make his NFL debut in Week 3. Harmon suffered an MCL sprain in Pittsburgh’s preseason finale and, should he be active on Sunday, will wind up missing about a month as forecasted at the time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6372-d6a5-adff-f7f7e6930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulder) isn’t on Philadelphia’s final injury report for Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6389-d6a5-adff-f7cdfdce0000</link>
      <description>Carter got in a full practice today and yesterday. He’ll be a big part of Philadelphia’s defensive game plan, per usual, as they attempt to disrupt the Rams’ banged-up interior line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6389-d6a5-adff-f7cdfdce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) is not on Philadelphia’s final injury report for Week 3’s game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-638b-d1b3-a5dd-63fb98b90000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full today to find his way off the questionable line entirely. The Rams don’t profile as a smash spot for Goedert, but you can certainly do worse at the back of the TE ranks in Week 3, and the Eagles haven’t exactly excelled at targeting their wideouts thusfar in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-638b-d1b3-a5dd-63fb98b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts TE Tyler Warren (toe) is questionable for Week 3 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6385-dfde-a1bd-7f8da7fe0000</link>
      <description>Warren’s return to practice on Thursday was encouraging, but his inability to practice in full on Friday is concerning. If the Colts allow him to suit up, he should be in starting lineups due to his already-elite per-play efficiency. He appears to be truly questionable, though. Fantasy managers should make backup plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6385-dfde-a1bd-7f8da7fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Will Shipley (oblique) is out for Week 3’s game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-638d-d93f-ad9d-7bcf1b080000</link>
      <description>Shipley got in back-to-back limited practices. so he’ll likely be a candidate to return in Week 4. Once Shipley is healthy, we expect him to assume the main RB2 role behind Saquon Barkley. It might start with a week of everyone sharing duties though while the Eagles make sure Shipley is fully good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-638d-d93f-ad9d-7bcf1b080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
