<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden (wrist) is active for Week 14 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa62-d77b-adfa-fae39a5f0000</link>
      <description>Golden will play for the first time since Week 11. He has missed much of the second half of the season to date with wrist and shoulder injuries. With Jayden Reed also back this week, Golden’s role will likely be limited. He is a WR5/6 for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa62-d77b-adfa-fae39a5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals declared WR Marvin Harrison Jr., RB Emari Demercado, S Rabbit Taylor-Demerson, OL Evan Brown, WR Xavier Weaver, and DL Walter Nolen III inactive for Week 14 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa58-d005-a9bf-fa7c2bd90000</link>
      <description>Harrison will miss another game, making Michael Wilson a top-15 fantasy option in all formats in what should be negative game script for the Cardinals offense. Bam Knight is likely to serve as Arizona’s lead back with Demercado out; Knight could see a bump in routes and possibly targets against LA. Weaver’s absence could make Andre Baccellia the team’s WR2 since Greg Dortch in on IR with a chest injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa58-d005-a9bf-fa7c2bd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared WR Rome Odunze, CB Tyrique Stevenson, LB Ruben Hyppolite, DE Dominique Robinson, DT Jonathan Ford, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 14 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa67-d005-a9bf-fa7783dc0000</link>
      <description>Odunze was ruled out on Friday after missing all three practices this week. He is considered week-to-week with a stress fracture in his foot. Expect rookie Luther Burden to see more work with routes up for grabs in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa67-d005-a9bf-fa7783dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz (knee) exited in the third quarter of Week 14’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa5a-d77b-adfa-fadb69ac0000</link>
      <description>Ertz attempted to make a leaping grab, only to have his legs taken out by safety Jay Ward. Ertz remained down on the field for several minutes while having his right knee tended to, and was unable to put any weight on it while being assisted to the sidelines. It was a bad looking injury that is likely to sideline him for the remainder of the game and perhaps longer. If his day is over, Ertz will finish with a 1-11-0 line on two targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa5a-d77b-adfa-fadb69ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) is active for Week 14 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa69-d77b-adfa-faebbe690000</link>
      <description>Reed is returning to the lineup after missing over two months with foot and shoulder issues. Fantasy managers should take a wait-and-see approach with him this week. We suspect his role will be limited out of the gates. Inactive for the Packers are OL Donovan Jennings, DL Quinton Bohanna, WR Savion Williams, DL Lukas Van Ness, and DL Nazir Stackhouse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa69-d77b-adfa-faebbe690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is active for Week 14 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa6d-da9b-a9bf-fe6defac0000</link>
      <description>Adams missed practice on Wednesday and was limited on Thursday, but will suit up against the Cardinals. His involvement near the goal line has made Adams a weekly WR1 in 12-team leagues, though he’s become the rare TD-dependent elite wide receiver. Rams declared QB Stetson Bennett, CB Darious Williams, RB Jarquez Hunter, OL Beau Limmer, and DL Ty Hamilton inactive for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa6d-da9b-a9bf-fe6defac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz (knee) was carted to the locker room in Week 14’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa6e-da9b-a9bf-fe6fdbb00000</link>
      <description>It’s safe to say Ertz’s day is over after the veteran receiver suffered a devastating knee injury in the third quarter. Ertz, who caught one pass for 11 yards in Sunday’s game, could be seen in tears while being carted away. The 35-year-old is likely looking at a long-term injury that could prove to be a season-ender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa6e-da9b-a9bf-fe6fdbb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Bishop left Week 14’s game against the Bengals with a lower-body injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa3a-da9b-a9bf-fe3fd1d30000</link>
      <description>Bishop appeared to suffer a lower-body injury at the end of Week 13’s win over the Steelers, but didn’t miss any practice time this week. Then, in the second half of Week 14, he was seen repeatedly running in place on the sideline and trying to get loose. Unfortunately for him and the Bills, he was then taken into the locker room. Cam Lewis has come in to replace him, and newly-signed Darnell Savage could potentially step in next week if Bishop has to miss any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa3a-da9b-a9bf-fe3fd1d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) was ruled out in Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa81-d005-a9bf-fab561a20000</link>
      <description>Mitchell hobbled to the locker room near the end of the third quarter after totaling 76 yards on six rushes, including an explosive 55-yard run in the third quarter. Mitchell, who has a long history of serious knee injuries, has emerged as a solid complement to Derrick Henry in recent weeks. If he misses time, Rasheen Ali would presumably function as the team’s No. 2 running back and could be rostered in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fa81-d005-a9bf-fab561a20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
