<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers ruled out QB Jordan Love (concussion) for Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c77-d968-a19b-5cf7a48f0000</link>
      <description>Love remained limited in practice all week and was labeled him questionable to play yesterday. He was evidently unable to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol. Packers No. 2 QB Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) is expected to start in Love’s stead. Willis is not without risk, given his current state of being, but he is a viable QB2 starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c77-d968-a19b-5cf7a48f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulders) is off Philadelphia’s final Week 17 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c79-d56e-afff-fef9254b0000</link>
      <description>Carter will be good to go after practicing in full all week. The star lineman will likely have to have an offseason procedure on his shoulders per his own admission, but will try to make the most of the rest of the season while managing the injuries. The Eagles ruled out LB Nakobe Dean (foot) for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c79-d56e-afff-fef9254b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) is expected to start in Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c79-d35e-a1bf-5dfb60a50000</link>
      <description>Willis has an injury in his throwing shoulder and is currently sick, but the Packers evidently feel good about his ability to play this weekend. The backup quarterback has completed 12-of-14 passes for 134 yards and two touchdowns while rushing 13 times for 63 yards, appearing in three games this season. Earlier today, ESPN’s Dan Graziano said he believes “several [teams] have their eyes on” Willis as a “potential solution” at quarterback in 2026. Consider this an audition. He is officially questionable to play and can be treated as a viable QB2 starter, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c79-d35e-a1bf-5dfb60a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) was limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c7c-d56e-afff-fefc45320000</link>
      <description>Last week, London was limited on Wednesday and Thursday before getting a rest day Friday. That pattern looks to be repeating this week, although one day later in the week due to Atlanta’s Monday Night date with the Rams. If London practices tomorrow it’ll be good news, but regardless he’s almost a lock to be in your fantasy lineups in Week 17, even if last Sunday’s return wasn’t all smooth sailing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c7c-d56e-afff-fefc45320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) was limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c7f-d56e-afff-feff13810000</link>
      <description>He actually wasn’t listed on the injury report yesterday, but given how Pitts has been playing of late this is likely just managing through a minor concern. There’s no reason to doubt his status for Week 17 and he belongs on the TE1 line against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c7f-d56e-afff-feff13810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (finger) is questionable for Jacksonville’s Week 17 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c81-d968-a19b-5cf1ea500000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Tuten may indeed be able to make it back for the end of the regular season after initial reporting said he was unlikely to do so. He got in three limited practices this week and, given the initial reporting, is probably on the pessimistic side of questionable for this one. LeQuint Allen would be the main backup to Travis Etienne if Tuten sits again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c81-d968-a19b-5cf1ea500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed EDGE Will McDonald IV (knee) on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c8a-d35e-a1bf-5dcaf9370000</link>
      <description>McDonald marked eight sacks in 15 games this year and continues to look like a solid building block pass rusher. The Jets will face a decision on whether they want to pick up his fifth-year option this offseason. With the season over in all but name, the Jets also sent LB Kiko Mauigoa (neck) and DL Jay Tufele (foot) to the injured reserve list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c8a-d35e-a1bf-5dcaf9370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks ruled out LT Charles Cross (hamstring) for Week 17 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c83-d968-a19b-5cf3ec960000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know Cross’ participation level on Friday, but he remained sidelined on Wednesday and Thursday after missing the team’s Week 16 game against the Rams. The Seahawks could be taking the long view with Cross. The lowly Panthers are unimposing and the 12-4 Seahawks currently own the NFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. Hopefully, they can secure a victory while also allowing their stud left tackle to successfully rehab his hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c83-d968-a19b-5cf3ec960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c99-d35e-a1bf-5ddb9aa40000</link>
      <description>The Panthers get their left tackle back after a one-game absence. The Panthers (8-7) astonishingly hold the NFC South’s top spot. Getting Ekwonu back in time to face the Seahawks’ top-tier defense is good news for QB Bryce Young, who has one year remaining on his contract and will continue to be evaluated closely by the coaching staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c99-d35e-a1bf-5ddb9aa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) is expected to be sidelined for three weeks, “through the first two rounds of the playoffs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</link>
      <description>Wattenberg grades well as both a pass protector and run blocker, earning a 70.9 PFF offense grade. With Wattenberg sidelined, the Broncos signed C Sam Mustipher off the Chargers’ practice squad. Broncos C Alex Forsyth will operate as the starter with Wattenberg sidelined. Mustipher is his backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
