<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:30:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will restructure contracts of QB Dak Prescott, WR CeeDee Lamb and OG Tyler Smith, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a490-d89c-a1be-afdf7d790000</link>
      <description>Restructuring the contracts of Prescott, Lamb and Smith will create $66 million in cap space. Schefter also passes along that Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said the Cowboys will rework the contracts of DTs Kenny Clark, Quinnen Williams and Osa Odighizuwa, who are scheduled to count around $63 million against the cap. With the new cap set at $301.2 million, the Cowboys had negative-$56.1 million in cap space. These moves help Dallas become compliant and have money to work with this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a490-d89c-a1be-afdf7d790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patriots have explored a trade for WR A.J. Brown, but feel the Eagles’ asking price is unserious, according to the Boston Herald’s Andrew Callahan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a52c-d89c-a1be-afff5fe00000</link>
      <description>The Patriots are an obvious fit for Brown, who was previously coached by Mike Vrabel in Tennessee. New England also has the need for another offensive weapon and cap space to take on a contract as large as Brown’s. According to a previous report by the Athletic’s Chad Graff, the Patriots will be active in trade talks for Brown, though they could be reluctant to give up their first-round pick. It’s difficult to imagine the Eagles moving Brown without receiving top draft capital in return. Brown is one of the biggest offseason dominos yet to fall, though a resolution should be expected ahead of the legal tampering period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a52c-d89c-a1be-afff5fe00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame RB Jeremiyah Love ran an official 4.36 40-yard dash on his second run at the 2026 NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a576-d042-afbc-fdf6b2a20000</link>
      <description>It’s a blistering time for the running back prospect that came into the Combine expected to clock the fastest run. There is an interesting dynamic to this year’s free agency and draft in that there is no shortage of viable options with available veterans, meaning we could see rookie backs fall more in the draft than in recent years. Either way, Love is doing his part to bolster his draft capital ahead of April’s NFL Draft, and he could have just solidified his case as the favorite to be the first back off the board.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a576-d042-afbc-fdf6b2a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Washington Jr. ran an official 4.33 40-yard dash at the 2026 NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a595-d629-a1bc-b59dae580000</link>
      <description>Not only did that give Washington the fastest time amongst running backs, but he did so at 6' 1", 223 pounds, giving him a 99th percentile weight-adjusted 40 time. There have been questions about his draft profile throughout the process this offseason, but his weight-adjusted speed score alone could catapult him up draft boards in the coming months ahead of the NFL Draft in April. He did his part to help his case on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a595-d629-a1bc-b59dae580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jenna Laine reports the Bucs will “aggressively pursue” Mike Evans in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a59a-d042-afbc-fddaef7d0000</link>
      <description>Bucs officials met with Evans’ representation at the NFL Combine and appear ready to make an all-out push to bring back the veteran for 2026. Evans, entering his age-33 season, said this month he would return for a 13th NFL season, but declined to say where he might play. Evans in 2025 struggled through injuries, including a collar bones injury, catching 30 passes for 368 yards and three touchdowns while missing nine games. He posted the second lowest receiving success rate of his storied NFL career. Evans would be a good fit for multiple contenders, including the wideout-needy Patriots and Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a59a-d042-afbc-fddaef7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers are expected to release OT Calvin Anderson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a59a-d89c-a1be-afdf22590000</link>
      <description>The move will save $2 million against the cap in 2026. Anderson has appeared in only 18 games across the previous three seasons, mostly serving as depth on the end during that time. The Steelers will be on the hook for a $415,000 cap hit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a59a-d89c-a1be-afdf22590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas QB Taylen Green sets Combine record with 43.5-inch vertical.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a5c2-d042-afbc-fdd2a5620000</link>
      <description>Green broke the record held by Anthony Richardson with his vertical and also erupted for a 4.36-second 40-yard dash, just 0.03 seconds behind the all-time record for a quarterback set by Michael Vick. The physical specimen quarterback is likely viewed as a developmental prospect in this year’s draft, albeit one that comes with tantalizing upside. There is a case to be made for teams to take that gamble towards the end of the first round come April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a5c2-d042-afbc-fdd2a5620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma WR Deion Burks ran an official 4.30 40-yard dash at the 2026 NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a61d-d629-a1bc-b61ded540000</link>
      <description>That goes down as the fastest 40 at this year’s Combine for a wide receiver, in a year that has the fastest composite 40-yard times in NFL history. Burks profiles as a slot wide receiver capable of inflicting damage with the ball in his hands in the open field, a profile that typically results in a late day two or early day three pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a61d-d629-a1bc-b61ded540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate ran an official 4.53 40-yard dash at the 2026 NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a6a1-d89c-a1be-afff5ee50000</link>
      <description>It was a slower time than some expected from Tate, who ran an unofficial 4.54 on both attempts. That said, it’s still a solid time for the 6-foot-2, 192-pound receiver who is viewed by many as the top receiver in this year’s class. Tate will have a chance to improve his time at Ohio State’s pro day, which is scheduled for March 25th, but we wouldn’t expect this time to have any kind of impact on his draft stock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a6a1-d89c-a1be-afff5ee50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Daniel Jeremiah believes Deshaun Watson is the favorite to be the Browns’ QB1 in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a6db-d629-a1bc-b6df9fba0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Todd Monken has already said the team will have an “open competition” at quarterback this summer. Watson, who is returning from a torn Achilles he suffered in 2024, remains under contract through this season for what is the final year of the record-setting deal he signed in 2022. Watson’s deal makes him nearly impossible to move on from this offseason, as a release would count for an absurd $131 million in dead cap money. Assuming he’s healthy and on the roster, Watson should have every chance to win the job in camp and will likely have the inside edge over Shedeur Sanders, who struggled mightily as a rookie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a6db-d629-a1bc-b6df9fba0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
