<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 22:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs had 15 rushes for 219 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 12 win against the Giants, adding 11 catches for 45 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b297-d90e-a9da-bf9f39460000</link>
      <description>Every time you looked up Gibbs was ripping off another chunk gain as the centerpiece of the run-heavy Detroit offense facing off against the NFL’s worst run defense. Gibbs averaged a stunning 14.6 yards per carry, often going untouched through gaping holes in the New York defensive line. His 69-yard scamper proved to be the winning score in overtime after the Giants choked away a fourth quarter lead with inexplicable fourth down decision making. Gibbs’ 12 targets were second on the team; he now has 25 targets over his past three outings. With increased touches since Dan Campbell took over as the Lions’ offensive play caller, Gibbs is an every-week fantasy matchup-flipping player with a CMC-like workload. Unlike CMC, Gibbs can outrun every defender on the field. He’ll be an elite option on Thanksgiving against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b297-d90e-a9da-bf9f39460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison failed to catch his only target in Minnesota’s Week 12 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-d413-ad9f-b7dfec170000</link>
      <description>Only one target for Addison? Well, the Vikings didn’t really seem interested in throwing the ball for the entirety of the first half. The rest of it is the whims of J.J. McCarthy. Addison retains FLEX status at best after putting up four games of 108 receiving yards with his second-year quarterback. It’s a tough ticket to be holding as we start to enter the fantasy playoffs in a few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-d413-ad9f-b7dfec170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Reichard made 2-of-2 field goals in the Vikings’ Week 12 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a3-d90e-a9da-bfaf05d30000</link>
      <description>The second-year kicker hit from 52 and 59 early to keep the Vikings in the game against the Packers. You won’t want to hold him against the Seahawks next week just based on the projected scoring load for Minnesota, but he’s kicking well. Reichard has now gone a month since his last field-goal miss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a3-d90e-a9da-bfaf05d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco completed 19-of-37 passes for 183 yards with a touchdown and an interception in the Bengals’ 26-20, Week 12 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-db57-afda-f6bf64040000</link>
      <description>Things were always going to be tough for Flacco against this defense without Ja’Marr Chase (suspension), and that’s exactly how it played out. The 40-year-old quarterback was under pressure frequently and unable to find many receivers open downfield for much of the game. However, he did lead a fourth-quarter touchdown drive to get the Bengals to within three and had a chance to lead a game-winning drive, but came up just short deep in New England’s territory. Joe Burrow (toe) was close to returning this week, so Flacco has likely started his last game of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-db57-afda-f6bf64040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameis Winston completed 18-of-36 attempts for 366 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Giants’ Week 12 loss against the Lions, adding four rushes and 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a3-db57-afda-f6b356340000</link>
      <description>Winston, against all odds, also had a receiving touchdown on a trick play in the second half. Winston caught the ball at the ten yard line and shed a tackler before reaching the end zone in one of the more awkward receiving scores in recent memory. Though he missed some routine throws in the second half, Winston had several strong throws to Wan’Dale Robinson, who had nine grabs for 156 yards and a touchdown in this one. Winston also connected with Isaiah Hodgins for a short score. The Giants tried to be run heavy for the second straight week but were forced into a passing script in the second half. Winston delivered with a typical Winston game: Lots of air yards, some wild throws, and some clutch, fantasy-rich completions down the field. Winston would be a viable streamer in Week 13 against the Patriots if Jaxson Dart (concussion) remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a3-db57-afda-f6b356340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 18 times for 66 yards in a Week 12 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a5-db57-afda-f6b7d12a0000</link>
      <description>Henderson also added 15 yards receiving on three catches. The 21 overall touches were nice to see, especially since Rhamondre Stevenson had only seven in his return from an ankle injury. However, Henderson was unable to get anything going against what had been a really vulnerable defense coming into this game. Perhaps more troubling is that the Patriots lost both their starting left tackle and left guard to injuries in this game, which could make the sledding a bit tougher for Henderson going forward if those injuries linger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a5-db57-afda-f6b7d12a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 5-of-6 targets for 58 yards in the Ravens’ Week 12 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-d82c-a79a-b39f350b0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens mustered just 67 yards of offense in the first half, but their loan field goal was set up by receptions that Flowers took for 14, and 20 yards, respectively, to get them into field goal range. Flowers continues to make the most of his targets, topping 50 yards in four-straight games despite not seeing more than six targets in any of those outings, and remains the unquestioned No. 1 pass catcher in the Ravens’ offense. It would be nice if he scored a touchdown once in a while, as his first and only score of the season came back in Week 1, but Flowers remains in the mix as a strong WR2 play in Week 13 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b29f-d82c-a79a-b39f350b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed six times for five yards in a Week 12 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a8-d90e-a9da-bfafbd610000</link>
      <description>Stevenson was returning after missing almost a month with an ankle injury. The 27-year-old didn’t see the field for almost the entirety of the first two drives before playing a snap on a third-and-long to end the second drive. He was out-touched by TreVeyon Henderson 21-to-7, but Stevenson did see two carries inside the three-yard line. The problem was that he was unable to convert on either one of those. It wouldn’t be a surprise to see Stevenson work into a slightly larger role next week against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2a8-d90e-a9da-bfafbd610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 9-of-13 targets for 149 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 12 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2aa-d413-ad9f-b7ffea2e0000</link>
      <description>It was a nice bounce back from St. Brown’s two-catch performance last week against the elite Eagles defense. His stat line could have been headier if Jared Goff hadn’t missed St. Brown on a couple easy middle-of-the-field throws, including one in the end zone. St. Brown also had a drop. Jameson Williams went back to being a tertiary option in this one, failing to catch a pass on three targets. With Sam LaPorta (back) out indefinitely, St. Brown could have a fantasy season-changing runout as one of only two reliable Lions fantasy options. He’ll be a top-three option in Week 13 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2aa-d413-ad9f-b7ffea2e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
