<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys ruled out WR CeeDee Lamb for Week 5’s game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abc5-d6e9-af9d-abd52d4c0000</link>
      <description>As expected, Lamb will spend another week on the shelf. Most reports had Lamb in line to miss 3-4 weeks after leaving Week 3’s game against the Bears and Lamb should enter Week 6 as more of an open question regarding his return to play. It would — obviously — be huge for all Dallas’ offensive weapons to re-add Lamb to the fold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abc5-d6e9-af9d-abd52d4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos removed WR Marvin Mims (hip/ankle) from their final Week 5 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abc9-d6e9-af9d-abd98bb00000</link>
      <description>Mims practiced in full on Friday to get removed from the report. He’s more of a touchdown-dependent FLEX at this stage of the Broncos offense, as Troy Franklin has taken on a more-or-less full-time role next to Courtland Sutton with the starters. Mims is a tough-but-defensible start in that role against a good Eagles defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abc9-d6e9-af9d-abd98bb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 5 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abcb-d95b-addb-ebcf75800000</link>
      <description>Dissly practiced in full on Friday after a couple of limited sessions. His (anticipated) return will likely cut into Oronde Gadsden Jr.'s upside as a stream play at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abcb-d95b-addb-ebcf75800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets removed TE Mason Taylor (ankle) from their final Week 5 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abcc-deb6-a7fd-fbdfff410000</link>
      <description>He’ll play and be a borderline TE1/TE2 against one of the worst pass defenses we’ve ever seen in the NFL through four weeks — the Cowboys. Taylor did break out to some extent against the Dolphins with a 5/65 line and it would make sense for the Jets to continue to feed him and Garrett Wilson as main targets against Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abcc-deb6-a7fd-fbdfff410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) is questionable for Baltimore’s Week 5 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abce-d6e9-af9d-abdecd3c0000</link>
      <description>He ominously did not practice the last two days of the week and John Harbaugh said his injury felt worse after Wednesday’s session. We’d consider Hamilton on the pessimistic side of questionable. Baltimore will have Nate Wiggins (elbow), who was cleared off the report, and won’t have Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring) after three straight DNPs. In theory these are moves that should boost Houston’s pass offense, but we’re not sure if such a thing is actually possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abce-d6e9-af9d-abdecd3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OLB Odafe Oweh (eye) is questionable for Baltimore’s Week 5 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd2-deb6-a7fd-fbdf2e530000</link>
      <description>Oweh popped up on the report with a limited session on Thursday and did not practice at all on Friday. For some teams this would qualify as ominous, but for Baltimore in 2025 it’s just another day at the factory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd2-deb6-a7fd-fbdf2e530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) is questionable for Las Vegas’ Week 5 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd5-deb6-a7fd-fbdf695d0000</link>
      <description>He took part in a limited basis all three weeks, but the history of concussions tagged as “questionable” is not pretty as far as clearing the report. Mayer won’t be a fantasy option either way, but if he made it back against the Colts, he could cut into Brock Bowers’ upside somewhat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd5-deb6-a7fd-fbdf695d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Devontez Walker (oblique) is questionable for Week 5’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd7-dca3-a9fb-bfdf98c20000</link>
      <description>He got in a full session and is one of the few Ravens that seem likely to play against the defending AFC South champions on Sunday. Walker’s got plenty of upside in a full role, but no path to one that has emerged thus far in his second season for the Ravens. He can be left on fantasy benches in the leagues deep enough to roster him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abd7-dca3-a9fb-bfdf98c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OT Ronnie Stanley (ankle) is questionable for Week 5’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdb-d95b-addb-ebdf61b90000</link>
      <description>He got in two limited practices on Thursday and Friday, marking him as likely on the optimistic side of questionable ahead of Week 5’s game versus the Texans. Stanley left Week 4’s game midway through with the injury and Joe Noteboom replaced him at tackle. Noteboom would be in line for more work against the Texans if Stanley doesn’t play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdb-d95b-addb-ebdf61b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys T Tyler Guyton (concussion) will not play in Dallas’ Week 5 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdd-d6e9-af9d-abdd51cb0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys could have four backup linemen starting with Cooper Beebe on IR, Tyler Booker (ankle) already ruled out, and G Tyler Smith (ankle) extremely questionable for Week 5. Neither Guyton, Booker, nor Smith practiced all week for the Cowboys. While OC Klayton Adams has made great results out of subpar ingredients, this is going to be a big ask for Dallas as they take on a rough Jets defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdd-d6e9-af9d-abdd51cb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
