<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) won’t play in New England’s Week 18 game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fef-d35e-a1bf-7fef41f00000</link>
      <description>Spillane is one of New England’s best run-stuffers and getting him as healthy as possible for the playoffs is of paramount importance to the Patriots. He hasn’t set foot on the field since Week 13, but was spotted at practice on Friday. Mike Vrabel also ruled out LG Jared Wilson (concussion), DT Khyiris Tonga (foot), and OLB Harold Landry (knee) against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fef-d35e-a1bf-7fef41f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin (groin) won’t play in Cleveland’s Week 18 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ff6-d35e-a1bf-7ff6ee720000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week. Fannin had a wildly successful rookie season, pushing David Njoku out of his role down the stretch despite dealing with a groin injury in Week 17 that knocked him out of action after a touchdown catch. He’ll likely be in the top-seven tight ends for 2026 re-draft. Fannin finished his rookie season with 72 catches for 731 yards and six scores on 107 targets. It would help Fannin out a lot if the Browns could develop an offensive plan that moved beyond “having to run the ball a lot to protect their quarterback” this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ff6-d35e-a1bf-7ff6ee720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee/personal) won’t play in Cleveland’s Week 18 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ff9-dc7a-af9b-ffffa7a80000</link>
      <description>Njoku was targeted just seven times after Week 8 as Harold Fannin took over as Cleveland’s main tight end. Entering free agency this offseason, Njoku has shown enough flashes at times over the past three years to be considered on the TE1 line if he lands in a good spot. He does, unfortunately, get banged up enough that he probably shouldn’t be the only tight end you draft if you go that route in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ff9-dc7a-af9b-ffffa7a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LB Carson Schwesinger (quad/ankle) won’t play in Cleveland’s Week 18 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ffc-d35e-a1bf-7ffe81180000</link>
      <description>Schewsinger battled through 16 games despite an ankle injury and looks to be the favorite to walk away with the defensive rookie of the year award after posting 156 tackles, 2.5 sacks, and two interceptions in his inaugural season. Bengals running backs could operate a little more freely than usual in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ffc-d35e-a1bf-7ffe81180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Gunnar Helm (toe) will not play in Tennessee’s Week 18 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ffe-dc7a-af9b-fffff9ea0000</link>
      <description>Helm finishes a successful rookie season with a 44/357/2 slash line, and looked to be making a climb up Tennessee’s target pecking order before injuries largely derailed his final month. It’s hard to rely on anything in Tennessee’s offense until we see exactly what happens with the coaching staff, but there are offseason runouts that will put Helm as a high-end TE2 with Chig Oknokwo slated for free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ffe-dc7a-af9b-fffff9ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Van Jefferson (forearm) will not play in Tennessee’s Week 18 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8001-d968-a19b-d8f19c790000</link>
      <description>Jefferson finishes the 2025 season with a 29/350/1 line — this is the standard, as Jefferson has finished between 209 yards and 369 yards in five of his six NFL seasons. The sacrificial X will be a free agent this offseason and tuns 30 in July. Zero fantasy upside, but he could find a real role again in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8001-d968-a19b-d8f19c790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Isaiah Davis (concussion) won’t play in New York’s Week 18 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8005-d35e-a1bf-c5c7c7790000</link>
      <description>Davis never really had a sustained run where he looked to potentially be the lead back in his second season, finishing with a 43/236/1 line on the ground and never crossing the 10-carry threshold. It’s likely that if Breece Hall isn’t brought back, Davis will remain behind Braelon Allen (knee) on the depth chart to open 2026. Davis could grow into a bigger receiving role if Hall leaves, making him a potential Kenny Gainwell-type player next year and someone who could be on the draft radar in what, well, doesn’t look like a very good team at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8005-d35e-a1bf-c5c7c7790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 18 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-800e-d968-a19b-d8ffb26a0000</link>
      <description>He is, per Raheem Morris, expected to play on Sunday. Playing through a PCL sprain that is clearly limiting him, London is probably more of a WR2 this week with the hopes that the volume works out and the Saints’ leaky pass defense gets him some yardage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-800e-d968-a19b-d8ffb26a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 18 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8010-d56e-afff-e6f8b1bf0000</link>
      <description>He was limited in practice for most of the week, but Raheem Morris said he was expected to play. Pitts is a mid-range TE1 given a dearth of options this week, but don’t expect Tampa Bay on Thursday night in Week 18 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8010-d56e-afff-e6f8b1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (knee) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 18 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8011-d56e-afff-e6f9ee170000</link>
      <description>Even if he does play, Mooney’s form has been bad enough this year while fighting through injuries that he probably doesn’t need to be in fantasy lineups at this point. You can do better, especially with Drake London and Kyle Pitts also expected to play. Mooney hasn’t cracked 40 yards or scored since November 23.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8011-d56e-afff-e6f9ee170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
