<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold completed 21-of-24 passes for 330 yards, four touchdowns, and one interception in the Seahawks’ 38-14, Week 9 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47e5-d713-ad9e-6ff583330000</link>
      <description>Darnold set a career high with 17 straight completions, 15 of which occurred in the first half as the Seahawks jumped out to a 31-7 lead while scoring on all five possessions before the break. His second incompletion of the evening was his only real mistake as he attempted a cross-body throw over the middle of the field that led to an interception. He eventually gave way to Drew Lock with just over six minutes remaining to play in the fourth quarter. The convincing win sends the Seahawks to a tie atop the NFC with a 6-2 record, and they have now won 11 of head coach Mike Macdonald’s first 12 road games since the start of the 2024 season. Up next for Darnold and the Seahawks are the Cardinals at home in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47e5-d713-ad9e-6ff583330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker rushed 11 times for 42 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 9 win over the Commanders, adding 19 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f1-d673-a39e-e7f129ee0000</link>
      <description>Walker continued to operate in a strict timeshare with Zach Charbonnet, the latter of whom managed just 25 yards on eight carries and an additional 21 yards on his lone reception. The Seahawks ran only 49 offensive plays, which was mostly due to the extreme efficiency they enjoyed against a hapless Commanders team that chose to deploy man coverage throughout the first half. A 31-7 halftime lead set the backs up well for additional production after the break but the team took their foot off the gas after tacking on an additional score in the third quarter on a one-yard rushing score from tight end AJ Barner. Walker and Charbonnet could be busier in Week 10 when the Seahawks host the Cardinals, although the split in usage keeps both heavily reliant on touchdowns to return usable counting stats in a fantasy setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f1-d673-a39e-e7f129ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 8-of-9 targets for 129 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 9 win over the Commanders, adding 11 yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f5-d713-ad9e-6ff583aa0000</link>
      <description>The only thing Smith-Njigba failed to do in this one was find paint, with both Elijah Arroyo and Cody White scoring their first professional touchdowns and rookie Tory Horton tacking on two more. Smith-Njigba remains one of the premier receivers in the game and continues to lead the league in receiving yards through the midway point in the season, now having gone over 100 yards through the air in six of his first eight games. He’ll look to continue his torrid start to the season when the Seahawks host the Cardinals in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f5-d713-ad9e-6ff583aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton caught all four targets for 48 yards and two touchdowns in the Seahawks’ Week 9 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f9-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb97490000</link>
      <description>Horton caught both touchdowns and all four targets in the first half as the Seahawks built a 31-7 lead while scoring on all five possessions before the break. His second score was the most impressive as he generated over five yards of separation from the defender for an easy score on a post route to the corner of the end zone from 25 yards out. Horton cashed in on increased opportunity with Cooper Kupp, Jake Bobo, and Dareke Young all out of action in Week 9, with fantasy managers holding him on their bench left hoping he can replicate the performance in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47f9-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb97490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo caught both targets for 29 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 9 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47fd-d673-a39e-e7fd4ccc0000</link>
      <description>Arroyo notched his first professional touchdown in the second quarter during a scoring onslaught by the Seahawks to start the game. They scored on all five first half possessions while building a 31-7 lead before the break, the third of which was Arroyo’s score from 26 yards out on a fade against busted coverage. Arroyo continues to share time at tight end with blocking specialist AJ Barner, who also scored on a third quarter sneak from one yard out to add to his 24 yards on three receptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-47fd-d673-a39e-e7fd4ccc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 12 times for 38 yards in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks, adding three yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4800-d673-a39e-ec9131930000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt continues to be highly susceptible to game script as he returned another poor fantasy showing in a loss. That is bad news for fantasy managers considering quarterback Jayden Daniels appeared to break his left arm in the fourth quarter, setting up Marcus Mariota to start under center for the foreseeable future. The Commanders have a date with the 5-3 Lions fresh off a loss of their own in Week 10, meaning fantasy managers should be looking elsewhere for running back help in the coming week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4800-d673-a39e-ec9131930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed 12 times for 65 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4805-d1e7-a1fa-5aef216f0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez saw increased work after the team fell behind 31-7 entering the half, cashing in on his second garbage time touchdown in a three-game span. The Commanders lost quarterback Jayden Daniels to what appeared to be a broken left arm in the fourth quarter, potentially setting up another game with negative script for the Commanders when they host the Lions in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4805-d1e7-a1fa-5aef216f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught all four targets for 46 yards in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4807-d673-a39e-ec97bc3e0000</link>
      <description>Another week, another blowout loss for a Commanders team that is now going to be without starting quarterback Jayden Daniels for the foreseeable future following a fourth quarter broken arm. Ertz has notched no more than four receptions in the three games started by Marcus Mariota this season, spelling trouble for his fantasy expectations for the rest of the season. That starts with a Week 10 matchup with the 5-3 Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4807-d673-a39e-ec97bc3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 5-of-6 targets for 41 yards in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks, adding three yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-480a-d1e7-a1fa-5aea2b8a0000</link>
      <description>Samuel and the rest of the Washington receiving cadre will be without quarterback Jayden Daniels for the foreseeable future after the second-year starter appeared to break his left arm in the fourth quarter of the blowout loss. The five receptions were a season low in games started by Daniels, but Samuel has caught only 11 balls in three Marcus Mariota starts this season. Fantasy managers are likely best looking elsewhere for wide receiver production, starting in Week 10 when the Commanders host the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-480a-d1e7-a1fa-5aea2b8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports X-rays on Jayden Daniels’ elbow were negative.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d0-d713-ad9e-6dd42a700000</link>
      <description>These negative X-rays confirm that Daniels did not suffer any kind of fracture when he went down in Sunday night’s game against the Seahawks. The MRI, however, will determine what, if any, ligament damage occurred and how severe it is. There’s still a lot to learn here, but this news, coupled with an earlier report from Rapoport that said “there is a chance this is not a season-ending injury” for Daniels, is a very encouraging sign. We’ll likely know more before the day is over, but it goes without saying that Daniels is out for the foreseeable future, putting Marcus Mariota back in the starting role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d0-d713-ad9e-6dd42a700000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
