<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers said he “for sure” still desires to be traded.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0873-d99b-a1df-3a7ff5b00000</link>
      <description>Asked about the trade deadline, Meyers said “I got no control over that. If I’m here, I’m here.” He also noted that he is open to an extension with the Raiders, but that “that window kind of just closed with the offseason ... If it gets done, I don’t care for real. I really just want to be in a good spot for me [and] my family.” It certainly makes plenty of sense for the Raiders to move on from Meyers given how far away they look right now, and it could enable them to give a longer trial to second-rounder Jack Bech inside. But it sounds like Meyers just wants an extension either way, perhaps limiting his market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0873-d99b-a1df-3a7ff5b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn told Ben Standig that “the plan” is for Terry McLaurin (quad) to have a full week of practice ahead of Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0894-d99b-a1df-3a9c48bd0000</link>
      <description>Of course, the plan has shifted a few times on the Commanders with McLaurin’s return, and Quinn hasn’t exactly offered a full endorsement that he’ll be back, so take this for what it is. It’s an encouraging sign that the coach thinks McLaurin can practice in full this week, but we’ll be monitoring his status on Thursday, Friday, and Saturday closely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0894-d99b-a1df-3a9c48bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn told Ben Standig that “the plan” is for Deebo Samuel (heel) to have a full week of practice ahead of Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-089e-d99b-a1df-3a9ed4740000</link>
      <description>Deebo seemed the closer call of the two for Week 7, and the Commanders do have an extra day of rest this week, so we’re a little more optimistic that he’ll be ready to roll against the Chiefs. This injury remains firmly in the “check every practice” phase. Samuel could be a fantasy WR2 if he clears this week, particularly if Terry McLaurin (quad) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-089e-d99b-a1df-3a9ed4740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated WR Jonathan Mingo (knee) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08a8-d99b-a1df-3aac7cbd0000</link>
      <description>He’ll return to a reserve role, perhaps challenging Jalen Tolbert for some snaps. Ultimately, nobody lower in the Dallas pecking order at receiver is worth rostering for fantasy purposes with how interchangeably they’re being used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08a8-d99b-a1df-3aac7cbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Audric Estime to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08c7-d651-a9df-69d726190000</link>
      <description>With Kendre Miller down for the year with a torn ACL, Estime looks like the replacement back between the tackles. Devin Neal is set up to have the first run behind Alvin Kamara, but it’s possible that Taysom Hill gets so many of the carries and gadget plays that Neal has no real ceiling. No need to rush out and claim Estime, but if he impresses the Saints in their building, perhaps he’ll get a shot later in the season. New Orleans re-signed Velus Jones to their 53-man roster as a direct replacement for Miller, but Jones is just a kick returner at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08c7-d651-a9df-69d726190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) is “doubtful” for Week 8, according to head coach Jim Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08cc-da18-a39a-dadfe2190000</link>
      <description>Haskins was an estimated DNP in Monday’s practice and now Jim Harbaugh is calling the 25-year-old doubtful for the Chargers’ Week 8 game against the Vikings. He likely suffered the strain on Sunday and without practicing the first two days of a short week, Haskins is unlikely to go on Thursday night. Nyheim Hines looks to be Kimani Vidal’s backup, though Vidal is the only fantasy-relevant player in the Los Angeles backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08cc-da18-a39a-dadfe2190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said, “we’re pressing forward with everybody that we have” when discussing the team’s offensive struggles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08fe-d651-a9df-69ff4c050000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s DJ Bien-Aime reports Ryans has no plans to move off of offensive coordinator Nick Caley, despite the team’s offensive struggles. The Texans are coming off a 27-19 Monday night loss to the Seahawks and have crossed 20 points only in games against the weak Titans and Ravens defenses. C.J. Stroud and company have not found the same success as his 2023 rookie season and despite the issues, Ryans is not making changes yet. He said, “It all starts with me...We got to play better. We got to execute better on game day.” The Texans head into a Week 8 matchup against a 49ers defense that ranks No. 7 in scoring and may be missing WR Nico Collins (concussion) for the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-08fe-d651-a9df-69ff4c050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) was a limited participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-090a-d99b-a1df-3b0e617f0000</link>
      <description>Both Alt (ankle) and Pipkins (knee) were practicing in a limited capacity on Tuesday after being listed as limited for Monday’s practice session. Alt has been out since injuring his ankle in Week 4 and was able to get in a pair of limited practice sessions last week; his ankle was heavily taped in Tuesday’s practice while Pipkins wore a brace on his knee. Head coach Jim Harbaugh said Alt is “doing anything and everything he can” to play Thursday against the Vikings. He added that Alt and Pipkins are both “game-time decisions, day-of-game decisions” for Week 8. Getting both tackles back would be a big boost to Justin Herbert’s protection moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-090a-d99b-a1df-3b0e617f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) was limited in Tuesday’s walk-thru practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0930-df81-ab9b-7ff76cb90000</link>
      <description>McCarthy was limited in another practice at the beginning of Week 8 while Carson Wentz (shoulder) was a full participant. Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell confirmed Wentz will be starting on Thursday against the Chargers as McCarthy continues to ramp up from the ankle injury he suffered over five weeks ago. Max Brosmer will be the backup for now with McCarthy seemingly working to 100-percent health before starting again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0930-df81-ab9b-7ff76cb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Raiders have told EDGE Maxx Crosby “they aren’t shopping him and won’t trade him.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0955-d651-a9df-6955acb80000</link>
      <description>Crosby has been on the perennial trade block with the Raiders’ struggles to become a competitive team. Las Vegas sits at 2-5 in a difficult AFC West division, leading to further speculation about a Crosby trade and reports the Cowboys inquired about the 28-year-old. However, Pelissero reports the Raiders told Crosby he isn’t being shopped despite interest and that Crosby would like to stay with the Raiders. The four-time Pro-Bowler has 63.5 sacks in 102 career games thus far and looks to be staying in Vegas for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0955-d651-a9df-6955acb80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
