<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 14:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports D’Andre Swift (quad) will play in Week 3 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c31-d6a5-adff-fef554c70000</link>
      <description>Swift was limited in practice throughout the week before being listed as questionable on Friday. With Swift handling the bulk of the touches through two games, the Bears were likely being extra cautious with their workhorse back. He has 29 carries and six catches this year and scored his first touchdown of the season in Week 2. Swift’s efficiency leaves something to be desired, but he sees all of the backfield work on a team staring down the barrel of a shootout with the Cowboys later today. He remains firmly planted in the RB2 ranks heading into Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c31-d6a5-adff-fef554c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaxon Smith-Njigba’s illness is “unlikely to affect his availability” for Week 3 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c37-d93f-ad9d-7ef779560000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, the young wideout is dealing with a stomach bug. He was added to the injury report on Saturday after making it through the week with a clean bill of health. Schefter noted that the team wanted to see how JSN felt today to be sure he was good to go, which warranted a mention on the injury report. It sounds like this will be a non-story by kickoff, but fantasy managers will want to check in on Seattle’s inactives to be safe. Assuming he is good to go, JSN is an unquestioned WR1 for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c37-d93f-ad9d-7ef779560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams EDGE Braden Fiske (oblique) will play in Week 3 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c3d-d1b3-a5dd-6d7db73f0000</link>
      <description>Fiske missed the first two practices of the week but returned for a limited session on Friday before being listed as questionable. Fiske has had a quiet start to his second NFL season with no sacks or TFLs through two weeks, but he does have a fumble recovery. The Rams are 2-0 with the fewest points allowed this season. The counting stats will come sooner rather than later for Fiske, assuming this oblique injury doesn’t persist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c3d-d1b3-a5dd-6d7db73f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is expected to play in Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c44-d6a5-adff-fec59bc80000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, safety Harrison Smith is also expected to make his 2025 debut this week after missing the first two games of the year with an illness. Darrisaw is still working his way back from the torn ACL he suffered last year and, as Rapoport notes, will rotate on and off the field for his first game of the season. Still, it’s good news for a Minnesota squad set to be without J.J. McCarthy for a few weeks while he nurses an ankle injury. Darrisaw will be protecting Carson Wentz’s blindside until McCarthy is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c44-d6a5-adff-fec59bc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) plans to play in Week 3 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c48-d6a5-adff-fecdc9750000</link>
      <description>Thomas has missed the first two games with a Lisfranc issue. He was limited in practice throughout the week before being assigned the questionable tag. Per Rapoport, the Giants will be cautious with their star left tackle and run him through a pre-game workout before making the final call on his status. Getting him back for Week 3 would be a notable boost for one of the league’s worst protection units.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c48-d6a5-adff-fecdc9750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bucs DT Calijah Kancey (pec) could return this season “if the team makes the playoffs and advances past the first round.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c4d-d93f-ad9d-7ecf17cc0000</link>
      <description>Kancey suffered a torn pec in Week 2 and was ruled out for the season later in the week. This update gives Bucs fans a sliver of hope that the injury isn’t as bad as initially believed, but it’s still unlikely we see the former first-round pick suit up again this season. Tampa Bay signed defensive tackle Elijah Simmons earlier this week, giving them some extra depth in the wake of Kancey’s injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c4d-d93f-ad9d-7ecf17cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports there is a “strong chance” Chris Godwin (ankle) plays in Week 4 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c52-d6a5-adff-fed74bf20000</link>
      <description>Schefter said the same of left tackle Tristan Wirfs, who is still working his way back from a knee injury he suffered in training camp. Both players returned to practice multiple weeks ago, giving them plenty of ramp-up time heading into Week 4. Per Schefter, Wirfs and Godwin are expected to get reps with the starters in practice this week. If all goes well, both should be back in the lineup for Week 4 against the Eagles. Godwin will be competing with rookie Emeka Egbuka for snaps out of the slot. If Godwin takes that role and looks like his old self, he could be back in the WR2 ranks as early as Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c52-d6a5-adff-fed74bf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Bengals “plan to stick with Jake Browning and not trade for another veteran quarterback.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c60-d6a5-adff-fee571ad0000</link>
      <description>Schefter mentioned more high school football stats than sources in his tweet, so it’s unclear if he’s getting this “report” from the team or if it’s just informed speculation. Either way, it does look like the Bengals will ride out Joe Burrow’s foot injury with Browning under center. Browning went 4-3 as a starter in 2023 and led the league with a 70.4 percent completion rate. He threw 12 touchdowns to seven interceptions and averaged 267 yards per game in his starts. The team then signed him to a two-year contract extension in the offseason. Browning is one of the league’s better backups and starting-caliber quarterbacks aren’t readily available via trade. There is a chance Burrow returns late in the year, but fantasy managers should be operating as if Browning is the Bengals’ starter for the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c60-d6a5-adff-fee571ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) is “expected to have his snaps monitored and potentially limited based on how he feels” in Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c6d-d6a5-adff-feed6fd60000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported yesterday that Egbuka is expected to suit up. The rookie only got in one practice before being listed as questionable for Week 3. Fantasy managers should be cautious with Egbuka entering his third NFL game. His production has largely been touchdown-based and now there’s a chance he is even less involved as the Bucs manage his workload. Egbuka is, at best, a high-risk WR3 for his Week 3 date with the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c6d-d6a5-adff-feed6fd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson is likely to undergo core muscle surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c74-d6a5-adff-fef56b9b0000</link>
      <description>Johnson is meeting with Dr. William Meyers of The Vincera Institute later this week, with the assumption that surgery will be the preferred option. Per Rapoport, Johnson could return in the second half of the season if he ends up undergoing the procedure. Johnson missed the first two games of the year while dealing with the injury. The fact that the Bears did not put him on injured reserve suggests the injury was worse than they initially expected. Johnson is one of many defenders out for Week 3, putting the Cowboys’ passing attack in a great spot to put up points with ease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c74-d6a5-adff-fef56b9b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
