<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (hamstring) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75df-d968-a19b-7dff8a030000</link>
      <description>Austin missed Week 17 with the hamstring issue. DK Metcalf will be out for Week 18 to finish serving his two-game suspension, meaning Austin could immediately return to a high-volume role. The Steelers will lean on their ground game this week in battle for the AFC North with the Ravens, but fantasy managers can pencil Austin in for a handful of targets if he is active, putting him on the WR4/5 radar for the final week of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75df-d968-a19b-7dff8a030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75d1-d56e-afff-f7f92b1e0000</link>
      <description>The Bills released K Michael Badgley from the practice squad on Monday. He had an extra point attempt blocked by the Eagles last week. Given Badgley’s release and Prater’s full participation, we expect Prater to kick for the Bills in Week 18 against the Jets. He could be fairly busy in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75d1-d56e-afff-f7f92b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said DT Brandon Dorlus “dodged a big-time bullet” with his knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75ee-d35e-a1bf-75ee96870000</link>
      <description>Dorlus went down with the knee injury in Week 17 and there was concern that it was a major issue. He won’t play in Week 18, meaning his season is over, but Morris said he would only be out for a couple of weeks. It doesn’t sound like this will affect his offseason routine at all, which is good news for the former fourth-round pick. His breakout second season comes to an end with 8.5 sacks and 26 pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75ee-d35e-a1bf-75ee96870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Nation’s Vincent Bonsignore believes the Raiders will use “a combination of Kenny Pickett and Aidan O’Connell” in Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75e6-d968-a19b-7df7b90b0000</link>
      <description>Bonsignore seems to imply both players will take reps in Week 18. Pickett has been the first player off the bench, so we assume he will get the start. Should the Raiders actually employ a two-quarterback game plan, neither player should be anywhere near a re-draft or DFS lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75e6-d968-a19b-7df7b90b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said “it doesn’t look like” LT Jamaree Salyer (hamstring) will play in Week 18 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7603-d56e-afff-f6eb72190000</link>
      <description>Salyer went down with the hamstring issue in Week 16 and did not suit up last week. With little to play for this week, he will rest up ahead of LA’s upcoming Wild Card Round game. Austin Deculus is the favorite to start at left tackle in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7603-d56e-afff-f6eb72190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo said there have been no talks of a contract extension between him and the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-760a-dc7a-af9b-ffbfcacf0000</link>
      <description>He did, however, say that he wants to stay in Tennessee. Okonkwo turned his three grabs into 55 yards and a score last week. That put him at a 54/558/3 receiving line on the year. All three of those numbers are either new career-highs for Okonkwo or at least tie his previous high-water mark. Okonkwo may never hit the next gear for fantasy purposes, but he’s a capable start who works well with the ball in his hands. He should have no issues finding a multi-year contract as a free agent in the spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-760a-dc7a-af9b-ffbfcacf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams designated Tyler Higbee (ankle) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7614-d35e-a1bf-77d6b2750000</link>
      <description>Higbee will return to practice this week, though it’s unclear if he will be ready for LA’s Week 18 date with the Cardinals. The Rams only have minor differences in seeding to play for this week, so they will likely hold him out until the playoffs, even if he could return on Sunday. Higbee will split reps with Colby Parkinson and Terrance Ferguson in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7614-d35e-a1bf-77d6b2750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said there is “a non-zero chance” that LT Charles Cross (hamstring) can play in Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75fa-d56e-afff-f7faf4500000</link>
      <description>Per Macdonald, there are still “tests” for Cross to “take” later this week. We do not expect the Seahawks to have their stud left tackle on the field on Saturday, though. Seahawks No. 2 OL Josh Jones (knee/ankle) “just got banged up” and will be able to play if Cross cannot. Fortunately for the Seahawks, the 49ers’ defensive front has been thinned out by injuries of its own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75fa-d56e-afff-f7faf4500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ribs) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-762c-d56e-afff-f6ec288f0000</link>
      <description>Robinson caught 11 passes last week. Seeing him appear on the injury report today is somewhat unsurprising. He still has a chance to suit up for the Giants’ Week 18 game against the Cowboys, though we would like to see him resume practicing tomorrow. He is a WR3 if active against the Cowboys’ accommodating defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-762c-d56e-afff-f6ec288f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns placed RG Wyatt Teller (calf) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7619-d35e-a1bf-77db49680000</link>
      <description>Teller returned from the calf issue last week but only played a handful of snaps before leaving the game. His season is now over. The team signed Kingsley Eguakun in a corresponding move. Eguakun comes from the Lions’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7619-d35e-a1bf-77db49680000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
