<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle was forced from San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles with a right achilles injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af30-d35e-a1bf-eff293950000</link>
      <description>Playing through an ankle injury of late, Kittle planted with extreme force in the second quarter and suffered what appeared to be a ruptured achilles’ tendon. We, obviously, are not doctors, but these have become sadly easy to spot. Even were the worst-case scenario somehow avoided, Kittle is obviously done for the day and almost certainly for any potential 49ers Super Bowl run. The question then quickly becomes if the 32-year-old can be ready by next Week 1. At this stage of the offseason, it is not terribly likely, even though achilles timelines have condensed in recent seasons. Jake Tonges is the next man up on Sunday and for however long San Francisco can stay alive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af30-d35e-a1bf-eff293950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brenton Strange caught 2-of-5 targets for nine yards in the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af32-d968-a19b-fff398130000</link>
      <description>A hip injury early in the year suppressed Strange’s numbers in what would have easily been a breakout season for the third-year tight end. He was placed on injured reserve and missed five games. Despite that, Strange’s 46 catches, 540 yards, and three touchdowns were all career-highs. He finished the year as a mid-range TE2 on a per-game basis. The Jags run four deep at receiver when everyone is healthy. Liam Coen dials up designed targets for his running backs a few times a week. That makes it hard for Strange to be a consistent target-earner, but he is a solid streaming option when bye weeks roll in. He will be stuck in the TE2 range in 2026 drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af32-d968-a19b-fff398130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 15 times for 46 yards in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af45-d56e-afff-efedc4300000</link>
      <description>No team allowed fewer rushing yards in the regular season than Jacksonville. Their front seven lived up to the hype in the Wild Card Round, limiting Cook to 3.1 yards per carry. Week 18 aside, it was Cook’s lowest rushing output since Week 1. Cook’s fantasy backers also got to watch Josh Allen steal two rushing touchdowns. Cook should fare better next week, no matter who the Bills face in the Divisional Round. He will still be one of the best DFS options on next week’s slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af45-d56e-afff-efedc4300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandin Cooks caught 3-of-5 targets for 58 yards in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af51-dc7a-af9b-efffb17a0000</link>
      <description>Cooks came down with a 36-yard bomb from Josh Allen late in the fourth quarter that eventually set up a go-ahead score. He finished the day second on the team in catches, targets, and yards. With Josh Palmer on IR, there was already plenty of volume up for grabs in the receiver room. The Bills then lost Gabe Davis to a knee injury late in this game. His status for the Divisional Round is up in the air. Cooks will likely operate as the team’s No. 2 receiver next week, putting him squarely on the DFS radar as a salary relief option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af51-dc7a-af9b-efffb17a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Falcons completed a head-coaching interview with former Browns coach Kevin Stefanski on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af59-d35e-a1bf-efdbcb340000</link>
      <description>Connected to at least half the openings out there, Stefanski has now completed interviews with at least the Falcons and Ravens. With seven openings besides his former job, Stefanski seems all but certain to land another job, but he could be in the awkward position where he ends up multiple teams’ second choice after someone like John Harbaugh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af59-d35e-a1bf-efdbcb340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs OC Matt Nagy completed a head-coaching interview with the Ravens on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5f-d35e-a1bf-efdf1a0d0000</link>
      <description>A hot candidate this cycle after doing a multi-year penance for his Bears tenure with the Chiefs, Nagy has commanded a lot of interest but no obvious spot where he might be considered the favorite. Especially with John Harbaugh and Kevin Stefanski likely to be first in line amongst recent retread head coaches, Nagy could have to wait a while for his second chance to actually develop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5f-d35e-a1bf-efdf1a0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 3-of-5 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5a-dc7a-af9b-efffb12c0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid got on the board with a touchdown in the fourth quarter, giving the Bills a temporary lead. He would go on to finish second on the team in targets and catches. The Bills are incredibly thin at receiver, meaning Kincaid gets to operate as a de facto WR2 behind Khalil Shakir. While he doesn’t run every route, he gets on the field enough to put up usable fantasy numbers and score the occasional touchdown. He will be a touchdown-or-bust fantasy option in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5a-dc7a-af9b-efffb12c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught all three of his targets for 30 yards in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d35e-a1bf-efe200fb0000</link>
      <description>Knox, Brandin Cooks, and Dalton Kincaid all tied for second on the team in catches. Khalil Shakir led the way with 12 grabs and 82 yards. Knox is a reliable backup tight end and a plus blocker, but his fantasy outlook is limited. He needs to get in the end zone to pay off and that has only happened four times this year. Knox is only worth a look in large-field DFS tournaments for the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d35e-a1bf-efe200fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) is active for the Wild Card Round against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d968-a19b-fff3f3500000</link>
      <description>As is EDGE Harold Landry (knee). With Mack Hollins out at least several more weeks with an abdominal injury, Boutte enters the postseason as the Pats’ primary deep threat. It’s been a profitable role this season, and is perhaps one worth betting on in playoff DFS. That being said, you might not want to do vs. the Chargers’ elite pass defense. Inactive for the Patriots are WR Jeremiah Webb, EDGE Bradyn Swinson, OT Marcus Bryant, OG Caedan Wallace, TE C.J. Dippre, QB Tommy DeVito and DT Khyiris Tonga.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d968-a19b-fff3f3500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton (ankle) is active for the Wild Card Round against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af78-d35e-a1bf-effa3c5d0000</link>
      <description>Hampton got in only one “limited” practice during the week, one where he was spotted wearing a “big brace.” That’s the long way of saying we have no idea of how “healthy” he might be in New England, but we would bet on him leading the Chargers’ backfield in touches. The Pats’ run defense has taken on water of late, making Hampton a nice risk/reward DFS option. Inactive for the Bolts are CB Isas Waxter, S Kendall Williamson, EDGE Bud Dupree, EDGE Kyle Kennard, OT Austin Deculus, WR Dalevon Campbell and TE Tyler Conklin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af78-d35e-a1bf-effa3c5d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
