<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cam Skattebo (ankle) was taken to a hospital for “further evaluation.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21ef-deb1-a39b-21ef74a10000</link>
      <description>Skattebo sustained a horrific ankle injury in the second quarter of the Giants’ Week 8 game against the Eagles. He was carted off the field after having his leg stabilized, and reportedly taken to a nearby hospital for further care. His injury looked similar to the one Chris Godwin suffered in October 2024. Skattebo is certainly done for the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21ef-deb1-a39b-21ef74a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Tyson Campbell (concussion) exited Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21ef-d245-adfb-b5ff30200000</link>
      <description>Campbell entered concussion protocol after hitting his head in the third quarter of the Browns’ Week 8 game against the Patriots. He headed to the locker room and was announced to be in concussion protocol, likely out for the rest of the game against New England. Rookie CB Dom Jones came in for Campbell and has already been picked on for a pair of touchdowns by the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21ef-d245-adfb-b5ff30200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (concussion evaluation) exited in Week 8 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21e4-d245-adfb-b5ffcb440000</link>
      <description>An earlier report suggested Burden was being evaluated for a concussion, but ESPN’s Adam Schefter has now confirmed those suspicions. If he is concussed, Burden’s day will end with one reception for a one-yard loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21e4-d245-adfb-b5ffcb440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) is questionable to return Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f3-d5d8-a3ff-f9f340180000</link>
      <description>Judkins exited in the third quarter against the Patriots with a shoulder injury. The Browns listed him as questionable to return. He has been a workhorse for Cleveland, but now fellow rookie Dylan Sampson will take over while Judkins is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f3-d5d8-a3ff-f9f340180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Bellinger (neck) is questionable to return in Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f5-d5d8-a3ff-f9f5d28f0000</link>
      <description>Bellinger picked up the injury near the end of the third quarter. He’s been a consistent part of the New York offense in recent weeks as the Giants lean toward two tight end sets. He had seven catches and a touchdown over his previous three games and had one catch for 21 yards before exiting Sunday’s game. Theo Johnson could see an increase in routes and targets if Bellinger misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f5-d5d8-a3ff-f9f5d28f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley entered the blue medical tent in Week 8 against the Giants with an apparent hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21fa-dab4-a3fb-bbfacb5a0000</link>
      <description>Barkley came up with a limp after a long run in the fourth quarter. He spent a couple minutes in the medical tent before emerging without his helmet. It would be surprising if Barkely re-entered the ballgame after totaling 174 yards and two touchdowns — one rushing, one receiving — in his biggest game of the season. Tank Bigsby appears to be the lead back with Barkley on the sideline. Bigsby has 58 yards on five rushes through three and a half quarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21fa-dab4-a3fb-bbfacb5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Christensen was carted off the field with a knee injury in Week 8</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f1-deb1-a39b-21ffe2f50000</link>
      <description>Somebody rolled into the back of his legs in the fourth quarter. He popped up after the play but immediately grabbed for his knee and fell back down. Then the cart was brought out. Christensen has played every spot on the offensive line for the Panthers but is primarily a guard. The Panthers are now down three starting offensive linemen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21f1-deb1-a39b-21ffe2f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons S Jessie Bates (ankle) will not return in Week 8 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2205-d5d8-a3ff-fb654d2c0000</link>
      <description>Bates suffered an ankle injury versus Miami and was ruled out in the fourth quarter. Bates has appeared in six games this year and has 39 tackles. Losing Bates is a big blow to an Atlanta defense that had looked like one of the league’s best units before today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2205-d5d8-a3ff-fb654d2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevin Wallace has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 8 against the Bills with a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2209-deb1-a39b-230ffd300000</link>
      <description>The Panthers have already lost three starting offensive linemen to injury, but will now also be without their signal caller on defense and starting middle linebacker. They’ll hope he can be cleared in time for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2209-deb1-a39b-230ffd300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Brown leaves Week 8 against the Bills with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-220e-d5d8-a3ff-fb6fb1a20000</link>
      <description>Brown limped off the field late in the fourth quarter with a knee injury and was in the blue medical tent for a while. He seemed to be in good spirits on the sideline afterward, but he was listed as questionable to return. The Panthers are down 40-9, so they likely just wanted to hold their best defender out with the Packers on deck next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-220e-d5d8-a3ff-fb6fb1a20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
