<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 16-of-31 passes for 161 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Steelers’ 25-10, Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee776f0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was far from sharp in this one, sailing his first interception over the head of alpha wide receiver DK Metcalf in addition to committing a fumble that would lead to a first half safety for the Los Angeles defense. His second interception was a deflection off the hands of Calvin Austin, so we’ll give him a pass on that one, but the theme of the game was inaccuracy and indecision for the veteran signal caller. The Chargers held the Steelers to only 221 yards of total offense as Rodgers failed to get anything going on offense, playing over 57 minutes of football before the team’s only touchdown of the game. Kicker Chris Boswell connected on a 59-yard field goal on the team’s second possession but missed another from 45 yards in the second quarter. Rodgers nearly doubled up on his interception total for the season, now sitting at five through nine games. The Steelers fall to 5-4, now just one game ahead of the surging Ravens, ahead of a divisional matchup with the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee776f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 14 times for 70 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers, adding 21 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c32-d713-ad9e-6c760db00000</link>
      <description>Warren accounted for 91 of the 221 yards of total offense from the Steelers as they struggled to move the football throughout against the Chargers. Even so, the team trailed only 5-3 until the last minute of the first half when Ladd McConkey broke the game open with a touchdown from 15 yards out. Warren also handily led the backfield, ceding only two carries to rookie Kaleb Johnson on back-to-back plays in the third quarter and three targets to Kenneth Gainwell, keeping him entrenched as an RB2 ahead of a plus matchup with the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c32-d713-ad9e-6c760db00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roman Wilson caught 2-of-3 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c34-d673-a39e-ecb5f3bb0000</link>
      <description>Wilson also led the team in receiving with a paltry 35 yards, highlighting the struggles of the Pittsburgh offense in the loss. The team managed just 221 yards of total offense while scoring a lone field goal until under three minutes remaining in the fourth quarter when Wilson willed his way into the end zone on a slant. Wilson remains off the fantasy radar even with the team in dire need of secondary production behind alpha receiver DK Metcalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c34-d673-a39e-ecb5f3bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-7 targets for 35 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Aaron Rodgers narrowly missed Metcalf for what would have been an easy touchdown on the team’s second possession, which was one of many overthrows by Rodgers on the evening. Another such overthrow resulted in a Los Angeles interception in the second quarter. Metcalf continues to be hamstrung by a low-volume pass offense, leaving his fantasy value lacking in any game he’s held out of the end zone. He gets a matchup boost in Week 11 when the Steelers take on the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught all three targets for 33 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</link>
      <description>The “Muth” chants from the well-traveled Pittsburgh fans weren’t enough to return any semblance of fantasy value for the veteran tight end on a night the offense managed only 221 yards of total offense on the road. Freiermuth remains a touchdown-dependent dart throw in fantasy circles ahead of a plus matchup against the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden is scheduled to undergo an MRI on his knee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6dec-d45b-affe-7dfe32820000</link>
      <description>A knee-to-knee collision knocked Gadsden out in the third quarter of the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers. Gadsden has totaled 35 receptions for 466 yards and two touchdowns this season and officially broke out in Week 7 against the Colts when he went for 7-164-1 on nine targets. His absence will make for a big hole in a Chargers offense that has been surprisingly pass heavy in their second year in Greg Roman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6dec-d45b-affe-7dfe32820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders DT Daron Payne has been suspended for one game after punching Amon-Ra St. Brown in Week 10’s loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e0e-d45b-affe-7f9ed8e30000</link>
      <description>Payne could appeal this, but the tape doesn’t exactly work in his favor. Payne took a blatant, cheap shot at St. Brown during the second quarter of Sunday’s game and was immediately ejected for his actions. Assuming this holds up, which it should, Payne will miss Week 11’s game against the Dolphins in Spain and will be eligible to return in Week 13 after the Commanders’ bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e0e-d45b-affe-7f9ed8e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rob Gronkowski retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</link>
      <description>Gronkowski will sign a one-day contract to retire as a Patriot on Wednesday, but he has technically been retired for four seasons. The future Hall of Famer last played in 2021 and returned to the game in 2020, joining Tom Brady and the Buccaneers after a year away. Gronk, a four-time Super Bowl champion and four-time All-Pro, will officially walk away as one of the best tight ends in league history. He currently ranks 10th amongst TEs in all-time receptions (621), sixth in receiving yards (9,286), and third in touchdowns (92).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he isn’t sure if Garrett Wilson (knee) will be able to play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</link>
      <description>Wilson re-aggravated the knee injury he suffered in Week 6 against the Broncos. It was Wilson’s first game back from the injury, and he failed to haul in any of the three targets that came in his direction. Although Justin Fields can certainly be blamed for some of that. Wilson will undergo additional imaging on his knee to determine where things stand right now, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he was again sidelined after this latest setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Azareye’h Thomas (concussion) will not play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is in the league’s concussion protocol after going down in Week 10’s win against the Browns. With the Jets slated to play on Thursday against the Patriots, the short turnaround was always going to make it tough for Thomas to clear protocol in time for Week 11. Thomas played on 24 defensive snaps in Sunday’s win and has seen an increased role in the Jets’ last three games after playing primarily as a backup through the first six weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
