<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OL Austin Corbett (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea7-d294-a19b-eef78ba80000</link>
      <description>Per Dave Canales, the Panthers will be placing Corbett on injured reserve and he is “leaving open the possibility” that Corbett could return this season. Losing both Corbett and Hunt is a big blow for Chuba Hubbard and the Panthers offense as a whole. Torn MCLs are not necessarily season-enders, and Corbett will be eligible to return in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea7-d294-a19b-eef78ba80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OG Robert Hunt (torn biceps) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea6-d294-a19b-eef68e550000</link>
      <description>Hunt didn’t seem optimistic about his injury following the Panthers’ Week 2 loss to the Cardinals. On Monday, the worst was confirmed, as an MRI revealed a torn left biceps for Hunt, who will now land on injured reserve and hope to make it back at some point in the season. Hunt made his first Pro Bowl with the Panthers last season and has become a staple along the offensive line. Backup guard Chandler Zavala replaced Hunt in Sunday’s contest and will likely draw the start in Hunt’s place for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea6-d294-a19b-eef68e550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 2’s loss to the Falcons and is unlikely to play vs. the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eac-d86f-abdd-4fbdf4d30000</link>
      <description>O’Connell said McCarthy came into the facilities on Monday sore with an ankle sprain and added that the team doesn’t anticipate him playing in Week 3’s game against the Bengals. McCarthy struggled again in his second career start on Sunday night against the Falcons, throwing for 158 yards and two interceptions while also taking six sacks and losing one of his three fumbles on the night. O’Connell has already said the team is preparing Carson Wentz to start on Sunday, suggesting McCarthy missing this week is all but a lock. We’ll see if anything changes when the team’s first injury report is released, but for now, we would expect to see Wentz into center into a game that is now the battle between backup QBs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eac-d86f-abdd-4fbdf4d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) is unlikely to play against the Bengals in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ead-d294-a19b-eefd767c0000</link>
      <description>It’s full steam ahead for Jordan Mason as a locked-in volume starter this week, although there’s now a big (bigger?) question mark under center for the Vikings. The Bengals have been one of the best teams for runners to face over the past few years. Jones remains remarkably hard to keep healthy and will likely be questionable for Week 4 as well. Zavier Scott is the only other healthy back on the roster and figures to take on a role of some sort behind Mason in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ead-d294-a19b-eefd767c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said the team is preparing Carson Wentz to start Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eb2-d294-a19b-eef27ff30000</link>
      <description>Wentz signed with the Vikings in late August after opting out of the Sam Howell experiment following training camp. The former first-round pick will suit up for his fifth different team in five seasons when he lines up under center for the Vikings against the Bengals, and has thrown for just 281-2-1 over the last two seasons. Wentz has a chance to do the funniest thing here in taking over for McCarthy, who has visibly struggled in his first two games outside of one good quarter of football against the Bears. It will take more than one strong outing for Wentz to take McCarthy’s starting role, but an impressive performance on Sunday could lead to some requesting another look at him if he’s able to flourish in an O’Connell offense that several other quarterbacks have excelled in in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eb2-d294-a19b-eef27ff30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Vikings expect to be without J.J. McCarthy (ankle) for 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ec9-d294-a19b-eef968ac0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy was revealed to have suffered a high-ankle sprain in Sunday’s loss to the Falcons and will now be sidelined for the foreseeable future. The Vikings play host to the Bengals on Sunday and will then play overseas games against the Steelers in Week 4 and the Browns in Week 5, which could further complicate McCarthy’s return. Carson Wentz is preparing to start in McCarthy’s absence, and could have a chance to elevate Vikings pass-catchers after McCarthy struggled to the tune of 301-2-3 while completing 58.5 percent of his passes during the first two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ec9-d294-a19b-eef968ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (knee) is “truly day-to-day” and that he “can’t tell” what that means for Sunday now.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4edf-da67-a99f-ceff62940000</link>
      <description>It’s coach-speak — Quinn added that “in the return to play, he and all of the guys have to hit all of the markers” — but it sure seems like Daniels has a real chance to miss Week 3. This will be one of the most significant injury situations to monitor ahead of Week 3. Marcus Mariota is set to play against the Raiders if Daniels is unable to go. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said earlier today that Daniels status for Week 3 is “in doubt.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4edf-da67-a99f-ceff62940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (nose) is “good to go” Thursday against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-dc44-a9d9-4fe67c9f0000</link>
      <description>Not a surprise after he returned to play in-game, but good to hear an affirmative answer on it. McDermott said “his nose looks good to me. It’s always looked good to me.” Allen will be a locked-in QB1 against a Dolphins defense that is redefining what it means to be Down Bad through two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-dc44-a9d9-4fe67c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (groin) is “a long shot” to play in Week 3 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-d86f-abdd-4fffd5ea0000</link>
      <description>Quinn said the same of tight end John Bates, who is also dealing with a groin injury. Brown has three catches for 38 yards on seven targets this season and was already well off the fantasy radar. Assuming he’s unable to play in Week 3, the Commanders would likely feature veteran Chris Moore in his spot, who is listed behind him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-d86f-abdd-4fffd5ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Chris Rodriguez will “be back in the fold” in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee8-d86f-abdd-4ffd5e550000</link>
      <description>We assume this means Rodriguez will be active behind Jacory Croskey-Merritt in the RB room, with Jeremy McNichols stealing some third-down snaps. Quinn also mentioned that they feel comfortable with Croskey-Merritt in pass protection. There’s a lot of runouts on the table for the Commanders in Week 3 at running back, especially when you consider Jayden Daniels’ health at the moment. Given where he’s starting from it seems unlikely that Rodriguez will be more than a small part of a committee in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee8-d86f-abdd-4ffd5e550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
