<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with 49ers OC Klay Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3f3-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e30000</link>
      <description>This is Kubiak’s first reported invitation to interview for a new role of any kind. Good for him. The 49ers’ offense is averaging 5.5 yards per play as it heads into a matchup against the division-rival Seahawks this weekend. The unit continues to perform very well despite missing key players for multi-game stints throughout the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3f3-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fb-d56e-afff-e7fb4ab20000</link>
      <description>Earlier this week, Rams head coach Sean McVay said he was “optimistic” about Ferguson returning to action. Ferguson’s continued full participation puts him firmly on track to play in the Divisional Round against the Bears. Rams RG Kevin Dotson (ankle) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fb-d56e-afff-e7fb4ab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager reports that former Ravens OC Todd Monken is one of five candidates “linked” to the Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c403-d35e-a1bf-c5c3e9380000</link>
      <description>Schrager puts Monken at the top of the list. Earlier today, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reported that Monken is “among the leading candidates” for the role. He should probably be considered the favorite. However, the four remaining candidates are Giants interim head coach Mike Kafka, Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase, former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury and Browns OC Tommy Rees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c403-d35e-a1bf-c5c3e9380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager linked Giants interim DC Charlie Bullen and four other candidates to the Giants’ defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fd-d56e-afff-e7fd13a40000</link>
      <description>Per Schrager, Bullen has a chance to remove the “interim” part of his title, which makes sense. He significantly improved the Giants’ defensive performance after receiving the in-season promotion in Week 13, improving their quarterback pressure rate from 32.9 to 39.9 percent and lowering their yards allowed per play average from 6.1 to 5.1. The remaining four candidates include former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon, Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver, Ravens DC Zach Orr and Browns DC Jim Schwartz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fd-d56e-afff-e7fd13a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals will interview 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy tonight.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c42f-d56e-afff-e6ef32eb0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers currently list six combined linebackers and defensive linemen on injured reserve, including defensive stars Fred Warner and Nick Bosa. Saleh has helped keep the 49ers’ Super Bowl aspirations intact in his first season back with his old team despite the personnel losses. His successes have earned him head-coaching interview requests with four different teams. Good for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c42f-d56e-afff-e6ef32eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c43a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa4120000</link>
      <description>Minter has completed head-coaching interviews with the Raiders, Falcons and Ravens since yesterday afternoon. He still has four more to go, two of which are with the Giants and Cardinals. Minter has spent the last four seasons studying under Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh, running his defenses in Los Angeles and at Michigan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c43a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa4120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c41b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf4b0c0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have been busy today. They completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for the same role just a few hours ago. Saleh, similarly, is scheduled to interview for the Cardinals’ head-coaching vacancy later tonight, after helping the 49ers’ defense navigate their way through an injury-impacted ongoing season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c41b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf4b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c45a-d968-a19b-dcfb53e40000</link>
      <description>McDaniel is the Ravens’ 11th head-coaching interviewee. Earlier today, ESPN’s Jeff Darlington reported that McDaniel “is very coveted” by teams with offensive coordinator vacancies. He could still make a lateral move at the head-coaching level, though. Pairing McDaniel with QB Lamar Jackson’s play-making ability would be very fun for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c45a-d968-a19b-dcfb53e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with QB coach Shane Day for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c464-d56e-afff-e6ecff0e0000</link>
      <description>Day has been on the Chargers’ coaching staff in four of the last five seasons, separated by a one-off campaign with the Texans, serving as a senior offensive assistant in 2023. From 2021-2022, he was the Chargers’ pass game coordinator and quarterbacks coach. He currently serves only as the quarterbacks coach at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c464-d56e-afff-e6ecff0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals will interview Steelers OC Arthur Smith for their head-coaching vacancy on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c473-d56e-afff-e6fb0f670000</link>
      <description>The news comes from the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette’s Gerry Dulac, who notes that Smith “will also interview with the Detroit Lions to be their offensive coordinator.” The implication seems to be that Smith will speak to the Lions on Friday as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c473-d56e-afff-e6fb0f670000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
