<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c41b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf4b0c0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have been busy today. They completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for the same role just a few hours ago. Saleh, similarly, is scheduled to interview for the Cardinals’ head-coaching vacancy later tonight, after helping the 49ers’ defense navigate their way through an injury-impacted ongoing season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c41b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf4b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c45a-d968-a19b-dcfb53e40000</link>
      <description>McDaniel is the Ravens’ 11th head-coaching interviewee. Earlier today, ESPN’s Jeff Darlington reported that McDaniel “is very coveted” by teams with offensive coordinator vacancies. He could still make a lateral move at the head-coaching level, though. Pairing McDaniel with QB Lamar Jackson’s play-making ability would be very fun for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c45a-d968-a19b-dcfb53e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with QB coach Shane Day for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c464-d56e-afff-e6ecff0e0000</link>
      <description>Day has been on the Chargers’ coaching staff in four of the last five seasons, separated by a one-off campaign with the Texans, serving as a senior offensive assistant in 2023. From 2021-2022, he was the Chargers’ pass game coordinator and quarterbacks coach. He currently serves only as the quarterbacks coach at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c464-d56e-afff-e6ecff0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals will interview Steelers OC Arthur Smith for their head-coaching vacancy on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c473-d56e-afff-e6fb0f670000</link>
      <description>The news comes from the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette’s Gerry Dulac, who notes that Smith “will also interview with the Detroit Lions to be their offensive coordinator.” The implication seems to be that Smith will speak to the Lions on Friday as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c473-d56e-afff-e6fb0f670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes Kevin Stefanski “is expected to have second interviews for multiple head coaching jobs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c70d-d968-a19b-dffd0f800000</link>
      <description>Stefanski said he believes the Titans, Falcons, and Ravens “are all potential landing spots” for the two-time coach of the year. Stefanski has been highly sought after since being fired by the Browns following a 5-12 season marred by problems at quarterback. Stefanski lost out to John Harbaugh for the Giants’ head coaching job, but with eight more openings, he’ll have plenty of opportunities to land elsewhere if he wants to continue his career elsewhere as a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c70d-d968-a19b-dffd0f800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns will interview Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c738-d56e-afff-e7f83a290000</link>
      <description>Minter has been in high-demand this offseason after leading the Chargers to a top-10 finish in points and yards allowed in his second season as a DC under Jim Harbaugh. The 42-year-old coach recently completed head coaching interviews with the Dolphins, Falcons, Raiders, and Ravens, and field eight interview requests in total. He seems like a lock to land a head-coaching role somewhere in the coming days, although he’s clearly taking his time vetting all options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c738-d56e-afff-e7f83a290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers interviewed Steelers ST cDanny Smith for the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7a9-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77310000</link>
      <description>A true veteran of the game, Smith, 72, has spent the last 13 seasons leading the Steelers’ special teams unit, and spent time as the special teams coordinator for the Bills (2001-2003), and Commanders (2004-2012) before that. Smith’s special teams units with the Steelers were often some of the best the league had to offer, making him an enticing candidate for the Buccaneers, who struggled mightily in that area last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7a9-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports Browns DC Jim Schwartz will have a second interview for the team’s head-coaching vacancy on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7c6-dc7a-af9b-cfffc7780000</link>
      <description>Schwartz isn’t the only candidate who will get a second interview to fill the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy, per Cabot, but the longtime defensive coordinator has already secured one. Schwartz has spent the last three seasons as the Browns’ defensive coordinator and served as the Lions’ head coach from 2009 until 2013. Promoting Schwartz to head coach would make for an easy transition for a defense that finished fourth in yards allowed last season and that has been among the league’s best in two of Schwartz’s three seasons at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7c6-dc7a-af9b-cfffc7780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports Browns OC Tommy Rees “is not expected to interview a second time” for the team’s head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7df-d56e-afff-e7ffb29f0000</link>
      <description>Rees is still cutting his teeth as a coach and was always considered a long shot for the Browns’ head coaching vacancy. The 33-year-old joined the Browns in 2024 as a pass game specialist and tight ends coach and was promoted to offensive coordinator for the 2025 season. Now out as a candidate for the Browns’ job, it’s fair to assume his days as the team’s offensive coordinator could be numbered once a new head coach is locked in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7df-d56e-afff-e7ffb29f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers DC Jeff Hafley will interview with the Steelers for their head-coaching vacancy on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7e5-d968-a19b-dff53df60000</link>
      <description>The Steelers requested an interview with Hafley on Thursday and have now been granted a chance to speak with the second-year defensive coordinator. Hafley has led a top-12 defense or better in each of his two seasons with the Packers since being named as the team’s defensive coordinator in 2024, and has also fielded interview requests from the Dolphins, Raiders, Titans, Cardinals, and Falcons this coaching cycle. He’s clearly in high-demand and is one of the safer bets to land a head coaching job in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c7e5-d968-a19b-dff53df60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
