<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 22:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Post’s Brian Costello reports Jets QB Justin Fields will start against the Bengals in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c46-d245-adfb-9d5f3d620000</link>
      <description>New York’s other option Tyrod Taylor was questionable and his since been ruled out with a knee injury. Given the Jets’ refusal to publicly name a quarterback prior to Taylor being ruled out, it’s safe to say the team wasn’t planning on giving Fields another start here. With six teams on bye week and quarterback injuries around the league, Fields is an upside QB2 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c46-d245-adfb-9d5f3d620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Post’s Brian Costello reports Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) has been ruled out against the Bengals in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c49-dab4-a3fb-9f7989b50000</link>
      <description>Taylor was likely in line to start over Justin Fields this week, but he popped up on the injury report earlier this week. The 36-year-old quarterback practiced in a limited fashion for most of the week. While Jets coach Aaron Glenn told reporters Friday that Taylor was trending in the right direction, he still refused to name a starting quarterback. Depending on how Fields does against the Bengals, Taylor could be an option to start for the Jets as soon as Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c49-dab4-a3fb-9f7989b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets downgraded WR Josh Reynolds (hip) to out for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c55-d5d8-a3ff-fd754d660000</link>
      <description>The Jets will now be without their top two receivers, in addition to quarterback Tyrod Taylor, for their game against the Bengals. Rookie tight end Mason Taylor is also listd as questionable but is expected to play, potentially serving as the top pass-catcher for Justin Fields in a plus matchup for tight ends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c55-d5d8-a3ff-fd754d660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants downgraded S Jevon Holland (knee) to out for Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c7e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e0d9a0000</link>
      <description>Holland’s absence is big news for a Giants team also without cornerback Paulson Adebo. The fantasy upside of DeVonta Smith and Dallas Goedert continues to grow as Sunday approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c7e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e0d9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed CB Trevon Diggs (concussion/knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c9a-deb1-a39b-3d9e3ce50000</link>
      <description>Diggs went from an at-home concussion to injured reserve in the span of two weeks, meaning he will now miss at least five total games from a freak incident away from football. The Cowboys have already been one of the league’s most forgiving defenses, something that only worsens with Diggs of the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c9a-deb1-a39b-3d9e3ce50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers activated WR Christian Watson (knee) from Physically Unable to Perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cc5-deb1-a39b-3dcf79cd0000</link>
      <description>That places the veteran receiver in line to make his season debut for the Packers when they face the Steelers. Watson has been on the shelf since tearing his ACL in Week 18 of the 2024 season but has made a speedy recovery, now likely to make his return to the active roster in under 10 months after the injury. He should mix in for light usage in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cc5-deb1-a39b-3dcf79cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons placed LB Divine Deablo (forearm) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cd3-d245-adfb-9ddfd5de0000</link>
      <description>Deablo suffered a fractured forearm in the team’s Week 7 loss to the 49ers and will now miss at least four games on injured reserve. His absence creates a significant hole in the interior for a defense allowing the second fewest yards per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cd3-d245-adfb-9ddfd5de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons downgraded WR Drake London (hip) to questionable for Week 8 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cf9-deb1-a39b-3dff0a9b0000</link>
      <description>The move comes after a limited showing Friday. The veteran receiver was initially absent from the final injury report but was downgraded by the team Saturday, placing his status in legitimate question considering the late-week status update. His status will be one to monitor into Sunday when the team will release its inactives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cf9-deb1-a39b-3dff0a9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants activated K Graham Gano (groin) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cfc-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdd72c0000</link>
      <description>Gano returns after missing the minimum number of games. Even so, he has struggled through multiple injuries for the previous two seasons and has been inconsistent when healthy since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cfc-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdd72c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns downgraded QB Shedeur Sanders (back) to questionable for Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1d34-d245-adfb-9d7f041a0000</link>
      <description>The team elevated Bailey Zappe from the practice squad in an associated move, making it likely Sanders is forced to miss Week 8 against the Patriots. Sanders continues to push for playing time behind Dillon Gabriel, although it appears as if his bid for the starting quarterback gig will be on hold for a week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1d34-d245-adfb-9d7f041a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
