<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s John Keim reports Terry McLaurin (quad) was on the field for the start of Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0ca-d95b-addb-e8cef2940000</link>
      <description>McLaurin could make a surprise appearance later in the session, but things are trending toward a DNP for his first practice of Week 5. McLaurin missed Week 4 with the quad issue and was considered week to week as of the end of last week. Dan Quinn said on Monday that he was trending in the right direction, though he didn’t say if he expected McLaurin to return for Week 5. Deebo Samuel will operate as the team’s top wideout if McLaurin remains out, putting him in the WR2 ranks for a date with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0ca-d95b-addb-e8cef2940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0d5-d95b-addb-e8d7052a0000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Doug McDermott, linebacker Matt Milano is also expected to be limited in practice. The Bills lost both defenders after Week 1. Neither player has practiced since, so even a limited session to open the week is a step in the right direction. At 4-0, the Bills don’t need to rush either player back. Drake Maye and the Patriots will be hoping both players take their time while recovering ahead of their Week 5 date on Sunday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0d5-d95b-addb-e8d7052a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0dd-d95b-addb-e8df04780000</link>
      <description>This was the expectation after NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported Jackson’s status as “week to week” earlier today. Previous reports have also indicated that Jackson will not suit up for Week 5 against the Texans. All signs point to Cooper Rush making his first start as a Raven. Rush was a competent passer in Dallas last year, going 4-4 as a starter while Dak Prescott nursed a hamstring injury late in the year. Losing Jackson is a devastating blow to the Baltimore offense, but Rush is at least one of the league’s more capable backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0dd-d95b-addb-e8df04780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Myles Garrett (ankle) will not practice on Wednesday is considered day to day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0e1-dca3-a9fb-bdf96f5d0000</link>
      <description>We aren’t awfully worried about Garrett’s status for Week 5 yet. Garrett doesn’t need the practice reps and a “day to day” status typically isn’t a big deal for veteran players. He should be good to go for Week 5 versus Minnesota as long as he practices in some capacity before the final injury report is released. Garrett has four sacks this year and will look to add to the total versus Carson Wentz on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0e1-dca3-a9fb-bdf96f5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f3-dca3-a9fb-bdfb2f960000</link>
      <description>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell told reporters on Tuesday he hoped McCarthy would practice at some point this week, but that won’t happen today. McCarthy was already unlikely to suit up on Sunday. A DNP to open the week all but locks Carson Wentz in as the starter. McCarthy is likely eying a Week 7 return after the team’s Week 6 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f3-dca3-a9fb-bdfb2f960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f1-deb6-a7fd-f3ff85a00000</link>
      <description>We expect Hubbard to be listed as a non-participant on the injury report later today. The Panthers’ starter played through Week 4 without re-injuring his calf, which is a positive. Unfortunately, Panthers head coach Dave Canales is evidently dead set on rotating No. 2 RB Rico Dowdle in fairly regularly, which limits Hubbard’s weekly upside. He has a great matchup against the Dolphins this week, though, so he should play efficiently on his limited workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f1-deb6-a7fd-f3ff85a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LG Donovan Jackson (wrist) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f5-deb6-a7fd-f3ffa71f0000</link>
      <description>Jackson missed Week 4 with the wrist injury and will likely remain sideliend for the Vikings’ upcoming matchup with the Browns. Center Ryan Kelly suffered a concussion in Week 4 and right tackle Brian O’Neill went down with a knee injury. Neither player practiced on Wednesday. Carson Wentz is set to face the Browns without three of his starting offensive linemen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f5-deb6-a7fd-f3ffa71f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart (hamstring) won’t be limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f9-d95b-addb-e8ff878d0000</link>
      <description>Dart left Week 4’s win over the Chargers for a concussion evaluation and also suffered a hamstring injury. He returned after a brief check from the medical staff. While Dart needs to do a better job of protecting his body, he appears to be fine after a rollercoaster of an NFL debut. His rushing output will keep him in the QB2 ranks for Week 5 versus the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f9-d95b-addb-e8ff878d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reports that Chiefs RB Brashard Smith is expected to have “more involvement in the offense” moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f9-d95b-addb-e8ff9df20000</link>
      <description>Smith logged 19 offensive snaps last week, hitting the double-digit mark for the first time this season. He likewise hit season highs in carries (four) and targets (four). Isiah Pacheco and Kareem Hunt are playing very inefficiently and Smith’s pass-catching profile fits well with the Chiefs’ preferred offensive approach. His chance to establish himself as the Chiefs’ committee leader, or more, appears to be upon us. Seventh-round rookies cannot be viewed as guaranteed to succeed, but he is absolutely worth adding wherever available right now, before we find out if Smith has what it takes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0f9-d95b-addb-e8ff9df20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Browns are “really excited” about WR Isaiah Bond, TE Harold Fannin Jr. and RB Quinshon Judkins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a10f-d95b-addb-e94fa0b20000</link>
      <description>Bond is set to assume a larger role in the offense with WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) landing on injured reserve this week. Bond posted season highs in routes (27), targets (six), receptions (three) and yards (58) last week. He is tough to trust against the Vikings in rookie QB Dillon Gabriel’s first start, but he should be stashed by wide receiver-needy managers. ESPN’s Dan Graziano adds that Fannin’s “usage will only expand” as the season progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a10f-d95b-addb-e94fa0b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
