<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 02:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne had 20 rushes for 50 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos, adding four catches for 16 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43b6-d968-a19b-5bf7f2580000</link>
      <description>With Bhayshul Tuten (finger) done for the rest of the season, Etienne saw an uptick in usage against Denver. He accounted for 16 of the Jaguars backfield’s 20 running back carries and all four of the team’s running backs targets while running a pass route on 26 of Trevor Lawrence’s 46 drop backs. LeQuint Allen did see an inside-the-five rush, however, raising concerns about Etienne’s goal line role in Week 17. Etienne’s receiving touchdown was his fourth over the past two games. That can’t last, but his involvement in the pass game means Etienne won’t be sensitive to game script moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43b6-d968-a19b-5bf7f2580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacoby Brissett completed 16-of-31 passes for 203 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Cardinals’ 26-19, Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43af-d968-a19b-5bffa7060000</link>
      <description>A few missed connections in the end zone proved costly for Brissett’s box score. He daringly targeted WR Marvin Harrison Jr. 39 yards downfield, in the Falcons’ end zone, on the first drive, but the ball was thrown just out of Harrison’s reach. Later in the third quarter, Brissett targeted him again from 26 yards out, but Harrison failed to catch it. Later in the game, Brissett perfectly threaded the needle between two defenders on a 16-yard end zone target thrown to TE Trey McBride, but McBride let the pass hit him in the chest and tumble to the ground. They two had nearly linked up in a similarly scenario early on, but the ball hit the turf before McBride could dive for it. Brissett is a low-end QB1 against the Bengals next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43af-d968-a19b-5bffa7060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey had seven rushes for 50 yards in the Broncos’ Week 16 loss against the Jaguars, adding four catches for 71 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43bb-d56e-afff-e7fb9c390000</link>
      <description>Harvey got there for fantasy managers against an elite Denver defense. He accounted for seven of the team’s 12 running back rushing attempts and was tied for third on the team with five targets. Harvey logged a pass route on 26 of Bo Nix’s 51 drop backs, a relatively strong rate, especially considering Harvey was targeted on a healthy 23 percent of his routes. Harvey’s biggest play came on a 38-yard touchdown rush in which he shed a couple tacklers and sprinted past Denver defenders. Harvey’s workload is strong enough to make him a must-play RB2 option in Week 17 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43bb-d56e-afff-e7fb9c390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 2-of-3 targets for 52 yards and one touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43bd-d968-a19b-5bfd225f0000</link>
      <description>Wilson made both catches count. On the Cardinals’ second drive, QB Jacoby Brissett targeted him down the right sideline from 32 yards out. The ball hit Wilson’s chest and headed toward the ground, but Falcons CB Coby Bryant’s left arm stopped it from hitting the ground as the two players tumbled into the end zone. Wilson unbelievably grabbed the ball before it made contact with the turf. The refs initially ruled it an incompletion, but the Cardinals successfully challenged the initial ruling, resulting in a touchdown for Wilson. Wilson later got open against Bryant via a double move, faking a post route at the top of the stem before breaking outward and hauling in the 20-yard catch. Wilson remains a WR2 against the Bengals next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43bd-d968-a19b-5bfd225f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 4-of-6 targets for 66 yards in the Broncos’ Week 16 loss against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43cf-d35e-a1bf-47cfa7290000</link>
      <description>Franklin functioned as the Broncos’ WR2 behind Courtland Sutton despite Pat Bryant returning to the lineup after a Week 15 hamstring injury (Bryant would be carted off the field in the fourth quarter with a neck injury). Franklin saw 65 air yards on the day, a distant second to Sutton’s 223 air yards. Franklin ran a route on 37 of Bo Nix’s 51 drop backs and came down with one of Nix’s two downfield completions. Franklin will be an interesting if volatile WR3/4 play in Week 17 against the Chiefs if Bryant is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43cf-d35e-a1bf-47cfa7290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught both of his targets for 36 yards in the Broncos’ Week 16 loss against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43d4-d56e-afff-e7fc3ced0000</link>
      <description>Engram didn’t do much against his former team. He ran a pass route on 27 of the Broncos’ 51 drop backs and outside of a 33-yard reception in the first quarter, he was largely invisible in a game that saw Bo Nix throw 47 passes. Engram, who has more than four receptions in just three games this season, will be a deep league option in Week 17 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43d4-d56e-afff-e7fc3ced0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 1-of-3 targets for 14 yards in the Cardinals Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43d3-d35e-a1bf-47d3e5ee0000</link>
      <description>Harrison’s lone catch occurred on a comeback route with less than six minutes left in the game. He earned two targets before that, both of which were downfield passes thrown into the end zone. The first, 36 yards downfield, occurred on the Cardinals’ first drive, but he was slightly overthrown while being double-covered. Harrison failed to secure the second, thrown 26 yards downfield, in the third quarter. He remains a volatile WR3 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43d3-d35e-a1bf-47d3e5ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 4-of-8 targets for 27 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43a2-d35e-a1bf-47e24e890000</link>
      <description>McBride’s day should have been a lot bigger. He had two missed connections with QB Jacoby Brissett that should have resulted in touchdowns. The first was on Brissett, who threw the ball into the turf, just outside of McBride’s reach near the goal line. The second was a 16-yard pass that hit McBride in the chest, which Brissett threaded through double coverage into the end zone. Brissett locked onto the safe, underneath option by linking up with No. 2 TE Elijah Higgins instead of looking downfield, where McBride was running freely down the seam. McBride remains an elite TE1 next week against the Bengals, who field the NFL’s worst tight end-coverage unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43a2-d35e-a1bf-47e24e890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brenton Strange caught 5-of-7 targets for 39 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43da-d968-a19b-5bfb28690000</link>
      <description>Strange caught his second touchdown of the season on a first quarter red zone throw from Trevor Lawrence. Strange saw strong usage against Denver, logging a pass route on 33 of the Jaguars’ 46 drop backs and seeing the third most targets among Jacksonville pass catchers. In a red hot Jaguars offense, Strange should be started in most 12-team leagues every week. That includes Week 17 against the Colts. Strange had three receptions for 27 yards the last time he played Indy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43da-d968-a19b-5bfb28690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas, Jr. caught 2-of-3 targets for 18 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43e3-d35e-a1bf-47e375230000</link>
      <description>Thomas was an afterthought in this one, as Parker Washington led the Jaguars in targets, receiving yards, and air yards. Thomas, again showing no chemistry with Trevor Lawrence, was targeted on 6 percent of his pass routes, losing the air yards-heavy role he had seen over the previous three games. He still has just two touchdowns in 2025. Thomas will be a touchdown or big play-dependent WR3/4 play in Week 17 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43e3-d35e-a1bf-47e375230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
