<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared RB Jaylen Wright, CB Storm Duck, QB Quinn Ewers, DT Zeek Biggers, and WR Cedrick Wilson Jr. inactive for Week 5 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf920d930000</link>
      <description>Wright looks like a healthy scratch for Week 5. Ollie Gordon has run away with the No. 2 job in Miami behind De’Von Achane. Gordon is a touchdown-or-bust RB4 for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf920d930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Braxton Berrios, CB Zion Childress, QB Graham Mertz, LB Christian Harris, OL Jarrett Kingston, and OL Trent Brown inactive for Houston’s Week 5 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf9248320000</link>
      <description>All of these players are healthy scratches. The only players ruled out for Houston on Friday were placed on IR before the game or are designated to return players still in their 21-day window. Notably, Dameon Pierce is active as Houston’s third running back. Berrios missed the first two weeks with a hamstring injury and has not been active yet this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf9248320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson (ankle) is active in Week 5 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd461bbd0000</link>
      <description>With Foster, Mauro and Tyson Hill also both active, the Saints will have their top three tight ends all active for the same game for the first time this season. What that means for all of their usage remains to be seen, but it’s hard to start any of them with confidence this week until we see how the Saints deploy them. The Saints declared OG Cesar Ruiz, CB Isaac Yiadom, DE Chase Young, DT Khristian Boyd, OT Xavier Truss, and RB Devin Neal inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd461bbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared TE Ja’Tavion Sanders, CB Chau Smith-Wade, RB Chuba Hubbard, LB Claudin Cherelus, DT Jaden Crumedy, and DT Tershawn Wharton inactive for Week 5 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdea60000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as both Sanders and Hubbard were ruled out earlier in the week. Sanders is dealing with a high-ankle sprain and is expected to miss multiple weeks. Tommy Tremble will start in his place, putting him on the TE2 periphery for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdea60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) is inactive for Week 5 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-dca3-a9fb-bd9d0d2a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson was questionable entering the weekend but will now miss his third-straight game due to the ankle injury he suffered in Week 2. Johnson was the only questionable player the Jets had heading into Sunday. In addition to him, the Jets also declared CB Michael Carter (concussion), RB/KR Kene Nwangwu (hamstring), TE Stone Smartt, TE Jelani Woods, DT Leonard Taylor, and OT Esa Pole inactive for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-dca3-a9fb-bd9d0d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Adonai Mitchell is inactive for Week 5 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b507-d6e9-af9d-bf9772d20000</link>
      <description>Mitchell will supposedly be limited after his mistake-plagued Week 5, but with Alec Pierce (concussion) on the shelf, consider us skeptical. Mitchell probably won’t be out there for the first series, but all bets are off after that. Joining Pierce on the shelf are QB Riley Leonard, CB Kenny Moore II, RB Tyler Goodson, LB Buddy Johnson, OT Luke Tenuta and DT Eric Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b507-d6e9-af9d-bf9772d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants ruled RB Tyrone Tracy Jr., ILB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles, OL Evan Neal, DL Elijah Garcia, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 5 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b506-d6e9-af9d-bf9662510000</link>
      <description>Tracy is nursing a shoulder injury and had been listed as doubtful, but he was always a longshot to play this weekend. He’s getting closer and could make his return next week, but it will be Cam Skattebo dominating the snaps and touches for another week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b506-d6e9-af9d-bf9662510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught all four targets for 13 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 5 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b540-deb6-a7fd-f7df04720000</link>
      <description>Fannin’s role held steady in this game. He saw a few snaps at nearly every position on offense and finished second on the team in receptions behind only David Njoku. Fannin also caught his first career touchdown on a well-designed play-action look at the goal line. Fannin has a solid floor of three to four catches per week, but the ceiling isn’t there yet. He will be a mid-range TE2 when the Browns return from their Week 6 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b540-deb6-a7fd-f7df04720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 7-of-11 targets for 123 yards in the Vikings’ Week 5 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b544-dca3-a9fb-bdddb5d60000</link>
      <description>Jefferson now has 75, 126, and 123 yards in three Carson Wentz starts. Wentz hasn’t had the cleanest runout as a Viking, but he has more than enough arm talent to rifle intermediate and deep shots to his No. 1 receiver. Jefferson, in turn, has done his best to corral some of Wentz’s errant passes, allowing both to thrive in the absence of J.J. McCarthy. It’s too early to say who will be the team’s starting quarterback when the Vikings return from their Week 6 bye, but fantasy managers will be begging for Wentz to keep the job. Assuming he does, Jefferson will remain at the top of the WR1 ranks when he faces the Eagles in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b544-dca3-a9fb-bdddb5d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 5-of-6 targets for 41 yards in the Vikings’ Week 5 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b548-d95b-addb-fd4e7d9e0000</link>
      <description>Addison did not take the field for either of the Vikings’ first two drives of the game. It was reportedly a coaching decision, meaning Addison was benched for disciplinary reasons. He started to get some reps in the second quarter and was seemingly back to a relatively normal role after halftime. Addison made good on his opportunities in the second half. He reeled in a perfectly-placed end zone shot from Carson Wentz with just seconds left on the clock in the fourth quarter to take the lead over Cleveland. The incredible pitch and catch ultimately won Minnesota the ball game. We will presumably get more info on why Addison was benched later this week, but the issue appears to have been handled internally. Addison will be back in the WR3 ranks when his team returns to face the Eagles after their Week 6 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b548-d95b-addb-fd4e7d9e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
