<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (illness) has been ruled out for Week 18 agaisnt the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cf-d968-a19b-ddff9f040000</link>
      <description>Bateman didn’t practice all week, and the 26-year-old wideout will miss the winner-take-division matchup against the Steelers. He should be available if Baltimore advances to the Wild Card round with a win over Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cf-d968-a19b-ddff9f040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed WR Savion Williams on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85d2-d35e-a1bf-c5d23a820000</link>
      <description>Williams, 24, was a non-factor for Green Bay in 2025 with 10 catches for 78 yards; although he did a solid job as a kick returner with 717 yards on his 28 attempts. The 2025 third-round pick has the athleticism to be a helper in 2026, but fantasy managers in redraft leagues shouldn’t count on it .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85d2-d35e-a1bf-c5d23a820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills elevated EDGE Matthew Judon from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85de-d35e-a1bf-c5de67db0000</link>
      <description>Judon was signed by the Bills in the middle of December after being released by the Dolphins, and he’ll have a chance to show he could be a helper as a pass-rusher in the playoffs in Week 18 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85de-d35e-a1bf-c5de67db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers elevated QB DJ Uiagalelei from the pracice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85f9-d56e-afff-e7f9321d0000</link>
      <description>It will be Uiagalelei who backs up Trey Lance for the Week 18 finale against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85f9-d56e-afff-e7f9321d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks elevated RB Cam Akers and CB Tyler Hall for Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8601-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7f180000</link>
      <description>Akers will be the third running back for the season finale versus San Francisco behind Kenneth Walker and Zack Charbonnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8601-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7f180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens elevated WR Keith Kirkwood from the practice squad for Week 18 agaisnt the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8608-d35e-a1bf-c7ca64900000</link>
      <description>Kirkwood will essentially take the roster spot of Rashod Bateman, with Bateman ruled out due to illness. The 32-year-old won’t likely do much outside of special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8608-d35e-a1bf-c7ca64900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LT Josh Jones (ankle/knee) active for Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8612-dc7a-af9b-cfbff89f0000</link>
      <description>Jones will be the starting left tackle agaisnt the 49ers with Charles Cross (hamstring) unable to go. The inactives for the winner-take-all game for Seattle will be Cross, TE Nick Kallerup, S Coby Bryant, QB Jalen Milroe, LB Jared Ivey, OL Mason Richman and OL Bryce Cabledue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8612-dc7a-af9b-cfbff89f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared LT Trent Williams (hamstring), WR Ricky Pearsall (knee), RB Isaac Guerendo, DE Robert Beal Jr., DT Kevin Givens, LB Curtis Robinson and CB Chase Lucas inactive for Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8634-d56e-afff-e6fc650e0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers will be shorthanded without Pearsall and Williams, but George Kittle (ankle) will be active for the massive contest against the Seahawks. The hope is that both will be back for the 49ers’ first playoff game either on the road or after a bye if San Francisco can win Saturday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8634-d56e-afff-e6fc650e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle (ankle) is active for Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-860a-dc7a-af9b-cfbff9750000</link>
      <description>Kittle was limited all week in practice, but it’s no surprise that the 32-year-old will go in a must-win game for the 49ers if they want to win the division, and they do. With no Ricky Pearsall, Kittle could be inline for an even bigger amount of targets against the tough Seattle defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-860a-dc7a-af9b-cfbff9750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports that Browns HC Kevin Stefanski is believed to be “on the hottest seat” in the organization.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-864b-d968-a19b-defb38c50000</link>
      <description>Schultz reports that the Browns are expected to move on from Stefanski either via termination or trade, although Schultz says the latter isn’t a likely outcome. Stefanski has gone 44-56 over his six-plus seasons with Cleveland including a 4-12 record in 2025, but he likely will be one of the top candidates on the open market for several jobs if the Browns do move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-864b-d968-a19b-defb38c50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
