<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d94-dca3-a9fb-7d9d027d0000</link>
      <description>Porter Jr. suffered the hamstring issue in Week 1 and has been out ever since. He did not practice at all last week, so a limited designation is a step in the right direction. Pittsburgh’s defense has been underwhelming to start the year and injuries have been part of the issue. Getting Porter Jr. back would be a big help in turning things around against Carson Wentz and the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d94-dca3-a9fb-7d9d027d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d99-deb6-a7fd-7fdf46380000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez was limited for all three practices last week. The team initially listed him as questionable to play but then downgraded him to out over the weekend. He may need to get in a full practice before being cleared to action. Thursday and Friday’s injury reports will provide more info on the young corner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d99-deb6-a7fd-7fdf46380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is practicing in full for Week 4 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7da0-d95b-addb-7de69a0e0000</link>
      <description>Worthy is still working his way back from the shoulder injury he suffered via a collision with Travis Kelce in Week 1. He was back on the practice field the next week, but this is his first full session since dislocating his shoulder. A full practice this early in the week all but guarantees Worthy returns for Week 4 to face Baltimore. He could still be on a pitch count and will be wearing a harness to protect his shoulder, so fantasy managers shouldn’t get their hopes too high for his first game back. Still, a potential shootout with the Ravens will keep him in the WR3 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7da0-d95b-addb-7de69a0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7da6-deb6-a7fd-7fff78f50000</link>
      <description>Diggs was already playing through a knee issue heading into Week 3. He then exited the game with a shoulder injury and did not return. A DNP on Wednesday puts him on the wrong side of questionable to start the week. Dallas’s defense continues to lose valuable bodies and it’s only Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7da6-deb6-a7fd-7fff78f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes (right wrist) is practicing in full for Week 4 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db1-dca3-a9fb-7db95bdb0000</link>
      <description>Mahomes was added to the injury report last week with the wrist issue. He practiced in full throughout the week and never seemed bothered by the injury on Sunday. He did, however, scale back his rushing volume after topping 50 yards in each of the first two weeks. He went for a measly two yards on the ground versus the Giants. Despite being more cautious last week, he should be more inclined to open things up in an AFC showdown with the Ravens this time around. Mahomes remains a fantasy QB1 in a potential shootout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db1-dca3-a9fb-7db95bdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet (foot) is questionable for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db5-dca3-a9fb-7dbd4ef60000</link>
      <description>It’s a bit of a surprise to see Charbonnet with an injury status after he opened the week with two full practices. Weird stuff like this is standard fare for the Seahawks, so it’s hard to read too much into the questionable tag. For now, it looks like he should be back in the lineup after missing Week 3. Charbonnet had 27 carries to Ken Walker’s 23 before going down with the foot issue. Assuming he is good to go, fantasy managers can treat Charbonnet as an RB3 after the one-game absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db5-dca3-a9fb-7dbd4ef60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db8-d6e9-af9d-ffb8ec5e0000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon went down with the knee issue in Week 1 and has been out ever since. It’s a good sign to see him back after two weeks, given that the Seahawks had a short turnaround to Thursday Night Football for Week 4. Fellow defensive back Julian Love is also good to go for Seattle’s NFC West showdown with Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7db8-d6e9-af9d-ffb8ec5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) was a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddb-d6e9-af9d-ffdbff760000</link>
      <description>Wirfs is trending towards returning in Week 4 as he recovers from a training camp knee injury. The Bucs could use the boost to a battered offensive line heading into a showdown against the Eagles’ stout defensive front. Expect Wirfs to give Baker Mayfield a little more time in the pocket on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddb-d6e9-af9d-ffdbff760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (biceps) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddf-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2f90000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was listed as a limited participant due to a right biceps injury on Wednesday. The veteran has taken hits behind a battered offensive line this season and took on a limited workload to begin the week, though there is no indication that his status for Week 4 against the Eagles is in jeopardy. He will get extra help with Tristan Wirfs (knee) and Chris Godwin (ankle) slated to return this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ddf-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Will Shipley (oblique) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7de8-deb6-a7fd-7fff6ff60000</link>
      <description>Shipley was a full participant for the first time since injuring his oblique in the season opener. He had three carries for 26 yards against the Cowboys in Week 1 and profiles as Saquon Barkley’s primary backup. He is back on fantasy radars as a valuable handcuff as the Eagles play the Bucs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7de8-deb6-a7fd-7fff6ff60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
