<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said it’s “too early to say” if Deshaun Watson or Shedeur Sanders will be their Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</link>
      <description>Between the smoke on Ty Simpson and Malik Willis and Berry refusing to really stamp a player as “in the lead” here, it sure feels like this situation is unsettled heading into free agency. Sanders probably enters training camp as the main favorite for the job if the Browns don’t sign Willis, but anything could happen there. Up to and including a drafted quarterback winning the organization over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said OC Brad Idzik will call offensive plays for the Panthers in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910f-d629-a1bc-b11f731e0000</link>
      <description>We’re interested in seeing if Idzik will bring more of a deep-shot focused approach to the table, it’s an area where the Panthers have sporadically been good with Bryce Young, but one they seemingly can’t access every game. Otherwise we’d generally call moving to an unknown playcaller a theoretical downgrade for the Panthers, but it’s hard to get too caught up in it given Canales wasn’t exactly blowing anyone away in the coach tape community.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910f-d629-a1bc-b11f731e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks GM John Schneider said “obviously we’d love” to have Kenneth Walker back, but didn’t comment on the idea of franchise-tagging Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9117-d57c-a1dd-951f66260000</link>
      <description>Walker has been bandied about as a possible target for the tag, though Adam Schefter reported it was unlikely last week. This could perhaps be another space for the transition tag, as Breece Hall is learning. That tag would simply allow the Seahawks to match any offer Walker signs in free agency. Regardless of what they do, with Zach Charbonnet likely out well into the season, the Seahawks are heavily incentivized to keep Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9117-d57c-a1dd-951f66260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Kevin Stefanski said “i’m not big on giving out positions in February” when asked if Michael Penix is the team’s starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9122-d57c-a1dd-952abc890000</link>
      <description>“I think you guys know how I feel about Michael and I’m excited about his trajectory. I also know he’s focused on his rehab, which is the right thing to do,” Stefanski continued. Penix certainly appears to be the starting quarterback on the roster by default, but it’s possible that the Falcons could get involved in free agency to find a bridge quarterback — or perhaps more — to upgrade the room. It’s not as if Penix’s first two years of action were unimpeachable proof he has to start in 2026. It’s a situation to watch as free agency unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9122-d57c-a1dd-952abc890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper believes G Mekhi Becton could be a cap casualty.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9137-d57c-a1dd-953fed6d0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers would save $10 million by moving on from Becton, who openly seemed to not jive with former OC Greg Roman’s preferred blocking structures. Chargers GM Joe Hortiz said “I’m not going to talk about that right now” when asked about a Becton release at the NFL Combine. Becton, entering just his age-27 season, would be an interesting rebound candidate on the open market after a woeful year in Los Angeles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9137-d57c-a1dd-953fed6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles GM Howie Roseman said they’ll talk to Dallas Goedert’s agent in the coming days.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-913d-d57c-a1dd-953d05cd0000</link>
      <description>That’s not necessarily a guarantee something will get done, but it’s not like the Eagles have better options on the roster than Goedert after his 11-touchdown regular season. The 31-year-old should be a decent bet for low-end TE1 status in a return to Philadelphia, should it happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-913d-d57c-a1dd-953d05cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals GM Monti Ossenfort said WR Michael Wilson “is about everything we want in our program to be about, and hopefully he is here for a long time” when asked if he would offer Wilson an extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-914c-d57c-a1dd-954ce9690000</link>
      <description>It’s an indirect answer, but it’s hard to read the gushing as a non-yes. Ossenfort also pumped up Paris Johnson Jr., who will likely have his fifth-year option picked up ahead of next season. Wilson is entering the final year of his rookie deal as a third-round pick and would be a priority to extend sooner rather than later. How big a price tag the Cardinals put on Wilson, should they get down this road, will tell us a lot about how they feel about him as a main cog in this offense next to Trey McBride and Marvin Harrison Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-914c-d57c-a1dd-954ce9690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Houston’s Aaron Wilson reports the Texans are expected to part ways with Joe Mixon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9151-d57c-a1dd-95594dd90000</link>
      <description>Nick Caserio said earlier today that he “thinks” Mixon had a surgery this offseason and that he was “not trying to be evasive.” We’re earnestly surprised Mixon is still on the roster at this point, and the fact that the Texans keep defending him and pointing at the idea of him getting back to full health makes it feel like they’re taking this a lot more seriously than anyone on the outside is. We defer to Wilson’s sources here, who also add that the Texans will “explore” the “high-end free agent running back market.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9151-d57c-a1dd-95594dd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers GM Omar Khan said he’s spoken with Kenneth Gainwell’s agent and “he knows we want him back.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916c-d89c-a1be-bfff938e0000</link>
      <description>Gainwell doesn’t seem to be a major free-agent priority signing for anybody, but figures to do quite well for himself after putting up 73/486 through the air and amassing 1,000 yards from scrimmage. He figures to be a potential third-down back upgrade for several teams in free agency, though the Steelers remain a great fit for him as he slotted in well behind Jaylen Warren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916c-d89c-a1be-bfff938e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports LT Trent Williams and the 49ers are “struggling to find a contractual solution” and Williams could be released.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916f-d042-afbc-fdff04230000</link>
      <description>Williams is entering the final year of a three-year, $82.66 million contract with the 49ers and is carrying a $38.8 million cap figure for this season. Releasing him would only save about $5 million in cap space unless it was done with a post-June 1 designation. The 49ers also already have plenty of cap space, so it feels more like a separation for the sake of getting out of the Williams business as he enters his age-38 season. Williams played as well as ever last year — he had a 91.1 PFF grade despite a slow start in Seattle while injured at the start of the season. He has definitely seemed more injury-prone of late. Several teams should probably be interested in Williams’ services if he hits the free-agent market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916f-d042-afbc-fdff04230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
