<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:12:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 2-of-2 targets for 26 yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-baba-d90d-a5bd-bafbe4950000</link>
      <description>Caleb Williams targeted Loveland via play action on the first play from scrimmage, completing the pass for an eight-yard gain. Williams’ second target went to Cole Kmet for a 29-yard gain, marking Kmet’s lone target. Later, Williams found Loveland wide open on a post route, connecting for an 18-yard gain. Fantasy managers should expect both tight ends to remain involved in the regular season, particularly early on. Loveland has already established himself as a first-team contributor, though, which puts a TE1 finish within his range of outcomes. He looked great on his two opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-baba-d90d-a5bd-bafbe4950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 2-of-2 targets for 16 yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bae8-d45c-a7fc-bafa87650000</link>
      <description>Moore connected with Caleb Williams on a third-and-five conversion, gaining 10 yards on an out route. It was a simple play but good to see the two players link up in crunch time. Moore must continue developing his relationship with Williams after a bumpy first season together.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bae8-d45c-a7fc-bafa87650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 0-of-1 targets in the Bears’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba9f-d05a-adda-ba9ffc190000</link>
      <description>Odunze dropped his lone target against the Bills. He got open on a third-and-five curl route but was unable to secure it as he dove toward the sideline to make the catch. The first-team offense was then done for the day. Hopefully, the starters take the field again next week, allowing Odunze and Caleb Williams to get on the same page against a live NFL defense before Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba9f-d05a-adda-ba9ffc190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus caught 1-of-2 targets for 36 yards and one touchdown in the Bears’ preseason game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-baf0-d05a-adda-baf24b180000</link>
      <description>Caleb Williams spotted Zaccheaus open in the shallows and hit him in stride as he scooted past the first-down marker. Zaccheaus was off to the races after that, shedding an ankle-grab as he snaked downfield. Zaccheaus is beginning to look like he may warrant a few WR5/flex starts against soft defenses early in the year. He has Williams’ trust. The coaching staff will undoubtedly give Luther Burden opportunities to take the WR3 job from him, so Zaccheaus’ fantasy relevance could dry up rapidly, but for now, Zaccheaus appears to be on track for WR3 duties in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-baf0-d05a-adda-baf24b180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Davis rushed three times for five yards and caught 0-of-1 targets in the Bills’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb01-d05a-adda-bb8315c80000</link>
      <description>Davis was bottled up against the Bears, but he promisingly started and played 11-of-11 first-team snaps through three drives. Davis remains a high-end bench stash entering his second NFL season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb01-d05a-adda-bb8315c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer caught 1-of-1 targets for two yards in the Bills’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb12-df63-a199-fb3b19070000</link>
      <description>Palmer was on the field for the Bills’ first eight plays, earning a target on the second. The offense struggled to move the ball downfield, so his showing does not stand out positively or negatively, beyond him having earned his team’s first target. Palmer is a moderately efficient player who could return flex value, operating as the Bills’ No. 1 perimeter receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb12-df63-a199-fb3b19070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden III caught 3-of-3 targets for 49 yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 2 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb18-d45c-a7fc-bb1a5cdb0000</link>
      <description>Burden did not take any snaps with the first-team offense, instead playing on drives three-to-six. The rookie looked elusive and athletic, averaging 7.7 yards after the catch. Perhaps, Burden’s best play occurred on a Bears rushing touchdown from two yards out, in which Burden bulldozed Bills S Damar Hamlin out of RB Brittain Brown’s way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bb18-d45c-a7fc-bb1a5cdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rob Demovsky reports Packers RB MarShawn Lloyd could miss the Packers’ season-opener or more after suffering a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd16-df63-a199-fd3f3fd50000</link>
      <description>The injury bug continues to bite Lloyd, who had just returned to practice last week after being sidelined by a groin injury. Lloyd’s rookie season was also marred by injuries. The 2024 third-round pick appeared in just one game as a rookie, rushing six times for 15 scoreless yards while adding one catch for three yards. We could get a better sense of how long the team expects him to be out when roster cutdown day comes. If he’s at risk of missing multiple games, a trip to the IR could be in his future, which would require him to miss a minimum of four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd16-df63-a199-fd3f3fd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports free agent EDGE Matthew Judon is scheduled to meet with the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd3a-d90d-a5bd-bf7b54f40000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, both the Dolphins and Judon “are motivated to reach a deal,” suggesting a signing could he imminent if all goes well. Judon spent last season with the Falcons after being traded away from the Patriots. The veteran pass rusher was hoping to parlay a strong 2024 performance into a lucrative payday that the Patriots refused to give him, but he has instead been without a job after totaling 5.5 sacks and seven TFLs in 17 games last season. Judon can still provide some value as a situational pass rusher, but his days as an elite pass rusher may be over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd3a-d90d-a5bd-bf7b54f40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
