<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6048-d713-ad9e-6c5c9f470000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars will have one of their starting perimeter wide receivers on the field this week. Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) and WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee, injured reserve) are both out. Brown sneaks onto the FLEX radar against a stout Texans defense this week, earning targets against slot WR Parker Washington and newcomer WR Jakobi Meyers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6048-d713-ad9e-6c5c9f470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars ruled out TE Hunter Long (hip/knee) for Week 10 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6046-d45b-affe-75d6a07e0000</link>
      <description>Long has been filling in for TE Brenton Strange (hip/quad), but has yet to earn more than three targets in a game, so his absence is hardly consequential. Jaguars TE Johnny Mundt is the next man up, though he should not be considered for TE1 purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6046-d45b-affe-75d6a07e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) will not play in Arizona’s Week 10 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6052-d1e7-a1fa-7afa50780000</link>
      <description>Neither will (inhale): CB Max Melton (concussion), LB BJ Ojulari (knee), or LB Mack Wilson (ribs) — the good news is that Budda Baker (hamstring) upgraded to full today and has been removed from the injury report. Arizona’s defense looked good against the Cowboys on Monday night, but their cornerback depth will be tested against Jaxson Smith-Njigba and Rashid Shaheed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6052-d1e7-a1fa-7afa50780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is questionable to play in Week 10 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6050-d713-ad9e-6c5467fa0000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reporters on Thursday that a decision on whether Purdy will “suit up” would be made this afternoon. Apparently, that decision is a “maybe,” though only as the backup, if active. 49ers QB Mac Jones will once again serve as the team’s starter. He profiles as a high-end QB2 against the Rams’ tough defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6050-d713-ad9e-6c5467fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 10 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6057-d45b-affe-75d7009b0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall will now miss his sixth game of the season. The extremely unfortunate saga continues. Pearsall’s PCL sprain, suffered in Week 4, has kept him sidelined for weeks now. Hopefully, Pearsall can at least resume practicing next week, though we have received no indications from the team or beat reporters as to when he might return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6057-d45b-affe-75d7009b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (ribs) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6057-d713-ad9e-6c577c8d0000</link>
      <description>The Rams’ No. 1 wide receiver would never leave a fantasy squad in the lurch. The team gave Nacua a half-day on Wednesday before upgrading him to full participation on Thursday and Friday. The No. 5 wide receiver in half-PPR per-game scoring (18.7) is ready to rock in a divisional tilt against the 49ers on Sunday. He is an elite WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6057-d713-ad9e-6c577c8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) did not practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-607b-d713-ad9e-6c7f82db0000</link>
      <description>This is a bad sign for Golden’s availability on Monday night. With Packers TE Tucker Kraft (knee) out for the year and WR Jayden Reed (foot/collarbone) on injured reserve, the team’s notoriously deep pass-catching corps could be operating as a condensed, fantasy-friendly unit led by WRs Romeo Doubs and Christian Watson, and fill-in starting TE Luke Musgrave. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-607b-d713-ad9e-6c7f82db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-608a-d1e7-a1fa-7aeafd960000</link>
      <description>Wicks could need another week to rehab the calf injury that he picked up in Week 8, but his continued participation is at least positive. That said, Wicks’ inconsistent play makes him extremely difficult to trust in 12-team re-draft formats, even with WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) having been downgraded to a DNP on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-608a-d1e7-a1fa-7aeafd960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed “might need to play extensively” in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-60e0-d713-ad9e-6cf454bf0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks listed WR Cooper Kupp (heel /hamstring) as questionable, WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) as doubtful, while ruling out WRs Jake Bobo (calf) and Dareke Young (hip) on Friday. Fortunately, “Shaheed’s transition to the Seahawks should be streamlined thanks to his familiarity with [OC] Klint Kubiak’s scheme,” and Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the team has “a plan for him” this weekend. Horton also serves as the team’s primary punt returner, while Young is one of the two primary kickoff returners. Shaheed is expected to contribute in both special teams roles as well, having notably earned first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors in 2023 as a punt returner. Shaheed can be started right away as a WR3, regardless of Kupp’s game-day availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-60e0-d713-ad9e-6cf454bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (knee) is questionable for Week 10 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-615d-d673-a39e-e5ddb4270000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also listed LB Tatum Bethune (thigh), DL Alfred Collins (hip), DL Kalia Davis (ankle) and DL Keion White (groin) as questionable and are expected to place DL Mykel Williams (knee) on injured reserve. Williams’ expected injured reserve placement, after suffering a torn ACL, will make him the fourth San Francisco pass rusher to be moved there this season. Williams’ 19 quarterback pressures rank second on the team. 49ers LB Fred Warner was placed on injured reserve after suffering a season-ending dislocated ankle injury in Week 6, yet Warner still accounts for the team’s second-highest tackle total (39). Winters leads the way with 53. Rams QB Matthew Stafford should have comfortable pockets this weekend, and RB Kyren Williams could have fairly easy sledding on runs up the middle, 49ers’ questionable statuses pending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-615d-d673-a39e-e5ddb4270000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
