<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed eight times for 51 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens, adding 27 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4457-d35e-a1bf-45d725460000</link>
      <description>Stevenson was thrust into workhorse duties following the second quarter departure of rookie TreVeyon Henderson due to a concussion, although the negative game script capped his rush attempts the remainder of the way. Stevenson made the most of the opportunity in the fourth quarter, catching a two-point conversion to bring the Patriots within three points with just over nine minutes left to play before springing loose off tackle for a 21-yard score to complete an 11-point comeback later in the frame. Fantasy managers in the Championship round will want to follow the status of Henderson closely in the coming week of practice as Stevenson could be looking at a robust role in a good matchup against the Jets in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4457-d35e-a1bf-45d725460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 9-of-10 targets for 138 yards in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-445c-d56e-afff-e6fcf4770000</link>
      <description>Diggs served as quarterback Drake Maye’s primary target throughout a game that was played tightly throughout, reaching the 100-yard threshold for the fourth time this season. Arguably more important than his contributions on the field was his leadership off the field as Diggs was consistently shown on the broadcast hyping up his team on the sideline, something that helped to spark the team’s first fourth quarter comeback win after being down by 11 or more since their Super Bowl victory over the Falcons. The 138 yards were more than Diggs had amassed in his previous three games combined and helped to secure a playoff berth for New England following a three-year drought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-445c-d56e-afff-e6fcf4770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught 7-of-9 targets for 69 yards in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4460-d56e-afff-e6e8dc9f0000</link>
      <description>The veteran journeyman made his presence felt early as he flashed across the middle of the field for a chunk gain in the second quarter, following it up with numerous catches to help move the chains. Hollins continues to play in a rotational role for the Patriots, although his big play ability gives him paths to fantasy utility in the right environment. That said, pass volume could be more sparse when the Patriots face the Jets on the road in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4460-d56e-afff-e6e8dc9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams caught 2-of-3 targets for 46 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4463-dc7a-af9b-cfff19ac0000</link>
      <description>Williams’ primary contribution was a ridiculous catch through two defenders in the corner of the end zone from 37 yards out in the fourth quarter, a play that helped spark the Patriots’ first fourth quarter comeback from 11 or more down since their Super Bowl victory over the Falcons. A modest snap rate and deep aDOT keep Williams from true weekly fantasy utility, although he continues to flash his big play ability in key situations. Keep an eye on Williams in best ball drafts in the coming offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4463-dc7a-af9b-cfff19ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 6-of-7 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4466-dc7a-af9b-cfff35980000</link>
      <description>Henry got the team on the scoreboard in the second quarter from one yard out, shedding his block on a Drake Maye bootleg for an easy score after his defender committed to keeping Maye from the end zone. His solid red zone role has kept his fantasy value afloat this season, even through a modest aDOT and route participation for the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4466-dc7a-af9b-cfff35980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Huntley completed 9-of-10 passes for 65 yards in the Ravens’ 28-24, Week 16 loss to the Patriots, adding two yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4469-d968-a19b-5cf98a2c0000</link>
      <description>Huntley entered the game in the second quarter following a back injury to starter Lamar Jackson. He wasn’t asked to do much through the air as the defense allowed the Ravens to ride Derrick Henry in the second half, ultimately coming up short of the much needed win after the Patriots surged from 11 points down to snatch the victory away. The loss removes control from the team’s path to the postseason, now requiring a loss by the Steelers in Week 17, a win over the Packers, and to beat their divisional opponents in Week 18 to reach the playoffs. They could also be forced to do so without Jackson, pending follow-on testing to his injured back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4469-d968-a19b-5cf98a2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 18 times for 128 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-446e-d35e-a1bf-45eed2120000</link>
      <description>Henry erupted in the second half following the departure of starting quarterback Lamar Jackson, quite literally putting the team on his back as the Ravens built an 11-point lead in the fourth quarter. The veteran bruiser overcame a lost fumble in the first quarter for his second consecutive 100-yard showing, sixth 100-yard outing, and fourth multi-touchdown game of the season. Even so, the Ravens fall to 7-8 with the loss and no longer control their own destiny for a playoff berth. King Henry gets a difficult matchup against the Packers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-446e-d35e-a1bf-45eed2120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught all seven targets for 84 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots, adding 18 yards and a touchdown on once carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4472-d56e-afff-e6fab5050000</link>
      <description>Flowers was the main cog of the offense through the air on a night starting quarterback Lamar Jackson departed in the second quarter with a back injury. His departure contributed to the team attempting only 20 passes, seven of which were directed to the veteran speedster. His returns were sparkling until a game-sealing fumble with just over two minutes remaining cost the Ravens the game and lowered their chances of reaching the playoffs. Flowers gets another difficult matchup against the Packers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4472-d56e-afff-e6fab5050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</link>
      <description>Not one of Hopkins’ four catches was routine as the veteran receiver made several spectacular grabs throughout. Arguably the most impressive was a ball down the sideline that deflected off the defenders hands, which he corralled in time to drag the trailing foot as he headed to the ground. Hopkins doesn’t play enough snaps for the low volume Ravens to warrant weekly fantasy consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are never a high pass volume offense, but things got worse in this one following the departure of starting quarterback Lamar Jackson in the second quarter. The team shifted to a heavier emphasis on Derrick Henry in the second half, which appeared to be working until they allowed the Patriots to overcome an 11-point fourth quarter deficit to steal the win. Now at the tail end of his career, Andrews rarely returns fantasy utility if he is held out of the end zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
