<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0d-d673-a39e-ff9da9260000</link>
      <description>We never love to see a mid-week downgrade. If Worthy isn’t able to make it to Sunday, Hollywood Brown will get a fantasy boost against the Broncos. A healthy Worthy is probably a WR3 play against the Broncos’ stellar defense in Week 11, while Brown stepping into the second receiver role would probably be a FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0d-d673-a39e-ff9da9260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed WR Garrett Wilson on injured reserve with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f16-d713-ad9e-7f56bac10000</link>
      <description>Wilson will now miss at least four games as he rehabs his injured knee. He will be eligible to return when the Jets face the Jaguars in Week 15. Following reports on his rehab progress will be worthwhile. Starting a player immediately following an injured reserve stint can be dicey in Week 15. Hopefully, he is practicing in full that week and can be trusted in fantasy lineups. Unfortunately, there is a chance that the team chooses to shut him down for the rest of the year, given their poor record. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f16-d713-ad9e-7f56bac10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Isiah Pacheco (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f16-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe5c0d0000</link>
      <description>It sure feels like it’ll be Kareem Hunt in a tweener RB2/RB3 role for fantasy purposes as the lead back on Sunday, with Brashard Smith involved behind him. Pacheco has not practiced since injuring the knee in Week 8’s win over the Commanders. We don’t think he’s heading to injured reserve but he certainly appears to be week-to-week for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f16-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe5c0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f18-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa60720000</link>
      <description>He looks to be trending towards playing after getting in two limited sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. Matt LaFleur said yesterday that he was “definitely close” to playing. With Dontayvion Wicks (calf) also picking up limited sessions in each of the first two days, it looks like Green Bay will have their four best receivers ready for Week 11 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f18-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa60720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (pectoral) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1b-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbcd570000</link>
      <description>He’s missed back-to-back practices, but told reporters he was optimistic about Friday. Highsmith always seems to be fighting through something, but he has played each of the last five weeks and should be considered questionable for this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1b-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbcd570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers T Broderick Jones (groin) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe71950000</link>
      <description>Generally offensive linemen will play off murkier statuses than most positions, so we’d be surprised if Jones wasn’t at least questionable now that he has made an appearance following Wednesday’s DNP. Calvin Anderson would be the next man up if Jones isn’t able to get right for Week 11’s game against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe71950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Flacco (right shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0c-d45b-affe-7f9e79110000</link>
      <description>The Bengals are simply managing Flacco’s reps as he rehabs an AC joint sprain in his throwing shoulder. Ideally, the team needs him for two more games, before QB Joe Burrow’s (toe) hopeful return. Expect Flacco to continue producing as a QB1 against the Steelers’ defense this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0c-d45b-affe-7f9e79110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f24-d713-ad9e-7f7484720000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is highly unlikely to play after injuring his foot during a hip-drop tackle in Week 10. Broncos head coach Sean Payton has employed a fantasy-unfriendly running back rotation with his backups at times, but rookie RB RJ Harvey is currently in a position to handle an RB2-worthy workload in Week 11 against the Chiefs. Fellow backup RB Tyler Badie can be added in deep PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f24-d713-ad9e-7f7484720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2d-d45b-affe-7fbf99290000</link>
      <description>Fellow backup RB Justice Hill (toe) remains sidelined, setting up Mitchell for No. 2 running back duties against the Browns. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters earlier this week that he hopes to further incorporate Mitchell on game day. That should not be an issue with Hill heading toward a Week 11 absence. Mitchell should be stashed at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2d-d45b-affe-7fbf99290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (hip) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2c-d1e7-a1fa-7fee28af0000</link>
      <description>Likely should have no issue suiting up on game day, though he can only be started as a touchdown-dependent TE2, operating as TE Mark Andrews’ sidekick. Andrews is barely a better option than Likely, though Andrews has QB Lamar Jackson’s trust in the red zone, leading to three touchdowns scored over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2c-d1e7-a1fa-7fee28af0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
