<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 13:08:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 3-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b70-d294-a19b-eff0a8560000</link>
      <description>London tied for third on the team in targets with Darnell Mooney, behind the five targets of Kyle Pitts and Bijan Robinson. The low target totals were a product of only 21 Michael Penix pass attempts in a game the Falcons were able to control on the ground throughout. London’s first quarter fumble came in a 6-0 game and allowed the Vikings to pull within three points with a field goal of their own. The two teams traded field goals to end the second quarter but the Falcons would bully their way to a victory via 39 combined rush attempts, limiting the upside of all Atlanta pass-catchers in the process. A similar game environment could develop in Week 3 when the Falcons travel to Carolina to face the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b70-d294-a19b-eff0a8560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 4-of-5 targets for 37 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b76-d294-a19b-eff693010000</link>
      <description>Pitts tied for the team lead in targets, something that doesn’t bring fantasy managers any comfort due to the low pass volume of an Atlanta offense that bullied their way to a victory behind 39 rush attempts. The early-season returns from Pitts are encouraging following three consecutive mundane seasons after a breakout rookie campaign, and he should be more involved in games the Falcons don’t control so handily via their run game. That said, fantasy managers might want to consider other options at the tight end position ahead of a Week 3 matchup with the reeling Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b76-d294-a19b-eff693010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 2-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7b-d294-a19b-effbf3d00000</link>
      <description>Mooney’s four targets tied for third on the team with Drake London and were one behind co-leaders Kyle Pitts and Bijan Robinson. Fantasy managers of any Atlanta pass-catcher were left wondering where the volume was on a night Bijan Robinson and Tyler Allgeier combined to see 38 carries, a script that could play out again in Week 3 when the Falcons face the Panthers in Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7b-d294-a19b-effbf3d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy completed 11-of-21 passes for 158 yards and two interceptions in the Vikings’ 22-6, Week 2 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7e-d294-a19b-effeaee80000</link>
      <description>McCarthy and the Vikings were unable to replicate their fourth quarter magic from Week 1 after struggling to move the football for three quarters, managing just six points before the break and being held off the scoreboard entirely in the final two frames. The second-year effective rookie also put the ball on the ground three times, losing one fumble, as the Vikings gained just 198 total yards of offense on a modest 23:28 time of possession. The early-season returns are less than adequate to sustain viable fantasy production for managers that invested in Kevin O’Connell’s offense, something the team will look to correct ahead of a Week 3 meeting with a Bengals team without quarterback Joe Burrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7e-d294-a19b-effeaee80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed nine times for 33 yards in the Vikings’ Week 2 loss to the Falcons, adding eight yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b84-d86f-abdd-4fbd5ca60000</link>
      <description>The Vikings were held to just 46 offensive plays in a game the Falcons controlled throughout via an imposing run game, yielding just 12 opportunities for Mason. His 3.3 yards per carry were indicative of the team’s struggles to move the football as their offensive line clearly showed the wear of missing two starters. Fellow running back Aaron Jones departed in the second half with a hamstring injury, something that could propel Mason to a featured role ahead of a Week 3 meeting with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b84-d86f-abdd-4fbd5ca60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 3-of-6 targets for 81 yards in the Vikings’ Week 2 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b87-d294-a19b-eff7a2390000</link>
      <description>Quarterback J.J. McCarthy attempted just 21 passes on a night the Vikings managed just 46 offensive plays, yielding just six targets for Jefferson in the process. Things looked to be turning around late in the first half when McCarthy connected with Jefferson on a 50-yard catch-and-run in the middle of the field to set up a field goal as time expired, but the two could not rekindle their late-game magic from Week 1. The salt in the wound came late in the fourth quarter when McCarthy badly overthrew Jefferson for a pick, allowing the Falcons to effectively run out the clock to end the game. Jefferson is likely to return better production when the Vikings host the Bengals in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b87-d294-a19b-eff7a2390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 1-of-3 targets for 12 yards in the Vikings’ Week 2 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b8b-dc44-a9d9-4fefdb100000</link>
      <description>Hockenson’s receiving line tells the tale of the Vikings’ game, one in which they managed just 46 offensive plays while getting completely manhandled in the trenches on both sides of the ball. What’s worse, the Vikings only trailed 9-6 at the half and had every opportunity for a curtain-call performance in the final quarter, but the team could not rekindle the late-game magic from Week 1 and fell to a 1-1 record in the process. Hockenson has now gone two games with no more than 15 yards, something fantasy manager hope is rectified in short order considering he went off the board as the fantasy TE4 in drafts this summer. Maybe a matchup against the tight end-funnel Bengals will kick start his season in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b8b-dc44-a9d9-4fefdb100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Nailor caught 1-of-3 targets 28 yards in the Vikings’ Week 2 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b8f-dc44-a9d9-4fefebf10000</link>
      <description>Nailor remains buried behind Justin Jefferson, T.J. Hockenson, and the backfield in the target pecking order for the Vikings, leaving little room for weekly fantasy value. He should remain on the waiver wire, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b8f-dc44-a9d9-4fefebf10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Joe Burrow “will need surgery that will sideline him a minimum of three months.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4d62-da67-a99f-cdf743410000</link>
      <description>The most talked-about toe in America will officially sideline Burrow for the next three months and, maybe longer. Things felt like they were trending in this direction after reports surfaced late in the night that surgery could be on the table after we learned the Bengals sent images to foot expert Dr. Robert Anderson last night. A three-month absence puts Burrow’s timeline for return somewhere around mid-December. How the Bengals are faring at that time could ultimately determine whether or not we see him again in 2025 or if they opt to shelve him until 2026. For now, this is Jake Browning’s team going forward. He’ll make his first start of the season in Week 3 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4d62-da67-a99f-cdf743410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
