<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 19 times for 55 yards in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears while adding one catch for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab63-dc7a-af9b-efffd7360000</link>
      <description>Jacobs also returned two kicks in this game despite never returning a kick in an NFL game before, and his first attempt saw him fumble with the ball fortunately landing in the hands of a Packers’ special-teamer. The tailback found very little room in the run game, and the word “plod” would be an accurate descriptor for much of the contest. While he did rush for 13 touchdowns in 2025, he also was held to a 4.0 average on his 234 carries (929 yards). The 27-year-old should be back with Green Bay in 2025, and he’ll open the year as a low-end RB1 thanks to his knack for finding the end zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab63-dc7a-af9b-efffd7360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson rushed once for three yards in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab64-dc7a-af9b-efffecbe0000</link>
      <description>Wilson was not involved in the Packers’ gameplan, nor was Chris Brooks who finished with one carry for 16 yards and a catch that went for 11. He wasn’t terribly efficient in his work in the regular season, either, finishing with a 4.0 YPC and 496 yards on his 125 attempts with 15 receptions for 99 for good measure. He’ll be an RFA this winter, and it’s likely he’ll just be a backup tailback whether he’s back with the Packers or joins a new club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab64-dc7a-af9b-efffecbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 8-of-11 targets for 124 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab65-d35e-a1bf-efe7dab00000</link>
      <description>On a night where Jordan Love spread the ball around to several wideouts, Doubs was still clearly his top target, and he was rewarded with a one-yard touchdown near the end of the first half that gave Green Bay a 21-3 lead. The 25-year-old ‘s season is over because the Packers fell apart in the second half, and he finished the 2025 campaign with 55 catches for 724 yards with six touchdowns. There were several clunkers for the wideout — the same is true for all Packers’ receivers in 2025 — but there were enough flashes to suggest he still has a bright future in this league. The question is where he’ll be playing in 2026, as he’ll be able to test free agency for the first time this winter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab65-d35e-a1bf-efe7dab00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught 4-of-5 targets for 84 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6c-d968-a19b-fbfd02580000</link>
      <description>Golden’s touchdown was spectacular; a 23-yard pass that showed off his speed and ability to weave through traffic that gave the Packers a 27-16 lead with 6:36 remaining in the contest. The Bears would score the next 15 points, however, so Golden and Green Bay’s season has come to a close. The 2024 first-round pick disappointed for the majority of 2025, as he finished with just 29 receptions for 361 yards without a regular-season score, and he went above 60 yards just once before Saturday night. The talent is readily apparent, and while fantasy managers would be foolish to bank on it, it’d be anything but surprising if he broke out in 2026; especially if there’s some changes to the Green Bay receiving room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6c-d968-a19b-fbfd02580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught 4-of-7 targets for 43 yards with a touchdown in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6d-d56e-afff-efed0de00000</link>
      <description>Reed gave the Packers a 14-3 lead with an 18-yard connection with Jordan Love; one of four touchdowns for Love in the contest. He wasn’t a major factor after the trip to the end zone, and it ends a disappointing season for Green Bay and for Reed. He was limited to just seven games in the regular season, and after scoring in the opener, he didn’t find the end zone again until Saturday night. He has one more year left on his contract before becoming a free agent in 2027, and assuming Reed remains with Green Bay, he’s a pretty solid bounceback candidate for the coming campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6d-d56e-afff-efed0de00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 3-of-7 targets for 36 yards with a touchdown in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-d968-a19b-fbff035e0000</link>
      <description>Watson came very close to a second touchdown, but he fumbled into the end zone with the ball being recovered by Green Bay and placed on the one-yard line to set up another score. The product of North Dakota State didn’t have any success in the second half, and the Packers’ second-half collapse keeps the Bears from moving on. Watson’s season line of 35 catches for 611 yards with six touchdowns is more impressive when you consider he didn’t play until the end of October, and the wideout appeared to build up chemistry with Jordan Love towards the end of the campaign; even with a lot of mouths to feed in the Green Bay passing attack. He’s under contract for 2026, and he’ll begin the 2026 campaign in the low-end WR, high-end WR3 conversation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-d968-a19b-fbff035e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 1-of-2 targets for nine yards in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-dc7a-af9b-efffda780000</link>
      <description>Musgrave wasn’t involved despite the Packers throwing 46 times in the loss, and the 2023 second-round pick finishes a disappointing campaign with another ineffective fantasy outing. He ended the year with just 24 catches for 252 yards, and even after Tucker Kraft went down with his ACL injury in Week 9, he didn’t he didn’t make an impact with zero touchdowns and just one game with over four catches. The 25-year-old is under contract for one more year, and there’s no reason to think he should be on radars when draft season begins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-dc7a-af9b-efffda780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon McManus missed both field goal attempts while making 3-of-4 extra points in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-abd6-dc7a-af9b-efffa56e0000</link>
      <description>McManus missed two critical kicks; an extra-point that would have put the Packers up by 13 with two minutes left, and a field goal that would have extended the Green Bay lead to six. The 34-year-old made 24-of-30 field goals in 2025, but he went just 6-for-12 on kicks beyond 40 yards. He is signed through 2027, but there’s no guarantee that McManus will be back in Green Bay in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-abd6-dc7a-af9b-efffa56e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said LB T.J. Edwards suffered a fractured fibula in the team’s Wild Card Round win over the Packers and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad36-dc7a-af9b-efbf0e640000</link>
      <description>Edwards was carted to the locker room in the second quarter of Chicago’s stunning comeback victory over the Packers and did not return. He appeared in 10 games this year, logging 67 combined tackles, .5 sacks, and a pick-six. D’Marco Jackson took his spot in the lineup in the second half of Saturday’s game. Jackson has largely been a backup this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad36-dc7a-af9b-efbf0e640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said LT Ozzy Trapilo suffered a patellar injury in the team’s Wild Card Round win over the Packers and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad3d-d35e-a1bf-edff09ac0000</link>
      <description>The second-round rookie didn’t see much action early in the year but took over as the team’s starting left tackle in Week 12. He has held down that job ever since. Pro Football Focus has him graded as a top-40 tackle this year. Theo Benedet took his spot in the lineup late in Saturday’s game. He will presumably start in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad3d-d35e-a1bf-edff09ac0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
