<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived DT Michael Dwumfour.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31c-db7b-a5dd-e31c5a590000</link>
      <description>He was signed only recently and looked fairly good against the Saints in Denver’s final preseason tune-up, notching a 79.7 PFF pass rush grade against ... well, backup linemen. Joining Dwumfour on the early cut list are DB Micah Abraham, LB Joaquin Davis, LB Andrew Farmer, DB Joshua Pickett, G Xavier Truss, and G Clay Webb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31c-db7b-a5dd-e31c5a590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Diana Russini reports that the Raiders are signing Amari Cooper to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e328-dbe3-a9bb-f37bd5d00000</link>
      <description>It’s a return to the organization that drafted and developed Cooper into one of the better wideouts in the sport before he moved on to the Cowboys, Browns and Bills; respectively. The 31-year-old isn’t the same playmaker he was in those previous Silver and Black years, and he’s coming off a season where he caught 44 passes for 547 yards with four touchdowns with Cleveland and Buffalo. That being said, the Las Vegas depth chart offers very little competition, and it’s pretty easy to see him being one of Geno Smith’s top targets for the 2025 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e328-dbe3-a9bb-f37bd5d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed RB Phil Mafah (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32a-d332-a1fd-f73ef8b60000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four weeks. This gives Dallas a little runway to see if Jaydon Blue or Miles Sanders can establish a true pecking order behind Javonte Williams. Mafah, Dallas’ seventh-round pick this year, ran hard in the preseason and has a chance to be a factor later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32a-d332-a1fd-f73ef8b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released QB Mike White.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e327-db7b-a5dd-e3270a5d0000</link>
      <description>White had a brutal Week 18 showing for the Bills last year, completing 3-of-11 passes for 28 yards. He fared slightly better during the preseason this month, completing 12-of-24 passes for 166 yards and two touchdowns. He may be able to find a spot on an NFL practice squad this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e327-db7b-a5dd-e3270a5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said he’s “optimistic” about WR Tory Horton (ankle) being available for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</link>
      <description>Horton hasn’t practiced since leaving Seattle’s second preseason game with the ankle injury, but it doesn’t seem like he’s at any risk of starting the year on injured reserve based on this update. Horton isn’t someone you need to roster in your home fantasy league right away, but he’s got a chance to grow into a real role in year one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Buccaneers are releasing QB Kyle Trask.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will work out an injury settlement for Trask, as he’s currently dealing with a shoulder issue. A second-round pick for some reason in 2021, Trask has been the backup quarterback for the Bucs over the last four seasons, but that honor will now apparently go to Teddy Bridgewater. Trask is likely a practice squad player for a new organization in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived RB Audric Estime.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e346-dbe3-a9bb-f357e4b70000</link>
      <description>Estime is the odd man out from the Broncos’ running back room, with the team jettisoning him a year after spending a fifth-round pick on him. He tallied 76 carries for 310 yards and two touchdowns in a committee last season, but does not add much as a pass-catcher. With R.J. Harvey and J.K. Dobbins joining Denver’s backfield, Estime’s lack of passing-down work could not beat out the likes of Jaleel McLaughlin and Tyler Badie. He could find work on a team needing a downhill runner in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e346-dbe3-a9bb-f357e4b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions waived RB Deon Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e339-d332-a1fd-f73f17b50000</link>
      <description>Jackson, 26, was signed in August and didn’t stand much of a chance to make the opening roster. The Lions also waived DT Myles Adams and DE Nate Lynn ahead of Tuesday’s deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e339-d332-a1fd-f73f17b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams released LB Brennan Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e362-de13-afdc-e7eb058d0000</link>
      <description>Jackson was second in sacks during the preseason, but that wasn’t enough for him to make the initial roster to begin the 2025 campaign. The 24-year-old is a strong candidate for the practice squad if another team doesn’t procure his services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e362-de13-afdc-e7eb058d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived RB Blake Watson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ backfield is taking shape with Audric Estime and Watson being waived today. Watson had just four carries for 10 yards last season and suffered a PCL strain last week. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports there was some trade interest in him, so he is a candidate to be claimed. If not, the Broncos likely want him back on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e367-db7b-a5dd-e36706870000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
