<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports the Colts “don’t know when or if Anthony Richardson (eye) will be cleared at any point” to return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fee8-da9b-a9bf-feedff900000</link>
      <description>The Colts are waiting to receive official word on Daniel Jones’ Achilles injury, but it’s a widely held belief that Jones will miss the remainder of the season with a torn Achilles. Richardson suffered an orbital fracture ahead of Week 6’s game against the Cardinals and has been on injured reserve ever since, leaving Riley Leonard as the primary backup to Jones. Leonard is currently positioned to be the Colts’ starting quarterback for the remainder of the season, but Richardson could step into the role if he is cleared to return. The former No. 4 overall pick has shown flashes as a starter and is an imposing presence on the ground when he takes off to run. That said, it doesn’t sound like anyone is expecting a return any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fee8-da9b-a9bf-feedff900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers waived DT Naquan Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feff-da9b-a9bf-feff89590000</link>
      <description>Jones appeared in eight games for the Chargers this season, tallying 10 tackles and one TFL while playing in a backup role. The decision to waive Jones likely has to do with rookie RB Omarion Hampton being activated ahead of Monday night’s game against the Eagles. If he clears waivers, Jones will be free to sign with any team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feff-da9b-a9bf-feff89590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said Jaycee Horn (concussion) is trending toward playing in Week 15 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff1a-d77b-adfa-ff9ba21b0000</link>
      <description>Horn remains in the league’s concussion protocol, but he’s nearly two weeks removed from the brain injury he suffered in Week 12 against the 49ers. Horn has appeared in 12 games for the Panthers this season, totaling a career-high five interceptions while breaking up an additional six passes. The Panthers, who sit at 7-6 and are in the thick of a playoff hunt, will be in search of their eighth win in Week 15 against the Saints, and will get an added boost if Horn can return. In addition to Horn, Canales also said LB Claudin Cherelus (concussion) is trending toward a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff1a-d77b-adfa-ff9ba21b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said Shedeur Sanders will remain as the starting QB for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff21-d005-a9bf-ff358c670000</link>
      <description>Speaking Monday, Stefanski said Sanders “has constantly and consistently gotten better” while adding that he feels “good about where his development is heading.” Sanders threw for a career-high 364 yards and three touchdowns in Week 14’s loss to the Titans, and nearly led the Browns to a comeback after trailing by 14 points with just over six minutes left in the game. Through four games, three of which are starts, Sanders has thrown for 769-5-3 while completing 52.4 percent of his passes. While he hasn’t looked like the first-round talent many expected to see, Sanders has shown plenty of flashes to warrant a longer look after Dillon Gabriel offered up nine games of ultra-conservative play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff21-d005-a9bf-ff358c670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns C Ethan Pocic suffered a torn Achilles in Week 14’s loss to the Titans, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff23-da9b-a9bf-ff2f86960000</link>
      <description>The Browns confirmed the worst on Monday after Pocic left Sunday’s game with what was initially diagnosed as a calf injury. A replay of the injury, however, suggested a potential tear for Pocic, who will now spend the remainder of this season and all offseason rehabbing his injury. Pocic has started all 13 games he’s appeared in this season for the Browns, earning a PFF grade of 63.6 while allowing two sacks and 14 pressures. It wouldn’t be surprising if this injury impacted Pocic’s offseason, as his current deal with the Browns is set to expire, making him a free agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff23-da9b-a9bf-ff2f86960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Daniel Jones suffered a torn Achilles in Week 14’s loss to the Jaguars, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff35-d8cf-affb-ff3f5ecc0000</link>
      <description>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz was the first to confirm the news. It’s a brutal end to the season for Jones, who was enjoying a career year in his first season with the Colts while leading the team to an 8-4 start to the season. Jones joined the Colts on a one-year deal this offseason and beat out Anthony Richardson for the starting job in camp. Jones threw for 3,101-19-8 in 13 games this season, completing a career-high 68 percent of his passes. He was on pace for a career-best 4,055 passing yards before going down, and now he enters an interesting offseason. Jones turns 29 next offseason and is likely facing a 9-12-month rehab, depending on the severity of his injury, and seems unlikely to be ready for the start of next season. His performance was the best the Colts have experienced in the Shane Steichen era, and the Colts won’t be in a position to draft a QB high in next year’s draft without orchestrating a trade. It wouldn’t be surprising to see Jones re-up with the Colts, but the deal he receives could look much different than what he was hoping for before his injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff35-d8cf-affb-ff3f5ecc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LT Paris Johnson (knee) left Arizona’s Week 14 game against the Rams and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff40-d8cf-affb-ff6a66680000</link>
      <description>Cardinals reporters noted that he stayed on the sideline after being ruled out, but the Cardinals don’t exactly have a reason to push Johnson through this injury given they’re already eliminated from playoff contention. Arizona has just one starter left from its season-opening line and faces the Texans in Week 15. Jacoby Brissett was already pummeled by the Rams on Sunday and Week 15 shapes up as more of the same.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff40-d8cf-affb-ff6a66680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Denzel Ward (calf) left Cleveland’s Week 14 game against the Titans and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff45-da9b-a9bf-ff4db1a80000</link>
      <description>Kevin Stefanski had no update on Ward’s status on Monday, but the rule-out was not encouraging. We’ll monitor his practice status, but we imagine he’s likely on the doubtful side of questionable for Week 15 at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff45-da9b-a9bf-ff4db1a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RT Braden Smith (concussion) left Indianapolis’ Week 14 game against the Jaguars and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff48-d8cf-affb-ff6a406f0000</link>
      <description>The last thing the Colts need with Riley Leonard under center against the Seahawks is a new lineman at right tackle. So, naturally, that appears to be on the table this week. Rookie fourth-rounder Jalen Travis took over for Smith and would figure to be Smith’s replacement in Week 15 if he can’t clear concussion protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff48-d8cf-affb-ff6a406f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) left Seattle’s Week 14 game against the Falcons and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff4b-d005-a9bf-ff7fa9220000</link>
      <description>Arroyo has faded down the stretch as he hasn’t cracked two targets since October 20. He suffered the knee injury in the first half and Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald didn’t have an update on him after the game. This injury won’t create much new fantasy value for the Seahawks, who are already struggling to feed enough targets to their non-JSN receivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff4b-d005-a9bf-ff7fa9220000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
