<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 03:11:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Omarion Hampton (ankle) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-d94a-a79d-bb2f3f600000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games. It’s devastating fantasy news as Hampton had just taken on a more-or-less full-time role in Los Angeles’ backfield. Without him, they’ll form a committee with Hassan Haskins and Kimani Vidal leading the way. Haskins is probably the better bet for fantasy managers since he has actually spent some of this year on the roster. We would not expect miracles out of either player, but a Week 6 matchup with the team that brought you “Rico Dowdle, 200-yard rusher” should make Haskins a borderline RB2/FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-d94a-a79d-bb2f3f600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles listed Saquon Barkley (knee) as DNP on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-db72-a199-fb6f999c0000</link>
      <description>It’s only an estimated report, but an estimated DNP is still concerning for Barkley, who has struggled on the ground to start the season. We’ll see if things change come Tuesday when the Eagles actually hold a practice, but this is clearly something worth monitoring until we receive word that Barkley is in the clear for Thursday night’s game against the Giants. If Barkley is unable to go, A.J. Dillon could be in line to handle early-down touches while Will Shipley mixes in on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb2f-db72-a199-fb6f999c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nakobe Dean (knee) was listed as a full participant on Monday’s estimated injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb5c-dd4c-afb9-ffddb43d0000</link>
      <description>Dean returned to practice last week in a limited capacity but was upgraded to full by the end of the week. The fact that he was limited as a full participant to start this week is an encouraging sign for his Week 6 availability, but the Eagles still have time to delay his return if they don’t think he’ll be ready to play on a short week. Dean totaled 128 tackles and three sacks in a breakout 2024 performance. When he returns, he should slot in as the Eagles’ No. 1 inside linebacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb5c-dd4c-afb9-ffddb43d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Saquon Barkley (knee) “had general soreness” after Week 5’s loss to the Broncos but expects to play in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb64-dd4c-afb9-ffe5ca300000</link>
      <description>The Eagles had fans and fantasy managers buzzing on Monday when they listed Barkley as a DNP due to a knee injury. That said, this appears to be a very minor issue, and any decision to sit Barkley early in practice is out of precaution. We’ll be sure to monitor his status throughout the week, but we’d expect Barkley to be ready to go come Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb64-dd4c-afb9-ffe5ca300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said the team will monitor Kyler Murray’s foot throughout the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73b6d0000</link>
      <description>Murray suffered a foot injury in Week 5’s loss to the Titans and briefly left the game to be evaluated. He missed only two plays, but it’s clearly something the team feels the need to watch throughout the week. Given the fact that Murray played through the injury and barely missed any time, we will assume he’ll be good to go for Week 6 against the Colts until we hear otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73b6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed G Ben Powers (bicep) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb8d-db72-a199-fbcf3a110000</link>
      <description>Powers is a massive loss on the interior offensive line for an offense that derives its identity from the unit. The veteran guard is expected to miss the better part of the next two months as he heals from a torn bicep. The team said they hope to get him back for the stretch run in late December.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb8d-db72-a199-fbcf3a110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions HC Dan Campbell said CB D.J. Reed will be “out indefinitely” with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb97-def2-abdb-bff7fe250000</link>
      <description>Fellow cornerback Terrion Arnold is also expected to miss significant time with a shoulder injury, leaving the team extremely shorthanded on the back end ahead of a Week 6 matchup with the Chiefs. Safety Kerby Joseph has been tending to a knee injury as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb97-def2-abdb-bff7fe250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared DE Travon Walker, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Wyatt Milum, DL Danny Striggow, and DT Khalen Saunders inactive for Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb9d-db72-a199-fbdfca370000</link>
      <description>Walker was attempting to play just over a week after having surgery on his wrist but ultimately did not do enough to avoid being inactive. A win against the Chiefs will give the Jaguars more wins through five games than they had in all of the 2024 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb9d-db72-a199-fbdfca370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) is active for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbb9-d94a-a79d-bbbd26960000</link>
      <description>Worthy returned to the lineup in Week 4 following two missed games with a separated shoulder but experienced swelling in his ankle on the flight to Jacksonville, ultimately prompting the questionable tag. He is active and will play against the Jaguars, giving the Chiefs their primary option through the air. Inactive for the Chiefs are CB Kristian Fulton, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, DT Omarr Norman-Lott, OL Hunter Nourzad, and DE Malik Herring</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbb9-d94a-a79d-bbbd26960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) questionable to return to Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbbc-d94a-a79d-bbbdf98f0000</link>
      <description>Strange exited in the third quarter after a hit to the midsection and was labeled questionable to return on the same drive. He managed 22 yards on one reception prior to departing. Expect Johnny Mundt and Hunter Long to fill the void at tight end for the rest of the game against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbbc-d94a-a79d-bbbdf98f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
