<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon did not have an update on Marvin Harrison Jr. (appendicitis) to start the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7cb-db57-afda-f7fbe71a0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals wasted little time ruling out Harrison for last week’s game against the Jaguars. Harrison has now missed back-to-back games since undergoing surgery for appendicitis ahead of Week 11, and could be at risk of missing Week 13’s game against the Buccaneers. We might have to wait until Wednesday’s injury report to see where things stand, but another absence for MHJ would be music to the ears of fantasy managers rostering Michael Wilson. Since Harrison has been sidelined, Wilson has caught 25 passes for 303 yards. He would be a must-start against the Bucs if MHJ sits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7cb-db57-afda-f7fbe71a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports an MRI revealed a low-grade sprain to Baker Mayfield’s shoulder.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7fc-d413-ad9f-b7fdab2b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that this is “good news with an eye toward next week,” suggesting Mayfield could miss at least one game with the injury. We’ll see if this changes throughout the week, but if Mayfield is unable to go against the Cardinals, Teddy Bridgewater would draw the start in his absence. Bridgewater threw for just 62 yards on 15 pass attempts in last week’s loss to the Rams, and would be an immediate downgrade for all Buccaneers pass-catchers. Mayfield’s status will be one to monitor when the first practice report drops on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b7fc-d413-ad9f-b7fdab2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Lamar Jackson is fine physically after Week 12’s win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b80e-d413-ad9f-bddf4cc70000</link>
      <description>Although Jackson was listed as a “DNP” on Monday’s estimated practice report, this time due to a toe injury, head coach John Harbaugh downplayed any lingering issues for the veteran signal caller. Jackson appeared a step slower in Sunday’s win over the Jets, but shut down any idea that injuries have held him back in recent weeks. Jackson hasn’t rushed for more than 36 yards in a game since returning from the hamstring injury he suffered in Week 4, and is averaging just 2.8 yards per carry in his last four games. Jackson and Harbaugh can deny it all they want, but it’s hard to ignore one of the most dynamic runners in the league suddenly looking far less dynamic. Hopefully this is something he can work through while still playing, but fantasy managers banking on Jackson’s rushing upside carrying them into and through the fantasy playoffs in the coming weeks may need to temper expectations a bit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b80e-d413-ad9f-bddf4cc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Kyle Hamilton (ankle) will “have a chance” to play in Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b816-d90e-a9da-bf1fd2380000</link>
      <description>Hamilton was already playing through a shoulder injury entering Week 12, and was knocked from Sunday’s win over the Jets with an ankle injury that he suffered after slipping on the turf. Hamilton is one of the premier defenders in the league and would make for a massive loss if the Ravens are without him against Joe Burrow, Ja’Marr Chase, and the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b816-d90e-a9da-bf1fd2380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Rashee Rice (hamstring) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b823-db57-afda-fe3325bc0000</link>
      <description>We never like seeing wide receivers dealing with hamstring issues considering the nature of the position, but there likely isn’t reason to be concerned ahead of the team’s Thanksgiving matchup against the Cowboys. As things currently stand, Rice’s hamstring issue is nothing more than something to monitor on a short week. Running back Isiah Pacheco was listed as a full participant, making it likely he returns from a three-game absence in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b823-db57-afda-fe3325bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b827-d413-ad9f-bdff1c410000</link>
      <description>Bateman has been sidelined in consecutive games after suffering an ankle injury in Week 10, but appears to be nearing a return to the game-day roster. Fantasy managers will want to monitor his status when the team takes the practice field in earnest on Tuesday before making any roster decisions for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b827-d413-ad9f-bdff1c410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared K Eddy Pineiro, RB Jordan James, WR Jordan Watkins, OL Connor Colby, DL Robert Beal Jr., DL Kevin Givens, and LB Tatum Bethune inactive for Week 12 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b82a-d82c-a79a-bbbef8bb0000</link>
      <description>Linebacker Tatum Bethune and kicker Eddy Pineiro are the two most notable names missing for the 49ers as they fight to keep pace with the Rams and Seahawks at the top of a crowded NFC West. Matt Gay will fill in at kicker while the team will likely require a slight shuffling on the interior of their second level with Bethune out of action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b82a-d82c-a79a-bbbef8bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Hunter Renfrow, LB Trevin Wallace, LB Christian Rozeboom, C Cade Mays, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, and DT Cam Jackson inactive for Week 12 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b84a-d90e-a9da-bf4fe2a60000</link>
      <description>Nothing too out of the ordinary here, with the Panthers near full strength in what has become an important matchup for the team following the loss by the Buccaneers on Sunday. The two teams are currently tied atop the NFC South with the Panthers having yet to go on their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b84a-d90e-a9da-bf4fe2a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR George Pickens (knee/calf) did not practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b850-d413-ad9f-bdddab470000</link>
      <description>The team did not hold a full practice Monday on a short week, meaning Pickens’ status is simply an estimation. That said, the fact that he carried two injury designations does raise some level of concern for his availability on a short week. Fantasy managers will want to track his level of participation on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b850-d413-ad9f-bdddab470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn is being evaluated for a concussion in Week 12 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b861-d90e-a9da-bf6fd92b0000</link>
      <description>Sideline reporter Lisa Salters relayed that Horn was seen throwing up on the sideline following his second interception, hardly a good sign for his chances of returning to the game against the 49ers. Expect him to be ruled out in short order and enter the league’s five-step concussion protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b861-d90e-a9da-bf6fd92b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
