<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:03:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott completed 23-of-38 passes for 294 yards in the Cowboys’ 34-26, Week 15 loss to the Vikings, adding two yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2061-d1bc-a3fb-a56504250000</link>
      <description>Prescott and the Cowboys cashed in on their first two trips to the red zone, each time via a rushing score from one yard out. They would fail to find paint on their subsequent three red zone trips, each time resulting in a short Brandon Aubrey field goal. Two missed field goals from 50+ yards from Aubrey changed the tide of the game, as did the relentless and confusing pressure thrown at Prescott by Minnesota defensive coordinator Brian Flores. It also didn’t help to have a seemingly disinterested George Pickens, who was seen going through the motions on multiple occasions throughout the game. The loss all but ends the Cowboys’ chances at a postseason berth, now requiring three consecutive wins and three losses by the Eagles to make the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2061-d1bc-a3fb-a56504250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams rushed 15 times for 91 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2066-d8cf-affb-bc6ec3d10000</link>
      <description>Williams scored on the team’s first possession of the game after briefly departing following a hard hit to the shoulder. He was deemed questionable to return and missed the remainder of the first half before emerging from the break with the starters. Williams’ career resurgence in Dallas surely earned him a hard look for a significant contract in the coming offseason after playing 2025 on a one-year, prove-it deal with the Cowboys. Whether that will be handed out by owner Jerry Jones remains to be seen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2066-d8cf-affb-bc6ec3d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Davis rushed eight times for 21 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings, adding 16 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-206a-d1bc-a3fb-a56e2f820000</link>
      <description>Davis scored from one yard out on the team’s second possession following an injury to starter Javonte Williams. Williams departed in the first quarter and missed the remainder of the first half before returning with the starters after the break. Fantasy managers will want to track Williams’ activity level in practice in the coming week ahead of a Week 16 meeting with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-206a-d1bc-a3fb-a56e2f820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 6-of-10 targets for 111 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-206e-d77b-adfb-eaef4e850000</link>
      <description>Lamb handily led the team in targets and yardage but failed to find the end zone on a night quarterback Dak Prescott failed to throw for a score. The veteran alpha was leaned on heavily throughout as George Pickens’ bout of disinterested play continued into Week 15, but disguised coverages and unique blitz packages from Brian Flores’ Minnesota defense made life continually difficult for all parties. Now all but eliminated from postseason contention, Lamb and the Cowboys move forward in another lost season as they prepare to face the Chargers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-206e-d77b-adfb-eaef4e850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 3-of-6 targets for 33 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2071-d1bc-a3fb-a575d3ba0000</link>
      <description>Pickens was hammered by the media throughout the week after his effort level was called into question in the team’s Week 14 loss to the Lions, with those same tendencies rearing their head against the Vikings. He was seen giving up on the route at least once and was hardly a contributor to the run game, routinely running at half speed off the line on called rush attempts. He even walked off the line on one occasion. Pickens’ talent has never been in question but putting mental lapses like this on film is surely going to influence offseason contract discussions, even with his eruption on the field through the middle parts of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2071-d1bc-a3fb-a575d3ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2076-d1bc-a3fb-a57603d20000</link>
      <description>Ferguson played through a calf ailment that had him enter the weekend listed as questionable, ultimately unable to return usable counting stats on a night quarterback Dak Prescott failed to throw for a score for the third time this season. He has not failed to return a solid fantasy score in all five games since the team’s Week 10 bye, with his performance in the first week of fantasy playoffs hurting the most. His next chance to return TE1 production comes in a difficult matchup against the Chargers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2076-d1bc-a3fb-a57603d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Aubrey made 4-of-6 field goal attempts and two extra points in the Cowboys’ Week 15 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-207a-d8cf-affb-bc7a381d0000</link>
      <description>The normally elite kicker missed from 51 yards in the first half and from 59 yards after the break in a loss that all but ended the team’s chances at a postseason berth, now requiring three wins and three losses from the Eagles to do so. The two misses also matched his season total through 13 games after the veteran kicker connected on 27 of his first 29 attempts this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-207a-d8cf-affb-bc7a381d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said Woody Marks (ankle) could have returned to Houston’s Week 15 game over the Cardinals, but he wanted to “make sure Woody is good as we continue to go into the week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-21e4-d77b-adfb-ebe7cfab0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like with a 17-0 lead, Ryans prioritized Marks’ health — this is the third week in a row where he has been pulled mid-game with a nagging lower body injury. Sensible. Not fun for fantasy managers, but sensible. Marks enters Week 16 on the questionable line, with a big game possible against a Raiders defense that allowed 31 points to the Bad Vibes Eagles in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-21e4-d77b-adfb-ebe7cfab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Ravens fear LB Teddye Buchanan suffered a torn ACL in Week 15’s win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-222c-d1bc-a3fb-a72ca2d10000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Buchanan’s knee buckled under him while covering a punt early in Sunday’s win. The rookie linebacker is scheduled to undergo more tests on Monday to confirm things, but it sounds like Buchanan is trending toward missing the remainder of the season. Buchanan is second on the team with 93 tackles this season and has also registered five TFLs to go with one forced fumble and one pass breakup. His absence would be a big loss for the Ravens who are fighting to stay in the playoff hunt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-222c-d1bc-a3fb-a72ca2d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Williams caught 6-of-7 targets for 53 yards in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</link>
      <description>It was a career day for Williams, who ranked second among Jets receivers in routes (30) and third in snaps (41). Williams has played primarily on special teams this season and currently leads the league in punt return yards (396) and has two punt return touchdowns. He seemed to show good chemistry with Brady Cook, who he has presumably spent a lot of time with in practice, but his strong performance in Week 15 could warrant a stronger look over the final three weeks of the season. Williams has played 30-plus snaps and run 20-plus routes in back-to-back weeks. He’s worth a stash in deeper leagues ahead of next week’s game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2233-d77b-adfb-eab31c540000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
