<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RT Storm Norton (ankle) underwent surgery and will miss 6-8 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c889-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbc4e90000</link>
      <description>It feels likely that Norton will grab a PUP or IR listing at final cuts if this estimate holds. The veteran tackle has played in 31 games for the Falcons over the last two seasons, starting four. With Kaleb McGary going down in practice and requiring an MRI today, it is possible the Falcons are playing a third-string right tackle in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c889-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbc4e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Cordell Volson (shoulder) will undergo surgery and likely miss the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8b6-de13-afdc-ceff99400000</link>
      <description>Volson took a paycut after a rough 2024 season and now appears set to enter free agency after his rookie deal expires this offseason. The Bengals drafted Dylan Fairchild to replace him this offseason, so Volson was likely only set to be a depth piece for the Bengals in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8b6-de13-afdc-ceff99400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said G Dominick Puni (knee) is “iffy” for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8c7-d332-a1fd-def749700000</link>
      <description>Puni suffered a PCL sprain in San Francisco’s second preseason game. The 49ers signed G Michael Dunn on Wednesday, so it’s clear that they’re at least making sure they can get through their third preseason game with some healthy guards as Ben Bartch (elbow) also is currently shelved. If Puni does miss time, Shanahan mentioned Spencer Burford as a potential fill-in at guard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8c7-d332-a1fd-def749700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royce Lewis is not in the lineup Wednesday against the Athletics.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/baseball/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deff222a0000</link>
      <description>Lewis will get the day off — something that doesn’t happen often all that often — so Ryan Fitzgerald will start at third base and hit ninth against JT Ginn and the A’s bullpen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/baseball/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deff222a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR DeVonta Smith (groin) missed practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deffafe10000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are likely being conservative with both Smith and A.J. Brown (hamstring), with neither suiting up in recent practices. Smith has also dealt with a back injury in training camp. We don’t expect these injuries to spiral into Week 1 at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8cb-d332-a1fd-deffafe10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jesse Newell believes Brashard Smith could see first-team reps in Kansas City’s preseason finale.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d0-db7b-a5dd-e8d41d880000</link>
      <description>Newell describes Smith as fit in “a gadget-type role for Kansas City, which would showcase him as both a runner and receiver.” It sounds like the seventh-round pick has an inside track to a roster spot over Elijah Mitchell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d0-db7b-a5dd-e8d41d880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Tashan Reed believes WR Jack Bech is “firmly the fourth receiver in the rotation” for the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d5-dbe3-a9bb-f8d73ee70000</link>
      <description>It appears that Bech is the backup slot option behind Jakobi Meyers at this point, with fellow rookie Dont’e Thornton ahead of him on outside sets because Bech “lacks noteworthy long speed and is still learning how to beat press coverage at the line of scrimmage.” Oof. Bech appears to lack standalone value in dynasty drafts at this point, though with Meyers a pending free agent, it’s possible Bech could have some value in his sophomore season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8d5-dbe3-a9bb-f8d73ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired Jowon Briggs and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Browns for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8e7-d332-a1fd-def7e2940000</link>
      <description>A blockbuster. Briggs, who turns 24 in September, played 133 snaps for the Browns last year from Weeks 13 to 18, compiling a 66.5 PFF run defense grade. He’ll try to provide a boost for the Jets interior line. The 2024 seventh-rounder has three cost-controlled years left on his rookie deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8e7-d332-a1fd-def7e2940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Denzel Ward (shoulder) will be back “pretty soon.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f7-de13-afdc-ceff18810000</link>
      <description>Ward missed another practice on Wednesday, but it doesn’t seem like he’s in any real danger of missing Week 1 for the Browns. Cedric Tillman (thumb) wore a brace at today’s practice but it is another injury that is not considered serious, per Stefanski.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f7-de13-afdc-ceff18810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Kenny Pickett (hamstring) won’t play in Cleveland’s third preseason game on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f9-db7b-a5dd-e8fd91080000</link>
      <description>It seems that preseason Week 3 will set up as a split between Shedeur Sanders and Dillon Gabriel, with Sanders back throwing in individual drills. Pickett has not attempted a pass in any preseason game this year and that might make him a tough trade target for teams across the league, perhaps increasing the chances the Browns carry four quarterbacks at the start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c8f9-db7b-a5dd-e8fd91080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
