<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai (knee) will play in Week 13 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c668-d82c-a79a-f7fca9860000</link>
      <description>Monangai was listed as a full participant on Tuesday’s injury report and continued to be listed as a full participant throughout the week. The rookie was removed from the injury report on Thursday, meaning he’ll be good to go against a matchup between 8-3 teams hoping to keep pace with the Rams for the top spot in the NFC. Monangai enters Week 13 with a three-game touchdown streak, but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a boom-or-bust RB3 given his low receiving totals and rushing outputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c668-d82c-a79a-f7fca9860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) for Week 13 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c66d-d6c4-abfb-d66f5d8b0000</link>
      <description>The Bears also ruled out LBs Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder) and Noah Sewell (elbow) ahead of Friday’s game. Hyppolite is a lightly used backup who has totaled just six tackles this season, while D’Marco Jackson will take over for Edwards and Sewell, who have both been key contributors for the defense when active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c66d-d6c4-abfb-d66f5d8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown is questionable to return in Week 13 against the Packers after suffering an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c693-d82c-a79a-f797dd6b0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown was embracing the Lions’ “no block, no rock” philosophy by attempting to help RB Jahmyr Gibbs pick up yards on a run play. The Packers’ defender stood St. Brown up just before fill-in starting C Trystan Colon and LG Kayode Awosika hit the ground behind him, simultaneously rolling in the back of St. Brown’s legs. Lions trainers were seemingly assessing St. Brown’s right ankle before the broadcast cut to commercial. He headed straight to the locker room once he was on his feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c693-d82c-a79a-f797dd6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c67d-d82c-a79a-f7fd8fe30000</link>
      <description>Benson could still get limited work in later on, but Benson appears to be heading toward a DNP today. The Cardinals’ running back logged four straight limited sessions dating back to last week. We were hoping to see him upgrade to full participation today or tomorrow. We will provide an update if the official injury report reveals that Benson did indeed manage to participate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c67d-d82c-a79a-f7fd8fe30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6a3-d82c-a79a-f7b7154a0000</link>
      <description>Both Rodgers and Metcalf sat out on Wednesday. Their return to full participation puts them on track to play in Week 13 against the Bills. Opponents tend to attack the Bills’ soft run defense. Rodgers can be treated as a QB2. Metcalf is a borderline WR2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6a3-d82c-a79a-f7b7154a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR DK Metcalf (ankle) practiced full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6bb-d90e-a9da-dfbf1f000000</link>
      <description>Metcalf and Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) both sat out practice on Wednesday. Metcalf’s inactivity was a tad surprising. Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin initially told reporters that Metcalf would be “limited” early in the week. That is all in the rearview now. Metcalf’s full participation puts him on track to face the Bills this weekend. He is a borderline WR2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6bb-d90e-a9da-dfbf1f000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6c6-db57-afda-d6f64a570000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor stalls out in the limited column. He has a chance to play, but a return to full participation would have been great to see. The Titans’ rookie perimeter player would be a slightly risky FLEX option against the Jaguars if he can retake the field in Week 13. He sat out in Week 12 after failing to practice all week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6c6-db57-afda-d6f64a570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6cb-d82c-a79a-f7df141a0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo has played through this foot injury for weeks. Over the last two, he banked half-PPR TE11 and TE19 finishes. The downgrade is not encouraging and he does not need to be in fantasy lineups against the Jaguars in Week 13, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6cb-d82c-a79a-f7df141a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6cd-d82c-a79a-f7ddfa600000</link>
      <description>Finally, a positive update. Kincaid strained a hamstring in Week 10 against the Dolphins and has been unable to practice ever since. Today’s limited session does not guarantee he suits up in Week 13 against the Steelers. It could indicate the opposite, as he has not yet been cleared to practice fully. But it is a positive development nonetheless. If he can resume practicing in full tomorrow, he has a shot. Expect a return in Week 14 against a Bengals defense that has given up 962 receiving yards to opposing tight ends. They are the only defense to allow 800 or more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6cd-d82c-a79a-f7ddfa600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6da-db57-afda-d6fa457b0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is seemingly on track to retake the field this weekend against the Titans. While the matchup is hardly imposing, the Jaguars’ second-year wide receiver has been a colossal disappointment this season, and it is hard to believe his play will improve following a high-ankle sprain. He is theoretically a WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c6da-db57-afda-d6fa457b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
