<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eb7-d713-ad9e-fef7c8050000</link>
      <description>Godwin continues to work back from a fibula issue and was listed as limited in a Wednesday walk-through practice. He was limited in practice all of last week and now has a shot to play in Week 12 against the Rams. Godwin is still ramping up to full health and would be a fantasy WR4 should he return to play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eb7-d713-ad9e-fef7c8050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers EDGE Haason Reddick (ankle/knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eba-d45b-affe-dfbe287f0000</link>
      <description>Reddick has not been able to play since Week 7 and is not yet back at practice. Also not practicing on defense were Jamel Dean (hip) and Chris Braswell (foot). Dean is week-to-week with his injury while Braswell’s is new and Reddick does not have a timeline for his return. The Bucs defense will be sparse if neither of the three can suit up for Week 12 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9eba-d45b-affe-dfbe287f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ebe-d45b-affe-dfbec3010000</link>
      <description>Also limited due to illness were WR Emeka Egbuka, OG Dan Feeney, C Graham Barton, OT Luke Goedeke, and DE Logan Hall. The Bucs had a walk-through practice, so the designations are just estimates, but there seems to be a bug going around the team. Neither Mayfield, Egbuka, nor any of the others are in jeopardy of missing Week 12 against the Rams yet, but keep an eye out on the team’s practice statuses later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ebe-d45b-affe-dfbec3010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Sterling Shepard (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec4-d673-a39e-bed5e0800000</link>
      <description>Shepard and OT Tristan Wirfs popped up on the injury report with shoulder injuries on Wednesday. The Bucs held a walk-through, so practice designations were estimates, but still important to note. Shepard has a role as long as Chris Godwin (fibula) remains out, while Wirfs is the team’s franchise left tackle. Neither are in danger of missing Week 12 yet, barring setbacks later in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec4-d673-a39e-bed5e0800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks DT Johnathan Hankins (back) will not play this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec7-d713-ad9e-fed7ea3f0000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said on Wednesday that the 33-year-old Hankins will not play this season due to a back injury. Hankins has been dealing with the injury since July, landing on the non-football injury list. He was re-signed to a one-year deal by Seattle in the offseason, but he did not play and does not expect to play the rest of the 2025 season. Macdonald said, “I’ll probably just leave it private right now with what’s going on with his health, but he won’t be with us this year.” Hankins was a complimentary piece to the Seattle defensive line last year, but will now focus on getting healthy for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ec7-d713-ad9e-fed7ea3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking Wednesday, Bears coach Ben Johnson confirmed he believed Luther Burden has earned more playing time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9f8c-d713-ad9e-ffdcf91d0000</link>
      <description>“You get what you earn,” Johnson said. “And I think he’s earned the increased snaps. He’s steadily climbed.” It seems to be confirmation that Burden’s Week 11 ascension ahead of Olamide Zaccheaus will be a permanent feature. It seems like a long-overdue move, though Burden was always more raw as a prospect than some draftniks would have probably liked to admit. Burden is a big play waiting to happen with the ball in his hands, but it still takes some effort to get it there, while the Bears prefer a balanced approach on offense. Burden is growing more viable as a WR4, but he is still someone who is probably best left on 12-team league benches for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9f8c-d713-ad9e-ffdcf91d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Aaron Rodgers (left wrist) is expected to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a1bd-db57-afda-f7bff4690000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was held out of practice on Wednesday but should be back on the field today. As Rapoport notes, the issue is largely a matter of Rodgers’ ability to protect himself. The injury is to his left (non-throwing) wrist. The Steelers will get a better feel for that during today’s practice. Pittsburgh takes on Rodgers’ old rival, Chicago, this week. That matchup undoubtedly means a little more to the grizzled veteran, and we would bet he is pushing to play through the wrist injury for Week 12. Assuming he does suit up, Rodgers will remain a mid-range QB2 versus Chicago. Mason Rudolph would draw the start if Rodgers can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a1bd-db57-afda-f7bff4690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed EDGE Alex Wright to a three-year, $33 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a20a-d82c-a79a-b39e7c7c0000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Adam Schefter, the deal includes $21 million guaranteed. The former third-round pick is on the final year of his rookie deal. He has three sacks and 10 pressures in nine appearances this year. Wright is also owns Pro Football Focus’s No. 3 run defense grade for an EDGE. He is now under contract with the Browns through 2028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a20a-d82c-a79a-b39e7c7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) practiced on Thurdsay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a22a-d90e-a9da-bf2f32050000</link>
      <description>Chris Godwin was also spotted at practice. Both players were limited for Wednesday’s session. Irving practiced in a limited capacity last week, but the team has taken an extremely cautious approach with his return from the pair of injuries. He was held out of Week 11’s game and may need to get upgraded to a full session before the team clears him for action. Sean Tucker would be in line for lead-back duties if Irving is held out again. Rachaad White has been relegated to a backup role with extra work on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a22a-d90e-a9da-bf2f32050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a22d-d82c-a79a-b3bd6ab70000</link>
      <description>We will need to wait until the Bucs drop their official injury report to find out if it was a limited or full session for the veteran wideout. Godwin was listed as limited for Wednesday’s walkthrough. He hasn’t played since Week 5. A full session would put him on track to return this week while a limited tag would leave him as a coin flip for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a22d-d82c-a79a-b3bd6ab70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
