<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:29:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 6-of-6 targets for 46 yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db0d-db72-a199-fb4f6f210000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo tied for the lead in team targets and had one of the biggest plays of the day with a 20-yard reception in the fourth quarter. Okonkwo ran 31 routes while TE Gunnar Helm ran 15 routes and caught two of his three targets for 15 yards. With Sunday’s performance, Okonkwo now has three usable fantasy outings over his past four games and could be viable in deeper formats next week against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db0d-db72-a199-fb4f6f210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Jefferson caught 4-of-6 targets for 75 yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db14-db72-a199-fb5fd2020000</link>
      <description>Jefferson emerged as the Titans’ top pass catcher after Calvin Ridley left the game in the first half with a hamstring injury. Jefferson was targeted on a meager 17 percent of his pass routes but made the most of the opportunity. His 23-yard catch in the third quarter was the Titans’ longest play of the day in another muted offensive performance. Jefferson could be somewhat interesting in 14-team leagues if Ridley is sidelined for the team’s Week 7 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db14-db72-a199-fb5fd2020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 6-of-7 targets for 58 yards in San Francisco’s Week 6 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db14-d94a-a79d-db1d75940000</link>
      <description>The only answer the 49ers reliably had against the Todd Bowles blitz was the Tonges screen, and he managed 38 yards, 27 after the catch, when targeted on blitzes per TruMedia. Mac Jones had only nine passing yards on 11 dropbacks on blitzes when he didn’t target Tonges. The 49ers are one of the real life teams that truly scrapes new meaning out of the term week-to-week. Tonges’ status for Week 7 will depend on if George Kittle is ready to get activated off injured reserve or not. If Tonges starts, he can again remain a high-floor TE1 option against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db14-d94a-a79d-db1d75940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquez Valdes-Scantling caught 2-of-3 targets for 22 yards in San Francisco’s Week 6 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db18-db72-a199-fb5b1abe0000</link>
      <description>Valdes-Scantling played 41 of 68 snaps, distancing himself from Demarcus Robinson (13), but the two finished with roughly identical target lines. It feels like the 49ers want him on the field, but MVS probably won’t have a real shot at fantasy value in Week 7 without Jauan Jennings sitting and the rest of San Francisco’s passing game weapons (Pearsall, Kittle) remaining sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db18-db72-a199-fb5b1abe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 5-of-6 targets for 51 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 6 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db1a-def2-abdb-df7bcc030000</link>
      <description>That’s 11 targets in two weeks for Otton, who the Buccaneers have relied on more without Mike Evans. It’s impossible to peg Tampa’s receiving room now that we’re dealing with three different major injuries to their main wideouts, so it’s hard to say what opportunity Otton will have next week until we see who else is playing. But on paper he certainly would appear to be a viable TE1 for Week 7’s Monday night showdown against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db1a-def2-abdb-df7bcc030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pollard had ten rushes for 34 yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders, adding two catches for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db1a-db72-a199-fb5b44640000</link>
      <description>Pollard out-carried Tyjae Spears, who had five rushes, but lost out on the primary pass-catching role out of the Tennessee backfield. Pollard ran fewer routes than Spears and saw just two targets to Spears’ four targets. It’s an ugly backfield split in an offense that won’t produce much in the way of yards or touchdowns. Pollard, who had 17 touches last week against the Cardinals, will be a flex play in 14-teams leagues in Week 7 against an improving Patriots defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db1a-db72-a199-fb5b44640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 3-of-5 targets for 27 yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db21-def2-abdb-df61e7d70000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor surprisingly didn’t take on the team’s WR1 role after Calvin Ridley left the game in the first half with a hamstring injury. It was Van Jefferson who led Titans wideouts with 75 yards on four receptions with Ridley sidelined. After a promising start to the season, Ayomanor has faded into the background of the Titans’ lifeless passing attack and can be left on waiver wires this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db21-def2-abdb-df61e7d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sterling Shepard caught 2-of-3 targets for 51 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 6 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db21-dd4c-afb9-ffe1bde90000</link>
      <description>The 36-yard strike that Shepard had in the fourth quarter amounted to more yards than the veteran receiver had in either Week 4 or Week 5. More of a zone-buster at this stage of his career, he would seem to be a tough fit in Week 7’s matchup against the aggressive Lions. Then again, he also might be the most veteran receiver left in the room if rehabs go poorly in the run-up to Monday night. Tampa’s injury report leaves the whole situation as something that’s hard to forecast so far out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db21-dd4c-afb9-ffe1bde90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears had five rushes for 31 yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders, adding four catches for 19 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db26-def2-abdb-df6711f80000</link>
      <description>Spears was far more efficient than Tony Pollard, who had 34 yards on 10 rushing attempts against Vegas. Spears operated as the primary pass catching back, running more routes and seeing more targets than Pollard. It was far more action than Spears saw last week against the Cardinals (four carries, no targets). Though Spears likely has more juice than Pollard, he won’t be a reliable 12-team fantasy lineups unless Pollard misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db26-def2-abdb-df6711f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tez Johnson caught 1-of-3 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 6 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db28-dd4c-afb9-ffe935f00000</link>
      <description>If you’re going to make only one catch, make it a wildly impressive 45-yard post deep strike that lands you in the end zone. Johnson’s target count was a bit curious given his 4/59 line last week and the loss of Emeka Egbuka, but he was simply outJohnsoned in this one. Johnson certainly seems like the safer bet of himself and (Kameron) Johnson to continue to function in this offense based on the snap counts. But he was not the one that finished with the best line in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db28-dd4c-afb9-ffe935f00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
