<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 21:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 30-of-46 passes for 287 yards, one touchdown and an interception in the Patriots’ 20-13, Week 1 loss to the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ef-dbe3-a9bb-35ffa40e0000</link>
      <description>Maye also had a fumble the Pats luckily recovered, and an “incomplete pass” that certainly looked like another fumble. It was an unimpressive performance, one where Maye struggled with his accuracy. He took four sacks. Coach Mike Vrabel said afterward he wanted a more balanced offense to take pressure off his young signal caller. The Pats handed the ball off to running backs just 13 times vs. the Raiders. Not exactly what fantasy managers want to hear, though this is not a team that should be throwing 46 times. We’ll see if tension ends up surfacing between run-minded Vrabel and pass-obsessed OC Josh McDaniels. New England visits Miami for Week 2. Considering how awful the Dolphins’ defense was in Indy, Maye will still have some streamer juice for that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ef-dbe3-a9bb-35ffa40e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Fred Warner returned to Week 1 against the Seahawks after visiting the blue medical tent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25eb-de13-afdd-67eba4940000</link>
      <description>Warner appears to be ready to rock after briefly visiting the blue medical tent. Warner landed hard on the right side of his chest and jogged off the field under his own power. He returned later in the drive, in time to watch Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet punch in a one-yard rushing touchdown, bringing the game up to a 7-7 tie in the first quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25eb-de13-afdd-67eba4940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanner Conner caught 2-of-4 targets for 20 yards in a Week 1 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f0-de13-afdd-67fb83ae0000</link>
      <description>With Darren Waller inactive for Week 1, it was Conner who served as the Dolphins’ top tight end. It didn’t amount to much on the statsheet, but he could be a name to monitor in two-tight-end leagues if Waller continues to miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f0-de13-afdd-67fb83ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow completed 14-of-23 passes for 113 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ 17-16, Week 1 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25e5-dbe3-a9bb-35f7e2830000</link>
      <description>Bengals head coach Zac Taylor played his starters in the preseason for the first time in years to help the team exorcise their slow start demons. While Cincy did come away with the one, it wasn’t a pretty one despite facing a rebuilding Browns club. Burrow and the passing game couldn’t get much going downfield and instead settled for nine completions to the running backs and tight ends with just five combined catches for Tee Higgins and Ja’Marr Chase. Burrow also took three sacks, all three of which came on a single drive in the fourth quarter. He and the offense should rebound in Week 2 versus the Jags, keeping him well within the QB1 ranks for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25e5-dbe3-a9bb-35f7e2830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-6 targets for 67 yards and two touchdowns in the Bucs’ Week 1 win against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ee-de13-afdd-67ef0ce30000</link>
      <description>Egbuka came through after months of hype surrounding the first-round wideout, catching the game-winning score from Baker Mayfield on a perfectly-placed seam ball over the head of the Atlanta safety. The rookie’s 19 percent target share was second on the team behind Mike Evans (25 percent). He made the most of his opportunities, and gained nine yards on a first half rushing attempt on a designed touch behind the line of scrimmage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ee-de13-afdd-67ef0ce30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleb Johnson rushed one time for minus-two yards in Steelers’ Week 1 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ef-db7b-a5dd-a5ef103c0000</link>
      <description>On the bright side, he did draw a 15-yard penalty for being hit out of bounds on his first NFL carry. He played just two snaps. Johnson doesn’t necessarily need to be dropped — he’ll likely make in-roads over the first month or so of the season — but he certainly can be in smaller leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ef-db7b-a5dd-a5ef103c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 7-of-9 targets for 76 yards in a Week 1 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f2-db7b-a5dd-a5f6831b0000</link>
      <description>Warren was exactly as advertised in his NFL debut. Daniel Jones looked to him often over the middle of the field, and Warren showed the ability to avoid tackles or run through them once he had the ball in his hands. The Colts also got creative and lined Warren up as a fullback in the red zone, so it’s clear that the team wants to get him involved in multiple ways. He should remain on the TE1 radar all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f2-db7b-a5dd-a5f6831b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson caught 7-of-9 targets for 95 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 1 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f4-de13-afdd-67ffefc20000</link>
      <description>He did drop his final target on fourth down, sealing the Jets’ defeat, but we doubt fantasy managers are upset about that. Wilson showed plenty in burning Darius Slay for a long score in the first quarter, and managed fantasy viability despite the Jets rarely showing interest in throwing the ball. Wilson will be on the WR2 line in Week 2 against the Bills, who have plenty of issues of their own at cornerback heading into Sunday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f4-de13-afdd-67ffefc20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Ekeler rushed six times for 26 yards in the Commanders’ Week 1 win over the Giants, adding three receptions for 31 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f2-de13-afdd-67fbb37b0000</link>
      <description>Ekeler saw nine total opportunities in the game, with seven of those looks coming in the first half. The veteran running back drew the start for the Commanders on Sunday and was rather efficient with his touches (6.3 YPT), but he played backup to rookie Jacory Croskey-Merritt in the second half. Ekeler should continue to have a role in the passing game, but he saw one carry to Croskey-Merrit’s six in the second half. Ekeler’s age and injury history have long foreshadowed a third-down role for him in 2025, and Croskey-Merritt’s performance on Sunday isn’t going to do anything to change that opinion. Ekeler will have some PPR upside in Week 2 against the Packers, but it would be surprising if he drew the start on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f2-de13-afdd-67fbb37b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught his only target for 20 yards in the Jets’ Week 1 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f7-dbe3-a9bb-35f7b0c50000</link>
      <description>He actually was out-targeted by Jeremy Ruckert (2/16) but neither Jets tight end looks likely to generate fantasy value unless the team trails for most of the game. The rookie could be interesting in a different game script, but doesn’t need to be rostered in shallow leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25f7-dbe3-a9bb-35f7b0c50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
