<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers agreed to terms with former Raiders DC Patrick Graham to the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cc3-dead-af9e-6cc717990000</link>
      <description>The news was broken by Josina Anderson. Graham is only 47 years old but is becoming a coordinating lifer, spending the past four years in Vegas and a year in Miami before that. A Bill Belichick acolyte, Graham’s Steelers connection comes from his year on Mike McCarthy’s Packers staff in 2018. The Raiders’ defense was not “the problem” for the Silver and Black last season, but it certainly wasn’t the solution, either. Graham will have more to work with in the Steel City. It’s not a needle-moving hire, but it’s not a bad move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cc3-dead-af9e-6cc717990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Giants will interview Chargers QBs coach Shane Day for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cde-dead-af9e-6cdf3e830000</link>
      <description>Schultz claims Day was a “serious candidate” for an L.A. promotion before head coach Jim Harbaugh eventually settled on big-named organizational outsider Mike McDaniel. Coaching in the NFL or FBS since 2006, Day has spent most of his time in the big leagues, including time on Kyle Shanahan’s staff. He has never been a play-caller or offensive coordinator, while this would make for an unusual jump from one brother’s staff to another. John might be wondering why he wasn’t good enough for Jim’s job, but we digress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cde-dead-af9e-6cdf3e830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills hired former Broncos senior offensive assistant Pete Carmichael as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f0b-d89c-a1be-afdf6d800000</link>
      <description>Carmichael spent two seasons working with new Bills head coach Joe Brady in New Orleans (2017-2018), when Carmichael was the Saints’ offensive coordinator. Carmichael joined the Broncos in 2024 and won’t be tasked with calling plays in Buffalo after Brady said he would continue to oversee play-calling duties. Carmichael provides a strong veteran presence in the building and has been part of several successful offenses with Sean Payton and Drew Brees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f0b-d89c-a1be-afdf6d800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles hired former Buccaneers OC Josh Grizzard as pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f52-d89c-a1be-afdf48740000</link>
      <description>The Eagles passed on Grizzard for their offensive-coordinator vacancy when they decided to hire Sean Mannion, but apparently liked enough of what they heard to pair him with Mannion this upcoming season. Grizzard served as the Buccaneers’ pass game coordinator during the 2024 season, when they finished sixth in yards per attempt and ranked in the top three in both passing yards (4,257) and passing touchdowns (41). He and Mannion take over an Eagles offense that finished 13th in yards per attempt last season, but ranked just 26th in total pass attempts. Hopefully, these moves lead to more pass attempts and a more aggressive down field attack for Jalen Hurts and company in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f52-d89c-a1be-afdf48740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Ravens run game coordinator Travis Switzer is considered the favorite to fill the Browns’ offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f73-d355-a5bd-8f7757330000</link>
      <description>Switzer has spent the last three seasons as the Ravens’ run game coordinator. The ninth-year coach didn’t have much trouble producing with the combination of Derrick Henry and Lamar Jackson, but he will have a new challenge in front of him if he lands the job with the Browns. Switzer has never served as an offensive coordinator, although we would expect head coach Todd Monken to serve as the team’s primary play-caller regardless of who is brought in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f73-d355-a5bd-8f7757330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Todd Monken told Shedeur Sanders “we tried to draft” you in the 2025 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f8b-d042-afbc-7fdb7f7c0000</link>
      <description>We’re cleaning up the exact quote a bit, but regardless, Monken’s comments confirmed a report from last season that the Ravens attempted to draft Sanders only for Sanders and his team to say he didn’t want to be Lamar Jackson’s backup. As Monken also mentioned in a video that can be found on the Browns’ socials, “it’s all worked out” now for Monken and Sanders, who, for now, are paired together for the 2026 season. Sanders struggled mightily as a rookie last season and the Browns are expected to add at least one quarterback to their room this season, per ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler. While he shouldn’t be considered a lock to open next season as the Browns’ starter, it appears Monken had some genuine interest in the former fifth-round pick, which could be a good sign for his future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f8b-d042-afbc-7fdb7f7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL has said it will “consider possible tweaks” to its kickoff format after an increased concussion rate in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f99-d89c-a1be-afdf57040000</link>
      <description>This comes from the Washington Post’s Mark Maske, who notes that the concussion rate on kickoffs was higher than on plays at the line of scrimmage. NFL Executive Vice President Jeff Miller said the league feels “good about the progress, but there’s more work to do” to improve the kickoff moving forward. This will be something to watch for after the season winds down and the league begins to more closely review rule changes for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0f99-d89c-a1be-afdf57040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns hired former Ravens run game coordinator Travis Switzer as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0fca-d042-afbc-7fda283b0000</link>
      <description>Shortly after, it was rumored that Switzer was the favorite to land the job; the former Ravens run game coordinator is now set to be the Browns’ OC. Switzer has spent the last three seasons working alongside Todd Monken in Baltimore, and the hope is that his knowledge of the run game, paired with Monken’s explosive passing attack, can improve an offense that ranked 31st in scoring and 30th in total yards last season. This is only one piece of the puzzle that Monken and the Browns need to figure out, as they still have plenty to do to address quarterback, offensive line, and receiver, but Switzer now has his first gig as an offensive coordinator and will continue to grow alongside Monken in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0fca-d042-afbc-7fda283b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers HC Mike McCarthy said he believes the team has “a playoff roster” already assembled.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0fe8-d355-a5bd-8ffc9ee90000</link>
      <description>There’s certainly no denying the Steelers made the playoffs in 2025, but with no quarterback of note on the team and no notable receiver behind DK Metcalf on the depth chart, it’s hard to definitively say the Steelers have a playoff roster in place for next season. Add in two aging veterans on the defensive side in Cam Heyward and T.J. Watt and things get even more complicated. That said, McCarthy said he does not view the Steelers’ job as “a start-over opportunity,” so it will be interesting to see what the team’s roster turnover looks like in the coming months. As was the case with Mike Tomlin for several years, the Steelers still have to find a quarterback who can be a mainstay on the roster for more than two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0fe8-d355-a5bd-8ffc9ee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings fired GM Kwesi Adofo-Mensah.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1000-d424-a3fd-f718b6e70000</link>
      <description>The Vikings signed Adofo-Mensah to a multi-year extension last offseason and sent him to the Senior Bowl earlier this week. The move comes as a major surprise, but per The Athletic’s Alec Lewis, there “had been a lot, a lot, a lot of noise in recent weeks.” Adofo-Mensah was hired as the Vikings’ general manager in 2022 and oversaw the team’s last four free agent and draft classes. His extension came after he helped build the Vikings into a 14-3 team that unexpectedly rode the arm of Sam Darnold to the postseason, but the decision to let Darnold walk in the offseason coupled with the struggles of second-year pick J.J. McCarthy are likely one of a handful of decisions made my Adofo-Mensah that ultimately led to his dismissal. With their GM spot now vacant, the Vikings have even more to figure out heading into an offseason that was already going to be headlined by a quarterback controversy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1000-d424-a3fd-f718b6e70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
