<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders requested an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b395-d968-a19b-fbf5b9110000</link>
      <description>That makes four interview requests for Minter, who already has heard from the Ravens, Titans, and Browns. He’s the seventh name on Las Vegas’ interview request list, joining Packers DC Jeff Hafley, Broncos DC Vance Joseph, Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak, Chiefs OC Matt Nagy, Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase and Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb. Minter’s defense did great work last night against Drake Maye, even if it ultimately didn’t lead to a win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b395-d968-a19b-fbf5b9110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Bailey Zappe to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b398-d56e-afff-f7f8e3e40000</link>
      <description>Zappe has the roster-joining ability of a young Tim Boyle. The Jets will hope to never have to go to Plan Zappe in a real game, though until they solve the position we guess we’re at “anything is possible.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b398-d56e-afff-f7f8e3e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ad-d35e-a1bf-f7efd05a0000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury has only been connected to the Titans and Ravens so far after the Commanders unceremoniously dumped him to elevate David Blough to offensive coordinator. We have not yet heard about any itinerary for Thailand for Kingsbury. It seems more likely that he finds a spot as an offensive coordinator than a head coach based on the early interest, but we’re not quite at the section of the offseason where Kingsbury is in danger of running out of spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ad-d35e-a1bf-f7efd05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers interviewed Lions assistant special teams coach Jett Modkins for their special teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3b0-d35e-a1bf-f7f229010000</link>
      <description>It’s the second interview for Jett Modkins in the coveted special teams coordinator cycle. We have blurbed both of them because it’s very pleasing to type Jett Modkins. Try it. The Buccaneers fired Thomas McGaughey after a season that concluded with them kicking the ball into the end zone because they were scared of returns (Todd Bowles’ actual words) and are likely hoping that Jett Modkins has answers for that. Jett Modkins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3b0-d35e-a1bf-f7f229010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview Cowboys DL coach Aaron Whitecotton for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ca-d968-a19b-fbfb57bf0000</link>
      <description>Whitecotton, who came over from the Jets staff under Robert Saleh, was reportedly instrumental in the Quinnen Williams trade. It is not known how Whitecotton would call a room as he has no NFL defensive coordinator experience, however, he’s not Matt Eberflus, so he has that going for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ca-d968-a19b-fbfb57bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Browns DC Jim Schwartz for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3cd-d35e-a1bf-f7cf19390000</link>
      <description>They were late to the game, but the Ravens are by our count now up to 12 head-coaching candidate interviews, trailing the Titans by four. Schwartz had an in-house interview with the Browns about a head-coaching elevation last week. He otherwise has not been contacted by an outside team. The former Lions head coach has been an excellent defensive coordinator over his last few stints in Philadelphia and Cleveland. This has shades of the return of Wade Phillips.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3cd-d35e-a1bf-f7cf19390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed WR Ainias Smith, G Ja’Tyre Carter, G Saahdiq Charles, WR Dan Chisena, RB Montrell Johnson, OLB Jamil Muhammad, LB Maz Mwansa, TE Bryce Pierre, WR Ja’seem Reed, S Demani Richardson, RB Anthony Tyus, LB Jacoby Windmon, LB Jared Bartlett, CB Tyrek Funderburk and G Joshua Gray to reserve/futures deals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3d1-d968-a19b-fbf14f250000</link>
      <description>The former fifth-round Eagles wideout did not have any NFL playing time in 2024 after a 7/41/1 debut for the Eagles in 2024. He spent the whole year with the Panthers practice squad and could have a chance to battle with lower-rung receivers like Brycen Tremayne for a roster spot in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3d1-d968-a19b-fbf14f250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Jaguars OC Grant Udinski for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3d5-dc7a-af9b-ffff89db0000</link>
      <description>Previously on Kevin O’Connell’s staff with Minnesota, Udinski took over as Jaguars offensive coordinator last offseason and appears to be on a rocket ship up the coaching ranks. The Jaguars struggled at the beginning of season, but eventually ended the year as one of the better offenses in the NFL. Udinski has no real playcalling experience as Liam Coen was Jacksonville’s playcaller and the (sigh) 30-year-old had never been higher than a lower level assistant prior to the 2024 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3d5-dc7a-af9b-ffff89db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes the Titans are “firmly in the mix” for former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3e5-d56e-afff-f7ed4c520000</link>
      <description>A source tells Garafolo that Harbaugh likes “Cam Ward, $100m+ in cap space, high picks, new stadium, GM Mike Borgonzi.” The rest of the Titans roster, which feels downright barren, somehow is not mentioned in this rundown. But the fact that the sources are coming out on the timeline leads us to believe that when the Harbaugh interview roses go out, the Titans may still be in contention to grab one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3e5-d56e-afff-f7ed4c520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ec-d56e-afff-f7ec996f0000</link>
      <description>It’s the first known interview for Harbaugh, who apparently did not leak his schedule to the entire insider crew at NFL Network. It would make sense for him to view this as one of the most appealing jobs out there despite the unsettled nature of the quarterback position, as the Falcons tied for the NFC South “lead” at 8-9 this year and have stars like Bijan Robinson and Drake London on tap along with a rising defense. We suspect we’ll be blurbing a lot more about this Harbaugh character over the next few days. He seems to be the first domino for most coaching searches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ec-d56e-afff-f7ec996f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
