<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh declined to address whether Najee Harris (eye) could begin the regular season on the reserve/non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</link>
      <description>When asked about Harris’ potential placement on the reserve/NFI list, Harbaugh danced his way around the answer by saying, “when Najee is ready to play, Najee will be ready to play.” He then told reporters that speculation regarding Harris’ status beyond “today” goes “over the legal limit of what-ifs.” This is not reassuring. If Harris begins the year on the reserve/NFI list, he will be required to sit out at least four games. Omarion Hampton is an RB2 with RB1 upside. Fantasy managers can treat rookie RB Raheim Sanders as a late-round bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris is expected to miss Thursday’s practice after leaving Wednesday’s practice early due to “tightness.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</link>
      <description>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh is being his typical, tight-lipped self on this one. Missing time is unideal for Harris, who has failed to secure the team’s X-receiver role. Harris will be afforded plenty more opportunities to secure a starting role, given his second-round draft capital. He should only be considered a dart throw in re-draft at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston (neck) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce3c-de13-afdc-ceffb6740000</link>
      <description>Johnston suffered the injury five days ago. His return coincides with Tre’ Harris’ (tightness) sidelining. Although Johnston has disappointed through two NFL seasons, he has yet another chance to secure a starting role in three-wide receiver sets. He will have a tough time reliably returning flex value, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce3c-de13-afdc-ceffb6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Tre’Davious White left practice early on Thursday after suffering an apparent leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdef-db7b-a5dd-edeffeb30000</link>
      <description>White reportedly hopped on one leg, over to Bills’ trainers, before being carted to the locker room. No word on the injury’s specifics yet. Fellow CB Christian Benford exited practice early as well, though he later said he is okay and “just needed some rest.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdef-db7b-a5dd-edeffeb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints announced QB Spencer Rattler will start in preseason Week 3 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce44-d332-a1fd-de76e5710000</link>
      <description>Saints quarterbacks have looked great, playing against backups through two preseason games. Last week, Rattler was the one who starred in the second half. Entering the third preseason game as the starter could suggest that Rattler has slightly pulled ahead of rookie QB Tyler Shough, though the Saints would likely prefer to have their new second-round pick win the role. Regardless, neither player is re-draft-relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce44-d332-a1fd-de76e5710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur addressed trade rumors regarding Romeo Doubs by saying, “that will not happen.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce7f-db7b-a5dd-ee7fd9460000</link>
      <description>LaFleur then explained why the organization is not open to trading Doubs, saying, “Rome is out there competing” and has done “everything that we need to see from him.” The team suspended Doubs for one game last year, after the veteran receiver complained about his target rate. It sounds like the two sides are in a good spot. Doubs is set to continue operating as a Packers starter and profiles as a matchup-based flex option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce7f-db7b-a5dd-ee7fd9460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen will not play in the Bills’ preseason Week 3 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cea4-db7b-a5dd-eea4e08e0000</link>
      <description>This is the first time in Allen’s NFL career in which he has not, and will not, play at all in the preseason. Allen said he would “appreciate” preseason reps but does not believe that he needs them. We agree. As Bills head coach Sean McDermott notes, Allen is the NFL’s reigning MVP. He finished as the overall QB2 in fantasy scoring last year and can be considered a contender for the overall QB1 spot this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cea4-db7b-a5dd-eea4e08e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones said, in his “mind,” the “term, amount, guarantees, everything” for Micah Parsons’ potential extension were established without Parsons’ agent present.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</link>
      <description>Jones’ statement effectively validates the timeline of events that Parsons outlined in a social media post. Parsons’ agent was not present for the private discussion in which Jones says the contract was negotiated, and Jones takes issue with the agent’s attempts to “improve off the mark that we’d already set.” These are bizarre circumstances. Agents are hired to represent players in contract negotiations. Jones seemingly disagrees with that practice in this specific instance. The two sides need to resolve this issue soon, ostensibly with Parsons’ agent involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Riley Leonard will start in preseason Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cee3-d332-a1fd-def7a05a0000</link>
      <description>The sixth-round rookie quarterback is expected to play throughout the first half. Per FOX59’s Mike Chappell, “the vast majority of the Colts’ other front-line players and top backups” will not play. Depending on how the season unfolds, Leonard could see playing time at some point this year, though that would likely mean something has gone terribly awry. Leonard is a capable rusher. Flashing improved arm talent against the Bengals could increase his stock in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cee3-d332-a1fd-def7a05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philly Voice’s Jimmy Kempski reports that Eagles WR Jahan Dotson “seems to have earned” Jalen Hurts’ trust.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef5-de13-afdc-ceffecbe0000</link>
      <description>A.J. Brown (hamstring) and DeVonta Smith (groin) have both missed time in training camp, affording Dotson the opportunity to catch passes “in bulk.” The Eagles’ No. 3 wide receiver reportedly “had a great close to camp” after a “quiet start.” Kempski is now the second beat reporter this month to suggest that Dotson will contribute more than he did last year, though Dotson set the bar quite low. If Brown, Smith and Dallas Goedert are on the field, fantasy managers should not expect Dotson to reliably produce. He could return flex value if Brown and Smith’s soft tissue injuries remain an issue in-season, though, and No. 4 WR Johnny Wilson (knee/ankle) is set to undergo season-ending surgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef5-de13-afdc-ceffecbe0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
