<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (finger) is not on Jacksonville’s final Week 18 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d56e-afff-e6e9a69a0000</link>
      <description>Tuten has missed two weeks after having finger surgery, but looks like he’ll be available for Week 18. The Jaguars could give him a real run if they happen to script the Titans into submission early. If the Titans make a game of it, they’ll probably stick with Travis Etienne for the majority of the game. Tuten still has a little RB3 steam if active, especially given the Jaguars being 13.5-point favorites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d56e-afff-e6e9a69a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said he does not expect WR Tory Horton (shin) to resume playing this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-809c-dc7a-af9b-cfbf2a6c0000</link>
      <description>Horton reportedly injured his shin while rehabbing a groin injury in Week 10, just two days after the Seahawks acquired WR Rashid Shaheed via trade. It was an extremely unfortunate series of events for the young, speedy receiver and return specialist. Horton never retook the field after that. In Weeks 1-9, Horton caught 13-of-22 targets for 161 yards and five touchdowns. He also returned 16 punts for 238 yards and one touchdown. In Week 3, Horton set the franchise record for the longest punt return in Seahawks history, a 95-yard touchdown, and became the third Seahawk ever to score a punt return touchdown and a receiving touchdown in the same game. Horton’s fantasy viability in 2026 remains uncertain. The team could choose to re-sign Shaheed, an impending free agent, and WR Cooper Kupp is under contract through 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-809c-dc7a-af9b-cfbf2a6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DL Jalen Carter (hip) won’t play in Philadelphia’s Week 18 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a8-d35e-a1bf-c5ea966e0000</link>
      <description>Carter, Jaelan Phillips (ankle), and Nakobe Dean (hamstring) were all ruled out and should all get better around the time Philadelphia’s first Wild Card playoff report comes out. Until then, it will be Philadelphia’s reserves dealing with Josh Johnson, Chris Rodriguez, and “Bill” Croskey-Merritt. Week 18 is here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a8-d35e-a1bf-c5ea966e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts ruled out QB Anthony Richardson (eye) for Week 18 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a9-d56e-afff-e6e9aeaa0000</link>
      <description>Richardson’s season comes to a close. He completed 1-of-2 passes for nine yards and rushed four times for minus-one yard. The 23-year-old now has three lost seasons under his belt. In August, Richardson reportedly lost a “very close” battle to Daniel Jones for the Colts’ starting quarterback job. Things only got worse from there. Richardson’s agent told reporters that trust in the organization had been lost and a report in early October indicated that Richardson “would be open to joining a premier play caller such as Sean McVay as a developmental player so he can reset for 2026.” That scenario never came to fruition. Richardson suffered an eye injury and an orbital fracture during a pre-game elastic band workout in Week 6. Jones’ season-ending Achilles tendon rupture could afford Richardson another opportunity to compete for the starting job in 2026, though. Richardson’s potential range of outcomes remains wide as ever, heading into the new year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a9-d56e-afff-e6e9aeaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) won’t play in Philadelphia’s Week 18 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80aa-d968-a19b-d8fbd0420000</link>
      <description>Johnson hasn’t played or practiced since Week 11, but did show up at the facility today. He will almost certainly try to give it a go in the Wild Card Round, but with no practice sessions it may be touch-and-go for Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80aa-d968-a19b-d8fbd0420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) will not play in Philadelphia’s Week 18 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80ae-d35e-a1bf-c5ee3dd70000</link>
      <description>Grant Calcaterra! Tanner McKee! It’s not quite the UFL, but you wouldn’t know it! We expect Goedert to be healthy for Philadelphia’s first Wild Card round injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80ae-d35e-a1bf-c5ee3dd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll declined to say whether Kenny Pickett or Aidan O’Connell will start against the Chiefs in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7ac10000</link>
      <description>Has anyone tried asking the Raiders to be normal? We’re just asking questions here. Carroll said both players would play. Neither player is worth rostering in superflex leagues in Week 18. O’Connell has probably performed like a better quarterback but spent all season buried on the depth chart for reasons that defy rational explanation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7ac10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d35e-a1bf-c5e36fce0000</link>
      <description>The Broncos will have their rookie wide receiver on the field as they attempt to retain the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed this week. Bryant has finished exactly as the half-PPR WR45 in each of his last three games and can be treated as a WR4 accordingly this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80a1-d35e-a1bf-c5e36fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (illness) is doubtful to play in Week 18 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e6-d968-a19b-d8f7aa530000</link>
      <description>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid initially said Worthy would be listed as questionable to play. Instead, the team lists him as doubtful. We do not expect him to play. The Chiefs will likely attempt to run out the clock in a lost season against the lowly Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80e6-d968-a19b-d8f7aa530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (illness) is not on the injury report for Week 18 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80eb-d56e-afff-e6ebf3b70000</link>
      <description>Carter returned to practice on Friday, logging a limited session. Giants DL Dexter Lawrence (illness) was also removed from the injury report, though he did not resume practicing. We tentatively expect both players to be on the field for Week 18, but projecting their snap counts is tough. The Giants and Cowboys have both been eliminated from playoff contention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-80eb-d56e-afff-e6ebf3b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
