<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said WR Jalen McMillan (neck) is “going to miss some time” in the regular season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c31c-dbe3-a9bb-f35fc3d00000</link>
      <description>McMillan landed awkwardly on a diving grab during last week’s preseason tilt against the Steelers and suffered what Bowles described as a “severely strained neck” that will cost him regular season games. Bowles said the neck injury shouldn’t threaten McMillan’s playing career. McMillan’s absence and the likely absence of Chris Godwin (ankle) means Mike Evans and Emeka Egbuka will dominate looks from Baker Mayfield. Trey Palmer now has a chance to work as Tampa’s WR3 for the early part of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c31c-dbe3-a9bb-f35fc3d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers (back) returned to practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c337-d332-a1fd-d737c6ed0000</link>
      <description>Nabers has dealt with a variety of offseason injuries, including a toe issue that began during his college days at LSU. He had missed practice recently with shoulder and back issues. The Giants are being very careful with their dominant WR1 head of the team’s Week 1 matchup with the Commanders. Look for the Giants to continue managing Nabers’ workload ahead of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c337-d332-a1fd-d737c6ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Cam Skattebo (hamstring) returned to practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c33b-dbe3-a9bb-f37b5efb0000</link>
      <description>Skattebo, who struggled with soft tissue injuries in college, missed two weeks of practice with a serious hamstring injury. That gave Tyrone Tracy a path to establishing himself as the Giants’ No. 1 running back ahead of the team’s season opener against Washington. ESPN’s Jordan Raanan said Tracy would “100 percent” function as the Giants’ lead back in 2025, with Skattebo operating a complement. That could include pass catching duties, as Skattebo was one of the nation’s best pass-catching backs at Arizona State last season. The rookie will have a chance to carve out a larger role as the season wears on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c33b-dbe3-a9bb-f37b5efb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) was activated off the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c341-d332-a1fd-d77754c70000</link>
      <description>Thomas is expected to make his return to practice in hopes of being ready to go for Week 1 against Washington. Thomas has been sidelined while rehabbing from a foot injury he sustained last October. His loss was a big one for the Giants, graded in 2024 as Pro Football Focus’ third worst pass-blocking offensive line. A fully healthy Thomas would be a boon for Russell Wilson and the rest of the New York offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c341-d332-a1fd-d77754c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Maxwell Hairston (knee) is “a ways away” from beginning a ramping up process.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c346-db7b-a5dd-e346facb0000</link>
      <description>It sure sounds like there’s a real chance Hairston opens up on injured reserve after spraining his knee early in training camp. Buffalo might have Tre’Davious White or Dane Jackson running next to incumbents Christian Benford and Taron Johnson in nickel sets to open the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c346-db7b-a5dd-e346facb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes the Cowboys and EDGE Micah Parsons are “headed towards divorce in time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c349-d332-a1fd-d77fa5400000</link>
      <description>Schefter adds “it sounds like at this point it’s personal.” Since Parsons’ trade request earlier in August, we haven’t had much in the way of real news updates, and Schefter says both sides haven’t negotiated since April. “The only question is when is that divorce going to happen, and how is it going to happen?” Schefter continues. There are very few non-quarterbacks who could be traded and cause a monumental shift before the season started, but Parsons qualifies. We’ve yet to blurb about any teams directly linked to acquiring Parsons, but it would likely take at least a first-round pick — and probably more than just that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c349-d332-a1fd-d77fa5400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said that it is “hard to say” there’s a future in Indianapolis for Anthony Richardson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c34f-dbe3-a9bb-f35f45980000</link>
      <description>“Obviously, Daniel (Jones) is our starter right now. And if something happens to Daniel at some point, AR gets another opportunity,” Steichen continued. It’s not exactly a smoking gun statement, but it is damning about Richardson’s chances of playing this season that Steichen couldn’t even give a token pushback on the question. If the Colts truly aren’t married to Richardson, it’s possible that they get a trade offer they can’t refuse at cutdowns for the former No. 4 overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c34f-dbe3-a9bb-f35f45980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Jalen McMillan will be placed on injured reserve and could be out “past the Bucs Week 9 bye.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c355-dbe3-a9bb-f35754470000</link>
      <description>We’ve gone from McMillan “avoiding anything major” to him being out half the season through the last two days. McMillan starting on IR will give runway to Emeka Egbuka to be a major contributor to Tampa Bay’s offense immediately. It also may give supporting options like Cade Otton more of a share than they’d normally have as Tampa threads the needle early without McMillan and Chris Godwin. McMillan isn’t a must-hold in shallow leagues based on this reported timeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c355-dbe3-a9bb-f35754470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mailata (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c375-dbe3-a9bb-f3776afd0000</link>
      <description>Even if he’d been healthy, it’s hard to believe the Eagles would have let Mailata play in the preseason finale anyway. He will probably be fine for Week 1, but brain injuries are no laughing matter and there are a few every season that turn into extended absences. The Eagles will obviously give their star left tackle all the time he needs to recover ahead of the season opener against Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c375-dbe3-a9bb-f3776afd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released RB J.J. Taylor.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c377-d332-a1fd-d777b2d90000</link>
      <description>Taylor appeared in five games last year, rushing 10 times for 44 yards, and has yet to receiver more than 23 carries in an NFL season. The 27-year-old will look to catch on elsewhere on a practice squad or on the backend of a roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c377-d332-a1fd-d777b2d90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
