<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (hip) is active for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97ae-dca3-a9fb-bfbfe12b0000</link>
      <description>Mims was a late-week addition to the team’s injury report with a hip injury Saturday, ultimately doing enough in pre-game workouts to be active against the Bengals. His presence is more of a boost to the offense than boon to his individual fantasy value considering his downfield, yet limited, role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97ae-dca3-a9fb-bfbfe12b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Braelon Allen (knee) headed to locker room Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97b1-d95b-addb-fff794170000</link>
      <description>Allen was hit hard in the knee during a kickoff return in the second quarter, eventually taken to the locker room ahead of the half. There has yet to be an update passed by the team but it certainly appears as if his night is done. Allen gained 26 yards on four carries and lost a fumble at the goal line prior to departing. Expect both Breece Hall and Isaiah Davis to see a slight uptick in usage in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97b1-d95b-addb-fff794170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Tyreek Hill (leg) was carted to the locker room in the third quarter of Week 4 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97fa-d6e9-af9d-9ffa30890000</link>
      <description>Hill is almost certainly done for the season with what looked like a gruesome lower leg injury. Team training staffs were both on the scene after the injury happened, cutting his cleat off to stabilize his leg. He was seen with a smile as he was carted to the locker room. Jaylen Waddle and Malik Washington will be tasked with stepping up through the air in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-97fa-d6e9-af9d-9ffa30890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields completed 20-of-27 passes for 226 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ 27-21, Week 4 loss to the Dolphins, adding 81 yards and a touchdown on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-981e-d95b-addb-f85ef50e0000</link>
      <description>Fields also lost a fumble on a fourth down sack in the second quarter. A Braelon Allen fumble just before crossing the goal line on the team’s first possession put the Jets into an early deficit, influencing their ability to pound the football on the ground and forcing Fields into more drop backs. That is not where this team needs to be considering little depth at pass-catcher behind alpha wide receiver Garrett Wilson, and the results against the Dolphins emphasize that point. Fields was able to keep the team afloat with his legs, scoring from 43 yards out on a play that was seemingly blown up. A quarterback keeper off right tackle was covered well by the Dolphins so Fields reversed his run, displaying his elite athleticism as he scored on his longest run of the night. A late touchdown to Wilson padded his counting stats, boosting him to two top-five fantasy finishes in as many healthy games this season. He remains a locked-in QB1 ahead of a meeting with the Cowboys in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-981e-d95b-addb-f85ef50e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall rushed 14 times for 81 yards in the Jets’ Week 4 loss to the Dolphins, adding 30 yards on five receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9870-d95b-addb-f876b70b0000</link>
      <description>Hall started the night off hot as the team leaned on their run game on their first possession. He was taken off the field after being banged up on his first reception only to watch as Braelon Allen fumbled as he attempted to cross the goal line. Hall shook off the potential injury to command the opportunities the rest of the way after Allen sustained a knee injury on a kickoff return, gaining 131 yards from scrimmage to end with a solid fantasy showing, even without a touchdown. Hall could be forced back into a workhorse role, pending the injury status of Allen in the immediate future. He would be a surefire RB1 in a matchup with the Cowboys in Week 5 without Allen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9870-d95b-addb-f876b70b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson caught 6-of-8 targets for 82 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 4 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9874-d95b-addb-f8765f5c0000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s touchdown came with under two minutes to play from 23 yards out, aided by Miami defensive coordinator Anthony Weaver’s questionable decision to send extra men on a blitz and leave Rasul Douglas isolated against the elite receiver on two consecutive plays while up by 14. The solid fantasy outing goes down as his third in four tries after notching three scores and 82 yards or more in those contests. Wilson has crept into fantasy WR1 territory in spite of the low volume exhibited by the New York pass offense through four games. Next up is a sparkling matchup against the injury ravaged Cowboys in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9874-d95b-addb-f8765f5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 5-of-7 targets for 65 yards in the Jets’ Week 4 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9888-d6e9-af9d-9a9870e60000</link>
      <description>Taylor finished second on the team in targets and yardage as the Jets were forced to work the intermediate areas of the field in the second half against soft shells from the Dolphins. He combined with alpha wide receiver Garrett Wilson and running back Breece Hall to account for 21 targets on 27 Justin Fields pass attempts, something fantasy managers are thrilled to see considering the general lack of pass-catching depth behind the top two options in the offense. Perhaps Taylor can keep the momentum going into a matchup with the Cowboys in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9888-d6e9-af9d-9a9870e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 17-of-25 passes for 177 yards and two touchdowns in the Dolphins’ 27-21, Week 4 win over the Jets, adding six yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988b-d95b-addb-f8cf35a70000</link>
      <description>Both of Tua’s passing scores went to newcomer tight end Darren Waller, emphasizing this team’s need for a legitimate red zone threat. In what seems like a constant drill for this Dolphins team in recent history, head coach Mike McDaniel will have to overcome more setbacks after star wide receiver Tyreek Hill saw his season end with a dislocated knee, something that could influence the team’s ability to attack downfield moving forward. Tagovailoa and McDaniel were able to overcome Hill’s injury in this one via cleverly designed short area passing build off play action, something that is only effective behind a threatening run game. Their offensive success in the near future likely depends on that ability. Lucky for them they get a reeling Panthers team in Week 5 before matchups against the Chargers, Browns, Falcons, and Ravens. Tagovailoa falls to a low-end QB2 with the injury to Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988b-d95b-addb-f8cf35a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 20 times for 99 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets, adding two yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9890-dca3-a9fb-bd99a59f0000</link>
      <description>Achane was the spark for the offense, behind which they were able to find success on short and intermediate passing via play action. That became a pressing need for the offense following the departure of Tyreek Hill, who suffered a dislocated knee early in the third quarter. Achane’s pass game involvement should return in Week 5 when the Dolphins take on the Panthers considering Hill’s absence, and he remains an elite RB1 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9890-dca3-a9fb-bd99a59f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 3-of-6 targets for 48 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9895-d6e9-af9d-9a9584710000</link>
      <description>Waddle’s volume was heavily influenced by positive game script as the Jets seemingly beat themselves with mistakes and penalties. That said, he could be counted on for a featured role moving forward after Tyreek Hill was lost for the season with a dislocated knee. Waddle has struggled to function as the primary target in previous seasons but will be tasked with that burden for the remainder of the 2025 season. Fantasy managers are hoping he can rise to the occasion and return WR2 numbers as the focal point of the offense through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9895-d6e9-af9d-9a9584710000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
