<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 18:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rob Gronkowski retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</link>
      <description>Gronkowski will sign a one-day contract to retire as a Patriot on Wednesday, but he has technically been retired for four seasons. The future Hall of Famer last played in 2021 and returned to the game in 2020, joining Tom Brady and the Buccaneers after a year away. Gronk, a four-time Super Bowl champion and four-time All-Pro, will officially walk away as one of the best tight ends in league history. He currently ranks 10th amongst TEs in all-time receptions (621), sixth in receiving yards (9,286), and third in touchdowns (92).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e25-d673-a39e-eeb533cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he isn’t sure if Garrett Wilson (knee) will be able to play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</link>
      <description>Wilson re-aggravated the knee injury he suffered in Week 6 against the Broncos. It was Wilson’s first game back from the injury, and he failed to haul in any of the three targets that came in his direction. Although Justin Fields can certainly be blamed for some of that. Wilson will undergo additional imaging on his knee to determine where things stand right now, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he was again sidelined after this latest setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e6c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee6f940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Azareye’h Thomas (concussion) will not play in Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is in the league’s concussion protocol after going down in Week 10’s win against the Browns. With the Jets slated to play on Thursday against the Patriots, the short turnaround was always going to make it tough for Thomas to clear protocol in time for Week 11. Thomas played on 24 defensive snaps in Sunday’s win and has seen an increased role in the Jets’ last three games after playing primarily as a backup through the first six weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e73-d713-ad9e-6e776a5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 4-of-4 targets for 89 yards in the Giants’ Week 10 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e79-d1e7-a1fa-7efb203e0000</link>
      <description>It was a typical low-volume day for Slayton, but he made the most of his looks. The veteran receiver hauled in one of the more impressive catches you will see in Sunday’s loss when he created just enough separation from the defender to turn around and make an outstretched, one-handed grab to pick up 31 yards and move the ball into Bears territory. He would haul in a 38-yard reception on the following play. Slayton has now gone for 62 or more yards in back-to-back games and but is averaging just 5.5 targets per game in his last four outings. He won’t be anything more than a desperation dart throw in Week 11 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e79-d1e7-a1fa-7efb203e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn opened Monday’s presser saying, “Please don’t ask me anything about the QBs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e82-d1e7-a1fa-7eea9d9c0000</link>
      <description>It’s par for the course for Glenn, who reminded reporters that “I’m not going to tell you” even if they do ask. Justin Fields threw for a whopping 54 yards in Sunday’s win over the Browns, which was only made possible by two special teams touchdowns and a 42-yard touchdown reception by Breece Hall that came on a screen pass. Glenn has been in Fields’ corner since day one and was nearly backed into benching him before an injury to Tyrod Taylor forced Fields back into the starting lineup for Week 9. Fields will likely continue to start until the losses again pile up, which could happen as early as Thursday when they take on the 8-2 Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6e82-d1e7-a1fa-7eea9d9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jackson Powers-Johnson’s ankle injury “could potentially end his season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</link>
      <description>Powers-Johnson will land on injured reserve, but it sounds like he’ll be evaluated later in the season to see if he can return. Powers-Johnson has started every game at right guard for the Raiders this season, earning a PFF grade of 63.8 while being one of the few bright spots of an underwhelming group. Backup Alex Cappa replaced Powers-Johnson in Week 10’s loss and will likely take over as the starter for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ea3-d45b-affe-7fb7a1bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Bills DE Landon Jackson suffered a torn MCL and PCL in Week 10’s loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ec4-d713-ad9e-6ed43b0b0000</link>
      <description>The Bills took Jackson in the third round of this year’s draft. The rookie has only appeared in three games this season and has been in on 30 defensive snaps. The team is still determining a timeline for his recovery, but Jackson’s season has now come to an end. He did not record a tackle in his rookie campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ec4-d713-ad9e-6ed43b0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said there is still no timetable for Bucky Irving’s (shoulder) return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ed3-d1e7-a1fa-7efb0a0b0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the Buccaneers are already preparing to be without Irving for Week 11 against the Bills. While we continue to wait for good news regarding Irving’s availability, Bowles did share that Irving’s shoulder injury is the only thing currently holding him back from getting on the field, suggesting that the ankle injury that initially sidelined him is a non-issue at this point. We’ll see if Irving’s practice status changes when the first injury report drops on Wednesday, but we aren’t expecting much at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ed3-d1e7-a1fa-7efb0a0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants fired HC Brian Daboll.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ede-d45b-affe-7fdeb76a0000</link>
      <description>Sunday’s loss to the Bears marked the third-straight season in which the Giants opened with a 2-8 record. It’s been a quick fall from grace for Daboll, who led the Giants to a 9-7-1 record in his first season, as well as their first playoff win since 2011. In that first season, Daboll was able to squeeze decent quarterback play out of Daniel Jones while leading an offense that ranked 15th in scoring and 18th in yards per game. That said, a four-year extension to Jones in the offseason was followed by disastrous quarterback play in 2023 and 2024, although he seemed to have finally found his guy in Jaxson Dart this season. Daboll’s Giants blew four leads this season on their way to their disastrous start and lost a brutal Week 5 game to the Saints. The Giants have already named OC Mike Kafka as the interim head coach, and could hand him the keys to the team in 2026 if he impresses over the final seven games of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6ede-d45b-affe-7fdeb76a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
