<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 18:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared DT John Ridgeway, DT Khristian Boyd, CB Rejzohn Wright, S Ugo Amadi, TE Jack Stoll and RT Taliese Fuaga inactive for Week 10 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6972-d713-ad9e-6d7643500000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as RB Alvin Kamara is active for Week 10 against the Panthers. The Saints are in good health heading into the divisional showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6972-d713-ad9e-6d7643500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars LB Devin Lloyd (calf) is active for Jacksonville’s Week 10 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6974-d1e7-a1fa-7bfee4630000</link>
      <description>The linebacker had four interceptions in six games before missing most of the last month with a calf injury, he’s up to hunt another from Davis Mills. Inactive for the Jaguars are: CB Jourdan Lewis (neck), WR Brian Thomas Jr (ankle), RB Cody Schrader,, OL Ezra Cleveland (knee/ankle), TE Hunter Long (hip/knee) and DL Austin Johnson. All players with injuries were ruled out on Friday, the other two are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6974-d1e7-a1fa-7bfee4630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared RB Rhamondre Stevenson, S John Saunders, DT Eric Gregory, OG Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito, WR Kayshon Boutte and LB Christian Elliss inactive for Week 10 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac5c00000</link>
      <description>Stevenson never appeared particularly close to practicing this week, and should be considered on the wrong side of questionable for Week 11 as fantasy managers begin to look forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac5c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (hamstring) is active for Carolina’s Week 10 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d1e7-a1fa-7bfba29b0000</link>
      <description>As expected, McMillan will plug in as a WR2/3 candidate against the Saints while the Panthers mainly focus on their running attack. Inactive for the Panthers are: WR Hunter Renfrow, G Chandler Zavala (elbow), DE Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, WR Brycen Tremayne (hip) and DT Cam Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d1e7-a1fa-7bfba29b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs OG Luke Haggard (shoulder) is inactive for Week 10 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa21200000</link>
      <description>Third-year pro Haggard has made four starts this season, but he’s been battling a shoulder issue. Joining Haggard on the sidelines are EDGE Haason Reddick, RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin Jr., DL C.J. Brewer, EDGE Markees Watts and fellow OG Elijah Klein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfa21200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Hunter Renfrow, G Chandler Zavala, DE Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, WR Brycen Tremayne and DT Cam Jackson inactive for Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d713-ad9e-6d7d63760000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is inactive once again with Tetairoa McMillan and Jalen Coker active. The Panthers are at full strength as they matchup with the Saints in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6979-d713-ad9e-6d7d63760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared K Graham Gano, CB Paulson Adebo, OLB Victor Dimukeje, DL Chauncey Golston, C John Michael Schmitz, G Evan Neal, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 10 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac4d40000</link>
      <description>Younghoe Koo, who was cut by the Falcons last month, will take over as New York’s kicker against the Bears in poor Chicago weather. Koo won’t be fantasy viable for Week 10. The Giants defense remains one of the most injury-ridden in the league and should be exploited by Caleb Williams and the run-heavy Chicago offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697a-d1e7-a1fa-7bfac4d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) is active for Week 10 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d45b-affe-7dfe3b940000</link>
      <description>Gordon suffered an ankle injury in week 9 but always looked likely to suit up for today’s game. As massive underdogs to Buffalo this week, the Dolphins aren’t likely to establish much of a ground game. Gordon is nothing more than an RB5. Inactive for the Dolphins are QB Quinn Ewers, S Ashtyn Davis, CB Rasul Douglas, OLB Chop Robinson, LB Andre Carter II, WR Dee Eskridge, and TE Julian Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6978-d45b-affe-7dfe3b940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is active for New Orleans’ Week 10 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d45b-affe-7dfe06970000</link>
      <description>The pattern continues. Kamara is limited in practice most weeks, but makes it to Sunday just fine. Kamara will be a RB3/FLEX candidate against the Panthers given how good their defense is and how Kamara is splitting snaps of late. DT Bryan Bresee (back) is also playing off a questionable tag. Inactive for the Saints are: DT John Ridgeway, DT Khristian Boyd, CB Rejzohn Wright, DB Ugo Amadi, and TE Jack Stoll (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d45b-affe-7dfe06970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Harrison Bryant (shoulder) is active for Houston’s Week 10 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697e-d713-ad9e-6d7e4b100000</link>
      <description>The Texans ruled out six on Friday: C.J. Stroud (concussion), Jalen Pitre (concussion), Tytus Howard (concussion), Ed Ingram (knee), Ka’imi Fairbairn (quad), and Christian Harris (shoulder) — they’ll be joined by healthy scratch Jarrett Kingston on the inactives list today. Bryant was questionable and doesn’t figure to be much of a fantasy factor today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697e-d713-ad9e-6d7e4b100000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
