<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:02:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 19 times for 60 yards and a touchdown in the Raiders’ Week 10 loss to the Broncos while adding three receptions for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c8d-d45b-affe-5d9f011f0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty was responsible for the only touchdown of the game for the Raiders on a short plunge into the end zone on their second drive of the game. He was also responsible for Geno Smith’s (quad) interception, as he dropped a pass that landed in the arms of Dondrea Tillman. The touchdown helps and there were some solid runs — one of them a long gain that was erased by penalty — but it’s yet another game where Jeanty cannot get above four yards a carry, which makes six in a row for the rookie. He’ll look to show more efficiency against the Cowboys on Monday Night Football in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c8d-d45b-affe-5d9f011f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 1-of-3 targets for 31 yards in the Raiders’ Week 10 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c8d-d1e7-a1fa-5eef06cc0000</link>
      <description>After a dominant effort against the Jaguars in Week 9, Bowers was a non-factor outside of the 31-yard connection. In fact, Michael Mayer ended up receiving more receptions (3) and yards (37) as Geno Smith didn’t feel comfortable looking Bowers’ way. Credit to Denver for clearly taking the second-year wideouts looks away — and it’s worth noting that the weather played a factor in the contest — but the results are still massively disappointing. Expect Bowers to be much more involved against the Cowboys in Week 11 on Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c8d-d1e7-a1fa-5eef06cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Lockett caught 5-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Raiders’ Week 10 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d713-ad9e-7cd634420000</link>
      <description>Lockett was the Raiders’ leader in receiving yards, catches, and targets. Not the compliment it seems. The 33-year-old was Geno Smith’s safety valve as the Denver defense gave Smith no time to throw before he left with a quad injury. Lockett will get his looks — especially with Jakobi Meyers playing elsewhere — but he’s hard to trust as a fantasy option against the Cowboys next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d713-ad9e-7cd634420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 2-of-3 targets for 28 yards in the Raiders’ Week 10 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d713-ad9e-7cd639890000</link>
      <description>Tucker had a touchdown taken off the board when Dont’e Thornton was called for offensive pass interference. The wideout was hardly involved on a day where the Raiders mustered all of 188 total yards against the stout Denver defense. Tucker and the Las Vegas passing game will get a chance to get going against the Cowboys in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d713-ad9e-7cd639890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 5-of-9 targets for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 10 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d963f2a0000</link>
      <description>Franklin should also be credited with an interception if life were fair, as he flat-out dropped a pass from Bo Nix that landed in the hands of Kyu Blu Kelly. The 2024 fourth-round pick was able to find the end zone, however, on a dart from Nix in the second quarter to tie the game at 7-7. Franklin remains a FLEX option going forward, and that includes Week 11 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d963f2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 3-of-4 targets for 24 yards in the Broncos’ Week 10 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d9644550000</link>
      <description>Sutton was able to salvage last week’s disappointing effort with a touchdown. This week it’s just disappointment. The wideout was an afterthought in the passing game for much of the contest, and the Raiders clearly were more comfortable letting Troy Franklin ‘beat’ them (5/40/1). The wideout now has just 54 yards over his last two games, and while he remains on the WR2 radar, there’s risk that comes with potential reward for Week 11 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d9644550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 1-of-2 targets for 43 yards in the Broncos’ Week 10 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d964a980000</link>
      <description>Bryant was able to pick up the long reception on a busted coverage, and then only saw one more target. The Denver offense continues to struggle, and while the third-round pick does offer long-term upside, this passing game just isn’t good enough to suggest that Bryant has any short-term fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c96-d45b-affe-5d964a980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 2-of-5 targets for 12 yards in the Broncos’ Week 10 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ca1-d45b-affe-5db778940000</link>
      <description>This makes back-to-back duds for Engram, but at least he was able to haul in a pair of passes; that’s two more than he had against the Texans in Week 9. Because of the position scarcity Engram remains on the TE1 cusp, but fantasy managers who are counting on production from him have every right to be concerned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ca1-d45b-affe-5db778940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mayer caught 3-of-4 targets for 22 yards in the Raiders’ Week 10 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5cac-d1e7-a1fa-5eeeea910000</link>
      <description>It’s worth noting that Mayer had more targets and receptions than Brock Bowers, but that’s more of an insult to Bowers’ production (one catch for 31 yards) than compliment to Mayer’s. The 24-year-old is likely to be involved in the passing game if only because of the dearth of options for Las Vegas, but he’s still a low-end TE2 at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5cac-d1e7-a1fa-5eeeea910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith left Thursday’s Week 10 game against the Broncos with a quad contusion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5caf-d673-a39e-fcbfebef0000</link>
      <description>The quad bruise was clearly affecting Smith’s ability to maneuver against the Denver pass rush, but the good news for the veteran quarterback is that there doesn’t appear to be any structural damage. If Smith was unable to go next week it would be Kenny Pickett under center, but it seems more than likely that the 34-year-old will be ready to roll against Dallas in Week 11 in a Monday Night Football showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5caf-d673-a39e-fcbfebef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
