<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers TE Tucker Kraft suffered a torn ACL in Week 9’s loss to the Panthers, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aa9-d673-a39e-eeb900780000</link>
      <description>The worst was confirmed on Monday, as Kraft’s season now comes to an end. The third-year tight end will now land on IR with his injury. Kraft was on pace for the best season of his career, and already had two 100-yard games on his resume through the first nine weeks of the season. Kraft was on a 17-game pace for his first 1,000-yard season and will now set his sights toward another high-end season in 2026. Backup tight end Luke Musgrave is now expected to step up in Kraft’s absence, and has caught just nine passes for 88 yards this season on 10 targets. He won’t replicate the production we saw from Kraft, but Musgrave could prove to be sneaky waiver wire add in fantasy for managers still looking for a dependable option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aa9-d673-a39e-eeb900780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said S Andre Cisco (pectoral) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4abf-d45b-affe-5fbfa8db0000</link>
      <description>Cisco suffered a torn pectoral in Week 8’s win over the Bengals. Returning from the team’s Week 9 bye, Glenn confirmed that the fifth-year safety will now miss the remainder of the season. Cisco signed a one-year deal with the Jets this offseason and started all eight games he appeared in while totaling 41 tackles, one TFL, and one pass breakup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4abf-d45b-affe-5fbfa8db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Garrett Wilson (knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac2-d713-ad9e-6ed671a20000</link>
      <description>Glenn didn’t say how much he expected Wilson to practice this week, but his return to the field is a good sign for his Week 10 availability against the Browns. Wilson missed the last two games after suffering a knee injury in Week 6, but avoided a stint on injured reserve. Assuming he’s able to get on the field every day this week, Wilson should have a chance to suit up for the Jets coming off their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac2-d713-ad9e-6ed671a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn declined to name a starting QB for Week 10’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac3-d45b-affe-5fd721f90000</link>
      <description>With such a big game on tap, we can’t blame for Glenn wanting to keep his decision on QB close to the vest against **checks notes** the 2-6 Browns. Even after a Week 9 bye to further evaluate Justin Fields’ performance against the Bengals, Glenn on Monday refused to say who he would roll with in Week 10. Glenn has thoroughly enjoyed leaving the media in the dark when asked about his QB room, but it would be surprising to see him move off Fields following a solid Week 8 performance against the Bengals in which he threw for 244-1-0 on the way to getting the Jets their first win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac3-d45b-affe-5fd721f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said OC Tommy Rees will take over offensive play-calling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ad4-d713-ad9e-6ed4750c0000</link>
      <description>It’s the second time in as many years that Stefanski has turned over the team’s offensive play-calling. Rees was promoted from pass game specialist to offensive coordinator this offseason and also served as offensive coordinator for Notre Dame (2020-2022) and Alabama (2023). Rees will look to improve an offense that currently ranks 30th in scoring and 31st in yards. It’s also looked far more conservative under QB Dillon Gabriel than it did under Joe Flacco, who wasn’t shy about airing it out in his four starts this season. Rees will get his first crack at play-calling in Week 10 when the Browns take on the one-win Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ad4-d713-ad9e-6ed4750c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) was seen practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adb-d1e7-a1fa-5afb56ed0000</link>
      <description>Judkins was seen participating at the start of practice following the team’s Week 9 bye. Head coach Kevin Stefanski said Judkins would be considered “day-to-day” following his Week 8 shoulder injury, so a return to the field on Monday is a good sign for his Week 10 availability. The Browns won’t release their first injury report until Wednesday, but it sounds like Judkins has a legitimate chance to play after this promising start to the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adb-d1e7-a1fa-5afb56ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Simmons (personal) hs returned to the Chiefs after four weeks away.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</link>
      <description>Simmons was away from the Chiefs for four weeks to tend to a family issue. We don’t know the specifics beyond that, but the rookie tackle who started the first five games of the season is now set to return following his absence, and should immediately slot in as the team’s left tackle when the team returns from its Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Kayshon Boutte is day-to-day with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aec-d1e7-a1fa-5aee37140000</link>
      <description>It’s an encouraging sign for Boutte following his early exit from Sunday’s win over the Falcons, although Vrabel did add that he doesn’t expect Boutte to practice “early in the week.” His practice status will be one to monitor when the Patriots release their first injury report on Wednesday, but as of now, Boutte does have a chance to play in Week 10 in a game that could feature plenty of scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aec-d1e7-a1fa-5aee37140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ribs) would undergo a scan but that he feels “optimistic ... in regard to where we’re potentially heading.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b12-d45b-affe-5f9682ad0000</link>
      <description>A scan means we’re not completely out of the woods yet, but Nacua has bled on the field this year and we doubt a small-scale fractured rib would keep him out. (Easy for us to say.) Nacua’s status will be worth tracking, but we’d enter Week 10 expecting him to play based on the rhetoric so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b12-d45b-affe-5f9682ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Commanders are open to dealing OLs Andrew Wylie and Nick Allegretti.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b0e-d45b-affe-5f9e4b710000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, Wylie and Allegretti are one of “several players” the 3-6 Commanders are open to dealing. Wylie first joined the Commanders in 2023 and has started four games this season at right guard, while Allegretti, who started the first two games at right guard, hasn’t taken an offensive snap since Week 4. Wylie is on an expiring contract, and Allegretti’s deal ends after the 2026 season. Both players have plenty of starting experience and could serve as stopgaps for contenders looking to improve along the offensive line before the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b0e-d45b-affe-5f9e4b710000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
