<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) will not return in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90c8-d95b-addb-f8ced7cd0000</link>
      <description>Kelly has a lengthy concussion history dating back to his time in Indianapolis. The Vikings will stay in Europe for Week 5 before getting a bye and returning to action in Week 7. That looks like a likely target for Kelly’s return. Right tackle Brian O’Neill has also been ruled out for the remainder for the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90c8-d95b-addb-f8ced7cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared S Kevin Winston, RT JC Latham, WR Bryce Oliver, OT John Ojukwu, OL Jackson Slater and CB Samuel Womack inactive for Tennessee’s Week 4 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90f9-d6e9-af9d-9af992970000</link>
      <description>Winston (hamstring) has not been active yet this year as a third-round pick, dealing with an ACL recovery and a litany of other injuries. Oliver is out with a knee and Latham with a hip. The other three are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90f9-d6e9-af9d-9af992970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared TE Will Dissly, WR Derius Davis, S R.J. Mickens, CB Nikko Reed, OG Mekhi Becton and DT Otito Ogbonnia inactive for Week 4 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fb-deb6-a7fd-d3ff09d00000</link>
      <description>The Chargers also have Tyler Conklin, but coach Jim Harbaugh has indicated rookie Oronde Gadsden II could be the primary beneficiary of Dissly’s lost snaps and targets. Gadsden is an intriguing if zero-floor TE2 dart throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fb-deb6-a7fd-d3ff09d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared CB Adoree’ Jackson, OLB Azeez Ojulari, QB Sam Howell, C/G Drew Kendall, and WR Xavier Gipson inactive for Week 4 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fc-d95b-addb-f8fe27770000</link>
      <description>The Eagles defense will be without Jackson against Baker Mayfield and a Bucs offense that will get back Chris Godwin (but will be missing Mike Evans). Philly’s defense comes into Week 4 relatively beat up and vulnerable to efficient offenses like the Bucs. This game could shape up as a back-and-forth affair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fc-d95b-addb-f8fe27770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared OT Spencer Brown, DE Landon Jackson, DT Ed Oliver, LB Matt Milano. CB Ja’Marcus Ingram, and KR/PR Brandon Codrington inactive for Week 4 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fa-dca3-a9fb-bdfb8a8a0000</link>
      <description>We knew that the bills would be without Matt Milano and Ed Oliver, who are still nursing injuries, but now it appears they will be without their starting right tackle as well. Expect Ryan Van Denmark to start in Brown’s place, and that’s a spot to watch as the Bills have given up the least amount of pressure on their own quarterback so far this season. With Codrington also inactive, the Bills will have a new return man for the first time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fa-dca3-a9fb-bdfb8a8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared RB Tyrone Tracy, DL Chauncey Golston, OL Evan Neal, TE Thomas Fidone, EDGE Rakeem Nuñez-Roches, S Beau Brade and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 4 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fd-d95b-addb-f8ff38850000</link>
      <description>Tracy is expected to be sidelined multiple weeks, giving fourth-round rookie Cam Skattebo runway to run away with the Giants’ starting job as fellow rookie Jaxson Dart gets comfortable under center. Tracy is a tenuous hold in shallower 12-team leagues, though you are probably best served holding onto him through at least this afternoon’s games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fd-d95b-addb-f8ff38850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curtis Samuel is active for Week 4 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fe-dca3-a9fb-bdff937a0000</link>
      <description>This is the first time Samuel has been active so far this season. None of the Bills other wide receivers are inactive, but Brandon Codrington, their primary return man, is inactive, so it remains to be seen if Samuel will be taking that primary return role</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90fe-dca3-a9fb-bdff937a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared WR Trey Palmer, RB Devin Neal, CB Rejzohn Wright, OL Xavier Truss, OL Dillon Radunz, DT Jonathan Bullard, and DE Chase Young inactive for Week 4 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90ff-dca3-a9fb-bdffe4400000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here. The Saints will have a fully healthy offensive line going against a banged up Bills defensive line. We’ll see if that’s enough to make this game closer than the spread thinks it will be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-90ff-dca3-a9fb-bdffe4400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LT Tristan Wirfs (knee) is active for Week 4 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9109-deb6-a7fd-d3df1de60000</link>
      <description>Wirfs will make his season debut following knee surgery in the summer. The Bucs have reportedly been careful with Wirfs in his recovery from the knee injury. He should be a full go today against the Eagles. It’s a positive development for Baker Mayfield against a vicious Eagles front seven. Pro Football Focus grades Tampa’s pass protection as the 11th worst in the NFL over the season’s first three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9109-deb6-a7fd-d3df1de60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (shoulder) will not return in Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-911f-d6e9-af9d-9b9f976d0000</link>
      <description>Austin went down in the second half with a shoulder injury and was initially listed as questionable to return. He was later spotted exiting the stadium in an ambulance with his shoulder in a sling. The Steelers get their bye next week, but Austin’s injury is likely much more serious than a one-week absence. Roman Wilson and Ben Skowronek will see an uptick in work until Austin returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-911f-d6e9-af9d-9b9f976d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
