<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:03:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0596-d77b-adfb-cf97d3240000</link>
      <description>Otton has now been listed with a DNP on back-to-back days. With a short week ahead of a Thursday game against the Falcons, Otton will likely need to log a practice Wednesday in order to play. If he cannot go, Chris Godwin should see a bump in usage while Payne Durham is next up at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0596-d77b-adfb-cf97d3240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed RB Trayveon Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-059a-d005-a9bf-ddbe8dbd0000</link>
      <description>Williams spent August with the Browns and was released in September. He eventually made his way onto the Chargers’ practice squad in the middle of the season after Omarion Hampton’s injury and appeared in three games, totaling three carries for a loss of one yard. The Browns just put Jerome Ford on injured reserve and now add Williams to help fill Ford’s role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-059a-d005-a9bf-ddbe8dbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts QB Philip Rivers has “a very real chance” to start Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-05a7-d8cf-affb-bdafc8bf0000</link>
      <description>The 44-year-old Rivers signed with the Colts on Tuesday and could be immediately thrust into the starting role. With Daniel Jones out for the season, Anthony Richardson still dealing with an eye injury, and Riley Leonard now dealing with a “Grade 1 PCL injury”, Rapoport says there is “a very real chance that Rivers is the starting quarterback for the Colts this Sunday.” We will see how Rivers practices having been out of the league for nearly five seasons, but the Colts may be making the move to start him as soon as Week 15 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-05a7-d8cf-affb-bdafc8bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer said he’s not worried about George Pickens’ effort level.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-087c-d8cf-affb-bc7e01000000</link>
      <description>Pickens reverted to the low-effort Pittsburgh version of himself in Week 14’s loss to the Lions, giving up on routes and appearing generally disinterested in the proceedings. Pickens had just 37 yards on nine targets against Detroit. “We talked a little bit about it,” Schottenheimer said Monday. “In his words, he said, ‘Hey Schotty, I didn’t play my best game.’ I think that, unfortunately, none of us played our best game. But again, I don’t worry about George and his love for football and playing this game. You know, for five or six weeks, he was the talk of the sporting world. ‘Look at George Pickens.’ We didn’t coach or play well enough to win that game in Detroit. They beat us. It is what it is.” Hopefully Pickens gives better effort in Week 15 against a Minnesota secondary that has been burned on deep throws for much of the season. He’ll be a top-12 fantasy option, and a top seven or eight option if CeeDee Lamb (concussion) is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-087c-d8cf-affb-bc7e01000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed TE Zach Ertz on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-08a0-d77b-adfb-caa34b800000</link>
      <description>Ertz’s 2025 season is over after a Week 14 cheap shot resulted in a torn ACL for the 35-year-old veteran. He ends the season with 50 receptions for 504 yards and four touchdowns. Ertz was tenth among tight ends in catches and 12th in yardage before the injury. John Bates will likely operate as Washington’s TE1 for now, though Ben Sinnott could mix in as the Commanders play out the rest of their lost season. Neither Bates nor Sinnott should be played in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-08a0-d77b-adfb-caa34b800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder reports Colts coaches were impressed by Philip Rivers’ arm strength during his team workout.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-08d7-d77b-adfb-cad766b70000</link>
      <description>“He can still spin it,” a Colts official told ESPN. Another team source added, “I’d still take him at this stage over most 22- to 23-year-old [backups].” Rivers during his workout with the Colts threw on the run and worked the entire route tree. His familiarity with head coach Shane Steichen’s offensive system could land Rivers, 44, under center in Week 15 against the Seahawks. Riley Leonard is dealing with a knee injury and is considered week to week after subbing in for Daniel Jones (Achilles) in Week 14 against the Jaguars. Rivers — a recent grandfather — is not yet in typical NFL shape, however. “He needs to get in football shape, but there’s no question he can throw it,” a team source told ESPN. “Sources maintain that how Rivers handles his first week of practice will determine whether he plays Sunday.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-08d7-d77b-adfb-cad766b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Mike Evans (collarbone) “has shown everything he needed to show” to play in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0922-d77b-adfb-cba3aae40000</link>
      <description>Evans is practicing this week and — barring a setback — should suit up Thursday night against Atlanta. Evans over the season’s first three weeks led the Bucs offense with a 41 percent air yards share and a 27 percent target share. His return to the Tampa lineup could limit Emeka Egbuka’s opportunities, though the rookie should remain in most 12-team lineups against the Falcons. Evans needs to be started in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0922-d77b-adfb-cba3aae40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Philip Rivers said his Hall of Fame eligibility is “not a factor” in determining if he’ll play in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-092c-d77b-adfb-cbafbf440000</link>
      <description>Rivers’ HOF eligibility will reset if he’s on the Colts’ active roster at any point in the coming weeks. Rivers was set to be eligible for the Hall as early as 2026. “I haven’t been holding my breath on that,” Rivers said during a Wednesday presser. “I haven’t been counting down the years.” If that’s the case, Rivers could be under center in Week 15 against the Seahawks, as QB Riley Leonard deals with a knee injury he sustained in Week 14 against the Jaguars. Rivers reportedly impressed Colts coaches and officials in his workout. Rivers would profile as a desperation superflex play in fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-092c-d77b-adfb-cbafbf440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills EDGE Joey Bosa (hamstring) practiced in a limited capacity Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0931-da9b-a9bf-df3d699e0000</link>
      <description>Bosa was sidelined last week against the Bengals with a hamstring issue but could return for the Bills’ critical Week 15 matchup against the Patriots. Buffalo’s vulnerable defense will need all the help it can get to slow down MVP frontrunner Drake Maye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0931-da9b-a9bf-df3d699e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (personal) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0933-d77b-adfb-cbb3d59a0000</link>
      <description>Knox in Week 14 led the Bills in receiving with six grabs for 93 yards. If he doesn’t return to practice by Friday, Dalton Kincaid could see an expanded role, making him a must play in Week 15 against the Patriots. Twenty-five percent of the Bills’ targets have gone to the tight end position in 2025, the sixth highest rate in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0933-d77b-adfb-cbb3d59a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
