<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 17:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught all four targets for 30 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fd3-d93f-ad9d-7fd72edf0000</link>
      <description>Slayton remains well behind both Malik Nabers and Wan’Dale Robinson in the target pecking order despite finishing second in the team in receiving behind running back Cam Skattebo, beating both other receivers on the night. It will be difficult to trust Slayton as anything more than a bye week desperation start moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fd3-d93f-ad9d-7fd72edf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fda-d1b3-a5dd-6ffb427a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson now has six catches for 49 yards through three games and has not yet lived up to the offseason hype. He can safely remain on, or be returned to, waiver wires, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fda-d1b3-a5dd-6ffb427a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Noah Fant suffered a concussion in the Bengals’ Week 3 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-715a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf6ee80000</link>
      <description>Fant will now need to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to suit up in Week 4 against the Broncos. Fant has been a key part of the Bengals’ offense through the first three weeks, drawing 14 targets over that span while totaling 12 catches for 80 yards and a score. Even if he’s able to clear protocol in time for next week, Fant shouldn’t be valued as anything more than a boom-or-bust TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-715a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf6ee80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said “we’ll talk about that today as a staff” when asked about Justin Fields returning as QB1 after he clears concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-719c-d6a5-adff-f7dded3c0000</link>
      <description>Glenn followed up his initial statement by adding, “Justin came in as our starter. He’s been our starter. Tyrod was the backup.” If we’re attempting to read between the lines, one might infer that Glenn referencing both QB’s statuses in the past tense could be a sign a change is coming, but we’ll wait until Glenn offers up a clearer explanation on where things stand ahead of Week 4. Fields still needs to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to play next week against the Dolphins, but Taylor played well enough against the Buccaneers to nearly earn the Jets their first win of the season, and held up well under pressure. Even if Fields does return as the starter, it’s safe to assume he’ll be on a short leash after his Week 2 debacle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-719c-d6a5-adff-f7dded3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Ben Standig reports the Commanders are meeting with free agent S Darnell Savage on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71e6-dfde-a1bd-7fef08550000</link>
      <description>The Commanders’ meeting with Savage comes a day after the team lost safety Will Harris to a fractured fibula. While we don’t yet know the extent of Harris’ injury, the decision to meet with Savage this early suggests he will miss significant time. Savage was released by the Jaguars last week after appearing in the first two games to start the season in a backup role. He’s a seven-year vet with 82 games of starting experience under his belt and could immediately fill a key role if called upon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71e6-dfde-a1bd-7fef08550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado is the early favorite to handle RB2 duties for the Cardinals heading into Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71fd-d93f-ad9d-7bff11de0000</link>
      <description>The third-year vet saw a truly limited snap count in Sunday’s Week 3 loss to the 49ers following James Conner’s season-ending ankle injury. He played on a whopping seven snaps in the loss and ran two routes while dropping a key pass in the red zone. Fantasy manaagers have flirted with Demercado before, and with little success. He’s popped up for six top-24 PPR performances since entering the league in 2023, and best profiles as another backfield PPR scam who could see most of his snaps on third downs and passing downs. He could make for an interesting stash, but fantasy managers shouldn’t be rushing to start him in Week 4 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71fd-d93f-ad9d-7bff11de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed CB Mike Hilton, formerly of the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7212-d93f-ad9d-7ad771970000</link>
      <description>Hilton’s signing comes a day after slot corner Kenny Moore exited Week 3 with a calf injury. Hilton is an eight-year vet who spent the last four years of his career in Cincinnati under current Colts defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo. He can serve as an immediate plug and play corner for a Colts defense that currently ranks in the top-10 in both points and yards allowed through the first three weeks of the season, and has plenty of starting experience under his belt if needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7212-d93f-ad9d-7ad771970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts CB Kenny Moore will miss a few weeks with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7228-d93f-ad9d-7aefe96a0000</link>
      <description>Moore exited Week 3’s game against the Titans and didn’t return to the field. The Colts went out and signed veteran slot corner Mike Hilton early Monday morning, which served as the initial indicator that Moore, whose injury is not believed to be too serious, was set to miss some time. We’ll hopefully get a more exact timeline on Moore’s absence when head coach Shane Steichen speaks to the media, but it sounds like he is looking at a multi-week absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7228-d93f-ad9d-7aefe96a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Tyrone Tracy will miss time after suffering a dislocated shoulder in Week 3’s loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7243-dfde-a1bd-7ecf5ab10000</link>
      <description>It felt like things were trending in this direction after Tracy took a hard hit in the first quarter and immediately exited the game. Tracy didn’t return to the game and is now slated to miss a few weeks while recovering from the injury. Rookie Cam Skattebo, who rushed 10 times for 60 yards and a touchdown in Week 3’s loss to the Chiefs, is expected to take on a significant workload with Tracy now sidelined, and will profile as a strong RB2 with potential RB1 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7243-dfde-a1bd-7ecf5ab10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
