<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:14:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Giants OLB coach Charlie Bullen will remain with the team in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-571f-d355-a5bd-df5fe2eb0000</link>
      <description>Bullen will have the title of run-game coordinator added to his title for the upcoming season. The 41-year-old coach received interviews for defensive coordinator openings from the Browns, Cowboys, and Cardinals after being passed on for the Giants’ DC role, but opted to remove his name from consideration for the remaining openings. Bullen joined the Giants in 2024 and briefly served as the team’s interim defensive coordinator in 2025 after Shane Bowen was fired in late-November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-571f-d355-a5bd-df5fe2eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Turron Davenport reports Cam Ward’s shoulder injury “hasn’t impacted his offseason training.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5770-d355-a5bd-df7411dc0000</link>
      <description>According to Davenport, Ward has “been working mostly on footwork” this offseason. The No. 1overall pick of the 2025 NFL Draft is hoping to rebound from a challenging rookie season and will have a new offensive coordinator in place in Brian Daboll. Ward suffered his shoulder injury in the final week of the season, but exams revealed it was a sprained AC join that would not require surgery. Ward and the Titans have a lot to improve on in 2026 after the offense finished 30th in scoring and 31st in total yards. Hopefully a healthy offseason will lead to some growth for the second-year signal-caller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5770-d355-a5bd-df7411dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jenna Laine reports that “based on conversations with those closest to him,” Mike Evans is expected to continue playing in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-577f-d355-a5bd-df7f22640000</link>
      <description>Retirement will soon be in Evans’ future, but the veteran receiver isn’t expected to hang it up after the 2025 season. Evans, who will be 33 at the start of next season, had the worst season of his career this year. He caught 30 passes for 368 yards and three touchdowns while missing nine games due to injuries. Laine reports that the soon-to-be unrestricted free agent has yet to discuss his future, suggesting a departure from the Buccaneers could be possible this offseason. It’s hard to know how much Evans has left in the tank at this stage of his career, and his days as a true WR1 could be behind him. That said, if healthy, there would be plenty of teams he could still help if he were to opt to leave Tampa in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-577f-d355-a5bd-df7f22640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders offensive coordinator David Blough said the Washington offense will be “built around” getting Terry McLaurin 10 targets a game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5742-d042-afbc-7fd28ea50000</link>
      <description>Blough is taking over as offensive coordinator after the Commanders fired Kliff Kingsbury. His first order of business will be to revive the passing game that thrived in 2024 and flopped in 2025. McLaurin probably won’t average 10 opportunities per game in the literal sense. His career-high in targets per game is 8.9. Still, it’s good to see Blough committed to getting the ball in the hands of his team’s best pass-catcher, even if he’s fudging the numbers a little. McLaurin missed most of the offseason last year in search of a new contract and couldn’t stay healthy when he finally rejoined the team. He appeared in just 10 games and posted a 38/582/3 receiving line on the year. Health permitting, McLaurin should return to the WR2 ranks in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5742-d042-afbc-7fd28ea50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs pleaded not guilty to felony strangulation and other criminal charges.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5790-d89c-a1be-ffdf3fdf0000</link>
      <description>Diggs is facing felony strangulation and suffocation charges, along with misdemeanor assault and battery charges stemming from an incident that involved him and his personal chef. Diggs is next scheduled to appear for a pretrial hearing on April 1st. Diggs’ attorney said he “categorically denies these allegations.” This is a situation that is likely to play out over the next several months, but we would expect the league to decide whether or not to hand down a fine and/or suspension once this is resolved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5790-d89c-a1be-ffdf3fdf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the NFLPA’s publicizing of team report cards was determined by an arbitrator to be in violation of the CBA “and ordered it to stop making public any future report cards.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-57b6-d89c-a1be-ffffd0140000</link>
      <description>It’s a big win for the NFL and its owners, especially those owners who consistently score low on these team report cards — looking at you, Jets. Jets owner Woody Johnson saw his team rank 21st out of 32 teams in the 2024 report card, only for his team to drop to 29th after the 2025 season. Johnson ripped the surveys for being “totally bogus” and played a key role in the attempt to ban them from being published in the future. According to the independent arbitrator, the NFLPA “refused to produce any information or data related to prior years’ surveys” while adding “the Report Cards were designed by the union to advance its interests under the guise of scientific exercise.” Surveys were allowed to continue to be conducted in the coming seasons, but they will remain hidden from the public eye for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-57b6-d89c-a1be-ffffd0140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams assistant head coach and pass game coordinator Aubrey Pleasant will interview for the Raiders’ defensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-57e5-d355-a5bd-dff515290000</link>
      <description>Pleasant has also interviewed for openings with the Browns and Cardinals, although the Cardinals have already opted to retain last year’s defensive coordinator. Pleasant first joined the Rams in 2023 as their DB coach and passing game coordinator, and has never held a title of defensive coordinator in college or the pros. Pleasant played a key role in helping the Rams’ defense finish in the top-10 in points allowed while also ranking 12th in yards per attempt allowed. He’s drawn enough attention this coaching cycle to suggest that even if he doesn’t land a coordinator role this offseason, one could be in store for him in the very near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-57e5-d355-a5bd-dff515290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Seahawks will interview Cardinals pass game specialist Connor Senger for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5800-d355-a5bd-df54d1f40000</link>
      <description>Senger has been with the Cardinals since 2022, and recently interviewed for the Bears’ offensive coordinator position. Rapoport reports that the Cardinals hope to retain Senger for the upcoming season, but any chance to make the leap to coordinator would likely spell the end of his time in Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5800-d355-a5bd-df54d1f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports a court ruled that discrimination cases filed against the NFL by Brian Flores, Steve Wilks, and Ray Horton “now can proceed in open court.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-582c-d629-a1bc-f83d767c0000</link>
      <description>In the decision, the court writes that “an arbitration forum in which the defendant’s (NFL’s) own chief executive gets to decide the case would strip employees of their rights under the law,” while adding that “it is long overdue for the NFL to recognize this and finally provide a fair, neutral and transparent forum for these issues to be addressed.” Flores first filed a class-action lawsuit against the NFL, the Dolphins, Giants, and Broncos, for conducting “sham” interviews with him in 2022 to satisfy the league’s hiring rules. Wilks and Horton later add their names to the complaint and named the Cardinals and Titans. Should this head to open court, a trial would likely be set to take place where both sides will be heard before a jury ultimately decides if the league discriminated against Flores, Wilks, and Horton during various interview processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-582c-d629-a1bc-f83d767c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Seahawks defensive pass game coordinator and DBs coach Karl Scott will remain with the team next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5850-d629-a1bc-f85d8ce40000</link>
      <description>Scott was under consideration for the Cardinals’ defensive coordinator opening, but the team ultimately decided to stick with Nick Rallis, who joined the team in 2023. Scott has been with the Seahawks since 2022 and helped lead a top defensive unit to a Super Bowl championship this season. He’ll remain with the Seahawks in 2026, but Scott could continue to field calls for coordinator jobs in the future if he continues to coach up elite secondaries like we saw this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5850-d629-a1bc-f85d8ce40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
