<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 9-of-12 targets for 78 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 2 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2b-dc44-a9d9-4f6f1d270000</link>
      <description>A lot of these were little dumpoffs or play-action flat passes, but Ferguson managed a few seam balls to round out the line. Ferguson isn’t a focal point of the Cowboys passing game, but 18 targets in two games will certainly play in the dregs of the TE1 ranks. He’s not a must-start against the Bears in Week 3. However, it’s a good enough matchup that Ferguson will probably wind up inside the top 12 TEs on most ranking lists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2b-dc44-a9d9-4f6f1d270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts LG Quenton Nelson returned to Week 2 against the Broncos after suffering an apparent leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a24-da67-a99f-cef5c0ba0000</link>
      <description>Nelson was the downfield blocker on a delayed Tyler Warren screen pass when he was hurt. Broncos S Talanoa Hufanga went low on Nelson, which resulted in Nelson driving his quad-knee area into the diving Hufanga. Nelson immediately grabbed just above his knee as he went down. He then limped off the field under his own power and was seen talking to teammates with his helmet on, along the sideline. He returned on the following drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a24-da67-a99f-cef5c0ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Tolbert caught 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 2 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2d-d86f-abdd-4fbda93e0000</link>
      <description>He took over as Dallas’ third receiver with KaVontae Turpin (neck) out for the majority of the second half and overtime. Tolbert dropped a Prescott laser on one key third down and looked like he had no prayer to break a tackle on another one in overtime. Even if Turpin misses time, Tolbert would be an unexciting use of a roster spot in shallow leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2d-d86f-abdd-4fbda93e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 1-of-3 targets for nine yards in the Patriots’ Week 2 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2b-d294-a19b-eefbfacd0000</link>
      <description>Henry tied Austin Hooper in targets, both totaling three against a weak Dolphins defense. Drake Maye spread the ball around in the Pats’ passing attack, leading to low-ceiling finishes for Pats pass-catchers. Henry is still the team’s lead tight end, but there will be weeks where Hooper has a better finish, similar to last year. Fantasy managers can consider Henry a TE2 heading into next week against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a2b-d294-a19b-eefbfacd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 14 times for 71 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 2 loss to the Bengals, adding two catches for 18 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a24-d294-a19b-eef4c29d0000</link>
      <description>Etienne once again looked explosive on the ground, averaging 5.1 YPC with a long of 30 yards. Liam Coen also worked to get him in space through the air, dialing up a third-quarter screen pass that Etienne took 11 yards into the end zone. Backup runner Bhayshul Tuten also scored on a receiving play. Tuten totaled 10 touches to Etienne’s 16. Despite ceding some work to the rookie, Etienne remains a high-ceiling RB2 for his Week 3 matchup with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a24-d294-a19b-eef4c29d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed eight times for 42 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 2 loss to the Bengals, adding two catches for 32 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a32-da67-a99f-cef7f9eb0000</link>
      <description>The rookie played sparingly in Week 1, but the trade of Tank Bigsby opened a path for his role to grow in his second outing. That is exactly what happened as Tuten mixed in as the clear RB2 behind Travis Etienne, who totaled 14 carries and two catches of his own. Tuten put his name on the map in the third quarter by juking Bengals defensive end Cam Sample out of his shoes on a red zone check-down from Trevor Lawrence. Tuten sped into the end zone after blowing by Sample. Though he’s still behind Etienne in the rotation, Tuten’s Week 2 breakout has him in the RB4 mix for the Jags’ Week 3 date with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a32-da67-a99f-cef7f9eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 3-of-4 targets for 31 yards in the Steelers’ Week 2 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a34-d86f-abdd-4fbd956b0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth matched Jonnu Smith in routes and targets after catching three balls for 28 scoreless yards in Week 1 against the Jets. Until and unless one of the Steelers tight ends misses time or is phased out of the passing offense, neither Freiermuth nor Jonnu will be playable in 12-team formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a34-d86f-abdd-4fbd956b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara rushed 21 times for 99 yards in the Saints’ Week 2 loss to the 49ers, adding six receptions for 21 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a28-d294-a19b-eef86dcb0000</link>
      <description>You just can’t kill the concept of “Alvin Kamara, usage monster” in fantasy football. No other Saints running back did anything, with apparent No. 2 Kendre Miller turning his six touches into 10 yards. Rookie Devin Neal did not touch the football. Kamara’s efficiency has been waning for years, but his touches basline and touchdown opportunities keep him locked into the RB2 ranks despite playing in one of the league’s worst offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a28-d294-a19b-eef86dcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 11 times for 30 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots, adding eight receptions for 92 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a31-d294-a19b-eef136bf0000</link>
      <description>Achane caught 8-of-10 targets for 92 yards and a score, a line that would be good for any wide receiver, let alone a running back. The Dolphins’ ground game was nonexistent as Achane tallied just 30 rushing yards, but he saw a lot of designed touches on swing passes and screens to get him into space, where excels at making defenders miss. His touchdown came in the two-minute drill to end the first half on a 29-yard catch-and-run. Achane nearly had another score at the end of the game on what would have been a 44-yard receiving touchdown, but he stepped out of bounds for an 18-yard gain instead. Currently the lead back and a top-three receiver on the team, Achane is a fantasy RB1 heading into Week 3 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a31-d294-a19b-eef136bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson Jr. rushed six times for 20 yards in the 49ers’ Week 2 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a3c-dc44-a9d9-4f7ec4830000</link>
      <description>Robinson “added” a -1 yard reception. B-Rob remained a pure breather back behind workhorse Christian McCaffrey, but no other 49ers runner touched the ball on offense. Although a committee would likely form in the event of a McCaffrey injury, Robinson would easily lead it over Isaac Guerendo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a3c-dc44-a9d9-4f7ec4830000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
