<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said he feels “good” about WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) playing in Week 7 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f419-df81-ab9b-fedfa2ee0000</link>
      <description>Frankly, this is a little surprising. Mooney began the week with two limited practices before sitting out on Friday. Perhaps it was a scheduled day off as Mooney attempts to return from a hamstring strain suffered in Week 4. Despite Morris’ good vibes, the team lists Mooney as questionable to play on the official injury report. If he is active, he can be treated as a boom-bust FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f419-df81-ab9b-fedfa2ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (illness/calf) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f413-d99b-a1dd-fe1f6e6b0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was listed with an illness on Wednesday and Thursday, before having the calf designation added sometime late on Friday. For what it is worth, he did manage to practice in full today, so this could be a non-issue. Fantasy managers should closely monitor news on the matter this weekend, though. Packers RBs Emanuel Wilson and Chris Brooks are next in line if Jacobs cannot play. Wilson has out-touched Brooks 22-7 this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f413-d99b-a1dd-fe1f6e6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos released QB Sam Ehlinger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f429-da18-a39b-fe3b95490000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger was released from the team before being re-signed to the practice squad back in August, and later promoted to the active roster. He is expected to be re-signed to the practice squad again shortly, though he is free to pursue employment elsewhere. The Broncos recently activated LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) from injured reserve. Ehlinger’s release was likely done to create space for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f429-da18-a39b-fe3b95490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f42c-d99b-a1dd-fe2caf2b0000</link>
      <description>Sanders has been sidelined by his sprained ankle since injuring it in Week 3. The 22-year-old tight end will be difficult to trust in his first game back and can only be treated as a TE2. The Panthers are also getting back slot receiver Jalen Coker (quad), and Sanders will likely operate behind him in the target pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f42c-d99b-a1dd-fe2caf2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f483-d651-a9df-fd9721130000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon was a limited participant on Thursday. That is the good news. The bad news is that CB Riq Woolen (concussion) was downgraded from full participation on Thursday to a limited session on Friday. That suggests Woolen’s prior concussion symptoms may have recurred. Seahawks S Julian Love (hamstring) remains limited and LB Derick Hall (oblique) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f483-d651-a9df-fd9721130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak said he wants to give RB Kenneth Walker III “more opportunities” but does not want to “discount” RB Zach Charbonnet and RB George Holani.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f4ab-df81-ab9b-feefbf770000</link>
      <description>Kubiak also celebrated Walker’s improvement “as a practice player,” and for being “very intentional about the things we’re asking him to work on.” Kubiak’s initial statement leaves room for interpretation as to whether the team actually intends to increase Walker’s workload, though. Just yesterday, The Athletic’sMike Dugarasked head coach Mike Macdonald about whether Walker had earned more work with his per-play efficiency, to which Macdonald said the team takes stats “into account,” but that they “have a plan for their RB usage.” Referring to Walker and Charbonnet, Macdonald added that both players are playing “high-level football” and that they will both keep being used. Until we see Walker significantly out-touch Charbonnet, we can only treat Kubiak’s comments as wishful thinking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f4ab-df81-ab9b-feefbf770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (hamstring) and WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) were seen participating in practice on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f52f-da18-a39b-ff3f4df50000</link>
      <description>Evans’ return to practice is less of a surprise. The veteran receiver had a planned rest day on Friday ahead of the Buccaneers’ Monday night tilt with the Lions in Detroit. Egbuka, on the other hand, made a quicker than expected return from his hamstring injury. With the Lions’ secondary already in shambles due to injuries and a Brian Branch suspension, Evans could be a borderline WR1 this week if Egbuka and Chris Godwin are out. Egbuka is a must-start option if he’s able to suit up for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f52f-da18-a39b-ff3f4df50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) has been ruled out for the Week 7 matchup against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f818-da18-a39b-fa1b998a0000</link>
      <description>Slayton hurt his hamstring in Week 5 against the Saints and hasn’t practiced since. The 28-year-old wide receiver was ruled out Saturday to no one’s surprise. A sliver of hope fantasy managers can cling to is that Slayton is yet to be placed on injured reserve, which assumes the Giants believe he can return to the field before missing four games. Lil’Jordan Humphrey led Giants receivers with eight targets against the Eagles last week and will be in line for more work with Slayton out once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f818-da18-a39b-fa1b998a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles told reporters WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) is a game-time decision for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f81c-d651-a9df-f91d53eb0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka made a surprise appearance on the practice field on Saturday. Now his head coach is calling him a game-time decision. Egbuka has a chance to play against the Lions depleted secondary and is a must-start option if he’s ultimately available. Fantasy managers will need to have a backup plan in place, though, with two games on Monday night this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f81c-d651-a9df-f91d53eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders downgraded WR Deebo Samuel (heel) to out for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f879-da18-a39b-fa7bc95e0000</link>
      <description>Woof. Samuel’s absence leaves the Commanders extremely thin at pass-catcher with fellow wide receiver Terry McLaurin ruled out as well. Tight end Zach Ertz is listed as questionable, potentially leaving the team’s pass-catching corps in the hands of aging veteran Chris Moore, Luke McCaffrey, and Jaylin Lane. Expect a heavy dose of Jacory Croskey-Merritt for as long as the game environment allows against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f879-da18-a39b-fa7bc95e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
