<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker III rushed 10 times for 20 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 1 loss to the 49ers, adding three receptions for four yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26ab-dbe3-a9bb-36fb9d490000</link>
      <description>The 49ers’ defense deserves credit, but Walker was simply outplayed by backfield-mate Zach Charbonnet. Walker was on the field for the Seahawks’ first drive. Charbonnet was featured on the second. Curiously, Walker out-targeted Charbonnet three-to-zero, but it was Charbonnet who first took the field on the Seahawks’ final drive, as Seattle’s two-minute offense attempted to generate a comeback. Walker subbed in once the unit entered the red zone but a fumble lost by Sam Darnold ended that brief sequence unceremoniously. Ultimately, Walker totaled just 21 offensive snaps to Charbonnet’s 30. Walker is best viewed as an RB3/FLEX option against the Steelers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26ab-dbe3-a9bb-36fb9d490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 4-of-5 targets for 23 yards in the Lions’ Week 1 loss to the Packers, adding one carry for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26b9-db7b-a5dd-a6bddd1f0000</link>
      <description>Jared Goff faced plenty of pressure from Micah Parsons and the Packers’ pass-rush in this game, leading to a check-down-first approach. As the team’s primary deep threat, that spelled certain doom for Williams. He amassed a measly 13 percent target share and watched rookie Isaac TeSlaa score the team’s only touchdown of the day late in the fourth quarter. Better days will be ahead for Williams when Goff has more time in the pocket, but the Lions are working with multiple new starters on the offensive line and face a strong Chicago pass-rush next week. Williams will be a boom/bust WR3 for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26b9-db7b-a5dd-a6bddd1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley caught 4-of-8 targets for 27 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c4-dbe3-a9bb-36d74c570000</link>
      <description>Ridley struggled to get open with Patrick Surtain shadowing him for much of the contest. Seeing a team-leading 28 percent target share, Ridley could have salvaged his statistical day on two four quarter targets that he dropped, dooming the Titans’ last-minute comeback attempt against the heavily favored Broncos. Ridley accounted for 25 percent of the Titans’ air yards; Elic Ayomanor led the team with a 48 percent air yards share. Ridley will see far more favorable matchups this season, starting with Week 2 against the Rams. Fantasy managers should stick with Ridley as a flex option despite the rough start to 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c4-dbe3-a9bb-36d74c570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet rushed 12 times for 47 yards and one touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 1 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26a0-db7b-a5dd-a6a4c6e80000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet entered the game on the Seahawks’ second drive and began grinding out tough yards en route to a one-yard touchdown run against the 49ers’ talented defense. Charbonnet finished with zero targets, but the box score belies his passing game involvement. It was Charbonnet, not Walker, who initially took the field with the Seahawks’ two-minute offense on the final drive. Walker eventually subbed in and critically remained on the field in the red zone, but it would be unsurprising to see Charbonnet earn a target or two against the Steelers next week. He is an RB3/FLEX for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26a0-db7b-a5dd-a6a4c6e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pollard had 18 rushes for 60 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos, adding one catch for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26cb-de13-afdd-66cb65930000</link>
      <description>Pollard’s reception was by far the biggest play of the day for a moribund Titans offense. He handled 18 of 20 running backs carries for the Titans, even if it didn’t amount to a whole lot against a stiff Denver front seven. With Tyjae Spears (ankle) sidelined for at least the next three weeks, Pollard should have one of the best workloads of any running back outside the elite tier. Softer matchups should deliver better results for the veteran, who ran a route on 25 of 34 Cam Ward drop backs against the Broncos. Pollard takes on the Rams in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26cb-de13-afdd-66cb65930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 2-of-3 targets for 15 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 1 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c9-d332-a1fd-b6ff36cb0000</link>
      <description>Seattle’s passing offense ran through Jaxon Smith-Njigba, who earned 13 targets in this one. Kupp and Kenneth Walker III tied for second on the team, with three apiece. Kupp’s biggest play contribution was an end zone DPI call that set up Zach Charbonnet for a one-yard touchdown plunge, though Kupp had no real chance of corralling the errant pass. Kupp is unlikely to bounce back against the Steelers’ top-notch defense next week. He profiles as a shaky FLEX option, though the squeaky wheel could, of course, get greased with a few first-read looks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c9-d332-a1fd-b6ff36cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo caught 1-of-1 targets for seven yards in the Seahawks’ Week 1 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d39ce70000</link>
      <description>Heralded by head coach Mike Macdonald as the “silent engine” of the Seahawks’ offense in August, Seattle’s tight end group indeed was silent. Arroyo and AJ Barner, who caught 1-of-2 targets for zero yards and rushed once for two yards, were charted by PFF with 31 receiving snaps on 69 offensive snaps, blocking on 36 of them. Neither player can be considered for TE1 purposes against the Steelers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d39ce70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey had six rushes for 70 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans, adding one catch for -1 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e2-de13-afdd-66eb390b0000</link>
      <description>It was JK Dobbins who led the Denver backfield with 16 carries, but it was Harvey in his NFL debut who ripped off a 50-yard scamper in the third quarter — the longest play of the day for the Broncos offense. Harvey ran 14 routes on the day, trailing Dobbins’ 27 routes. Tyler Badie, meanwhile, logged 13 routes and saw six targets. Dobbins was the trusted option who saw all the fourth quarter totes for the Broncos. Harvey could be a while away from taking on a fantasy-friendly workload as long as Dobbins is healthy. Harvey should probably remain on fantasy benches in Week 2 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e2-de13-afdd-66eb390b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Badie caught 2-of-6 targets for 16 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e7-de13-afdd-66ef16220000</link>
      <description>He did not see a carry. Badie was targeted on a remarkable six of his 13 pass routes, as he split the pass-catching backfield role with JK Dobbins (two targets) and RJ Harvey (one target). Jaleel McLaughlin was a healthy scratch against the Titans, leaving Badie as the team’s No. 3 back. The Denver backfield is more muddled than anyone could have guessed this summer, and Badie is worth rostering in deeper formats in case Harvey or Dobbins get dinged up in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e7-de13-afdd-66ef16220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 6-of-9 targets for 79 yards in the Lions’ Week 1 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c8-dbe3-a9bb-36dbeedc0000</link>
      <description>LaPorta was the lone bright spot on a Detroit offense that came out flat in Week 1. The third-year tight end worked the middle of the field well, connecting with Goff for multiple chunk gains, including catches for 32 and 16 yards. LaPorta clocked in with a 24 percent target share, picking up wear he left off after finishing 2024 with a string of strong performances. He will stay in the top half of the TE1 ranks for Week 2 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c8-dbe3-a9bb-36dbeedc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
