<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released RB Royce Freeman.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e27b-dbe3-a9bb-f27bec040000</link>
      <description>Freeman had only joined the Bears last week — the veteran will probably find a practice squad by the time the week is over. The Bears also waived DB Millard Bradford, DL Xavier Carlton, DB Alex Cook, LB Power Echols, DB Kaleb Hayes, QB Austin Reed, RB Ian Wheeler, and TE Joel Wilson. Additionally they released DB Tre Flowers and OL Joshua Miles, and placed DB Zah Frazier on the NFI list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e27b-dbe3-a9bb-f27bec040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers released CB Bryce Hall.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e296-d332-a1fd-f6b686c00000</link>
      <description>Hall missed most of 2024 after fracturing his fibula in Week 1. In two preseason appearances, Hall allowed four receptions for 71 yards and one touchdown on four targets. FOX Sports’ Greg Auman believes Hall could “easily” land on another final roster, but would be welcomed back to the Buccaneers via the practice squad if he doesn’t.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e296-d332-a1fd-f6b686c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes it’s “possible” a potential suspension for Quinshon Judkins “could come at roster cuts.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-df33-de13-afdc-dffb19aa0000</link>
      <description>The Browns would “likely move toward signing him and probably seek a temporary roster exemption” if Judkins dodges a suspension. If the scenario plays out like that, it’s possible Judkins could be ready to hit the Browns roster around the start of October. A suspension for his battery charges that were dismissed is still possible as the league investigates further. Judkins is clearly who the Browns wanted to hand the backfield over to — at this point the question seems to be more “when?” than anything.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-df33-de13-afdc-dffb19aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers requested a trade amidst new contract negotiations.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e262-db7b-a5dd-e266e33f0000</link>
      <description>Rapsheet notes that Meyers recently requested a trade while the two sides were negotiating a new contract, which was denied by the team. “The team, citing his value, said they had not plans (to trade him),” Rapoport adds. The two sides attempted to negotiate a new contract but were unable to come to terms, leaving the veteran wide receiver to play out the final year of his three-year, $33 million contract with the Raiders in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e262-db7b-a5dd-e266e33f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said he’s “optimistic” Josh Downs (hamstring) will practice next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2af-db7b-a5dd-e2af075c0000</link>
      <description>Downs has been sidelined since August 14 with a hamstring injury. While it’s good to see some optimism, the fact that they’re already planning to keep him out this week paints a picture where Downs is probably questionable for Week 1 at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2af-db7b-a5dd-e2af075c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said he expects Jaire Alexander (knee) to return to practice next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2b4-dbe3-a9bb-f2f7245d0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh then added that he believes in the tooth fairy. (OK, not really.) Alexander has already had the knee drained this offseason and the maintenance of said knee probably leaves the Ravens in a scenario where he’ll be questionable on a weekly basis. When Alexander plays he should give the Ravens a third great corner, but they’ll have to manage him carefully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2b4-dbe3-a9bb-f2f7245d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said K Jason Sanders (hip) won’t be available for the start of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2b7-dbe3-a9bb-f2f765050000</link>
      <description>“Surgery isn’t necessary, but time is,” McDaniel said. This likely will wind up with Sanders being placed on IR and the Dolphins bringing in a kicker after last cuts. Don’t go drafting Sanders this week for your kicker spot. ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes Sanders will be sidelined 4-5 weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2b7-dbe3-a9bb-f2f765050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright (leg) will not play in Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2a9-de13-afdc-e6eba6e80000</link>
      <description>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said Wright’s expected return should come “not too far off... after that.” It’s a tough break for Wright, who may already be losing his job to rookie Ollie Gordon. De’Von Achane is also dealing with a calf injury, though his practice absences have been described as “preventative.” Gordon could find himself in a rotational role soon enough and is worth stashing on fantasy benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2a9-de13-afdc-e6eba6e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions waived QB Hendon Hooker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2cb-de13-afdc-e6cbf2350000</link>
      <description>Well, you can’t say they didn’t telegraph this as Hooker played behind Kyle Allen in their fourth preseason game and was pulled early in Detroit’s second game of the preseason for turning the ball over too often. Hooker could wind up back with Detroit on the practice squad, but it’s possible some other team likes the 27-year-old enough to give him a 53-man roster spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2cb-de13-afdc-e6cbf2350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs waived QB Bailey Zappe.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e28a-db7b-a5dd-e28e2ccf0000</link>
      <description>Zappe was unable to unseat Gardner Minshew for the Chiefs’ No. 2 quarterback gig, so he’ll seek a roster spot elsewhere. Zappe will likely find a home on a practice squad somewhere. He spent time on the Chiefs’ last year, before the Browns signed him to a rest-of-season deal in October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e28a-db7b-a5dd-e28e2ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
