<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins fired OLB coach Ryan Crow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-144a-d77b-adfb-decb6ba60000</link>
      <description>Crow was placed on leave earlier this year after being “arrested in late August on domestic battery charges.” Dolphins defensive assistant coach Sean Ryan will continue working with the outside linebackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-144a-d77b-adfb-decb6ba60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is questionable for Minnesota’s Week 15 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1451-d005-a9bf-dc7501f30000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session today to get to questionable after two DNPs earlier in the week. Darrisaw was active last week after missing Week 13 and his status seems to very touch-and-go at this point. We imagine he’s a game-time decision for the Vikings in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1451-d005-a9bf-dc7501f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Kenny Pickett will start Las Vegas’ Week 15 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1452-d1bc-a3fb-9576e67f0000</link>
      <description>Pickett may only be getting a one week audition here, as Carroll said that Geno Smith “will be back” against the Texans in Week 16. Against the Eagles’ stellar pass defense, Pickett is best approached as a QB3 in superflex leagues and even an optimistic view can’t see him as better than a low-end QB2 with almost nothing around him beyond Brock Bowers and Ashton Jeanty. It’s just not an ideal situation, even if he did look decent in relief of Smith in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1452-d1bc-a3fb-9576e67f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Geno Smith (shoulder/back) won’t play in Las Vegas’ Week 15 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1456-d8cf-affb-bc7e0dad0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week and Raiders coach Pete Carroll said he was “concerned” about the lower back injury while the shoulder injury is “manageable.” Carroll did say that Smith “will be back next week,” but we wouldn’t be surprised if this lingered on, especially if Kenny Pickett runs with the opportunity on Sunday. Smith was already off the 1QB league radar; this probably leaves him as droppable in superflex leagues if the roster spot is necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1456-d8cf-affb-bc7e0dad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-144c-d8cf-affb-bc6ecd260000</link>
      <description>Downs is a talented player, stuck in a crowded pass-catching corps, vying for targets thrown by either an unproven rookie quarterback or a 44-year-old who has not played since 2020. He is also facing an elite pass defense. Downs is a WR5 with a very low floor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-144c-d8cf-affb-bc6ecd260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (ribs) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1442-d1bc-a3fb-956691d40000</link>
      <description>The Colts’ field-stretching wide receiver is a capable player, but this is an unfortunate situation. The Seahawks’ pass defense is one of the league’s best, and the Colts still have not decided on whether Philip Rivers or Riley Leonard (knee) will start this week. Pierce is a boom-bust WR5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1442-d1bc-a3fb-956691d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) is questionable for Baltimore’s Week 15 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1459-d77b-adfb-dedb1a2e0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice Friday after popping up on the report as limited on Thursday — it sounds like he’s re-aggravated his ankle injury that had him miss a game last month. Bateman should be regarded as truly questionable, at best, to play against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1459-d77b-adfb-dedb1a2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Riley Leonard (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1453-d1bc-a3fb-9577e3a10000</link>
      <description>Leonard practiced all week after picking up a PCL sprain in his knee in Week 14. Leonard’s QB2 viability is tied directly to his rushing production, and Philip Rivers could be the team’s starter this weekend. Leonard is very difficult to trust as a QB2, even is he does get the start, facing the Seahawks’ elite defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1453-d1bc-a3fb-9577e3a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (NIR/rest) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 15 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-145a-d8cf-affb-bc7a9c980000</link>
      <description>As expected. He practiced in full each of the last two days and should be set to be whatever version of himself he can muster in Week 15 against the Bengals. It’s probably a game you have to start him into if you drafted him, but his recent form is not encouraging in the slightest even if he looks healthier than he did earlier in his comeback from the hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-145a-d8cf-affb-bc7a9c980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell (knee) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 15 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-145c-d005-a9bf-dc7c4e060000</link>
      <description>He’ll be wheels-up as a potential RB3/FLEX option against a sad sack Bengals defense. Mitchell had full practices in each of the last two days of the week. It appears his Week 14 injury was just a scare at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-145c-d005-a9bf-dc7c4e060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
