<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:15:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports the Titans will interview ex-Cowboys OC Jason Garrett for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9588-d968-a19b-ddf9697c0000</link>
      <description>Garrett, part of NBC’s NFL coverage since 2022, had an 85-67 career record as Dallas Cowboys head coach from 2010-2019. Our last blurbs on Garrett are from the 2021 season, where he was fired midseason as Giants offensive coordinator. We have not seen any interest in interviewing him for a head coaching or offensive coordinator position since that point. The Titans are casting quite a wide net in their head-coaching search.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9588-d968-a19b-ddf9697c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9596-d35e-a1bf-d5d656630000</link>
      <description>Wicks missed Week 18 with a concussion and starts out this week limited in practice. The 24-year-old finished the regular season with a 30/332/2 line amidst a crowded wide receiver depth chart. Tuesday’s practice was just a walkthrough for the Packers, but it is encouraging that Wicks was estimated to be a limited participant. He has a chance to return in the Wild Card round against the Bears. The Packers’ only non-participant Tuesday was CB/WR Bo Melton, who sat with a knee issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9596-d35e-a1bf-d5d656630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-959f-d56e-afff-f7ff24960000</link>
      <description>Ferguson sat out Week 18 after being a late addition to the injury report with a hamstring injury. He starts out the week listed as DNP as the Rams held a walkthrough on Tuesday. Also DNP were WR Jordan Whittington (knee) and OL Kevin Dotson (ankle). The Rams’ key offensive players will have a few days to practice ahead of a Saturday Wild Card showdown against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-959f-d56e-afff-f7ff24960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) was listed as a full participant for Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95a8-d35e-a1bf-d5ea9e930000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay has already said Adams is expected to play in the team’s Wild Card matchup against the Panthers Saturday. The Rams only held a walkthrough Tuesday, but the estimation that Adams would be a full practice participant is good news. The veteran sat out the last few games of the regular season since aggravating his hamstring injury in Week 15 but the Rams will get their goal-line target back for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95a8-d35e-a1bf-d5ea9e930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports the Cardinals have requested to interview Patriots pass game coordinator Thomas Brown for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95ac-d35e-a1bf-d5ee07bc0000</link>
      <description>Brown spent the 2025 season as the Patriots’ passing game coordinator and helped build a thriving offense around MVP candidate Drake Maye. The 39-year-old was an interim head coach for the Bears in 2024 and has had multiple roles with Sean McVay and the Rams from 2020-2022. Brown is now back on the head coaching radar, with Arizona first to come calling with an interview request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95ac-d35e-a1bf-d5ee07bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns beat writer Mary Kay Cabot reports the Browns have requested to interview Seahawks defensive coordinator Aden Durde for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95b0-dc7a-af9b-dfbf1f630000</link>
      <description>Durde joined the Seahawks as defensive coordinator for Mike Macdonald in 2024. Seattle finished the 2025 regular season posting the best defensive DVOA in the league and has had two successful defensive seasons under Macdonald and Durde. Though Macdonald is the prevailing defensive mind in Seattle, Durde still gets some of the credit for the No. 1 seed Seahawks and will get a chance to interview for a head coaching spot with the Browns and call his own defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95b0-dc7a-af9b-dfbf1f630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh is “expected to emerge as a favorite” for the Giants’ head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95b6-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5d70000</link>
      <description>As expected, Harbaugh is the top head coaching candidate on the market just moments after his firing. The Giants have been looking for a head coach since firing Brian Daboll midseason and now Schefter reports Harbaugh is expected to be the favorite for their open position. Schefter also reports that seven teams called Harbaugh’s agent, Bryan Harlan, with interest in hiring him within moments of his firing. Suffice to say, Harbaugh is a hot candidate on the head coaching market and the Giants are immediately a team to watch in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95b6-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95f4-d968-a19b-ddf5a5320000</link>
      <description>Tate is projected to be one of the draft’s top wide receiver prospects, foregoing his final season of eligibility to declare early out of Ohio State. He accomplished a sophomore year of 52 receptions for 733 yards and four touchdowns, following it up with a 51/875/9 line his junior year. Tate crossed the 100-yard mark in four games in 2025 as the Buckeyes’ No. 2 wide receiver and will now enter the draft early to first-round buzz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95f4-d968-a19b-ddf5a5320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Raiders requested to interview Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-963a-dc7a-af9b-dfbff1060000</link>
      <description>Webb is a former 2017 third-round pick who started one game in 2022 before the Broncos hired him as quarterbacks coach in 2023 under Sean Payton. He also held the role of passing game coordinator for the 2025 season. Webb’s role in developing Bo Nix through the first two years of his career explain the Raiders’ interest in him; Vegas has a quarterback likely on the way with the No. 1 overall pick. The Raiders await the opportunity to interview Webb for their head coaching job amidst the Broncos’ playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-963a-dc7a-af9b-dfbff1060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
