<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:02:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Penix completed 21-of-38 passes for 241 yards and one touchdown in the Falcons’ 20-10, Week 7 loss to the 49ers, adding six yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feb2-d99b-a1dd-febe258f0000</link>
      <description>He also lost a fumble in the loss while completing just 55.3% of his pass attempts. The Falcons now average under 11 points per game on the road this season, dead last in the league through seven weeks, and were shut out by the Panthers in their last road game way back in Week 3. Robert Saleh brought consistent pressure throughout the game in Week 7, sacking Penix only twice but placing him under consistent duress in the backfield. One such instance late in the game left Penix hobbled after he was forced to get rid of the football earlier than he would have liked. He shook it off to stay in the game, but fantasy managers will want to monitor his status in the coming week of practice as he did not look comfortable the rest of the team’s final drive. The Falcons fall to 3-3 with the loss ahead of a Week 8 meeting with the Dolphins at home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-feb2-d99b-a1dd-febe258f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 14 times for 40 yards in the Falcons’ Week 7 loss to the 49ers, adding 52 yards and a touchdown on six receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffa4-df81-ab9b-ffe776ab0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons struggled to move the football against a beat up San Francisco defense in the face of consistent pressure from Robert Saleh’s defense, gaining just 292 yards of total offense while lowering their league-low 11 points per game on the road in 2025. Robinson was able to contribute solid counting stats for fantasy managers regardless while scoring the only touchdown for the Falcons, buoying his fantasy score by 17.2 points in PPR formats. He remains an elite asset, particularly so ahead of a matchup with the reeling Dolphins in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffa4-df81-ab9b-ffe776ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 3-of-5 targets for 68 yards in the Falcons’ Week 7 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffa8-df81-ab9b-ffef57f30000</link>
      <description>The fact that Mooney led the team in receiving with only 68 yards tells the story of how the night went for the Falcons, who had no answer for Robert Saleh’s mounting pressure throughout. They managed only 292 yards of total offense while scoring just 10 points, now averaging under 11 points per game on the road this season. Fantasy managers were almost assuredly left wanting more from Mooney, but he did appear to make it through the entire contest absent an aggravation to the hamstring injury that cost him Week 6. Up next is a tantalizing matchup with the downtrodden Dolphins at home in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffa8-df81-ab9b-ffef57f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 7-of-10 targets for 62 yards in the Falcons’ Week 7 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffac-d99b-a1dd-ffac23700000</link>
      <description>Pitts was clearly a large part of the offensive game plan against the Fred Warner-less 49ers, seeing consistent targets as quarterback Michael Penix continually dealt with aggressive pressure from Robert Saleh’s defense. He was unable to generate meaningful yardage as his longest reception went for only 19 yards, but fantasy managers can take solace in the fact that he tied for the team lead with 10 targets. The early returns from Pitts unfortunately mimic his previous two seasons and not his breakout rookie year, making him a shaky TE2 ahead of a solid on-paper matchup against the Dolphins in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffac-d99b-a1dd-ffac23700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 4-of-10 targets for 42 yards in the Falcons’ Week 7 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffaf-df81-ab9b-ffef88cd0000</link>
      <description>London tied with tight end Kyle Pitts for the team lead in targets but was highly inefficient with his looks. In fairness to him, most of that was due to poor play from quarterback Michael Penix, who had no real answer for consistent pressure from Robert Saleh’s aggressive 49ers defense. Even so, London’s modest returns are worrisome considering they coincide with the return of Darnell Mooney to the lineup, something that has been a trend since the start of the 2024 season. Up next for London and the Falcons are the Dolphins at home in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffaf-df81-ab9b-ffef88cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 24 times for 129 yards and two touchdowns in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons, adding 72 yards on seven receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffb2-d99b-a1dd-ffbe53df0000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey quite literally put the team on his back against the Falcons, scoring both touchdowns while also leading the team in receiving. The return of tight end George Kittle appeared to do wonders for the room McCaffrey had prior to first contact, with the 139-yard outburst on the ground marking the first time since Week 1 in which he managed more than 57 yards rushing. Up next for the All-World veteran is a difficult matchup against the Texans on the road in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffb2-d99b-a1dd-ffbe53df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones completed 17-of-26 passes for 152 yards and one interception in the 49ers’ 20-10, Week 7 win over the Falcons, adding 11 yards on five carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffb5-da18-a39b-ffb7a2c00000</link>
      <description>Almost half of Jones’ 152 yards through the air were accounted for by running back Christian McCaffrey in a game the two teams combined for only 616 yards of total offense, but the veteran journeyman again did enough to will the 49ers to another victory. Jones is now 4-1 as a starter for the 49ers, playing through injury the previous two games while keeping the team tied with the Rams atop the NFC West. The box scores haven’t always looked pretty, but Jones continues to do his job by keeping the team competitive until Brock Purdy’s eventual return under center. It is unclear if he will be tasked with another start in Week 8, but fantasy expectations should be held in check should his number be called against a tough Texans team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffb5-da18-a39b-ffb7a2c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-7 targets for 31 yards in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbb-da18-a39b-ffbb41c40000</link>
      <description>Jennings continues to gut through multiple injuries, this time finishing one target off the team lead behind running back Christian McCaffrey. Even so, a muted game environment in which the two teams combined for only 616 yards of total offense led to only 26 pass attempts from quarterback Mac Jones, leaving Jennings’ fantasy returns of little interest. Up next is a difficult matchup with a stout Houston defense in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbb-da18-a39b-ffbb41c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught both targets for 14 yards in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbd-d99b-a1dd-ffbdce820000</link>
      <description>After amassing 284 yards the previous two games while working as the top pass-catcher, the returns of Jauan Jennings and George Kittle left Bourne with only two targets on a night quarterback Mac Jones attempted only 26 passes. It is clear that Bourne is capable of returning solid counting stats when he serves as the top option through the air, but that might not be the case as the team continues inching closer to full health. Bourne should remain on fantasy benches ahead of a Week 8 meeting with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbd-d99b-a1dd-ffbdce820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle failed to catch either of his two targets in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffc0-d651-a9df-ffd555420000</link>
      <description>Kittle left fantasy managers with a nice goose egg in his return from injured reserve but made his presence felt while helping to spring running back Christian McCaffrey for a season-high 129 yards on the ground. This was the first game all season in which the 49ers played with both Kittle and fullback Kyle Juszczyk for the duration of the game, and the returns were sparkling - at least as the team was concerned. Kittle remains unlikely to command elite volume but maintains a lofty weekly ceiling considering his per-catch upside, making him a wide range of outcomes play ahead of a meeting with the stout Texans in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffc0-d651-a9df-ffd555420000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
