<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is off Las Vegas’ final Week 3 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b0-d1b3-a5dd-63f11d720000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited practices this week. While he didn’t exactly look like he was going full-strength on Monday night, there’s no obvious reason to sit Bowers in Week 3 given he practiced more this week and no tight end in the league has the ceiling case that Bowers grants while healthy. If he’s fully healed from the Week 1 injury, Bowers should be the featured component of Vegas’ passing game against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b0-d1b3-a5dd-63f11d720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (biceps) is not on Los Angeles’ final Week 3 injury report against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7624b0000</link>
      <description>He’ll be full-go in Week 3 against the Broncos, it’s not an easy matchup, but McConkey should be able to exploit the middle of the field in the same way Josh Downs was able to last week against Broncos slot corner Brandon Jones. He’ll be on the WR1/WR2 borderline for Week 3 despite getting off to a (comparatively) slow start compared to Keenan Allen and Quentin Johnston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7624b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) will not play in Week 3’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b6-d1b3-a5dd-63f7c3320000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week. Tyler Conklin and Oronde Gadsden figure to see more opportunities with Dissly gone, though neither of them are better than TE2 dart throws for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b6-d1b3-a5dd-63f7c3320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Daiyan Henley (illness) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 3 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b8-d6a5-adff-f7fd7b230000</link>
      <description>It’s kind of surprising that the illness has lasted this long — Henley drew another DNP in practice on Friday after also missing Wednesday — and even despite him playing through it on Monday Night it’s certainly possible he sits this game out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b8-d6a5-adff-f7fd7b230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out TE Evan Engram (back) for Week 3 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d1b3-a5dd-63f3a6210000</link>
      <description>Like many 31-year-olds, Engram’s back is aching. Unfortunately for him, Engram plays professional football and is also coming off a calf injury. He was completely unable to practice this week, as was LB Dre Greenlaw (quad). At some point, Engram may regain his health and allow us to fully measure how much talent he has left in the tank, but for now, Engram can be dropped if an injured tight end like Dallas Goedert or Isaiah Likely is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d1b3-a5dd-63f3a6210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) is “highly unlikely” to start despite being questionable to play in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63c0-d6a5-adff-f7c530640000</link>
      <description>Tomorrow, the team will see how Purdy is feeling, to determine if he can be the No. 2 or emergency No. 3 quarterback. Fantasy managers who are in desperate need of a QB2 with moderate upside should have Mac Jones at their disposal. The pocket passer completed 26-of-39 passes for 279 yards and three touchdowns and rushed six times for six yards against the Saints last week. He also fumbled twice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63c0-d6a5-adff-f7c530640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63db-d1b3-a5dd-63fb56bf0000</link>
      <description>Jennings did not participate in Friday’s practice. Instead, he worked off to the side during the portion of practice open to the media. The 28-year-old veteran does not necessarily need to practice in order to play, but his inability to do so is concerning. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan typically lets his injured players take their normal allotment of snaps on game day, for good or ill. Given that, Jennings’ ceiling remains intact, but he would obviously be at risk of an in-game setback. He makes for a risky WR3/FLEX option if he is active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63db-d1b3-a5dd-63fb56bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said WR Jordan Watkins (calf) is a candidate for injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7a07d0000</link>
      <description>Watkins is expected to miss three or four weeks after injuring his calf on Thursday. The rookie wide receiver cannot catch a break. He was considered a candidate to assume Nos. 3 or 4 wide receivers duties at one point in training camp, but his progress was derailed by an ankle injury. Having successfully rehabbed that, he is unfortunately now dealing with a new issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63b3-d93f-ad9d-7bf7a07d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) is doubtful for Week 3 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63f3-dfde-a1bd-7fffd79a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson’s teammate, CB Max Melton, is questionable to play with a knee injury. He was limited in practice all week. Johnson was completely unable to participate. Injuries are never good, but the Cardinals may be catching a break this week, facing the Mac Jones-led 49ers. Jones is without George Kittle (hamstring), and Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) is questionable to play despite failing to practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63f3-dfde-a1bd-7fffd79a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said Jordan Mason is going to be used “a lot” in the Vikings’ Week 3 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-646e-dfde-a1bd-7eef844c0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings are expected to be without both J.J. McCarthy (ankle) and Aaron Jones (hamstring) for multiple games. McCarthy’s return timeline sits in the two-to-four week range while Jones must miss at least four games on injured reserve. Earlier this week, Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell expressed “confidence” in utilizing Mason as a “potential bellcow.” Unfortunately, C Ryan Kelly (concussion) and backup LT Justin Skule (concussion) are out for Week 3. LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is questionable. Still, Mason is a volume-based, high-end RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-646e-dfde-a1bd-7eef844c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
