<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel/NIR) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca83-d94a-a79d-cb8fe1990000</link>
      <description>We’re not overly concerned about this listing and Deebo also missed two practices with a heel injury last week before getting cleared off the injury report on Friday. We’d expect much the same treatment. ESPN’s John Keim noted that he “would not describe [Samuel] as worried about his chances for Monday” after talking to the veteran receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca83-d94a-a79d-cb8fe1990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca95-def2-abdb-dff5662b0000</link>
      <description>It’s the first we’re hearing about an injury for Rodriguez, who took most of the snaps on Washington’s final drive as they tried to close things out against Atlanta with a big lead. We already knew that “Bill” would be a massive favorite for snaps this week, but a Rodriguez injury could push his Croskey-Merritt’s ceiling even higher against the Bears in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca95-def2-abdb-dff5662b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (wrist) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca95-dd4c-afb9-efd5c3df0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown was joined by Lions No. 3 WR Kalif Raymond (neck), who practiced for the first time this week in a limited capacity. Hope for a game featuring Jameson Williams’ speed briefly flickered to life when both St. Brown and Raymond appeared on the Wednesday injury report as non-participants, but both players’ return likely pushes Williams back into his field-stretching role. While Williams should still be in fantasy lineups in what should be a high-scoring game against the Chiefs, St. Brown will undoubtedly dominate targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca95-dd4c-afb9-efd5c3df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Jayden Daniels (knee) is practicing in full ahead of Week 6’s game with the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca97-def2-abdb-dff74ac90000</link>
      <description>We have no reason to doubt that Daniels will play at this point, but it’s always worth pointing out when the quarterback is on the injury report. Daniels by all reports checked out okay after the game and should be a locked-in QB1 against the Bears in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca97-def2-abdb-dff74ac90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles activated LB Nakobe Dean (knee) from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca98-dd4c-afb9-efd999c00000</link>
      <description>He’ll make his season debut against the Giants on Thursday and likely be eased in after suffering a torn patella tendon in the playoffs last year during Philadelphia’s Super Bowl run. Jihaad Campbell has been just fine so there’s no rush for Dean to assume full-time duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca98-dd4c-afb9-efd999c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca9b-dd4c-afb9-efdbc9ed0000</link>
      <description>It puts him in a tough spot for Week 6. Mac Jones, who is also on the injury report, could grab another start against the Buccaneers. Adam Schefter believes that this DNP puts Jones “on track” to start. It certainly doesn’t appear that there’s much positive momentum with Purdy’s injury at the moment. He was spotted by reporters on a side field with Ricky Pearsall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca9b-dd4c-afb9-efdbc9ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca9f-db72-a199-fadf9cab0000</link>
      <description>Kyle Shanahan said he was “not counting” on Pearsall returning this week and after two straight missed practices, neither are we. Jauan Jennings did return to practice today, and it looks like Kendrick Bourne will once again operate as a main target for the 49ers with Mac Jones under center against Tampa Bay. Bourne’s situation is not quite as advantageous as it was last week if Jennings is able to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca9f-db72-a199-fadf9cab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) remained limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caaa-def2-abdb-dfeb38f40000</link>
      <description>It’s hard to tell if Watson is going to do enough to get activated off PUP after a couple of limited practices, but everything we’ve heard up to this point has been very optimistic about his odds of getting on the field soon. Perhaps it will be Week 7 or 8 instead of this week. Friday will likely need to be a ramp-up day if Watson is going to be activated to play against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caaa-def2-abdb-dfeb38f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caa9-db72-a199-faeb71fa0000</link>
      <description>That’s bad. Gonzalez missed Weeks 1-3 due to a hamstring injury. He was a little rusty in his Week 4 debut, but allowed just one reception on four targets in Week 5, notching one forced incompletion and two tackles. Hopefully, this is just a pre-planned rest day. Unfortunately, it could be a re-injury, though. The Patriots are tasked with containing the Saints’ capable wide receivers in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caa9-db72-a199-faeb71fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports, TE Daniel Bellinger is “expected to play a significant role” with Giants shorthanded at wide receiver in Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cab6-d94a-a79d-cbbf79f70000</link>
      <description>Bellinger led the Giants in receiving yards last week, catching 4-of-4 targets for 52 yards against the Saints. The Giants lost Malik Nabers (knee) in Week 4 and Darius Slayton (hamstring) after 55 snaps in Week 5. Head coach Brian Daboll used two-tight end sets at the sixth-highest rate last week (39.7 percent). While Bellinger is perhaps unlikely to post gaudy receiving sums, both he and TE Theo Johnson are viable TE1 streamers against the Eagles, thanks to their expectedly decent involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cab6-d94a-a79d-cbbf79f70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
