<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared WR A.J. Brown, OLB Azeez Ojulari, CB Adoree’ Jackson, C Cam Jurgens, and QB Sam Howell inactive for Week 8 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2119-d5d8-a3ff-f9798ee70000</link>
      <description>Brown is expected to return after the team’s Week 9 bye. DeVonta Smith becomes an elite fantasy play with Brown sidelined, going against a middling New York coverage unit. Dallas Goedert profiles as a top-five tight end play with Brown out. Philly’s secondary could continue to struggle with Jackson sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2119-d5d8-a3ff-f9798ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared DE Keion White, S Kyle Dugger, LB Caleb Murphy, DT Eric Gregory, OL Caedan Wallace, WR Efton Chism, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 8 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-d5d8-a3ff-f969e6580000</link>
      <description>Dugger is set to miss Week 8 with a knee issue that kept him limited in practice and landed him with a questionable tag heading into Sunday. Meanwhile, White is a surprise healthy scratch. Both White and Dugger could be on the trade block ahead of the November 4th trade deadline, but for now the Pats make both inactive against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-d5d8-a3ff-f969e6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is active for Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212f-deb1-a39b-212fc4380000</link>
      <description>Njoku was listed as questionable after a week’s worth of limited practices due to a knee injury he suffered in Week 6. He missed Week 7 against the Dolphins, but is now back for Week 8 against the Patriots. Rookie Harold Fannin’s presence makes the waters murky for Njoku’s fantasy value, but he is a solid low-end fantasy TE1 for this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212f-deb1-a39b-212fc4380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewers, DB Elijah Campbell, CB Juju Brents, S Jordan Colbert, WR Tahj Washington, DT Zeek Biggers, and TE Julian Hill inactive for Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b42170000</link>
      <description>Ewers is back to QB3 duties this week after getting a few reps in garbage time against the Browns in Week 7. Zach Wilson will back up Tua Tagovailoa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b42170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) is active for Week 8 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2131-d245-adfb-b57f85430000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson missed last week’s game against the Steelers, but a Thursday showdown was always going to be a hard turnaround for him to make. The mini-bye was more than enough to get him back on the field for Week 8, just in time to terrorize Justin Fields. Inactive for the Bengals are CB Marco Wilson, OL Matt Lee, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DT McKinnley Jackson, and DE Cam Sample.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2131-d245-adfb-b57f85430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared S Jevón Holland, WR Jalin Hyatt, CB Paulson Adebo, T James Hudson III, DL Chauncey Golston, OL Evan Neal, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2134-dab4-a3fb-bb74105e0000</link>
      <description>Holland continues to deal with a lingering knee injury. The absence of Holland and Adebo could make for a good matchup for Jalen Hurts and the Philly pass catchers. The Eagles have been far more pass heavy than usual in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2134-dab4-a3fb-bb74105e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier (hip) is active for Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-213f-d245-adfb-b57fd1740000</link>
      <description>Allgeier was limited in practice throughout the week but never appeared to be in much danger of missing today’s game. Even with Kirk Cousins under center, the Falcons are comfortable home favorites versus the lowly Dolphins. There should be more than enough carries to go around for the Falcons’ backs this week. Allgeier sits on the RB3/4 border for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-213f-d245-adfb-b57fd1740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Jets C Nick Mangold passed away at age 41.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-213e-deb1-a39b-213e4a5a0000</link>
      <description>Mangold posted online in mid-October that he was in need of a kidney transplant after being diagnosed with a genetic defect that led to chronic kidney disease. The Jets confirmed Mangold’s passing in an X post on Sunday. A first round selection by the Jets in the 2006 NFL Draft, Mangold served as the team’s starting center for 11 seasons, making seven Pro Bowls. Mangold is survived by his wife and children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-213e-deb1-a39b-213e4a5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Chargers CB Tarheeb Still suffered an MCL sprain in Week 8 against the Vikings and will miss 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2144-dab4-a3fb-bb748eca0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like Still will land on injured reserve, but it’s another blow to a Chargers team that has struggled to stay healthy this year. Still has started all eight games this year. He has 31 tackles, two TFLs, and six pass breakups. His absence could put the Chargers in the market for a cornerback as the trade deadline approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2144-dab4-a3fb-bb748eca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts QB Anthony Richardson had surgery to repair his orbital bone.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-216e-d5d8-a3ff-f96f153d0000</link>
      <description>There remains a chance, per Rapoport, that Richardson returns this season. It likely won’t matter for the Colts unless Daniel Jones misses time with injury. Richardson injured his eye in a freak pre-game accident earlier this month. He’s likely done with the Colts and could be dealt this offseason to a QB-needy team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-216e-d5d8-a3ff-f96f153d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
