<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a28d-db57-afda-f6bff6760000</link>
      <description>Swift can be counted on once again this weekend. The Bears’ starting running back continues to churn out usable stat lines despite the nagging hip issue. No. 3 RB Roschon Johnson continues to be a non-factor in an injury-plagued season, and this week is no different. After missing Week 8 with a back issue, Johnson is now nursing a thumb injury. Fellow backup RB Travis Homer (hamstring/knee) was downgraded to a DNP and a limited session on Wednesday. Expect Swift and Kyle Monangai to operate as usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a28d-db57-afda-f6bff6760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f2-d90e-a9da-bfff9a020000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound likely that Ayomanor will play against the Seahawks on Sunday, and with the Titans already down Calvin Ridley, it’s possible they get deeper into their depth chart for Week 12. Mason Kinsey and James Proche II, the current backups, are special teamers. The Titans team account has been spending a lot of time hyping practice-squad UDFA Xavier Restrepo this week. Putting those two things together, it’s certainly possible Restrepo plays a role in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f2-d90e-a9da-bfff9a020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f1-d90e-a9da-bfff24080000</link>
      <description>Bears LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) remains sidelined as well. The two players are on the wrong side of questionable for Week 12, which is bad news. They face the Steelers’ run-heavy offense this weekend, and RB Jaylen Warren (ankle) returned to practice today after taking the day off yesterday. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f1-d90e-a9da-bfff24080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f7-d82c-a79a-b3f718c40000</link>
      <description>Earlier today Arthur Smith said when asked about Rodgers that “I just trust him. This isn’t his first rodeo.” It does seem like the Steelers are planning to let Rodgers make the decision himself about whether he plays or not. If the wrist injury turns out to be worse-than-expected, he might be an in-game benching or re-injury risk against the Bears in Week 12, but he was already on the QB2 line and this is already a rough week for the QB2 line. Perhaps things turn around tomorrow, but the undercurrent here is that Rodgers will attempt to play through the wrist injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2f7-d82c-a79a-b3f718c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (pectoral) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2fa-db57-afda-f6fa45810000</link>
      <description>It’s the first practice he’s played in since injuring the pectoral in Week 10. It’s possible Highsmith will be out there against the Bears in Week 12, though we’d still bet on him hitting the questionable line at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2fa-db57-afda-f6fa45810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (groin) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2cf-d413-ad9f-b7df94510000</link>
      <description>Johnson underwent core muscle surgery earlier this season and was placed on injured reserve, along with slot CB Kyler Gordon, who aggravated a hamstring strain suffered in August. Since last Friday, the Bears have designated both players to return. Gordon and No. 2 perimeter CB Tyrique Stevenson (hip/calf) remain limited at practice, but the unit’s health is significantly improving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2cf-d413-ad9f-b7df94510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans waived RB Dameon Pierce.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a301-d413-ad9f-b7dd0c1f0000</link>
      <description>Pierce had only been active four times this season, taking merely 23 offensive snaps along the way while Woody Marks took over as the main early-down addition this year behind Nick Chubb. Pierce, still just 25, stands a good chance at being claimed. He nearly ran for 1,000 yards for the 2022 Texans and has proven to be a reliable kick returner as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a301-d413-ad9f-b7dd0c1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a300-d413-ad9f-b7ddbf4b0000</link>
      <description>This is Slayton’s first time practicing since aggravating his hamstring strain in Week 10. While his return is positive, he is not yet guaranteed to play in Week 12. Ideally, Slayton will practice fully before doing so. If active, he could return FLEX value on one or two deep targets, though he would possess re-injury risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a300-d413-ad9f-b7ddbf4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is practicing in full this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a30d-d82c-a79a-b39d25450000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a QB1 after last week’s decimation of the Cardinals for three touchdowns in a game where the 49ers eased off the gas in the second half. The Panthers defense is an attractive pass-funnel matchup for the 49ers, and one where we should see Purdy putting up mid-range QB1 numbers at least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a30d-d82c-a79a-b39d25450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) is practicing in full this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a30f-d413-ad9f-b7df67fa0000</link>
      <description>It’s good to have it confirmed that there were no setbacks from the long-term knee injury on Sunday. Despite the one-catch dud against the Cardinals last week, Pearsall did tie Jauan Jennings for a team high in snaps. He’ll be on the WR3 line this week against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a30f-d413-ad9f-b7df67fa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
