<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Buccaneers NT Vita Vea (foot) is likely to play in Week 1 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-20a6-d332-a1fd-b6b6c7d50000</link>
      <description>Vea has been a stalwart defender throughout his career and is a big reason for the teams continued successes against the run, making his likely presence when the Buccaneers take the field in Week 1 against the Falcons a significant boost to their defense. It seems a full practice Friday was enough for coaches to confidently start Vea to begin the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-20a6-d332-a1fd-b6b6c7d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter Travis Hunter is expected to serve as an “every-down wide receiver and situational corner” in Sunday’s season opener against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ec-de13-afdd-46eff09d0000</link>
      <description>It has been trending this way for some time, though Schefter reports things could change going forward. “It doesn’t mean that arrangement will hold in Week 2 or further into the season, according to sources,” Schefter reported. “The Jaguars plan to mix up Hunter’s usage throughout the course of the season, sources said, but they believe there will be some weeks when the rookie can and will be deployed as a full-time wide receiver and cornerback.” The truth is that not even the Jags might not know what is ultimately in store, but it’s been clear for some time Hunter was going to see enough offensive snaps and routes to merit immediate WR3 consideration in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ec-de13-afdd-46eff09d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Steelers DL Cameron Heyward has agreed to a reworked contract ahead of Sunday’s opener against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-21d6-de13-afdd-67df77f90000</link>
      <description>Heyward had been playing coy on whether or not he would suit up Sunday. Now he will after the Steelers added “over $3 million in incentives this year.” The 36-year-old could now max out at $18 million this season. Despite his advanced age, Heyward has remained one of the very best defensive lineman in all of football. The Steelers need him more than ever as this era of Pittsburgh football continues to sunset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-21d6-de13-afdd-67df77f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed WR Jameson Williams to a three-year, $83 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-223c-dbe3-a9bb-327fcc9f0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Schultz reports the deal includes a whopping $67 million guaranteed. That’s a monster sum considering Williams’ mixed track record and seeming inherent risk, but it’s also the Lions acknowledging the inevitable. Williams had two years remaining on his rookie deal, but the team just didn’t want any drama. It’s an approach a team like the Cowboys could learn from, for instance. A 2024 breakout star, the Lions’ coaching staff has talked up the possibility Williams further breaks out in 2025. A game-breaker at every level of the field, Williams is pushing for weekly WR2 value and could force his way up the ranks as the season goes. Still somehow only 24 years old, Williams could be a fantasy stud for years to come if he can manage to avoid further suspensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-223c-dbe3-a9bb-327fcc9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Giants have prepared “a package of plays” for QB Jaxson Dart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-240f-d332-a1fd-b63fca0f0000</link>
      <description>As Rapoport notes, there’s no guarantee they use these plays versus the Commanders. Still, it’s telling that the Giants are already flirting with the idea of playing their first-round rookie, even if Russell Wilson is the starter. Dart was electric in the preseason and drew rave reviews throughout training camp. Given his No. 25 overall draft capital, Wilson will have to be nearly flawless to hold off the rookie for an entire season. With Brian Daboll firmly on the hot seat for 2025, he will almost certainly be quick to give the rookie a shot if Wilson stumbles. For now, Wilson is a low-end QB2 on a short leash while Dart is a stash in Superflex and dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-240f-d332-a1fd-b63fca0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Lions and EDGE Aidan Hutchinson “are not expected to agree to terms on a new deal prior to the season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2416-d332-a1fd-b636a5bd0000</link>
      <description>As Rapoport notes, the Lions have made deals during the season in the past, but there’s no guarantee the two sides reach an agreement anytime soon. Hutchinson has one base year remaining on his rookie contract and another season for the fifth-year option, which has already been exercised. That gives them plenty of time to hammer out the specifics of an extension that is guaranteed to make Hutchinson the highest-paid defender in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2416-d332-a1fd-b636a5bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Packers EDGE Micah Parson (back) won’t get “a full compliment of plays” in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-241b-d332-a1fd-b63f0d720000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Parson is expected to play through his back injury. The fact that he will play a part-time role isn’t at all surprising. Parsons joined the Packers a little over a week ago and has seen limited work in practice because of his back injury. It makes sense for him to take the field for obvious pass-rush situations and get a breather versus the run. Part-time player or not, Parsons is set to turn the Packers’ defense from good to elite in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-241b-d332-a1fd-b63f0d720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Kyler Murray was added to the injury report with an illness but will play in Week 1 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2449-db7b-a5dd-a44d483a0000</link>
      <description>The fact that Murray wasn’t given a game status suggests the Cardinals are simply doing their due diligence and noting a minor issue for a player before kickoff. Whether the issue affects him in any way remains to be seen, but fantasy managers should count on a typical performance from Murray unless we hear otherwise. Murray gets a strong matchup versus the Saints this week, keeping him inside the top 12 fantasy quarterbacks for his 2025 opener.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2449-db7b-a5dd-a44d483a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Xavier Worthy suffered a dislocated shoulder in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-245c-de13-afdd-66dfd9f30000</link>
      <description>Rapoport couldn’t give any specifics on how much time Worthy is expected to miss, but he did note that “the most likely option” is for Worthy to wear a brace and play again at some point this season. That would be a great outcome for Worthy, given the severity of the injury. On the other hand, Rapoport mentioned surgery as a potential option, though it’s obviously one Worthy and the Chiefs want to avoid. With Rashee Rice still serving a six-game suspension, Hollywood Brown is slotted in as the team’s top receiver for the next month. He was targeted 16 times versus the Chargers and went for 99 yards. Brown will be one of the top waiver wire adds of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-245c-de13-afdd-66dfd9f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there is a real possibility, and even likelihood” that Browns RB Quinshon Judkins plays in Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2468-de13-afdd-66eb9a080000</link>
      <description>Judkins remained unsigned until Saturday and missed the entirety of training camp while away from the team. He was facing criminal charges relating to a domestic violence case, but the charges were eventually dropped. Despite that, he and the Browns took weeks to agree on a fully guaranteed rookie contract. The delay seemingly cost him Week 1, though that may be the only game he misses. Judkins is still under investigation by the NFL and is meeting with league officials this week. With no charges against him, it’s possible Judkins isn’t suspended and is ready to return for Week 2. Jerome Ford and fellow rookie Dyland Sampson will share the backfield for Week 1 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2468-de13-afdd-66eb9a080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
