<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 21:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tahj Brooks is questionable to return to Week 12 against the Patriots with a possible concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b21a-db57-afda-f63afdb20000</link>
      <description>Brooks was getting a chance to play more with Semaje Perine (ankle) inactive on Sunday. Unfortunately, Brooks suffered an injury of his own and is now being evaluated for a possible concussion. If he’s unable to return, that would mean Chase Brown would see almost all of the running back snaps the rest of the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b21a-db57-afda-f63afdb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LT Will Campbell left Week 12 against the Bengals with a leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b25c-d90e-a9da-bf5f768e0000</link>
      <description>The injury did not look good. Campbell was down and in considerable pain as the trainers examined his leg. He immediately went into the blue medical tent. The Patriots also lost starting left guard Jared Wilson to injury earlier in this game, so long-term losses for both of those would be a major concern for the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b25c-d90e-a9da-bf5f768e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (foot) left Minnesota’s Week 12 game against the Packers and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b21b-d413-ad9f-b7df2e4e0000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw left in the fourth quarter, with the Vikings down multiple scores. The almost-instant ruleout did not feel promising. J.J. McCarthy has already taken five sacks. Justin Skule replaced Darrisaw at left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b21b-d413-ad9f-b7df2e4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DE Jadeveon Clowney (neck) is active for Week 12 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b26f-d413-ad9f-b7ffef9d0000</link>
      <description>Clowney will suit against against an injury-marred Eagles offensive line after missing practice time this week while dealing with a shoulder/neck issue. It’s a plus for a Dallas defense that has gotten much healthier over the past few weeks. Cowboys declared RB Jaydon Blue, WR Jalen Tolbert, OL Hakeem Adeniji, DT Jay Toia, and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b26f-d413-ad9f-b7ffef9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Hamilton exited in the fourth quarter of the Ravens’ Week 12 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b25d-d90e-a9da-bf5f8ab20000</link>
      <description>Hamilton was running down Tyrod Taylor on a run when his right foot slipped on the turf, appearing to roll his ankle. The star safety remained down after the play before hobbling his way to the sideline with a trainer. Hamilton was already playing through a shoulder injury and was in obvious pain after the play. With a short week to prepare for Thursday’s game against the Bengals, it wouldn’t be surprising if we saw him miss Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b25d-d90e-a9da-bf5f8ab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings G Donovan Jackson (ankle) left Minnesota’s Week 12 game against the Packers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27a-db57-afda-f67af6370000</link>
      <description>Another late offensive line injury for the Vikings in this one, as they’re already down Christian Darrisaw outside. Blake Brandel replaced Jackson for a few fourth-quarter snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27a-db57-afda-f67af6370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared OT Lane Johnson, QB Sam Howell, RB A.J. Dillon, CB Mac McWilliams, and DT Ty Robinson inactive for Week 12 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27b-d90e-a9da-bf7fc2000000</link>
      <description>The Eagles’ beat-up offensive line will be without Johnson for at least one game after he sustained a foot injury last week. It could be an issue against a Dallas front seven that has gotten a lot healthier over the past few weeks. Jalen Hurts could be forced to run more than he has in recent weeks with Johnson sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27b-d90e-a9da-bf7fc2000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 14-of-21 passes for 139 yards in the Packers’ 23-6, Week 12 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27e-d413-ad9f-b7ff081a0000</link>
      <description>His most impressive throw came on a third-down blitz in the first half, where he guided the ball to Dontayvion Wicks over a dropped zone defender that was theoretically in the way. Love looked like the AC joint sprain was keeping him a little less explosive on the run and also handed off with his off-hands at times. He’s probably more of a QB2 against the Lions on Thanksgiving, but at least they might actually force him to throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27e-d413-ad9f-b7ff081a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins left Week 12’s game against the Patriots with a potential concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27e-d82c-a79a-b3fe19f40000</link>
      <description>Higgins was trying to make a spectacular one-handed catch late in the fourth quarter when he landed on his back, and the weight of the cornerback landed on Higgins’ head and slammed it into the turf. It was a scary situation where Higgins lay on his face for a while before the Bengals’ trainers were able to roll him over. Thankfully, he was able to walk off the field onto a cart, but it seems very likely that Higgins suffered a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b27e-d82c-a79a-b3fe19f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy completed 12-of-19 passes for 87 yards and two interceptions in the Vikings’ 23-6, Week 12 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b280-d413-ad9f-b7dd434a0000</link>
      <description>He added five sacks in what was reprehensible effort where he held the ball deep into the drop multiple times and simply seemed to not understand what he was seeing. The Vikings managed minus-1 total yard as an offense in the second half, a half that FOX’s Joe Davis intoned as “one of the worst halves of football I’ve watched in my life.” He brought -0.58 EPA per play to the table in a must-win division game. If McCarthy starts against the Seahawks in Week 13 — an open question at this point per our eyes — he would be usable in leagues where managers start three quarterbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b280-d413-ad9f-b7dd434a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
