<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Garrett Wilson (knee) is expected to play in Week 10 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68c6-d1e7-a1fa-7aeea7000000</link>
      <description>The news doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Wilson was listed as questionable on Friday after a full practice. Coming off the bye week, he was always expected to return for today’s game. Having seen at least eight targets in every game this year, Wilson is stepping right back into the WR1 ranks for his Week 10 date with the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68c6-d1e7-a1fa-7aeea7000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cedric Tillman (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 10 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68c9-d713-ad9e-6cdd3f670000</link>
      <description>Tillman was listed as questionable after being activated from injured reserve over the weekend. The questionable tag was largely a procedural matter. Tillman will return to a Browns offense helmed by Dillon Gabriel. The rookie hasn’t found much success this year. He has been at his best when checking the ball down to his tight ends. Tillman should remain on fantasy benches for at least one more week to develop some chemistry with Gabriel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68c9-d713-ad9e-6cdd3f670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Tetairoa McMillan (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68cc-d673-a39e-ecdd0c1f0000</link>
      <description>McMillan was a late addition to the injury report, popping up as a limited participant before being listed as questionable. The rookie seemingly suffered the injury during the final practice of the week, putting his availability for today’s game in jeopardy. The good news is that he is expected to be out there. Fantasy managers, however, should still be wary that he looks as great as usual and gets a full-time role. McMillan is normally a locked-in WR2. He will move to the WR2/3 border for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68cc-d673-a39e-ecdd0c1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “the Chiefs made a late strong push to acquire Seahawks linebacker Boye Mafe.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68cf-d673-a39e-ecdf57f10000</link>
      <description>Schefter noted that one of his sources believed the deal was complete. Seattle ultimately chose to hang onto Mafe at the deadline. Mafe had 15 sacks between the 2023 and 2024 seasons. He does not have a sack this year and his playing time has dipped in back-to-back seasons. Even in the midst of a downswing, Mafe is worth more to a contending Seahawks team than future draft picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68cf-d673-a39e-ecdf57f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Cooper Kupp (hamstring) has “a chance” of playing in Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68d3-d45b-affe-7dd7674b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport said Kupp has a better chance of playing this week than he did in Week 9. He was also listed as questionable last week but didn’t appear awfully close to suiting up over the weekend and was ruled out ahead of kickoff. Rapoport called his status “up in the air” for today’s game. With Tory Horton listed as doubtful, Rashid Shaheed could be the team’s No. 2 receiver for his first game in Seattle if Kupp isn’t active. Fantasy managers should avoid the WR2 situation on the Seahawks if Kupp is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68d3-d45b-affe-7dd7674b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Bills offered the Dolphins a 2027 first-round pick as part of a package for Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68e1-d1e7-a1fa-7aebcc7d0000</link>
      <description>Pelissero mentioned a 2026 third-round pick as part of the deal as well. Buffalo reportedly made the highest offer for Waddle, but the Dolphins turned away all callers and held onto their star wideout. The Dolphins view Waddle as part of their future, even if they are forced to make changes at head coach and quarterback. It sounds like there was almost no price a team could have paid to pry him away from Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68e1-d1e7-a1fa-7aebcc7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Colts plan to offer Daniel Jones a “long-term extension.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68e7-d1e7-a1fa-7aef27400000</link>
      <description>Extension talks between the two sides have not begun yet, but they are on the way after Indy pushed all their chips in by trading for Sauce Gardner. Jones currently leads the league with 2,404 passing yards. He has 14 passing scores and another five on the ground. He is at or near the top of most efficiency metrics and the Colts are 7-2. They are on track to get the lone bye in the AFC. Given the success Jones is having in Indy, we fully expect both sides to come to an agreement to keep him in town for years to come</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68e7-d1e7-a1fa-7aef27400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the 49ers are “hopeful” Brock Purdy will return in Week 11 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68eb-d713-ad9e-6cff1b9a0000</link>
      <description>Technically, Purdy could return today as the 49ers’ backup quarterback. He is listed as questionable for Week 10, but Mac Jones has already been announced as the starter. If he’s ready to play next week, the assumption is that he will be active as the starter. Purdy reaggravated the foot issue once already and the 49ers aren’t taking any chances with his second return to play. Jones’ solid play has also given them more leeway to take their time with Purdy’s recovery. Jones will remain a high-end QB2 for as long as Purdy is stuck on the sidelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68eb-d713-ad9e-6cff1b9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Cowboys included a provision in the Micah Parsons trade that gives them the Packers’ 2028 first-round pick if Parsons is traded to an NFC East team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68f0-d673-a39e-ecf17ecd0000</link>
      <description>The “poison pill” clause was specifically intended to block Green Bay from trading Parsons to the Eagles, who previously made offers for the star defender. The Packers, in turn, used the same clause on Kenny Clark, who cannot be traded to an NFC North team. As Schefter notes, this addendum to the trade was kept quiet until teams noticed both teams’ 2028 first-round picks were unavailable ahead of the trade deadline. Parsons was never likely to end up in Philly, given how much the Packers paid to land him and the $188 million contract he got from Green Bay. The poison pill clause was simply put in there to help Jerry Jones sleep at night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-68f0-d673-a39e-ecf17ecd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Justin Fields is expected to start in Week 10 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6904-d713-ad9e-6d54035a0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Aaron Glenn kept his starting quarterback a secret all week. The 1-7 Jets refuse to give up this gamesmanship gimmick, even though Fields was always going to start in Week 10 after picking up his first win of the year before the team’s Week 9 bye. Fields’ rushing output will keep him on the QB1/2 border versus the Browns, but his struggles as a passer make him a low-floor bet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6904-d713-ad9e-6d54035a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
