<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 02:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Badie caught 2-of-6 targets for 16 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e7-de13-afdd-66ef16220000</link>
      <description>He did not see a carry. Badie was targeted on a remarkable six of his 13 pass routes, as he split the pass-catching backfield role with JK Dobbins (two targets) and RJ Harvey (one target). Jaleel McLaughlin was a healthy scratch against the Titans, leaving Badie as the team’s No. 3 back. The Denver backfield is more muddled than anyone could have guessed this summer, and Badie is worth rostering in deeper formats in case Harvey or Dobbins get dinged up in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26e7-de13-afdd-66ef16220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 6-of-9 targets for 79 yards in the Lions’ Week 1 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c8-dbe3-a9bb-36dbeedc0000</link>
      <description>LaPorta was the lone bright spot on a Detroit offense that came out flat in Week 1. The third-year tight end worked the middle of the field well, connecting with Goff for multiple chunk gains, including catches for 32 and 16 yards. LaPorta clocked in with a 24 percent target share, picking up wear he left off after finishing 2024 with a string of strong performances. He will stay in the top half of the TE1 ranks for Week 2 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26c8-dbe3-a9bb-36dbeedc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 2-of-7 targets for 13 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26f4-dbe3-a9bb-36f7825a0000</link>
      <description>Though it won’t show in the rookie’s box score, Ayomanor had a full-time role in the Tennessee offense and took in a team-leading 48 percent of the Titans’ air yards, missing a couple downfield shots by a whisker. Only Calvin Ridley saw more targets (8) than Ayomanor against the stout Denver defense. While his production will likely be high variance — boom or bust — Ayomanor could be interesting in deeper 12-team formats if he maintains this role in the Titans offense. He gets the Rams in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26f4-dbe3-a9bb-36f7825a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 16-of-22 passes for 188 yards and two touchdowns in the Packers’ 27-13, Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26f1-d332-a1fd-b6f73fbd0000</link>
      <description>Love had a pick-six taken off the board because of a penalty on Detroit, leaving him with a near-perfect box score. Love hit Tucker Kraft with a dart over the middle of the field for his first score of the day in the opening quarter. He later found Jayden Reed for an easy lob into the end zone in the second quarter. With the Lions offense failing to get anything going, Love was only tasked with six pass attempts in the second half, limiting his fantasy potential. As long as Jayden Daniels and the Commanders can push Green Bay a little more, Love will climb the QB2 rankings for his date with Washington on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26f1-d332-a1fd-b6f73fbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft caught 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26fa-dbe3-a9bb-36fbab540000</link>
      <description>Kraft caught one of Jordan Love’s two touchdown tosses on the day, with the second going to Jayden Reed. Love threaded the needle to Kraft over the middle of the field for a score from 15 yards out on Green Bay’s opening drive. Even though he only caught two passes, Kraft’s four targets were good for an 18 percent target share. That’s not an elite mark, but it’s enough to keep him in the TE1 mix for his Week 2 matchup with the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26fa-dbe3-a9bb-36fbab540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught 3-of-5 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-270e-db7b-a5dd-a70e3fd90000</link>
      <description>Reed entered the game listed as questionable with a foot injury that he had been dealing with for over a month. The issue left him in a boot during August and cost him most of training camp plus the preseason. He ultimately suited up, led the team in targets, and was on the receiving end of one of Love’s two passing touchdowns. Even if Reed doesn’t run all of the routes, he continually looks like the team’s most explosive wideout. He will still be a frustrating fantasy bet going forward, but the weekly upside is undeniable heading into Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-270e-db7b-a5dd-a70e3fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Lockett did not catch his lone target in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2717-dbe3-a9bb-375786370000</link>
      <description>The grizzled veteran served as the Titans’ distant WR3 behind Calvin Ridley and Elic Ayomanor, who saw eight and even targets, respectively, against a tough Denver defense. Lockett logged a pass route on 27 of the team’s 38 drop backs but was an afterthought throughout. Ayomanor appears to be Cam Ward’s main downfield threat. Lockett should remain on waivers ahead of Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2717-dbe3-a9bb-375786370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught both of his targets for 16 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2713-d332-a1fd-b737f2c10000</link>
      <description>Golden was not overly involved in the Green Bay offense for his first game of the year. He earned a measly nine percent target share and only ran a route on 58 percent of the Packers’ dropbacks. The first-round rookie still has work to do before emerging as a true fantasy threat. His role should ramp up over time, but a short turnaround to a Thursday date with Washington won’t do him any favors. He is buried in the FLEX ranks for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2713-d332-a1fd-b737f2c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 3-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271d-dbe3-a9bb-375f630a0000</link>
      <description>Mims was bottled up on his three grabs and made some mental mistakes in the return game. The good news: Mims, a part-time gadget player last season, ran a pass route on 31 of Bo Nix’s 48 drop backs. Courtland Sutton and Troy Franklin had more routes than Mims on the day. Mims’ explosiveness on both short-area targets and downfield looks make him a high-variance weekly fantasy play. He gets the Colts in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271d-dbe3-a9bb-375f630a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 2-of-4 targets for 68 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Doubs was the Packers’ most trusted receiver, leading the team in routes. He ran a route on 18-of-24 Jordan Love dropbacks. He also finished second on the team in targets behind only Jayden Reed. Doubs isn’t the flashiest fantasy option, but his role is secure and he plays on an offense that won’t have any issues putting up points. He will stick in the WR4/5 range for Week 2 against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
