<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Khalil Herbert (undisclosed) missed practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96e8-d90d-a5bd-b6fb1ae30000</link>
      <description>This is Herbert’s second missed practice. The Indy Star’s Nate Atkins commented on the matter, saying this is a “setback” for Herbert “in the RB3 battle.” Herbert is not worth stashing on fantasy benches at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96e8-d90d-a5bd-b6fb1ae30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the tight end position is the offense’s “silent engine.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96af-d45c-a7fc-96bf2bc00000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Mike Dugar explains, “Seattle’s offense is built around the idea of making all the run actions look like their passing concepts and vice versa.” The Seahawks need to be able to put No. 1 TE AJ Barner and veteran Eric Saubert “on opposite ends of the line of scrimmage on early downs and make it difficult for the defense to predict which direction the run might go.” Dugar adds, “Barner continues to show he’s a great athlete with soft hands and the ability to make big-time catches,” while curiously abstaining from forecasting Elijah Arroyo’s exact role, beyond emphasizing Arroyo’s demonstrated receiving abilities. Barner appears to be the favorite to lead the position group in early-season snaps. Arroyo will likely need to prove himself as a blocker in order to have a full-time role, though operating in a specialized receiver role at least remains possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96af-d45c-a7fc-96bf2bc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton “continues to make plays” with the first-team offense while Marquez Valdes-Scantling “was again working a lot with the second team.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-970a-d05a-adda-bf8a07970000</link>
      <description>Horton is evidently playing well both as a field-stretcher and in the red zone. ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports that Horton “caught a red zone TD pass from Sam Darnold” on Sunday. The fifth-round rookie is making progress in his quest to relegate MVS to a backup role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-970a-d05a-adda-bf8a07970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (leg) is set to undergo an MRI on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9908-d45c-a7fc-9b1a7d170000</link>
      <description>Dickerson suffered a right leg injury during the team’s open practice on Sunday and had to be taken off the field on a cart. We don’t know much about the severity of his injury, but we will likely get the specifics when the MRI results are announced. Dickerson has been a Pro Bowler in each of the last three seasons and would be a massive loss for an Eagles offensive line that’s expected to be among the league’s best this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9908-d45c-a7fc-9b1a7d170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White (groin) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-990e-d05a-adda-bb8e1ec70000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on an official update on White’s injury, but he was seen in shorts for the start of Monday’s practice. White suffered a groin injury in Saturday’s preseason game against the Titans and was reportedly going to undergo further testing to determine the severity of it, so it’s possible we have an update after practice. Regardless, this situation remains one to monitor, and would make Sean Tucker an interesting late-round dart throw as a handcuff to Bucky Irving if White were to miss any time in the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-990e-d05a-adda-bb8e1ec70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Renfrow (hamstring) returned to practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-995a-d05a-adda-bbda75f60000</link>
      <description>Renfrow missed nearly two weeks of practice with a hamstring injury, but will now resume his comeback attempt. The veteran receiver had been impressing early in training camp and was sounding like a safe bet to make the roster before going down. Renfrow was back in full pads on Monday and could have a chance to suit up for the Panthers’ next preseason game, which is set for Saturday against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-995a-d05a-adda-bbda75f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaycee Horn (car crash, thumb) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-997c-d45c-a7fc-9b7eb9b60000</link>
      <description>Horn was involved in a car crash last week and reportedly suffered a thumb injury that required stitches. He was listed as day-to-day with his injury, and was not sporting pads in Monday’s practice, but Horn will hopefully be up to full speed later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-997c-d45c-a7fc-9b7eb9b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Robert Longerbeam suffered a torn patella tendon and will miss the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9986-df63-a199-d9afecc10000</link>
      <description>Longerbeam becomes the second Ravens rookie CB to be lost for the season due to a knee injury. Fellow rookie Bilhal Kone suffered a torn ACL and MCL in last Thursday’s preseason win over the Colts. Longerbeam, who was selected in the sixth round of this year’s draft, will now land on injured reserve and work toward returning next season. With two corners now out for the season, we can expect the Ravens to add a few new names to their secondary in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9986-df63-a199-d9afecc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jon Machota believes “no one has come close to running away with the No. 1 job” in the Cowboys’ backfield.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99b3-d05a-adda-bbb36a830000</link>
      <description>Machota notes that Javonte Williams has seen “the most reps with the starters,” but also points out the fact that Miles Sanders (knee) and Jaydon Blue (ankle) have both been sidelined with injuries. The fact that there are no standouts in Dallas’ backfield shouldn’t come as a surprise, considering the veterans of the group both underperformed in the previous season with their respective teams. Williams is a surefire bet to open as the team’s starter if both Sanders and Blue are unable to go, but there’s a good chance this backfield remains in flux early into the season until a clear-cut starter emerges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99b3-d05a-adda-bbb36a830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent RB Jamaal Williams is working out for the Dolphins on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</link>
      <description>Williams has now met with two teams since the weekend, as the veteran running back was also brought in by the Bears on Saturday. Williams blew up for 262-1066-17 in 2022 but has totaled just 470 yards and two touchdowns on 154 carries since 2023 despite playing in 27 games. Williams’ workout comes a day after Alexander Mattison suffered a neck/shoulder injury in preseason action against the Bears. Now entering his age-30 season, Williams won’t have much to offer outside of a rotational and/or short-yardage role, which would make him unreliable for fantasy wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
