<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:29:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs TE Noah Gray (concussion) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf0-d82c-a79a-bff4bf410000</link>
      <description>Gray has slowly seen his role in the passing game grow over the past month, accumulating 12 targets in Kansas City’s last four games. It looks very unlikely he’ll be up for Thursday’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf0-d82c-a79a-bff4bf410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs G Trey Smith (ankle) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf3-d82c-a79a-bff7167f0000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back DNPs have the star guard looking unlikely to play against the Cowboys on Thanksgiving. He’s reportedly dealing with both “high- and low-ankle sprains,” per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. It wouldn’t be surprising if he missed multiple weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf3-d82c-a79a-bff7167f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (ankle) participated in full during Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf4-db57-afda-fef6a9410000</link>
      <description>If you were ever going to start Worthy again, you’d have to figure it would be against the Cowboys, right? But they’ve improved enough on defense over the last few games that Worthy is probably still just a questionable FLEX play in Week 13 with no teams on bye. Worthy upgraded from a limited practice on Monday and continues to have his ankle injury managed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bcf4-db57-afda-fef6a9410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd03-db57-afda-ff33ebac0000</link>
      <description>Neither did Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder), LB Noah Sewell (elbow), or CB Tyrique Stevenson (hip) on the estimated report. The good news is that Kyler Gordon and Jaylon Johnson, both on IR, practiced in full on Tuesday. Still, down several linebackers, this could be a smash spot for the struggling Saquon Barkley on Black Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd03-db57-afda-ff33ebac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said he “doesn’t see” S Kerby Joseph (knee) playing this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd08-d90e-a9da-bf0f7c3d0000</link>
      <description>Joseph hasn’t played since October 12. We appreciate how good Joseph is and understand that the Lions would rather have him out there if at all possible, but there’s literally an injured reserve for this sort of thing. Brian Branch (toe/ankle) got in a full session today to upgrade over a Monday limited, and Terrion Arnold (concussion) remained limited and may be trying to clear protocol tomorrow to make the active line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd08-d90e-a9da-bf0f7c3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Isaac TeSlaa (hand) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd0b-d90e-a9da-bf0f873e0000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa would seem to be the beneficiary if Kalif Raymond (ankle, DNP for second day in a row) can’t go on Thursday. No need to rush the rookie wideout into your lineups as he has yet to do better than one catch in a game this year, but perhaps he’ll be a worthwhile monitor on Thursday with an eye towards the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd0b-d90e-a9da-bf0f873e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd38-d6c4-abfb-ff3b97b30000</link>
      <description>We haven’t heard anything concerning about Jacobs’ chances of playing in Week 13 to this point. He certainly seems to be trending towards playing, though Wednesday’s status report will tell the full tale. Jacobs has practiced on a limited basis for four consecutive days dating back towards last week, and as long as he has his full range of motion, we expect to see him out there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd38-d6c4-abfb-ff3b97b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said “you’ll find out Thursday” when asked if WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) plays Thanksgiving day against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd41-d82c-a79a-bfd57c7b0000</link>
      <description>Reed logged a limited practice participation for the Packers’ walkthrough practice on Tuesday. He just returned to practice last week after spending the bulk of the season on injured reserve and has yet to get in a full practice. The Packers list Reed with both the foot and shoulder/collarbone issues that ailed him this season. It’s still difficult to see Reed playing against the Lions on Thanksgiving, but LaFleur said, “You never know... you’ll find out Thursday.” Reed is inching his way back and his final status after Wednesday’s practice will provide more clarity on if he plays Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd41-d82c-a79a-bfd57c7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks waived CB Derion Kendrick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd53-d90e-a9da-bf5fd9f40000</link>
      <description>Kendrick joined the Seahawks in August after the Rams cut him in the final wave of roster cuts. He was a sixth-round pick of the Rams in 2022 and had a fruitful 2023 season, starting 12 games and tallying one interception and 10 passes defended. Kendrick had two interceptions and five passes defended with the Seahawks this year, but now heads to waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bd53-d90e-a9da-bf5fd9f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR DeVonta Smith (shoulder/chest) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdb0-db57-afda-ffb2f6ed0000</link>
      <description>Smith took some hard hits and falls in the Eagles’ Week 12 loss to the Cowboys and starts out the week as a non-participant in the team’s Tuesday walkthrough. The Eagles play the Bears on Friday, so Smith’s DNP to start the week is concerning for his game status. Fantasy managers should check back throughout the week; any sort of practice time would be a positive sign for Smith playing in Week 13. WR Xavier Gipson (shoulder) was also a DNP after he was shaken up on a punt return that he fumbled late in Week 12. Jahan Dotson would be next up for targets if Smith cannot go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bdb0-db57-afda-ffb2f6ed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
