<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:03:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df49-d6c4-abfb-df4b38d80000</link>
      <description>Arnold re-injured his shoulder in the Lions’ Thanksgiving game against the Packers and will undergo season-ending surgery in the coming days, per Pelissero. He had tried to play through the injury after hurting his shoulder in Week 5. The Lions secondary will take a hit with Arnold sidelined. Detroit has allowed the NFL’s seventh lowest drop backs success rate in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df49-d6c4-abfb-df4b38d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts are trying out K Blake Grupe, formerly of the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df97-d6c4-abfb-df97c4930000</link>
      <description>Michael Badgley missed a critical extra point in the Colts’ Week 13 loss to the Texans and head coach Shane Steichen was noncommittal on Badgley keeping the starting job for Week 14. Grupe, who was released by the Saints last week, had missed eight of his 26 field goal tries this season. An 85 percent field goal kicker during his NFL career, Grupe would have some fantasy upside in the Colts offense if he lands the starting job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df97-d6c4-abfb-df97c4930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed WR Elijah Moore, formerly of the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfea-d90e-a9da-dfef61770000</link>
      <description>Moore will start with Denver’s practice squad ahead of the team’s Week 14 game against the Raiders. Moore appeared in nine games for the Bills this season and had nine catches for 112 yards. If he’s active for the Broncos in the coming weeks, Moore would likely be a rotational player who sees limited snaps and routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfea-d90e-a9da-dfef61770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said he’s “hopeful” WR Brandon Aiyuk will play for the team this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfed-d82c-a79a-fffd6aa00000</link>
      <description>Lynch wouldn’t call it realistic for Aiyuk to suit up for the Niners late in the regular season or the postseason, but said he remained hopeful the wideout would play at some point in 2025. Aiyuk, coming back from a brutal knee injury, has not had his 21-day practice window opened and is unhappy with the team after the Niners reportedly voided his 2026 contract guarantees. The Athletic reported in November that Aiyuk had likely played his final game for the 49ers. It would be shocking if Aiyuk returned in the final weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfed-d82c-a79a-fffd6aa00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said DT Derrick Harmon (knee) won’t play in Pittsburgh’s Week 14 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03b-d82c-a79a-f3bfc1890000</link>
      <description>That’s two weeks in a row on the sideline for Harmon, who the Steelers badly missed on Sunday as the Bills ran all over them. Derrick Henry deserves a small rankings bump based on this news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03b-d82c-a79a-f3bfc1890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) won’t practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03d-d90e-a9da-ff3f617e0000</link>
      <description>He added that if St. Brown can possibly play, he will. And since he also ruled out fellow wideout Kalif Raymond in this presser, it sounds like there is a non-zero chance that St. Brown plays against the Cowboys on Thursday. We would still regard him as on the pessimistic side of questionable given the two missed practices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03d-d90e-a9da-ff3f617e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Kalif Raymond (ankle) will not play in Detroit’s Week 14 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03f-d6c4-abfb-f63f917e0000</link>
      <description>Since suffering this ankle injury in Week 12, Raymond has not yet practiced. Isaac TeSlaa took over as the third wideout last week and scored despite seeing just two targets. TeSlaa has already proven himself a big-play threat, but his target volume is so low he’ll be hard to trust in a FLEX spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03f-d6c4-abfb-f63f917e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he’d like to get Tutu Atwell (hamstring/IR) active “if that fits for the collective relative to the 48, there’s a lot of factors for that.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e04b-db57-afda-f67b36170000</link>
      <description>Atwell surprisingly carried no injury status for Week 13, but was not activated from injured reserve. Xavier Smith, who returns kicks, was up and managed a 3/83 day in Atwell’s absence. It doesn’t sound like the Rams are all that fussed about the $10 million Atwell getting back. He’s droppable in all but the deepest fantasy leagues based on this update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e04b-db57-afda-f67b36170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Tyrone Tracy told reporters he left New York’s Week 13 game against the Patriots with a hip contusion and a stinger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e060-d90e-a9da-ff6f19e30000</link>
      <description>In other words, he should be fine coming off New York’s Week 14 bye. Cancel the Devin Singletary As Rest Of Season RB1-sized FAAB bids, though Singletary has claimed enough of the backfield to merit consideration off waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e060-d90e-a9da-ff6f19e30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
