<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed 12 times for 42 yards and one touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 8 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e6-d245-adfb-b7ff5e3f0000</link>
      <description>Tucker’s hard-fought touchdown occurred on the run up the middle on the Buccaneers’ fifth drive. While fantasy managers will gladly accept the score, the fact that he even got the ball to begin with is notable. Buccaneers running backs took center stage on the team’s second drive, with both Tucker and RB Rachaad White helping the offense bring the ball downfield. Late in the drive, Tucker scooted from the Saints’ 16-yard line, on down to the one, where he (twice) and White (three times) were stuffed for no gain on five consecutive plays, despite being given an extra chance via a neutral zone infraction from the Saints’ defense. If RB Bucky Irvin’s (foot/shoulder) returns post-bye, in Week 10, Tucker will not be fantasy-relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e6-d245-adfb-b7ff5e3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Dobbins rushed 15 times for 111 yards in Denver’s Week 8 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e8-deb1-a39b-23eeb0590000</link>
      <description>Dobbins retained most of the workload, with 33 snaps of the 63 for Denver and Tyler Badie siphoning off more than usual towards the end of the game in a blowout. The veteran back has the most rushing yards by a Bronco through seven games since Willis McGahee in 2012. And he did not score any of the three touchdowns tonight, so fantasy managers are Mad Online. A grisly scene. Dobbins will remain a featured piece against the Texans in Week 9 and slots in as an RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e8-deb1-a39b-23eeb0590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pollard rushed 11 times for 44 yards in a Week 8 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e6-deb1-a39b-23ee260e0000</link>
      <description>Pollard got the first attempts for the Titans but was outplayed by Tyjae Spears, who seems to have more game-breaking ability than Pollard. Pollard ran hard, but he doesn’t seem to be able to make many defenders miss, and he’s simply not the weapon in the passing game that Spears is. It’s looking like Spears is beginning to take more work away from Pollard, and, in shallower formats, it’s OK to look elsewhere on the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22e6-deb1-a39b-23ee260e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed seven times for 46 yards and two touchdowns in Denver’s Week 8 win over the Cowboys, adding a one-yard touchdown for five yards on his only target.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22eb-d5d8-a3ff-fbeb7ff20000</link>
      <description>He finally got there, folks. Harvey did this on just 17 snaps, per the early PFF data. It turns out the real Joker that Sean Payton promised all offseason was “playing against Matt Eberflus’ defense.” This doesn’t feel like a major move from the rookie back given that snap count and the fact that JK Dobbins also ate sans any of the touchdowns. But perhaps Harvey has done enough here to force more usage and get him on the FLEX line for Week 9 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22eb-d5d8-a3ff-fbeb7ff20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 7-of-8 targets for 93 yards in a Week 8 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ec-d245-adfb-b7ff29470000</link>
      <description>With Tyler Lockett no longer on the team and Calvin Ridley hurt, Dike shared the lead receiver role with Elic Ayomanor. However, Ayomanor was used on the deeper shots down the field, while Dike operated more over the middle of the field. We’ll see what happens when Ridley returns, but there is a chance that Ridley gets traded at the deadline, and Dike would then find himself in a fantasy-friendly role for a team that figures to trail often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ec-d245-adfb-b7ff29470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb caught 7-of-10 targets for 74 yards in Dallas’ Week 8 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbefb82d0000</link>
      <description>Lamb’s fantasy managers wanted touchdowns, but the Broncos would not oblige. Lamb failed to get a second foot down on an early end zone target, and Riley Moss committed two pass interference penalties on Lamb in three plays in the end zone in the second half, a drive that ended with a Javonte Williams end zone plunge. Lamb, along with George Pickens and Dak Prescott, were benched for the final two series of the game with the Cowboys down 27 points. Lamb will remain a strong WR1 against the Cardinals in Week 9, and nothing we’ve seen thus far has been discouraging since his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbefb82d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 7-of-9 targets for 78 yards in Dallas’ Week 8 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f2-deb1-a39b-23fe5ab60000</link>
      <description>Pickens acquitted himself pretty well with Patrick Surtain in coverage on him early in the game — Surtain left at halftime with a shoulder injury — but didn’t really come close to scoring. Still, the targets and yardage are encouraging and had the game been closer, Pickens may have avoided a late-game benching as the Cowboys sat their stars down 27 in the fourth quarter. Dallas No. 2 receiver — who has 15 targets in two games since CeeDee Lamb’s return — will be on the WR2 line in Week 9 against Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f2-deb1-a39b-23fe5ab60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson failed to catch his only target in Dallas’ Week 8 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f3-deb1-a39b-23ffa5d10000</link>
      <description>Dallas’ whole play-action scheme was mostly junked against the Broncos, who seemed to be able to get pressure on Dak Prescott whenever they wanted. As a result, Ferguson failed to see the easy targets he’d been getting and disappeared into a fantasy black hole. A disappointing showing to be sure, but we’d still say Ferguson is on the TE1 line against the Cardinals in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f3-deb1-a39b-23ffa5d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Tolbert caught 2-of-2 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown in Dallas’ Week 8 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f6-deb1-a39b-23fe18760000</link>
      <description>A 35-yard bomb from Joe Milton hit Tolbert square in the hands — a thing of beauty — as the Cowboys were down 27 in the fourth quarter. Tolbert playing at that point tells you all you need to know about how his season is going, as he fell behind Ryan Flournoy 28 snaps to eight. Neither player is fantasy-interesting with CeeDee Lamb and George Pickens vacuuming up the targets in this offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f6-deb1-a39b-23fe18760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sterling Shepard caught 1-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 8 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f9-d5d8-a3ff-fbf9792a0000</link>
      <description>Shepard is now an afterthought, with Tez Johnson having assumed a larger role, though QB Baker Mayfield did give Shepard one, albeit errant, opportunity to make a play in the end zone. The Buccaneers’ quarterback looked the veteran wide receiver’s way from the Saints’ one-yard line but the pass was inaccurate and Saints CB Kool-Aid McKinstry nearly intercepted it. Shepard does not need to be in starting lineups following his team’s Week 9 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22f9-d5d8-a3ff-fbf9792a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
