<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Sauce Gardner (groin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a77-da68-ad9d-ff7f42e90000</link>
      <description>Gardner dealt with a reported calf injury in August before appearing on the Week 1 injury report with a fibula issue. He practiced in full yesterday and was not on the injury report at all. The development suggests Gardner suffered the injury in practice today, but its severity is currently unknown. The Jets are tasked with containing the Bills’ passing game this weekend. Hopefully, Gardner is able to practice in some capacity tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a77-da68-ad9d-ff7f42e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Josh Reynolds (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-da68-ad9d-ff7b54380000</link>
      <description>Reynolds is not fantasy-relevant but the Jets already possessed a terribly thin receiving corps. His three targets ranked second on the team last week. The Thursday downgrade makes it unlikely that he suits up against the Bills this weekend. Garrett Wilson should again comfortably pace the Jets in targets once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a71-da68-ad9d-ff7b54380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a80-dc44-a9d9-3fe6a7460000</link>
      <description>Bowers is “hoping to play” in Week 2 against the Chargers, but said that “we’ll see how it’s feeling throughout the week.” The Raiders are understandably giving Bowers an extra day off, with this week’s game scheduled for Monday night. The elite TE1’s practice participation on Friday and Saturday can tell us far more about his availability than today’s absence. In the meantime, for those who currently have Bowers in their starting lineup, stashing No. 2 TE Michael Mayer on fantasy benches is worthwhile. In Week 1, Bowers landed hard on his left knee after taking a hit to the right knee while running along the sideline. He was later seen limping with his left leg, and sported a sleeve on the left leg at today’s practice. It appears as though the fall was more of an issue than the direct hit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a80-dc44-a9d9-3fe6a7460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (back) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aa9-d86f-abdd-7fbddf310000</link>
      <description>Dickerson can be considered good to go for Week 2 against the Chiefs. It’s great news for an Eagles offense that must contend with one of the NFL’s best-schemed defenses, guided by DC Steve Spagnuolo. Dickerson will be hoping to get back on track after giving up four quarterback pressures, per PFF, against the Cowboys in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aa9-d86f-abdd-7fbddf310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (calf) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a7f-da67-a99f-fefff90a0000</link>
      <description>The 31-year-old tight end earned four targets in Week 1 after receiving decent training camp hype. He does not need to be in starting lineups, though he can be treated as a touchdown-dependent TE1, if necessary. Myriad options exist that can likely provide increased week-to-week stability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a7f-da67-a99f-fefff90a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aaf-da67-a99f-feff89f90000</link>
      <description>A second missed practice puts Porter on the wrong side of questionable. Fortunately, the Steelers still have Jalen Ramsey and Darius Slay. The Steelers face the Seahawks this week, whose only aerial threat in Week 1 was Jaxon Smith-Njigba. Cooper Kupp was a complete non-factor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aaf-da67-a99f-feff89f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aba-da67-a99f-feff34920000</link>
      <description>Jennings is now on the wrong side of questionable. He will need to practice in some capacity tomorrow if he is to suit up for Week 2 against the Saints. Perhaps, the only redeeming aspect of the 49ers’ brutal week is that their opponent is about as soft as one can hope for. Ricky Pearsall and Christian McCaffrey will be leaned upon in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aba-da67-a99f-feff34920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants sign WR/KR Xavier Gipson, formerly of the Jets, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ac1-d294-a19b-fef1f7820000</link>
      <description>Gipson signed with the Jets as a 2023 undrafted free agent, catching 27-of-46 targets for 268 yards and one touchdown in his time there. He’s averaged 26.0 yards per kickoff return on 44 career returns and 8.9 yards per punt return on 68 punt returns. He is likely to contribute on special teams again with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ac1-d294-a19b-fef1f7820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 2 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ae7-d294-a19b-fef7c0920000</link>
      <description>Decker underwent offseason shoulder surgery and missed time in training camp as a result. He played all 67 offensive snaps in Week 1 but “a problem with his shoulder caused” him to miss practice on both Wednesday and Thursday this week. Lions OC John Morton commented on the matter succinctly, saying, “we’re totally expecting Decker to play.” Decker’s availability does not appear to be jeopardized, but Detroit’s blindside protector is ailing. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ae7-d294-a19b-fef7c0920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) is active for Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdd7bb0000</link>
      <description>The Packers’ vaunted defense will have its new star pass rusher on the field. Unfortunately, the Packers declared CB Bo Melton, S Zayne Anderson, RT Zach Tom, LG Aaron Banks, TE Ben Sims and DL Warren Brinson inactive. Losing both Tom and Banks hurts Jordan Love’s protection. It would be unsurprising to see the Packers dial up quicky-hitting pass plays to help reduce pressure from Washington’s pass rush. On the plus side, Packers CB Nate Hobbs (knee) is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdd7bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
