<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:05:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said “I’m keeping my fingers crossed” that Matthew Stafford returns in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fb2-d629-a1bc-bfbf35d80000</link>
      <description>Stafford, who turns 38 this month, said he will take “some time” to decide whether or not to return for another season. The 17-year vet is coming off arguably his best season as a pro and could soon take home MVP honors after throwing for 4,707-46-8 while leading the Rams to a 12-5 record. The Rams have a talented roster in place around Stafford that should be more than capable of running things back next season should he decide to return. After coming so close to his second trip to the Super Bowl, it’s hard to imagine him walking away after such a successful season while still playing at a high level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fb2-d629-a1bc-bfbf35d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired former Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver to the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fc1-d89c-a1be-bfdfb7240000</link>
      <description>It’s a homecoming for Weaver, who spent the first four years of his career as a player with the Ravens and also served on their coaching staff from 2021 to 2023. Weaver fielded several head coaching interviews this coaching cycle and had multiple second interviews. When the dust finally settled on the process, he was left without a head coaching offer, and will now look to takeover a Ravens defense that’s already loaded with talent. Weaver’s defense finished 22nd in yards allowed and 24th in points allowed this season, but ranked in the top-10 in both categories the previous year. With head coach Jesse Minter already set to call plays, Weaver will likely be tasked more with the weekly game planning and preparation alongside Minter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fc1-d89c-a1be-bfdfb7240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs signed former Saints QB Jake Haener.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fce-d355-a5bd-9fdeaa970000</link>
      <description>Haener was a fourth-round pick by the Saints back in 2023 and spent the past season on their practice squad. Through two seasons, Haener has appeared in eight games while making one start. He has a career passing line of 226-1-1 on 39 attempts and a 46.2 completion percentage. Assuming he sticks with the team into training camp, Haener will be a long shot to make the 53-man roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fce-d355-a5bd-9fdeaa970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Matthew Stafford will not require surgery to repair a herniated disc in his back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fd3-d355-a5bd-9fd76f750000</link>
      <description>Stafford played through this injury all season. The same injury sidelined him for much of training camp and raised some doubts about his availability entering the season. Stafford played at an MVP caliber level despite dealing with the injury, and it sounds like the offseason will be all he needs to get right for next season, should he choose to return. Rapoport also noted that “as of at least a couple of days ago,” Stafford’s plan is to play next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1fd3-d355-a5bd-9fd76f750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos promoted pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb to offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2017-d042-afbc-7dd792340000</link>
      <description>A day after it was reported that Webb was “the leading candidate” to land the Broncos’ offensive coordinator job, the team made it official on Monday. Webb, who fielded multiple offensive coordinator requests this coaching cycle, will remain with the Broncos and finally get a chance to oversee a bit of the offense, although we would assume Payton will remain the team’s primary play-caller. Webb has long been viewed as an up-and-comer in the coaching ranks. A few successful year’s as the Broncos’ OC could put him in line for his first head coaching gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2017-d042-afbc-7dd792340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes the situation between the Browns and DC Jim Schwartz “remain TBD.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2022-d042-afbc-7df292690000</link>
      <description>New head coach Todd Monken is expected to meet with the media on Tuesday, and Garafolo said he doesn’t expect a firm answer on where things stand between the two sides. Schwartz has reportedly already cleaned out his office at the Browns’ facility after being passed over for the head coaching job, but remains under contract with the team. Things will get interesting if the Browns don’t let Brown out of his contract but he still opts to not return to the team. For now, all we can do is wait and see what Monken says about the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2022-d042-afbc-7df292690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired 49ers assistant HC Gus Bradley as their defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2047-d042-afbc-7dd7c3200000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz was first with the report. Bradley and new Titans head coach Robert Saleh both joined the 49ers last offseason and will now unite in Tennessee. Bradley served as a defensive coordinator from 2017 to 2024, overseeing operations for the Chargers, Raiders, and Colts over that span. A respected, veteran coach, Bradley, will not be tasked with play-calling duties, but will be a highly-valued voice in the room of a defense that finished 28th in points allowed and 21st in yards allowed last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2047-d042-afbc-7dd7c3200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced a return to Mexico City is planned for December 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-209e-d042-afbc-7dde77900000</link>
      <description>That brings the count to nine international games on the schedule for the 2026 regular season. Goodell added that his vision is to eventually get up to 16 international games per season as the league continues to expand to a more global market. The deal reportedly includes games in Mexico City for the next three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-209e-d042-afbc-7dde77900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jets QB Justin Fields declined an invitation to the 2025 Pro Bowl.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-20cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd3b3f0000</link>
      <description>Fields reportedly declined the invitation to focus on his offseason training as he continues his bid to return as a franchise quarterback after a tumultuous beginning to his career. Fields enters 2026 in the final year of a two-year deal signed with the Jets prior to the 2025 regular season but appears to be on the outs with the franchise, potentially auditioning for a backup gig somewhere else. The dual threat quarterback has started 53 games during a five-year NFL career while playing for three different franchises in the three previous seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-20cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd3b3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans QB C.J. Stroud declined an invitation to the 2025 Pro Bowl.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-212d-d042-afbc-7dff338a0000</link>
      <description>Both Stroud and Jets quarterback Justin Fields reportedly turned down invitations to the Pro Bowl Games, both citing their offseason preparations as the reason for the decision. It makes sense considering the crossroads of their respective careers, with Stroud set to play the 2026 regular season on the final year of his rookie contract prior to a team option in 2027. The fact that the Pro Bowl has become a glorified dog and pony show also likely influenced their decisions. Either way, there isn’t much to read into this non-news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-212d-d042-afbc-7dff338a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
