<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) was activated off the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c341-d332-a1fd-d77754c70000</link>
      <description>Thomas is expected to make his return to practice in hopes of being ready to go for Week 1 against Washington. Thomas has been sidelined while rehabbing from a foot injury he sustained last October. His loss was a big one for the Giants, graded in 2024 as Pro Football Focus’ third worst pass-blocking offensive line. A fully healthy Thomas would be a boon for Russell Wilson and the rest of the New York offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c341-d332-a1fd-d77754c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Maxwell Hairston (knee) is “a ways away” from beginning a ramping up process.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c346-db7b-a5dd-e346facb0000</link>
      <description>It sure sounds like there’s a real chance Hairston opens up on injured reserve after spraining his knee early in training camp. Buffalo might have Tre’Davious White or Dane Jackson running next to incumbents Christian Benford and Taron Johnson in nickel sets to open the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c346-db7b-a5dd-e346facb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes the Cowboys and EDGE Micah Parsons are “headed towards divorce in time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c349-d332-a1fd-d77fa5400000</link>
      <description>Schefter adds “it sounds like at this point it’s personal.” Since Parsons’ trade request earlier in August, we haven’t had much in the way of real news updates, and Schefter says both sides haven’t negotiated since April. “The only question is when is that divorce going to happen, and how is it going to happen?” Schefter continues. There are very few non-quarterbacks who could be traded and cause a monumental shift before the season started, but Parsons qualifies. We’ve yet to blurb about any teams directly linked to acquiring Parsons, but it would likely take at least a first-round pick — and probably more than just that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c349-d332-a1fd-d77fa5400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said that it is “hard to say” there’s a future in Indianapolis for Anthony Richardson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c34f-dbe3-a9bb-f35f45980000</link>
      <description>“Obviously, Daniel (Jones) is our starter right now. And if something happens to Daniel at some point, AR gets another opportunity,” Steichen continued. It’s not exactly a smoking gun statement, but it is damning about Richardson’s chances of playing this season that Steichen couldn’t even give a token pushback on the question. If the Colts truly aren’t married to Richardson, it’s possible that they get a trade offer they can’t refuse at cutdowns for the former No. 4 overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c34f-dbe3-a9bb-f35f45980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Jalen McMillan will be placed on injured reserve and could be out “past the Bucs Week 9 bye.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c355-dbe3-a9bb-f35754470000</link>
      <description>We’ve gone from McMillan “avoiding anything major” to him being out half the season through the last two days. McMillan starting on IR will give runway to Emeka Egbuka to be a major contributor to Tampa Bay’s offense immediately. It also may give supporting options like Cade Otton more of a share than they’d normally have as Tampa threads the needle early without McMillan and Chris Godwin. McMillan isn’t a must-hold in shallow leagues based on this reported timeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c355-dbe3-a9bb-f35754470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mailata (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c375-dbe3-a9bb-f3776afd0000</link>
      <description>Even if he’d been healthy, it’s hard to believe the Eagles would have let Mailata play in the preseason finale anyway. He will probably be fine for Week 1, but brain injuries are no laughing matter and there are a few every season that turn into extended absences. The Eagles will obviously give their star left tackle all the time he needs to recover ahead of the season opener against Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c375-dbe3-a9bb-f3776afd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released RB J.J. Taylor.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c377-d332-a1fd-d777b2d90000</link>
      <description>Taylor appeared in five games last year, rushing 10 times for 44 yards, and has yet to receiver more than 23 carries in an NFL season. The 27-year-old will look to catch on elsewhere on a practice squad or on the backend of a roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c377-d332-a1fd-d777b2d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed RB Patrick Taylor (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c38d-de13-afdc-c7cff57e0000</link>
      <description>That will end Taylor’s season before it begins — he suffered the shoulder injury in the second week of the preseason. Taylor has been a deep depth piece for the 49ers, drawing 39 carries for 183 yards and a score last year, and San Francisco’s injury woes at the position will continue. This slides Jeff Wilson into a stronger position at the start of the year, perhaps as high as Christian McCaffrey’s backup if Isaac Guerrendo and Jordan James aren’t able to recover from their injuries ahead of Week 1. The 49ers signed Nate Sudfeld to take Taylor’s place on the roster and absorb some punishment in Week 3 of the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c38d-de13-afdc-c7cff57e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indianapolis Star’s Joel A. Erickson reports Tyler Goodson (shoulder) avoided a major injury on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c394-dbe3-a9bb-f3d766440000</link>
      <description>Goodson injured his elbow in Indianapolis’ second preseason game on Saturday, but it appears the door will not be cracked for DJ Giddens just yet. At least not via injury, anyway. Goodson hasn’t returned to practice yet but it sounds like he has a decent shot at being available for the opener based on this report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c394-dbe3-a9bb-f3d766440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner believes WR Mitchell Tinsley is making the Bengals 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c397-db7b-a5dd-e3977ff30000</link>
      <description>Other than the Bengals sad first-team defense, Tinsley was the talk of last night’s preseason game between the Bengals and the Commanders with a 5/73/2 display on six targets, including two extremely nice end zone catches, one from Joe Burrow. Dehner adds that Tinsley’s performance “had him running with the first team during certain practices.” Do we need to scrap the entire depth chart and worry about Ja’Marr Chase’s target share? No. But Tinsley could potentially push Andrei Iosivas for some time in the third receiver role, and perhaps scoot ahead of Jermaine Burton at last cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c397-db7b-a5dd-e3977ff30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
