<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 2-of-4 targets for 46 yards in the Patriots’ Week 5 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b1-d6e9-af9d-bfb1961e0000</link>
      <description>Henry couldn’t replicate his torrid start to the season in this one as Diggs handily led the team with 12 targets on 30 Drake Maye pass attempts. His fantasy stats narrowly missed additional padding at the end of the first half when a designed target from the one bounced off his extended hand with one second remaining before the break. Henry gets a plus matchup in Week 6 against a Saints team fresh off their first victory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b1-d6e9-af9d-bfb1961e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught all three targets for 43 yards in the Patriots’ Week 5 win over the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b4-d6e9-af9d-bfb432b50000</link>
      <description>Boutte’s days of leading the team in receiving appear to be long gone, particularly considering veteran wide receiver Stefon Diggs’ performances the past two games. Diggs went over 100 yards for the second consecutive outing against the Bills, indicating he has worked his way back into game shape following a season-ending knee injury in 2024. To that end, Boutte can safely be returned to the fantasy wire as the team’s third option through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b4-d6e9-af9d-bfb432b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen completed 22-of-31 passes for 253 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Bills’ 23-20, Week 5 loss to the Patriots, adding 53 yards on nine carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b6-dca3-a9fb-bfbf2d650000</link>
      <description>The Bills uncharacteristically committed three turnovers against the Patriots, leading to just under three minutes of game time with a lead. The first half was a messy affair in which both teams could not refrain from penalties or turning the ball over, heading to the break in a 6-3 slugfest. Allen would lead the team down the field to take their first lead of the game on their first possession of the second half, but a quick answer from the Patriots saw the lead short-lived. The team ws never able to get into rhythm as their run game saw significant struggles, forcing a more one-dimensional offense to attack the short areas of the field. The loss removed all undefeated teams from the 2025 season after the Eagles also lost in Week 5 and brings the Patriots to within one game of the division lead, something the Bill will look to rectify on the road in Week 6 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7b6-dca3-a9fb-bfbf2d650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 15 times for 49 yards in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7bb-d95b-addb-fffff0ea0000</link>
      <description>Cook and the rest of the Bills struggled to get into rhythm, with two first half turnovers contributing to a sloppy first half that saw them enter the break in a 6-3 deficit. The Patriots were able to effectively clamp down on the run game and force the Bills into one-dimensionality, clearly evident in Cooks’ underwhelming box score. The loss drops the Bills to 4-1, now only one game ahead of the Patriots, ahead of a Week 6 matchup with the Falcons on Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7bb-d95b-addb-fffff0ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught all six targets for 108 yards in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7bf-d6e9-af9d-bfbf1bb70000</link>
      <description>Kincaid broke the century mark for the first time in his career, more than doubling up the nearest Buffalo pass-catcher in the process. Two first half turnovers allowed the Patriots to clamp down on the run, in turn forcing the Bills into a more one-dimensional offensive approach that focused on hitting the intermediate areas of the middle of the field through the air. Those variables led to the career night for the third-year tight end, who continually found space behind a linebacker unit that played close to the line of scrimmage throughout. Kincaid might find less room to operate against the Falcons in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7bf-d6e9-af9d-bfbf1bb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 6-of-9 targets for 45 yards in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c2-deb6-a7fd-f7dfa58b0000</link>
      <description>Shakir quickly became quarterback Josh Allen’s top target on a night the Patriots effectively removed the run game. The counter to New England’s linebacker unit playing so close to the line of scrimmage was tight end Dalton Kincaid, who went for a career-high 108 yards in the loss. The short-area nature of Shakir’s targets were not enough to return a usable fantasy outing, something he will look to rectify when the Bills take on the Falcons on Monday Night Football in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c2-deb6-a7fd-f7dfa58b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 4-of-7 targets for 23 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c5-deb6-a7fd-f7df4f710000</link>
      <description>Coleman routinely matched up against the top coverage corner from the Patriots in Christian Gonzalez, whose coverage all but eliminated Coleman from the game plan. A second half touchdown brought the Bills within three points and he narrowly missed adding a second on the following possession, although Gonzalez was able to leverage the back of the end zone to ensure Coleman didn’t get both feet down in the field of play. The modest fantasy outing now marks four consecutive games with four or fewer receptions after his Week 1 eruption, making Coleman nothing more than a touchdown-dependent FLEX option moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c5-deb6-a7fd-f7df4f710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer caught both targets for 36 yards in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c9-d95b-addb-ffcf47ea0000</link>
      <description>Palmer ranked behind Keon Coleman, Khalil Shakir, Dalton Kincaid, and Dawson Knox in offensive snaps played this season and has now gone four straight games with two or fewer receptions after his five-catch outing in Week 1. That leaves him unworthy of weekly fantasy consideration, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c9-d95b-addb-ffcf47ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) “is expected to go” for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b97c-de31-a999-bdfe32150000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, the Chiefs’ decision to place Worthy on their injury report was more out of precaution. He then added that the second-year receiver “is fine” and should be good to go for Monday night’s game against the Jaguars. Despite the optimism to start the morning, fantasy managers will still want to check the Chiefs inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to ensure Worthy is officially in the clear for tonight’s tilt with the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b97c-de31-a999-bdfe32150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said “it’s a very fair question after the turnovers that we had” when asked if he still believes in Jake Browning as the QB1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9a1-db72-a199-fbeb23610000</link>
      <description>The question about Taylor’s belief in Browning came following Taylor’s postgame remarks in which he said the team will “look at all personnel to make sure we’re doing the right thing.” Browning hasn’t been great in place of Joe Burrow. The backup has done most of his stat padding in meaningless garbage time, but the options behind him, which include journeymen Brett Rypien and Mike White, are unlikely to be much better. This felt like an inevitable problem the Bengals would face the moment Burrow (toe) went down in Week 2, but the Bengals’ offense has compounded in quick fashion. Since Week 3, the Bengals rank last in EPA per play, 31st in dropback success rate, and 29th in offensive success rate. It’s not good, folks. We’ll see if a change comes down the line, but as far as fantasy is concerned, anybody but Browning being under center could spell further disaster for Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9a1-db72-a199-fbeb23610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
