<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a great development as the Bucs come out of their bye week. There was hope Irving would be back at practice ahead of Tampa’s Week 10 game against the Patriots after being sidelined more more than a month with foot and shoulder injuries. If Irving can’t get in a limited practice Thursday or Friday, he’ll likely miss Week 10, leaving Rachaad White as the team’s lead back. White, who has 67 touches over his four games as the Bucs’ starter, would be a top-20 fantasy option against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</link>
      <description>Godwin continues to sit with a lingering fibula injury, even coming out of Tampa’s Week 9 bye. He would appear to be a long shot to suit up for Week 10 against New England unless he can practice tomorrow or Friday. Godwin hasn’t played since early October. Returning from a major 2024 ankle injury, he has six catches on 14 targets this season. Sterling Shepard and Tez Johnson could continue as Tampa starters this week if Godwin remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54f9-d1e7-a1fa-5efb46f30000</link>
      <description>It’s something of a surprise after Cook appeared fully healthy in Week 9 against the Chiefs. Cook had 114 scoreless yards on 27 rushes against KC, and now has 417 rushing yards over his past three outings. Cook’s DNP could be cautionary ahead of the Bills’ Week 10 matchup with a weak Miami defense. Cook drafters should keep a close eye on his late-week practice status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54f9-d1e7-a1fa-5efb46f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joey Bosa (wrist) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54fc-d673-a39e-f4fd1d3e0000</link>
      <description>Bosa apparently picked up the wrist injury in Week 9 against Kansas City. He’ll need to log a practice tomorrow or Friday if he’s going to suit up in Week 10 against the Dolphins. The veteran has four sacks and four forced fumbles this season on a Buffalo defense that pressures the quarterback at the NFL’s third highest rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54fc-d673-a39e-f4fd1d3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent CB Asante Samuel Jr. is visiting with the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5504-d673-a39e-f595f2e90000</link>
      <description>Samuel was recently medically cleared after undergoing a spinal fusion procedure and will begin visiting potential suitors, starting with the Panthers. The former Chargers star missed most of the 2024 season with a serious neck injury. He has six interceptions and 148 tackles over 50 NFL games. It would be something of a surprise if Samuel sees game action in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5504-d673-a39e-f595f2e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said the team is “sorting through the medical opinions” on Jayden Daniels (elbow).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5518-d713-ad9e-7d5c60a60000</link>
      <description>Quinn said the team would announce a plan on how to proceed with the serious elbow injury Daniels sustained in Week 9 after looking strongly into various medical opinions on how to address the injury. Quinn said Monday there is no timetable for Daniels’ return to game action, though there remains some hope Daniels can avoid surgery and return later this year. He did not suffer a fracture in his elbow. For now, Marcus Mariota will start for Washington. He’ll be a superflex option in Week 10 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5518-d713-ad9e-7d5c60a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed K Harrison Mevis, formerly of the Jets, to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-552a-d45b-affe-55befec60000</link>
      <description>The former Birmingham Stallions kicker will provide some competition for Joshua Karty. Karty has struggled mightily this year, connecting on just 10-of-15 field goals and 23-of-26 PATs. Two of his field goal misses came on Sunday against the Saints. Mevis could take the job from Karty as soon as Week 10 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-552a-d45b-affe-55befec60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553a-d673-a39e-f5bba80f0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson didn’t practice at all last week and was ruled out on Friday. A DNP to open the week is not a good sign for his availability in Week 10. TreVeyon Henderson led the backfield with 14 carries for 55 yards versus the Falcons in Week 9. He also caught four passes for 32 yards. On the other hand, backup Terrell Jennings saw 11 carries and operated as the short-yardage back, punching in the team’s only rushing touchdown of the day. Jennings’ presence in the backfield will make it hard to treat Henderson as anything other than a low-end RB2 for Sunday’s game against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553a-d673-a39e-f5bba80f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553f-d713-ad9e-7d7f67f30000</link>
      <description>Boutte suffered a hamstring injury in Sunday’s game against the Falcons. Head coach Mike Vrabel called him day to day earlier this week. A DNP to open the week is not a great sign, but New England’s next two practice reports will be more revealing. Mack Hollins and Kyle Williams will both be in line for more routes in Week 10 if Boutte is unable to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-553f-d713-ad9e-7d7f67f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5548-d713-ad9e-7d5c10c70000</link>
      <description>BTJ could get in some work during the portion of practice closed to the media, though we doubt that actually happens. This should go down as a DNP once the Jags release their first injury report. Thomas Jr. is dealing with a “low-grade high ankle sprain,” according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter. Even the lowest of high-ankle injuries typically result in a week or two of missed time. We aren’t holding our breath for BTJ to play this week. Parker Washington and the newly acquired Jakobi Meyers are in line to lead this team in targets on Sunday. Washington will clock in as a WR3. Meyers will get a week in the WR4 ranks while he learns the ropes of Liam Coen’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5548-d713-ad9e-7d5c10c70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
