<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 23:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated CB Trevon Diggs (knee) ahead of Week 16 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</link>
      <description>The team also placed fellow cornerback DaRon Bland (foot) on injured reserve in an associated move. As has been the case for most of the season, the Cowboys continue forward without pieces from their secondary. Diggs pushed his return up to the limit, meaning we might not see him play a full allotment of snaps in his first game in over two months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d1e-d35e-a1bf-7dde39a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders delared QB Jayden Daniels, RB Chase Edmonds, T George Fant, T Laremy Tunsil, TE Colson Yankoff, and DT Eddie Goldman inactive for Week 16 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d26-d35e-a1bf-7de62ff20000</link>
      <description>The Commanders will be without both starting offensive tackles in a game started by backup quarterback Marcus Mariota, potentially opening the door for defensive dominance from a relentless Eagles defense. Expect a reliance on the ground game to start while getting back Chris Rodriguez from a one-game absence, but that stance could quickly shift should the Commanders fall behind early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d26-d35e-a1bf-7de62ff20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared OLB Josh Uche, QB Sam Howell, CB Mac McWilliams, RB A.J. Dillon, TE/FB Cam Latu, T Lane Johnson, and DT Jalen Carter inactive for Week 16 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d77-da28-afbb-fd7f9cff0000</link>
      <description>The team gets back G Landon Dickerson, which could benefit Saquon Barkley and the run game against a far inferior Commanders roster. Philadelphia can clinch a playoff berth with a win over their divisional opponents, eliminating the Cowboys in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d77-da28-afbb-fd7f9cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers elevated OLB Jason Pierre-Paul ahead of Week 16 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</link>
      <description>The appearance will be the first regular season game for the soon-to-be 37-year-old veteran in a over two years. It’ll come in a must-win, divisional showdown with the Panthers. The two teams play twice in the final three weeks of the regular season to decide who will represent the NFC South in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d7d-dc7a-af9b-ffff0d3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d91-d35e-a1bf-7dd3b1460000</link>
      <description>The Bears get back one of their defensive leaders after Edmunds missed the previous four contests while on injured reserve. His return comes at the perfect time, ahead of a divisional clash with the Packers on Saturday evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d91-d35e-a1bf-7dd3b1460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) for Week 16 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d93-d35e-a1bf-7dd331a70000</link>
      <description>Pearsall picked up two injuries in Week 15 and will now miss the team’s Monday Night Football game against the Colts. His absence could thrust Kendrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson into more prominent roles, although it would likely be wide receiver Jauan Jennings and tight end George Kittle that stand to benefit the most against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3d93-d35e-a1bf-7dd331a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger off the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dc8-da28-afbb-fdfda71d0000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger will not be active for Week 16 against the Jaguars, but the quarterback will get a nicer paycheck will operating as the emergency signal-caller going forward. The 27-year-old was offered a chance to join the Colts’ active roster after the Daniel Jones’ injury, but he declined and chose to stick with Denver. One can’t help but think this is a reward for his loyalty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dc8-da28-afbb-fdfda71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Watson (Achilles) was not activated off injured reserve prior to the Texans’ Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dcc-da28-afbb-fdfd69bc0000</link>
      <description>Watson has been out of action since the middle of September with his Achilles injury. The 29-year-old could be an option in the final weeks, but in a role that provides zero fantasy upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dcc-da28-afbb-fdfd69bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce is off the injury report for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dd1-da28-afbb-fdfd5efc0000</link>
      <description>Pierce was able to get in a couple of full practices, and barring a setback, the 25-year-old should be ready to roll for the Monday Night Football tilt against the 49ers. Pierce’s skill set does not pair well with Philip Rivers, so he should be consider as a WR4 at best for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3dd1-da28-afbb-fdfd5efc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
