<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) got in a limited practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3a-db72-a199-ff7b9bdd0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the Falcons were just taking it easy on the veteran wideout after he left Week 4’s game with the hamstring injury. We’re probably trending towards Mooney either being a questionable for Monday Night or, perhaps, off the injury report entirely with another upward trend on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf3a-db72-a199-ff7b9bdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said he “anticipates” Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) to be available against the Lions in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4b-db72-a199-ff4bfcda0000</link>
      <description>Worthy was “moving around good” and “did everything” per Reid after missing Thursday’s session entirely. It does feel like Worthy is playing through the injuries as he’s had some fairly disappointing box scores compared to the amount of attention he could have gotten in the passing game. However he’ll be a WR2/WR3 borderline candidate against Detroit’s banged-up secondary in Week 6, his final week before Rashee Rice returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4b-db72-a199-ff4bfcda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) is doubtful for Week 6 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4f-def2-abdb-df6fef7a0000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters that Havenstein will not practice today and is not expected to play. Havenstein missed the Rams’ Week 5 game against the 49ers as well. Fortunately, for Matthew Stafford, the Ravens are now without their top-two pressure generators, with DT Nnamdi Madubuike (neck) on injured reserve and OLB Odafe Oweh having been traded to the Chargers earlier this week. Stafford should play efficiently in Week 6. Rams LB Omar Speights (ankle) is also doubtful to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4f-def2-abdb-df6fef7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 6 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf50-db72-a199-ff5b67a20000</link>
      <description>Atwell hasn’t had the targets to do much work with Davante Adams and Puka Nacua dominating the ball for the Rams, so only those in very deep leagues needed to worry about this. Jordan Whittington has actually had more snaps than Atwell through five weeks and figures to be the main deep-league replacement. Konata Mumpfield could also get more involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf50-db72-a199-ff5b67a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is questionable for New Orleans’ Week 6 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf53-d94a-a79d-cf5ffc9a0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like even if he does play, Kamara could yield more carries to Kendre Miller against a stout New England front. Kamara is best-approached as a high-end FLEX play this week despite his name value. Kamara-reliant managers should have backup plans in place for Sunday as it doesn’t sound like he’s a sure bet to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf53-d94a-a79d-cf5ffc9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Colby Parkinson (concussion) is questionable for Week 6 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf61-d94a-a79d-cf6d208a0000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters that Parkinson has cleared the concussion protocol and will continue to be monitored by team in the lead up to kickoff. As long as he remains setback-free, he should be good to go. Parkinson will only warrant streaming consideration if starting TE Tyler Higbee (hip) is unable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf61-d94a-a79d-cf6d208a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper believes Jerome Ford and Breece Hall could be “potential options” for the Chargers on the running back trade market.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf64-d94a-a79d-cf6df6580000</link>
      <description>He notes that how Hassan Haskins and Kimani Vidal handle an assignment this week against the Dolphins will probably help determine how aggressive they are in the running back trade market. Notably, Popper writes that having a second back next to Omarion Hampton is “how they want to play at their core.” With the Chargers already having struck a trade for Odafe Oweh, it sounds like they could be aggressive at the deadline to fix their holes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf64-d94a-a79d-cf6df6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 6 game against Miami.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf69-dd4c-afb9-efe982d90000</link>
      <description>Johnston did practice each day of the week, but always in a limited fashion. Today’s update from the beats had him working out on a side field. Barring something from Jim Harbaugh, we’d probably treat him as a true game-time decision. If Johnston is out, it will make Ladd McConkey and Keenan Allen more desirable plays against a weak Dolphins defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf69-dd4c-afb9-efe982d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is not practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf6c-d94a-a79d-cf6d215c0000</link>
      <description>If it weren’t for Pete Carroll’s chicanery last week to throw him on the questionable line, we’d say it’s almost a certainty that Bowers will be ruled out later today. Bowers missed last week’s game, hasn’t practiced this week, and admitted that he wasn’t playing full speed when asked about it last Friday. It doesn’t sound like there’s much to be gained by him trying to gut it out, but we’ll see what the Raiders decide later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf6c-d94a-a79d-cf6d215c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers ruled out LT Joe Alt (ankle) for Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf64-dd4c-afb9-efe5dcd50000</link>
      <description>The Chargers also ruled out RT Trey Pipkins III (knee), WR Derius Davis (knee) and DT Da’Shawn Hand (groin). They face a Dolphins pass rush ranking 25th in quarterback pressures (71) and tying for 18th in NFL sacks (nine), so Justin Herbert could be only moderately impacted by Alt and Pipkins’ absences. Fortunately, RG Mekhi Becton (hand) is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf64-dd4c-afb9-efe5dcd50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
