<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 13 times for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 8 win over the Steelers, adding 12 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23c1-deb1-a39b-23cf7c630000</link>
      <description>Jacobs found the sledding tough against the stout Pittsburgh defense and was completely overshadowed by both Jordan Love and Tucker Kraft. Even so, he made his presence felt in fantasy circles with a touchdown run in the fourth quarter to give the Packers their first lead since being up 7-3 in the first quarter. The team would not relinquish that lead, outscoring the Steelers 28-10 after the break. Jacobs remains a locked-in RB1 ahead of a matchup with the Panthers at home in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23c1-deb1-a39b-23cf7c630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft caught 7-of-9 targets for 143 yards and two touchdowns in the Packers’ Week 8 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23dc-dab4-a3fb-bbfc0b5d0000</link>
      <description>Kraft set career highs in receptions (seven) and yards (143) while tying a career high with two scores, also gaining over 100 yards after the catch on National Tight Ends Day. He made two spectacular catches over defenders, the first of which went for his game-long 59-yard reception on the team’s first possession of the third quarter, kickstarting a ferocious second half performance to overcome a nine-point deficit at the break. Kraft continues to perform in the midst of a true breakout season, something that could continue against the Cover-3-heavy Panthers in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23dc-dab4-a3fb-bbfc0b5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught all four targets for 85 yards in the Packers’ Week 8 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe18aed0000</link>
      <description>Watson drew the start in his first game since Week 18 of the 2024 season, making his return from a torn ACL in spectacular fashion. His contributions to the team made it appear as if he never left, routinely throwing massive blocks when he wasn’t touching the ball while flashing his downfield abilities with a solid 85-yard showing. Watson remains unlikely to see consistent volume in a spread aerial attack in Green Bay, but performances like this one serve as a reminder of his weekly upside moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe18aed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 3-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Packers’ Week 8 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e5-d5d8-a3ff-fbe51bdb0000</link>
      <description>He added a two-point conversion in the fourth quarter to put the Packers up by three points but was significantly overshadowed by tight end Tucker Kraft on National Tight End Day. Doubs remains an integral part of the Green Bay offense due to his well-rounded game, but a general lack of weekly volume keeps him reliant on touchdowns to return fantasy utility. Consider Doubs a viable FLEX when the Packers host the Panthers in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e5-d5d8-a3ff-fbe51bdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 24-of-36 passes for 219 yards and two touchdowns in the Steelers’ 35-25, Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e9-d245-adfb-b7ff134a0000</link>
      <description>The vaunted Green Bay pass rush left its mark on Rodgers, routinely pressuring the veteran quarterback to climb the pocket and throw under duress. That was particularly true for Micah Parsons, who notched one sack and gave Rodgers someone to think about on nearly every dropback. Rodgers was attempting to become the first quarterback in NFL history to beat all 32 NFL teams but came up short in his first game against the Packers, leaving the accomplishment one unlikely to be achieved in the near future. The Steelers seemed to be in control after taking a nine-point lead into the break but were outscored 28-10 in the second half to drop to 4-3. The devastating loss by the Bengals earlier in the day keeps their lead at 1.5 games as we approach the midway point in the season, but their margin for error continues to erode after consecutive losses. That is not the best position to be in ahead of a Week 9 showdown with the 7-1 Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23e9-d245-adfb-b7ff134a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 13 times for 62 yards in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers, adding 11 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbef5fc60000</link>
      <description>Warren did most of his damage in the first half while the Steelers played with a lead but touched the football only four times in the second half as the Packers stormed back to win. Much of that was due to an inability to move the football, although Kenneth Gainwell did mix in at increased rates after the break. Warren remains a fantasy RB2 ahead of a difficult matchup against the 7-1 Colts in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbef5fc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roman Wilson caught 4-of-5 targets for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f4-dab4-a3fb-bbf465520000</link>
      <description>Wilson notched his first professional touchdown late in the fourth quarter and set career highs in targets, receptions, and yards in the loss. The outburst is a promising sign considering the general lack of secondary options through the air for the Steelers, although Wilson will be a difficult start ahead of a Week 9 showdown with the 7-1 Colts. Fantasy managers could look to stash the youngster on benches for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f4-dab4-a3fb-bbf465520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 5-of-7 targets for 55 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf919af0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was flagged for a personal foul in the second half after poking a Packers defender in the eye through the face mask, an act that continued to spur heated interactions between the two teams. He was also flagged for offensive pass interference on a comeback screen in the first quarter, overshadowing his touchdown for real-world football in the process. Metcalf remains a low-volume WR2 that is heavily reliant on touchdowns, but the Steelers simply have very little competition to targets at the moment. That could change as the trade deadline approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf919af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 2-of-3 targets for 17 yards in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23fc-d245-adfb-b7ffa4ae0000</link>
      <description>Smith saw sparse usage throughout as the team continued its four-man rotation at tight end. He narrowly missed connecting with quarterback Aaron Rodgers on a deep seam in the fourth quarter that could have padded his counting stats for fantasy managers, but the ball fell to the turf just out of the sprawling reach of the veteran tight end. Smith remains off fantasy radars in all but the deepest formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23fc-d245-adfb-b7ffa4ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 3-of-4 targets for 13 yards in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ff-d5d8-a3ff-fbffb2ec0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth came down hard on his neck and head on the first play from scrimmage in the third quarter and had to be helped to the sideline, ultimately returning two series later to finish the game. It is unclear if he was checked for a concussion as it appeared to be his neck that bore the brunt of the fall. It remains difficult for Freiermuth to carry legitimate fantasy value while splitting time with three other tight ends in Pittsburgh, even after his two-touchdown showing a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ff-d5d8-a3ff-fbffb2ec0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
