<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz was not spotted at Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c7-deb1-a39b-27cfcdc00000</link>
      <description>This absence is presumably due to the injury to his non-throwing shoulder he dealt with ahead of Thursday night’s game against the Chargers. Wentz took a bit of a beating from the Chargers’ defense in that game, so his absence on Monday is notable. Monday’s practice won’t show up on the team’s injury report, which is released on Wednesday, but even if he is able to play in Week 9, Wentz is most likely to backup J.J. McCarthy, who is making his long-awaited return from an ankle injury he suffered in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c7-deb1-a39b-27cfcdc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Bryce Young (ankle) could practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c9-d245-adfb-b7dfe6e80000</link>
      <description>We remain a little more skeptical on Young returning this week given they’ll only speak in possibilities, but Andy Dalton’s performance yesterday is certainly extra fuel to get Young up and ready as soon as possible. Young didn’t practice all last week after suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c9-d245-adfb-b7dfe6e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ankle) is expected to practice this week and play in Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26cf-deb1-a39b-27cf10010000</link>
      <description>This was mostly expected after McVay said last week that Nacua would be good to go following the team’s Week 8 bye. Nacua attempted to play through the injury when he went down in Week 6 against the Ravens, which led many to believe the injury was relatively minor. We’ll monitor Nacua’s status throughout the week, but we would expect him to play even if he’s listed as a limited participant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26cf-deb1-a39b-27cf10010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said he expects Rob Havenstein (ankle) to practice and play in Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26d8-dab4-a3fb-bff837f00000</link>
      <description>Havenstein has missed the last three games with an ankle injury. That time away, coupled with the team’s Week 8 bye, has proven to be enough for the veteran tackle to return in Week 9 against the Saints. Havenstein has allowed one sack and 16 pressures on 154 pass blocking snaps this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26d8-dab4-a3fb-bff837f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said CB Storm Duck (knee) will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dc-dab4-a3fb-bffcb6850000</link>
      <description>A huge loss for those of us who believe in the power of names. Duck played only 44 snaps over two games as he dealt with an oblique injury early in the season. The 2024 UDFA should have a role in the 2026 Dolphins DB room, although with mass leadership changes looking somewhat likely, perhaps things could change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dc-dab4-a3fb-bffcb6850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports “teams have had a hard time getting a clear read” on whether or not the Raiders want to trade Jakobi Meyers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dd-d245-adfb-b7df2d2a0000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, multiple teams have shown interest in acquiring Meyers, who is in the final year of his contract. However, he also adds that “the belief is it would take at least a Day 2 pick for the Raiders to even consider [a trade].” A Day 2 pick would be close to top-100 territory, which feels like a steep price for a solid player who is on an expiring deal. The right offer could still get it done, but the Raiders would likely have to settle for something less than a Day 2 pick if they hope to get any kind of return for a player who has been vocal about wanting a trade and is a near lock to not re-sign with the team next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dd-d245-adfb-b7df2d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Joe Flacco is day-to-day with a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2702-deb1-a39b-270e74cb0000</link>
      <description>Flacco left the field late in Sunday’s game with the injury, but returned in time to try to will the Bengals to a win against the once winless Jets. The day-to-day timeline suggests there isn’t much to worry about here, which should come as good news to any fantasy managers who have Ja’Marr Chase or Tee Higgins rostered. We would expect Flacco to play in Week 9 against the Bears barring any setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2702-deb1-a39b-270e74cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendrickson is day-to-day after re-aggravating his hip injury in Week 8’s loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-271a-deb1-a39b-271e4bac0000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson re-aggravating his injury seems bad, but Taylor’s day-to-day timeline suggests Hendrickson will be good to go when it comes time to face the Bears in Week 9. Hendrickson has played in seven of the Bengals’ eight games this season, but has managed just 16 tackles and four sacks in those games. While the numbers have been decent, he’s well off the 17.5 sack pace he’s posted each of the last two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-271a-deb1-a39b-271e4bac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Michael DiRocco believes Travis Hunter could start “getting the WR1 treatment from the Jaguars in the season’s second half.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2730-d245-adfb-b77f5d0d0000</link>
      <description>DiRocco continues: “that’s partly due to his playmaking and run-after-the-catch ability, but also because Brian Thomas Jr. hasn’t played at that level all season.” Ouch. We’ve seen plenty of quotes from the coaching staff hinting at the best 11 on offense being used as much as humanly possible, but DiRocco spells out that Hunter is “going to be a significant player in the offense going forward.” Hunter probably starts Week 9 in the WR3 conversation, but it’s possible we could be seeing a shift in the Jaguars pecking order in the second half of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2730-d245-adfb-b77f5d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
