<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon McManus went 3-for-3 on his field goal attempts in Week 16’s loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f6d-da28-afbb-ff7d75e40000</link>
      <description>McManus also converted on his only extra point of the evening. The veteran kicker nailed field goals from 26, 22, and 28 yards in this one, helping hold off the Bears just long enough for the Packers to build a 16-6 lead, but that evaporated in the final minutes of the fourth quarter. McManus has now converted on 22 of his 28 field goal attempts this season and will be a solid Week 17 option against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f6d-da28-afbb-ff7d75e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cairo Santos went 3-for-3 on his field goal attempts in Week 16’s win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f70-d087-addf-bff0af250000</link>
      <description>Santos came up clutch late for the Bears when he nailed a 51-yard field goal with just under 11 minutes to go in the fourth quarter, only come back and knock down a 43-yard field goal at the two-minute warning in the same quarter. Santos hit the Bears’ only PAT of the night to send them to overtime and has now made 24-of-29 field goals this season. He will be on the kicking radar in Week 16 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3f70-d087-addf-bff0af250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Cardinals plan to ease Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) back in for Week 16 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4110-da28-afbb-c57dca4c0000</link>
      <description>Schefter obviously noted that MHJ is expected to play. That was a pretty safe assumption as of Friday when MHJ told reporters his heel is “good enough to go.” Michael Wilson has been posting video game numbers in Harrison’s absence. With the latter likely on a pitch count this week, we fully expect Wilson to operate as the team’s top wideout versus the Falcons. Wilson will stay in the WR2 ranks this week while MHJ is relegated to a WR4 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4110-da28-afbb-c57dca4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Drake London (knee) is expected to play in Week 16 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-411a-d35e-a1bf-45da5c4b0000</link>
      <description>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said as much earlier in the week, so this was always the expectation. London has been out since Week 12 because of a PCL sprain. Even with Kyle Pitts posting a historic stat line in Week 15, London will return to top dog status in the Atlanta offense. Playing in a likely shootout with the Cardinals, London is back in the WR1 ranks this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-411a-d35e-a1bf-45da5c4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Nick Chubb (ribs) is expected to play in Week 16 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-411d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf1ca00000</link>
      <description>Chubb practiced in full twice this week and shouldn’t be limited after missing Week 15’s game with the rib issue. Woody Marks, on the other hand, only logged one practice all week. It was a limited session on Friday, after which the team listed him as questionable. If he doesn’t suit up, Chubb would be in line for lead back duties and an RB2 ranking versus a lowly Raiders defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-411d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf1ca00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Christian Kirk (illness) is expected to play in Week 16 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4120-d087-addf-f1f037670000</link>
      <description>Players tend to play through illnesses, but Kirk was a late addition ot the injury report. The team added him on Friday and listed him as a DNP, putting him at some risk of missing today’s game. Per Schefter, he is good to go. Kirk has scored double-digit fantasy points just once this year. He is not on the fantasy radar for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4120-d087-addf-f1f037670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports, “T.J. Watt’s return to play remains murky and uncertain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4123-da28-afbb-c57f88010000</link>
      <description>Watt is dealing with a partially collapsed lung. He was hospitalized with the issue ahead of the Steelers’ Week 15 game against the Dolphins. Watt did not play in that game and has already been ruled out for Week 16. Per Schefter, “Watt’s focus has been on getting healthy,” and returning to the field is secondary. At this point, it’s safe to say Watt is unlikely to suit up in Week 17. The Steelers may ultimately choose to hold him out until the playoffs, if they make the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4123-da28-afbb-c57f88010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Ravens S Kyle Hamilton is “more likely to play than not” for Week 16 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4128-dc7a-af9b-cfbf55c30000</link>
      <description>Hamilton was a surprise addition to the injury report on Friday, being listed as a limited participant because of the ankle issue. Per Rapoport, Hamilton will still need to go through a pre-game workout before the team makes a final call on his status. The standout defensive back has 87 tackles, seven pass breakups, and one sack this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4128-dc7a-af9b-cfbf55c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Tyrod Taylor (groin/knee) is expected to be the Jets’ backup quarterback in Week 16 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-412c-d35e-a1bf-45ee4cba0000</link>
      <description>Brady Cook was named the starter early in the week. Taylor is technically listed as questionable, but he told reporters on Friday he “feels good enough to play.” With Justin Fields also banged up, Taylor will hold the clipboard this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-412c-d35e-a1bf-45ee4cba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Tee Higgins “was cleared from the NFL’s concussion protocol.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-412e-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcc2b0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals also had Higgins see a concussion expert to confirm his clearance and give Higgins extra reassurance. Higgins was listed as questionable on Friday but will be active when the Bengals release their inactives. Facing a defeated Dolphins squad, Higgins should be able to create a few big plays in Week 16, keeping him in the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-412e-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcc2b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
