<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:01:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons waived WR Nick Nash.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8a6-dbe3-a9bb-f8f7b4570000</link>
      <description>The Falcons also waived TE Joshua Simon, OL Joshua Gray, WR Dylan Drummond, CB Dontae Manning, DL Simeon Barrow Jr., RB Carlos Washington Jr., CB Cobee Bryant, K Lenny Krieg, RB Elijah Dotson, TE Nikola Kalinic, WR Quincy Skinner Jr. and S Josh Thompson. The Falcons released OL Jordan Williams, S Henry Black, S Jordan Fuller, EDGE Khalid Kareem, OL Brandon Parker, QB Easton Stick, DL Kentavius Street, CB Keith Taylor, OL Jake Hanson, CB CJ Henderson, LB/S Ronnie Harrison, WR Chris Blair, OL Matthew Cindric, QB Ben DiNucci, DL Morgan Fox, LB Caleb Johnson, CB Lamar Jackson, LB Nick Kubitz, WR Jesse Matthews and EDGE Ronnie Perkins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8a6-dbe3-a9bb-f8f7b4570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (ankle) and OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) both passed their physicals today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8c8-de13-afdc-eecbf6970000</link>
      <description>Godwin is still expected to miss regular season games, and could be out until October. He will, however, officially avoid being placed on any type of reserve list. Less is known about Wirfs’ expected return date but both players will now be allowed to practice with their teammates. Godwin could end up returning weekly WR3 value once he gets up to speed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8c8-de13-afdc-eecbf6970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans waived TE Luke Lachey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8bd-d332-a1fd-febf532d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans spent a seventh-rounder on Lachey, but part ways with him before the start of the season. The team also waived/released WR Quintez Cephus, QB Kedon Slovis, S Myles Bryant, LB Nick Niemann, CB Damon Arnette, TE Luke Lachey, FB Jakob Johnson, LB Jackson Woodard, LB K.C. Ossai, LS Blake Ferguson, DE Solomon Byrd, DT Junior Tafuna, C Eli Cox, OT Conor McDermott, OG LaDarius Henderson, WR Daniel Jackson, DE Casey Toohill, OT Trent Brown, CB D’Angelo Ross, RB J.J. Taylor, CB Arthur Maulet, TE Dalton Keene, S Russ Yeast, Jawhar Jordan, DT Haggai Ndubuisi, OT Jaylon Thomas, and OT Zach Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8bd-d332-a1fd-febf532d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) avoided opening the season on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ce-dbe3-a9bb-f8df162d0000</link>
      <description>Likely will begin the season as a member of the Ravens’ active roster and be eligible to play right away. Had Likely been placed on injured reserve with a designation to return, he would have been sidelined for at least four games. Likely can be stashed on benches by those who wish to see if head coach John Harbaugh’s All-Pro dreams for Likely come to fruition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ce-dbe3-a9bb-f8df162d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets waived QB Brady Cook.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8d2-db7b-a5dd-e8d6d5540000</link>
      <description>The Jets let go of Cook after the rookie UDFA posted 235 passing yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the preseason. The team also waived DB Jarrick Bernard-Converse, DB Dean Clark, DB Jordan Clark, RB Donovan Edwards, DE Kingsley Jonathan, G Kohl Levao, K Harrison Mevis, DT Payton Page, WR Jamaal Pritchett, LB Jackson Sirmon, WR Quentin Skinner, LB Aaron Smith, WR Brandon Smith, T Carter Warren, DE Eric Watts, G Leander Wiegand, DB Jarius Monroe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8d2-db7b-a5dd-e8d6d5540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos released QB Sam Ehlinger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ea-d332-a1fd-fefe92230000</link>
      <description>The Broncos had signed Ehlinger to a one-year deal in the offseason, but now choose to let him go with Jarrett Stidham the primary backup to Bo Nix. The team also released S Sam Franklin Jr., FB Adam Prentice, G Calvin Throckmorton and LB Garret Wallow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ea-d332-a1fd-fefe92230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs released TE Robert Tonyan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8f6-db7b-a5dd-e8f698bb0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs cut Tonyan after signing him to a one-year deal this offseason. However, Kansas City Star’sSam McDowellreports the plan is for Tonyan to return to the team. The Chiefs also released LB Cole Christiansen, S Mike Edwards, DT Mike Pennel, and DT Marlon Tuipulotu. They also waived CB Elijhah Badger, DE Owen Carney, CB Ajani Carter, T Dalton Cooper, S Jacobe Covington, WR Mac Dalena, T Chukwuebuka Godrick, G C.J. Hanson, CB Azizi Hearn, WR Jimmy Holiday, DT Coziah Izzard, LB Cam Jones, CB Kevin Knowles, C Joey Lombard, DT Fabien Lovett, DE Nate Matlack, S Glendon Miller, LB Xander Mueller, QB Chris Oladokun, T Esa Pole, WR Hal Presley, WR Key’Shawn Smith, CB Melvin Smith, TE Geor’Quarius Spivey, TE Tre Watson, RB Michael Wiley, and S Major Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8f6-db7b-a5dd-e8f698bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers released WR Rakim Jarrett.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e918-db7b-a5dd-e91c6c220000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers cleared up their wide receiver group with final cuts, waiving Rakim Jarrett after already waiving Trey Palmer. They also waived CB Tre Avery, DL Eric Banks, QB Connor Bazelak, DL C.J. Brewer, S Will Brooks, WR Garrett Greene, DL Mike Greene, G Luke Haggard, WR Dennis Houston, DL Nash Hutmacher, DL Dvon J-Thomas, LB Nick Jackson, RB Jase McClellan, T Tyler McLellan, T Lorenz Metz, OLB Warren Peeples, OLB Jose Ramirez, S Shilo Sanders, C Ben Scott, TE Tanner Taula, RB Owen Wright, CB JayVian Farr, LB Antonio Grier, C Jake Majors, T Raiqwon O’Neal and CB Roman Parodie. They released DL Adam Gotsis, CB Bryce Hall, WR Jacob Harris, G Michael Jordan, and G Sua Opeta. Terminated for non-football injury was LB Anthony Walker and waived for non-football illness was DL Desmond Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e918-db7b-a5dd-e91c6c220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens released RB Myles Gaskin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e92f-dbe3-a9bb-f97f92d50000</link>
      <description>Gaskin was brought in as a camp body by the Ravens, who have their running back room set. They now release him, along with CB Thomas Graham Jr., RB D’Ernest Johnson, WR Keith Kirkwood, WR Anthony Miller, and DL Brent Urban. They also waived WR Jahmal Banks, S Beau Brade, WR Malik Cunningham, G Darrian Dalcourt, OL Garrett Bellinger, OLB Malik Hamm, S Desmond Igbinosun, S Keondre Jackson, DL Jayson Jones, QB Devin Leary, T Gerad Lichtenhan, ILB Chandler Martin, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, DL Adedayo Odeleye, DL C.J. Okoye, G Jared Penning, DL C.J. Ravenell, CB Marquise Robinson, OLB Kaimon Rucker, C Nick Samac, FB Lucas Scott, and TE Scotty Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e92f-dbe3-a9bb-f97f92d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers released QB Taylor Heinicke.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e947-d332-a1fd-ff776d840000</link>
      <description>The Chargers had re-signed Heinicke this offseason, but choose to keep Trey Lance as the primary backup quarterback. The team also released CB Harrison Hand, S Tony Jefferson, LB Kana’i Mauga, RB Nyheim Miller-Hines, LB Del’Shawn Phillips, WR Jalen Reagor, and OT David Sharpe. They also waived G Karsen Barnhart, CB Trikweze Bridges, WR Dalevon Campbell, DL TeRah Edwards, WR Luke Grimm, LB Kylan Guidry, DL Christopher Hinton, WR JaQuae Jackson, LB Emany Johnson, G Nash Jone, C Josh Kaltenberge, TE Stevo Klotz, LB Tre’Mon Morris-Brash, OT Ryan Nelson, CB Myles Purchase, OLB Garmon Randolph, WR Brenden Rice, RB Raheim Sanders, CB Nehemiah Shelton, DL Nesta Jade Silvera, OT Corey Stewart, OG Branson Taylor, QB DJ Uiagalelei, RB Kimani Vidal and TE Thomas Yassmin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e947-d332-a1fd-ff776d840000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
