<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:01:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said he expects Jayden Reed (foot) to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a99-de13-afdd-5edb3c0d0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said he expects all 53 players on the roster to practice in some capacity. Reed was upgraded to a limited participant in Thursday’s practice and could have a realistic shot to play in Week 1 against the Lions. Even if Reed does play, he looks like a risky bet as far as fantasy is concerned. The third-year receiver is dealing with a fracture in his foot that he suffered less than a month ago, and with other players capable of filling his role, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Packers played him in a limited role if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a99-de13-afdd-5edb3c0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (hip) was seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1aa7-dbe3-a9bb-3af754c50000</link>
      <description>After being a surprise DNP on Thursday, Garrett was back on the field Friday which should put him on track to play in Week 1 against the Bengals. We’ll get a good sense of his availability when the team’s final injury report is released in the coming hours, but Garrett’s return to the field is an encouraging sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1aa7-dbe3-a9bb-3af754c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mekhi Becton (illness) has been added to the injury report and is questionable for the Chargers’ Week 1 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ab3-de13-afdd-5efba22a0000</link>
      <description>With the Chargers slated to play on Friday, Becton is a game-day addition to the injury report. While it’s not often that we see players miss games due to illness, the late addition for Becton is mildly concerning. The Chargers signed Becton to a two-year, $20 million contract this offseason after his stellar first season with the Eagles, and are hoping he’ll help bolster a rushing attack that ranked 24th in yards per carry last season. If he’s unable to play on Friday, fourth-year vet Jamaree Salyer would be the presumed starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ab3-de13-afdd-5efba22a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers listed LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) as doubtful for Week 1 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ac2-de13-afdd-5ecbfb6f0000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu was listed as a limited participant in Friday’s practice after sitting out the first two days. Despite this, the team has opted to list him as doubtful, which officially puts him on the wrong side of suiting up for Week 1 against the Jaguars. Ekwonu underwent an appendectomy on August 27th and was initially viewed as “day-to-day” by the team. Barring an unexpected change between now and Sunday, fifth-year vet Brady Christensen will likely draw the start against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ac2-de13-afdd-5ecbfb6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (elbow) is questionable for Week 1 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ad6-dbe3-a9bb-3ad70d160000</link>
      <description>DJ Giddens figures to be the No. 2 back for the Colts if Goodson can’t go. Neither player has any standalone Week 1 value with Jonathan Taylor healthy, but their passing-game involvement could make them interesting at some point in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ad6-dbe3-a9bb-3ad70d160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Damarri Mathis (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ada-dbe3-a9bb-3adbc0b10000</link>
      <description>Mathis had been claimed off waivers by the Panthers at last cuts, but unfortunately tore his ACL on his first day of practice with his new club. He’ll enter free agency this offseason and should compete for a roster spot somewhere as long as this is a relatively clean ACL tear. He was a depth piece for the Panthers so his loss shouldn’t change much about their cornerback rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ada-dbe3-a9bb-3adbc0b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Myles Garrett (hip) will play against the Bengals in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1adf-de13-afdd-5edfa2650000</link>
      <description>The Browns will need Garrett to hunt against the Bengals to have any chance of an upset win. Ultimately, he’s not on the final injury report. Garrett’s missed practice Thursday was surprising, but ultimately didn’t put his status in any real jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1adf-de13-afdd-5edfa2650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) will not play in Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ace-d332-a1fd-9efec8340000</link>
      <description>Things have been trending in this direction for a while. Gonzalez has been sidelined with a hamstring injury since late July and missed the first two days of practice to start the week. The Patriots have been holding off on predicting a return date for their star corner, but the fact that he avoided the injured reserve list to start the season suggested the team thinks he can return sometime during the first four weeks of the season. The team will now set its sights on a Week 2 return against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ace-d332-a1fd-9efec8340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L’Jarius Sneed (knee) is questionable for the Titans’ Week 1 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ae2-dbe3-a9bb-3af3f4670000</link>
      <description>Sneed was again out there on Friday, so he’s likely on the optimistic side of questionable. We’re not sure how much the Titans should expect from Sneed after all his time off, but they have to be hoping he can at least help contain Courtland Sutton and company on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ae2-dbe3-a9bb-3af3f4670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is questionable for Week 1 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1afc-d332-a1fd-9efe997d0000</link>
      <description>Mooney logged three limited practices this week, which is a good sign for his Week 1 availability despite the questionable designation. Fantasy managers in deeper leagues will still want to keep an eye out for his name popping up on the inactive list when they’re announced 90 minutes before kickoff, but Mooney has been practicing in some capacity for the last two weeks. If he’s unable to go against the Buccaneers, backup Casey Washington is listed as next in line on the team’s depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1afc-d332-a1fd-9efe997d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
