<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo caught 2-of-4 targets for 44 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843c-dca3-a9fb-bdbdf68a0000</link>
      <description>Both the targets and yards were new season highs for the rookie second-rounder, who also drew an end zone DPI and commanded another painted area target. Good stuff, though Arroyo is going to remain a zero-floor player as he fights for looks in this run-based offense. He has yet to demonstrate enough ceiling to be worth a TE2 look in 12-team re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843c-dca3-a9fb-bdbdf68a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 4-of-5 targets for 26 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843f-d6e9-af9d-8ebf46990000</link>
      <description>The four catches were Kupp’s second most in four games as a ‘Hawk, though he’s now been held below 32 yards in 3-of-4 contests. We have little doubt Kupp is doing the “little things” well for Seattle on the real-life gridiron, but it is abundantly clear he is not going to see enough targets to be a legitimate WR3 in fantasy, while even WR4 could prove to be a stretch. That theory will be put to the test for what could be a higher-octane game in Week 5 against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-843f-d6e9-af9d-8ebf46990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8441-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa32b0000</link>
      <description>Horton’s unconverted look was a deep target he probably should have caught at the goal line. The fifth-round rookie has now caught a pass in 3-of-4 contests, but he has just 10 total targets. Horton is a deep-shot role player who is unlikely to come into WR5 fantasy value this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8441-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa32b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 3-of-3 targets for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 4 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8444-d6e9-af9d-8ed40df60000</link>
      <description>The second-year pro now has a touchdown in 2-of-4 2025 appearances. Tonight’s was a 16-yard grab where he soundly beat Akeem Davis-Gaither 1-on-1. Good stuff, though rookie Elijah Arroyo was also more involved this evening. Barner is going to make some important real-life catches, but he seems unlikely to produce consistently enough to warrant a TE2 look in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8444-d6e9-af9d-8ed40df60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said Nick Bosa (knee) will undergo surgery to repair a torn ACL on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-85f1-d95b-addb-edf768b90000</link>
      <description>Bosa’s surgery will be performed by Dr. Neal ElAttrache, the same doctor who repaired his ACL during the 2020 season. The star pass-rusher’s season is over, but there’s hope that a “clean” tear will make for an easy procedure and recovery for the 27-year-old vet. Bosa’s 2020 ACL tear occurred in Week 2, and he was able to rehab in time to be ready for Week 1 of the following season. Hopefully, he can see a similar recovery timeline entering 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-85f1-d95b-addb-edf768b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) was not spotted at Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-867d-deb6-a7fd-d7ff7b870000</link>
      <description>The team will release its final injury report later in the day, but three-straight DNPs for McLaurin would make him a virtual lock to miss Week 4’s game against the Falcons. Fantasy managers still holding out hope for a positive turn of events here should have a backup plan in place, as McLaurin appears to be on the wrong side of playing this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-867d-deb6-a7fd-d7ff7b870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (biceps) was seen throwing during the early portion of Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8696-d95b-addb-eed6bb3c0000</link>
      <description>These aren’t the underhand throws Mayfield was seen making in Thursday’s practice, but rather normal-looking throws we’d expect to see a healthy quarterback making. Mayfield has been limited in practice throughout the week due to a biceps injury, but appears to be ramping things up just before the weekend. While he’s been limited, Mayfield has never felt like a player at risk of missing Week 4’s game against the Eagles, although we’ll have more clarity on that later in the day when the team releases its final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8696-d95b-addb-eed6bb3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) was not spotted at Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-869a-dca3-a9fb-bf9b0ecd0000</link>
      <description>It’s worth noting that this portion of the practice is open to the media. There’s still a chance that Daniels, who was limited in Wednesday and Thursday’s practices, could take the field later in the day. That said, it’s not a good sign for the QB1’s availability for Week 4 against the Falcons, as the team continues to be vague about his Week 4 availability. His status remains one to watch when the team releases its final injury report later in the day, but there’s a good chance we’ll be seeing Marcus Mariota under center for a second consecutive week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-869a-dca3-a9fb-bf9b0ecd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Ed Oliver (ankle) will not play in Week 4 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86a0-d95b-addb-eee66f680000</link>
      <description>The Bills will also be without LB Matt Milano, who will miss a second consecutive game with a pectoral injury. Oliver continues to work his way back from an ankle injury he suffered in Week 1, but the team’s decision not to place him on injured reserve suggests he could have a chance to return in Week 5. Oliver was a DNP all week, so any practice in a limited capacity would be an upgrade for him next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86a0-d95b-addb-eee66f680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LB Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) won’t play in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86b4-deb6-a7fd-d7ffd0ec0000</link>
      <description>Van Ginkel was a DNP all week. The veteran linebacker suffered a neck injury in Week 2 against the Bengals and will now miss a second-straight game with the injury. The Vikings also ruled out J.J. McCarthy (ankle) ahead of the weekend, but the second-year quarterback isn’t expected to return until close to Week 7, so this was always expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86b4-deb6-a7fd-d7ffd0ec0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
