<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:02:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot) upgraded to limited in Green Bay’s Tuesday estimated practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302c-db7b-a5dd-b02cddb60000</link>
      <description>A DNP on Monday looks to be managing the existing foot issue, which Reed played on in Week 1. We’d expect Reed and Dontayvon Wicks (calf — also limited, also played through it in Week 1) to be out there for Green Bay against the Commanders on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302c-db7b-a5dd-b02cddb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) was limited in Green Bay’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302e-db7b-a5dd-b02eec550000</link>
      <description>It was a walk-thru, so this is an estimation. Parsons will surely play a small package in Week 2 after his successful debut against the Lions in Week 1. It will likely be more of the same against Washington on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-302e-db7b-a5dd-b02eec550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers OL Zach Tom (oblique) and Aaron Banks (ankle/groin) did not participate in Green Bay’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3030-db7b-a5dd-b0349f810000</link>
      <description>Jordan Love was quoted earlier today as saying “we may have some guys out there who haven’t been out there” when asked about the offensive line, and it certainly appears to be trending that way on the injury report. Jordan Morgan would be a logical replacement for one of the spots. Darian Kinnard played right tackle in Tom’s absence in Week 1 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3030-db7b-a5dd-b0349f810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Austin Ekeler (shoulder) was limited in Washington’s Tuesday practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3036-d332-a1fd-b6368fff0000</link>
      <description>They conducted walkthroughs both days and the report is an estimation. Ekeler didn’t appear on the Week 1 report and did see noticeably fewer snaps in the second half against the Giants, so it is possible that it contributed to less Ekeler down the stretch. We’d still expect him to suit up for Week 2, perhaps with a role more similar to the one he had in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3036-d332-a1fd-b6368fff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Noah Brown (knee) remained limited in Washington’s practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3039-dbe3-a9bb-307b9cee0000</link>
      <description>He played through this designation last week, logging 33 snaps for the Commanders as their third receiver. He has some DFS solo slate appeal against the Packers, but otherwise probably isn’t involved enough to consider for standard fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3039-dbe3-a9bb-307b9cee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jauan Jennings (shoulder) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3035-db7b-a5dd-b03548720000</link>
      <description>Schefter’s source believes Jennings has a chance to play Sunday at New Orleans, which means he’ll be in line for a big share of the team’s workload with George Kittle down. How impressive that workload is probably depends on whether or not Brock Purdy (shoulder) actually plays this week. We’ll monitor the practice reports but the drumbeat is that Jennings should be considered in making projections for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3035-db7b-a5dd-b03548720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Giants LB Micah McFadden (foot) will undergo surgery and be out “significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3070-d332-a1fd-b676dd360000</link>
      <description>McFadden injured his foot in Week 1 and is “likely to return this season.” The post sending him to injured reserve is in the drafts already. The question is just how long it will be, and based on “significant,” we’re guessing this injury will require more than the minimum required four-week stay for McFadden. Darius Muasau played the most at linebacker in McFadden’s place. It’s a small boost for the Cowboys in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3070-d332-a1fd-b676dd360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed K Eddy Pineiro.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-307d-d332-a1fd-b67fca700000</link>
      <description>The fabled two-update day on Eddy Pineiro has come to pass. At some point this year he’ll probably be fantasy-interesting, though it might not be in Week 2 given how banged up the 49ers currently are.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-307d-d332-a1fd-b67fca700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter was fined $57,222 for spitting on Cowboys QB Dak Prescott Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-308d-d93a-abbb-79df9a050000</link>
      <description>Carter will forfeit his game check for Week 1 and won’t be suspended additional games for spitting on Dak Prescott in Thursday’s season opener. The NFL considered his ejection from Week 1 sufficient enough in terms of missed time, so the $57,222 game check forfeiture will be the only additional punishment on Carter. Head coach Nick Sirianni said any punishment or conversation from the Eagles will happen “in-house.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-308d-d93a-abbb-79df9a050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed WR Christian Watson to a one-year, $13.25 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-30d9-dbe3-a9bb-30dba1970000</link>
      <description>Watson’s contract was set to expire at the end of the 2025 season, but now the Packers extend the 26-year-old to keep him for an additional year. He is currently on the physically unable to perform list with a knee injury, so the extension gives Watson more room to recover without dealing with an impending free agency. Meanwhile, the Packers keep together a crowded wide receiver room that saw five different wide receivers catch a pass in Week 1. Watson will return to this group, though he won’t be high on the pecking order given he is returning from a torn ACL. He has dealt with several leg injuries throughout his young career, totaling 98 receptions for 1,653 yards and 14 touchdowns over 38 games in three seasons. Fantasy managers should not count on Watson for fantasy-relevant play upon his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-30d9-dbe3-a9bb-30dba1970000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
