<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 04:01:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brycen Tremayne caught 3-of-5 targets for 48 yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b44-dc44-a9d9-4f666fb40000</link>
      <description>Tremayne drew five targets on just 14 pass routes. His receptions included a 26-yard gain on a strong throw from Bryce Young in the second half. Tremayne, who spent time on the Commanders practice squad a couple seasons ago, was far more efficient and productive than Xavier Legette, who had -2 yards on eight targets against Arizona. Tremayne could be on his way to unseating Legette as Carolina’s WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b44-dc44-a9d9-4f666fb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleb Johnson had one rush for one yard in the Steelers’ Week 2 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b4b-d86f-abdd-4fff708e0000</link>
      <description>It was on special teams where Johnson committed a catastrophic error by touching a kickoff and letting the ball roll into the end zone, where Seahawks players fell on the football for a touchdown that essentially sealed the game for Seattle. Already in the dog house for pass protection issues in the summer, Johnson’s kickoff return error could banish him to special teams for his entire rookie campaign. Kenneth Gainwell would be the Steelers’ No. 1 back if Jaylen Warren were to miss time in 2025. There are exceedingly few scenarios in which Johnson gets a crack at weekly usage in the Pittsburgh rushing attack. The rookie has a lot of trust to earn in the coming weeks and months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b4b-d86f-abdd-4fff708e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Penix completed 13-of-21 passes for 135 yards in the Falcons’ 22-6, Week 2 win over the Vikings, losing one yard on a kneel down.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b48-d86f-abdd-4ffd10440000</link>
      <description>Penix and the Falcons traded field goals with the Vikings in the first half, eventually taking a 9-6 lead into the break. They would tack on field goals in the third and fourth quarters before the only touchdown of the game with just over three minutes remaining. The Falcons controlled the line of scrimmage on both sides of the ball, largely reliant on Bijan Robinson to move the football throughout. The lack of offense from a static Minnesota offense pried only 21 pass attempts from Penix as the Falcons game managed their way to victory. The team reaches 1-1 ahead of a road matchup with the reeling Panthers in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b48-d86f-abdd-4ffd10440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 22 times for 143 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings, adding 25 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b67-dc44-a9d9-4f6791700000</link>
      <description>The only true blemish on an otherwise sparkling performance from the electric fourth-year back was a drop in the second quarter. Robinson kick started the Atlanta offense with runs of 25 yards and 17 yards on the first two plays of the game, eclipsing his rushing yard total from Week 1 in under a minute while setting the tone of smash mouth football from the jump. Fantasy managers are sure to be pleased with the box score even though backfield mate Tyler Allgeier was handed 16 carries of his own and scored the lone touchdown for either team late in the fourth quarter. Robinson heads into a Week 3 matchup with the hapless Panthers as the potential overall RB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b67-dc44-a9d9-4f6791700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed 16 times for 76 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b6c-dc44-a9d9-4f6ea5350000</link>
      <description>The Falcons were able to control the flow of the game throughout, something that allowed the team to bully their way to a win behind 39 combined rush attempts versus just 21 pass attempts. The increased backfield usage propelled Allgeier to 16 carries behind the 22 of lead back Bijan Robinson, although it was Allgeier that found paint late in the fourth quarter for the only touchdown of the game. Allgeier won’t carry weekly fantasy value outside of games that play out similarly to this one, but managers that need help with looming bye weeks could do worse than stashing Allgeier to start in potential positive game environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b6c-dc44-a9d9-4f6ea5350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 3-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b70-d294-a19b-eff0a8560000</link>
      <description>London tied for third on the team in targets with Darnell Mooney, behind the five targets of Kyle Pitts and Bijan Robinson. The low target totals were a product of only 21 Michael Penix pass attempts in a game the Falcons were able to control on the ground throughout. London’s first quarter fumble came in a 6-0 game and allowed the Vikings to pull within three points with a field goal of their own. The two teams traded field goals to end the second quarter but the Falcons would bully their way to a victory via 39 combined rush attempts, limiting the upside of all Atlanta pass-catchers in the process. A similar game environment could develop in Week 3 when the Falcons travel to Carolina to face the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b70-d294-a19b-eff0a8560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 4-of-5 targets for 37 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b76-d294-a19b-eff693010000</link>
      <description>Pitts tied for the team lead in targets, something that doesn’t bring fantasy managers any comfort due to the low pass volume of an Atlanta offense that bullied their way to a victory behind 39 rush attempts. The early-season returns from Pitts are encouraging following three consecutive mundane seasons after a breakout rookie campaign, and he should be more involved in games the Falcons don’t control so handily via their run game. That said, fantasy managers might want to consider other options at the tight end position ahead of a Week 3 matchup with the reeling Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b76-d294-a19b-eff693010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 2-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Falcons’ Week 2 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7b-d294-a19b-effbf3d00000</link>
      <description>Mooney’s four targets tied for third on the team with Drake London and were one behind co-leaders Kyle Pitts and Bijan Robinson. Fantasy managers of any Atlanta pass-catcher were left wondering where the volume was on a night Bijan Robinson and Tyler Allgeier combined to see 38 carries, a script that could play out again in Week 3 when the Falcons face the Panthers in Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7b-d294-a19b-effbf3d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy completed 11-of-21 passes for 158 yards and two interceptions in the Vikings’ 22-6, Week 2 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7e-d294-a19b-effeaee80000</link>
      <description>McCarthy and the Vikings were unable to replicate their fourth quarter magic from Week 1 after struggling to move the football for three quarters, managing just six points before the break and being held off the scoreboard entirely in the final two frames. The second-year effective rookie also put the ball on the ground three times, losing one fumble, as the Vikings gained just 198 total yards of offense on a modest 23:28 time of possession. The early-season returns are less than adequate to sustain viable fantasy production for managers that invested in Kevin O’Connell’s offense, something the team will look to correct ahead of a Week 3 meeting with a Bengals team without quarterback Joe Burrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b7e-d294-a19b-effeaee80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed nine times for 33 yards in the Vikings’ Week 2 loss to the Falcons, adding eight yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b84-d86f-abdd-4fbd5ca60000</link>
      <description>The Vikings were held to just 46 offensive plays in a game the Falcons controlled throughout via an imposing run game, yielding just 12 opportunities for Mason. His 3.3 yards per carry were indicative of the team’s struggles to move the football as their offensive line clearly showed the wear of missing two starters. Fellow running back Aaron Jones departed in the second half with a hamstring injury, something that could propel Mason to a featured role ahead of a Week 3 meeting with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b84-d86f-abdd-4fbd5ca60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
