<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 20:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said he expects QB Kenny Pickett to be ready for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd00-dbe3-a9bb-fd53c2520000</link>
      <description>Stefanski also added that he is still working through who will back up Joe Flacco to start the season, potentially opening the door for one of the rookies to serve as the team’s top backup for Week 1. Pickett was originally in the running for the starting role for the Browns but an ill timed hamstring injury derailed those plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd00-dbe3-a9bb-fd53c2520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings released QB Brett Rypien.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd1d-de13-afdc-dfdf94140000</link>
      <description>That means the Vikings are moving forward with J.J. McCarthy, recent signee Carson Wentz, and undrafted free agent rookie Max Brosmer for the 2025 season. Rypien remains highly regarded for his veteran status, something that could lead to another opportunity elsewhere in short order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd1d-de13-afdc-dfdf94140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams (head) returned to practice for the Patriots on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd78-dbe3-a9bb-fd7bab190000</link>
      <description>Williams, 22, took a hard hit to the head during the Week 3 preseason tilt against the Patriots. The third-round pick is expected to have a significant role in the Patriots’ offense in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd78-dbe3-a9bb-fd7bab190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanner McKee suffered a fractured right thumb during the Eagles’ Week 3 preseason game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7c-d332-a1fd-df7e34e20000</link>
      <description>The fact that the Eagles traded for Sam Howell on Sunday is probably not coincidental. McKee’s status for Week 1 of the season is up in the air now due to the thumb injury. If McKee can’t go, Howell will all but certainly be the backup for that game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7c-d332-a1fd-df7e34e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released QB Tyler Huntley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd89-db7b-a5dd-fd8dc9bc0000</link>
      <description>The Browns certainly weren’t going to keep five quarterbacks, and Huntley was only in camp because of their plethora of injuries at the position. He’ll likely be a practice squad player for a new team in the coming days. The Browns also released S Nik Needham.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd89-db7b-a5dd-fd8dc9bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams waived QB Dresser Winn.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd78-de13-afdc-dffbb0d70000</link>
      <description>The Rams let go of Winn, along with 10 others, as they work their way toward the final 53-player roster. Waived alongside Winn are TE McCallan Castles, S Malik Dixon-Williams, OL Ben Dooley, DL Decarius Hawthorne, OG John Leglue, C Mike McAllister, OLB Josh Pearcy, DL Da’Jon Terry. The Rams released OG John Leglue and LB Tony Fields II.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd78-de13-afdc-dffbb0d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Carroll told reporters Sunday that the Raiders are in the market for a backup quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd90-dbe3-a9bb-fdd369c30000</link>
      <description>No surprise, as the raiders will be without QB Aidan O’Connell for up to eight weeks with his fractured wrist. One name that has been floated as a potential replacement is Ryan Tannehill, and even with the 37-year-old sitting out the 2024 season, it would make sense to acquire a player with his experience/relative success rather than roll with Cam Miller as the backup for Geno Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd90-dbe3-a9bb-fdd369c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings waived WR Silas Bolden.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd97-de13-afdc-dfdf40d50000</link>
      <description>Even with the Vikings in need of receiving bodies, Bolden didn’t do enough in camp to justify a roster spot. The Vikings also waived CB Reddy Steward, CB Keenan Garber, RB Tre Stewart, S Mishael Powell, T Logan Brown, OL Zach Bailey, WR Robert Lewis and DL Travis Bell to go along with the previously announced releases of QB Brett Rypien and OLB Cam Gill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd97-de13-afdc-dfdf40d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released DB Tre Herndon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7b-d332-a1fd-df7f7ee70000</link>
      <description>Herndon took preseason snaps with both the Bills and Colts this month. He spent the 2018-2023 seasons with the Jaguars, after signing on with them as an undrafted free agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7b-d332-a1fd-df7f7ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns waived TE Sal Cannella.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</link>
      <description>Cannella thrived in the UFL over the last two seasons, but didn’t produce enough in the preseason to justify a roster spot; at least to the Browns. Along with Cannella, Cleveland also waived CB Chigozie Anusiem, G Javion Cohen, T Sebastian Gutierrez, DE K.J. Henry, DT Ralph Holley, CB Christian Holmes, CB Keenan Isaac, T Jason Ivey, DE Titus Le, LB Marvin Moody, CB Darius Rush, LB Charlie Thomas III, T Lorenzo Thompson, G Dartanyan Tinsley, TE Mitchell Van Vooren and C Bucky Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
