<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 23:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers GM Omar Khan said he’s spoken with Kenneth Gainwell’s agent and “he knows we want him back.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916c-d89c-a1be-bfff938e0000</link>
      <description>Gainwell doesn’t seem to be a major free-agent priority signing for anybody, but figures to do quite well for himself after putting up 73/486 through the air and amassing 1,000 yards from scrimmage. He figures to be a potential third-down back upgrade for several teams in free agency, though the Steelers remain a great fit for him as he slotted in well behind Jaylen Warren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916c-d89c-a1be-bfff938e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports LT Trent Williams and the 49ers are “struggling to find a contractual solution” and Williams could be released.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916f-d042-afbc-fdff04230000</link>
      <description>Williams is entering the final year of a three-year, $82.66 million contract with the 49ers and is carrying a $38.8 million cap figure for this season. Releasing him would only save about $5 million in cap space unless it was done with a post-June 1 designation. The 49ers also already have plenty of cap space, so it feels more like a separation for the sake of getting out of the Williams business as he enters his age-38 season. Williams played as well as ever last year — he had a 91.1 PFF grade despite a slow start in Seattle while injured at the start of the season. He has definitely seemed more injury-prone of late. Several teams should probably be interested in Williams’ services if he hits the free-agent market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-916f-d042-afbc-fdff04230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons franchise-tagged TE Kyle Pitts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-917b-d042-afbc-fdfbe7a50000</link>
      <description>That’s a one-year, $16.3 million contract for Pitts assuming he does not sign an extension off the tag. There have been worse fates. It’s fair to wonder if the Falcons will emphasize Pitts earlier in the pecking order as he carried a very high aDOT (7.2) for a player who garnered over 100 targets last season. Kevin Stefanski had Harold Fannin down at 5.9 in a screen-heavy attack in Cleveland last year. It’s possible Pitts could be a post-post-post-post-hype sleeper this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-917b-d042-afbc-fdfbe7a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker posted on Instagram that he will return for the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9189-d629-a1bc-b19da0550000</link>
      <description>He had contemplated retirement after seemingly spending the entire year on the injury report with a shoulder injury. It’s a big keep for the Lions, who appeared to have no real pathway to another stalwart left tackle from the outside. Decker’s return should solidify some of the offseason questions and direction for the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9189-d629-a1bc-b19da0550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said OC Davis Webb will call plays for the Broncos in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91ac-d629-a1bc-b1bd6c360000</link>
      <description>It was rumored to be the case, and inadvertently brought to light by Bills GM Brandon Beane earlier today, but now it is an official known fact. The 31-year-old former quarterback will call plays for the Broncos this season. Per James Palmer, Webb called plays in a preseason game last season and players were “blown away” by Webb. We’re not sure exactly how much this changes the calculus in Denver, but you’d better believe we’ll be hoping to read more about it from the beat writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91ac-d629-a1bc-b1bd6c360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLLS’ Clarence Hill reports the Cowboys have an offer on the table to Brandon Aubrey that would make him the league’s highest-paid kicker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91b7-d89c-a1be-bfffe6bf0000</link>
      <description>And it’s still not enough, as Hill writes that Aubrey “wants more than they offered.” That is how contract talks be sometimes. The Cowboys have the right to tender Aubrey a deal as a restricted free agent and seem to be in no real danger of losing the kicker, but they’ve been trying to get him extended for a solid calendar year and still don’t seem to have the right number to do it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91b7-d89c-a1be-bfffe6bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts GM Chris Ballard said “any suggestion that” Michael Pittman isn’t going to remain a Colt is “a pure hypothetical in my mind.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91bb-d57c-a1dd-95bb5fa40000</link>
      <description>Ballard would almost certainly have to restructure Pittman’s contract to retain both Daniel Jones and Alec Pierce. Entering his age-29 season, there was some beat writer smoke around the Colts parting ways with Pittman — it does seem like Ballard would rather hang on to him than not. If the Colts run back last year’s receiver room, Pittman will likely be on the WR3 line in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91bb-d57c-a1dd-95bb5fa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs GM Brett Veach said he’d like to have CB Trent McDuffie “back for the long-term.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c0-d89c-a1be-bfdf82be0000</link>
      <description>McDuffie is entering the fifth-year option season on his rookie contract and the Chiefs could chop down his cap number for 2026 with an extension. Forced to play outside more over the past few years, McDuffie finally managed to be left off an All-Pro team in 2025. He managed a 75.6 PFF grade — as opposed to 82.0 and 84.8 the two seasons before that — in 688 snaps with the Chiefs while dealing with a knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c0-d89c-a1be-bfdf82be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports Kyler Murray and Cardinals GM Monti Ossenfort have not talked since the season ended.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c6-d629-a1bc-b1df461c0000</link>
      <description>Well, not much to talk about, is there? The Cardinals projected some “all options are on the table” stuff at Ossenfort’s presser ahead of questions, trying to pre-empt them. It seems more likely than not that the Cardinals will release Murray before his contract guarantees kick in. All that’s left is trying to bait a team in to trading for him before that happens. The fact that the two sides haven’t even talked says a lot about the odds of Arizona actually retaining Murray, making it appear that there is one less option on the theoretical table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c6-d629-a1bc-b1df461c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said he thinks the 49ers are “on the right track” in contract talks with LT Trent Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91cd-d57c-a1dd-95cd10a30000</link>
      <description>It’s certainly a vibes shift from Adam Schefter’s report that the two sides were struggling to find a contractual solution. Williams’ contract is indeed very tricky, tricky enough that moving on from it doesn’t really free up significant space for the 49ers. We’d be surprised if the 49ers moved on from Williams despite Schefter’s report, but it certainly isn’t completely off the table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91cd-d57c-a1dd-95cd10a30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
