<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart completed 15-of-33 attempts for 283 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos, adding five rushes for 11 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff49-d651-a9df-ff5debd30000</link>
      <description>Dart was patient with his throws and delivered a handful of accurate downfield shots against an elite Broncos secondary. Two of his touchdowns went to New York tight ends; the other went to Cam Skattebo on a well-designed screen play in the red zone. Dart scored his rushing touchdown on a one-yard dive after an end zone pass interference in the final minute of the game. Dart mostly avoided the massive hits he’s taken in recent weeks, picking his spots to take off and run. He targeted Wan’Dale Robinson relentlessly, as he dd in Week 6 against the Eagles. Dart’s rushing upside will make him a weekly top-12 fantasy play going forward. He’ll play the Eagles once again in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff49-d651-a9df-ff5debd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 3-of-10 targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff4f-da18-a39b-ff5ffd260000</link>
      <description>Franklin, as usual, ran a bunch of empty routes as the de facto WR2 in the Broncos offense. His touchdown came on a fluky tip that ended up in Franklin’s hands near the back of the end zone — one of Bo Nix’s two passing scores on the day. Franklin hasn’t had more than 55 receiving yards in a game since Week 2, and mostly profiles as a deep league fantasy option in the balanced Denver offense. He’ll face the Cowboys in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff4f-da18-a39b-ff5ffd260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Skattebo had 16 rushes for 60 yards in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos, adding three catches for 34 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff77-d99b-a1dd-ff7fad5e0000</link>
      <description>The tough Broncos front seven held Skattebo in check on the ground, often stopping the big back at or behind the line of scrimmage. His biggest play of the day came on a red zone screen pass that ended with a signature touchdown in which the rookie barreled through two would-be tacklers. Skattebo now has four touchdowns over his past two outings and at least 15 carries in four straight games. Tyrone Tracy logged nine carries against the Broncos and broke off a 31-yard touchdown, totaling 46 yards on the ground. Skattebo will be a top-12 PPR option in Week 8 against a struggling Eagles rush defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff77-d99b-a1dd-ff7fad5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Bellinger caught 3-of-4 targets for 88 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff81-df81-ab9b-ffc777010000</link>
      <description>Jaxson Dart found Bellinger wide open in the first quarter for a 44-yard score. Bellinger nearly caught a second touchdown later in the first half. He ran 21 routes while TE Theo Johnson ran 36 routes and caught three balls for 66 yards and a score. Bellinger, who has just seven catches all season headed into Week 7, won’t be a reliable fantasy play unless he starts running more routes in the run-first New York offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff81-df81-ab9b-ffc777010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy had nine rushes for 46 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff85-d651-a9df-ff9507c20000</link>
      <description>Most of Tracy’s production came on an out-of-nowhere 31-yard score in the second half. Cam Skattebo, meanwhile, had 16 rushes for 60 yards and scored on one of his three receptions. For now Tracy profiles as a contingency option who would be a top-20 weekly play if Skattebo were to miss time with injury. He can be stashed on fantasy benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff85-d651-a9df-ff9507c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 6-of-7 targets for 85 yards in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants, adding one rush for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff87-da18-a39b-ff97ef430000</link>
      <description>Mims’ spotty usage in the Denver offense has made him a frustrating fantasy play, as Troy Franklin continues running more pass routes and functioning as the (unproductive) WR2 behind Courtland Sutton. Sunday marked only the second time this season Mims has had more than three receptions in a game. Mostly used as a gadget player, Mims will be an interesting flex option in deep leagues next week against Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff87-da18-a39b-ff97ef430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 6-of-10 targets for 87 yards in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff8b-df81-ab9b-ffcf5ab10000</link>
      <description>Sutton was once again Bo Nix’s go-to guy in high-leverage situations, including in the game’s final drive, when Nix hit Sutton for a long gain to put the Broncos in field goal position. Sunday marked a nice bounce back game for Sutton after his one-catch performance in Week 7 against the Jets. Dominating air yards in the Broncos offense, Sutton will profile as an elite fantasy play next week against a Dallas secondary that has struggled throughout the season. He has at least 80 yards in three of his past four outings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff8b-df81-ab9b-ffcf5ab10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Drew Rosenhaus said Dolphins TE Darren Waller will undergo an MRI on Monday after suffering a “pec strain” in Week 7 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff89-d651-a9df-ff9d91de0000</link>
      <description>Rosenhaus adds that if the pectoral muscle is torn, “it could be a season-ending injury.” Agents often take an optimistic approach to injuries, so his reported outlining of the worst-case scenario is not reassuring. Any outcome is possible at this point, though, so fantasy managers should not resort to panic. If active next week, the 33-year-old tight end will be on the TE1 radar once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff89-d651-a9df-ff9d91de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey had four rushes for zero yards in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants, adding one catch for two yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff92-d651-a9df-ff9735fb0000</link>
      <description>Harvey once again played second fiddle to JK Dobbins, who logged 14 rushing attempts for 81 yards. His touchdown came on a flare-out route inside the five yard line — one of Bo Nix’s two passing scores on the day. The rookie has just ten rushing attempts over his past three games. Harvey is mostly a contingency option for now. He would be an intriguing fantasy option if Dobbins were to miss time in the second half of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff92-d651-a9df-ff9735fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil’Jordan Humphrey did not catch either of his targets in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff96-d99b-a1dd-ff9ec3650000</link>
      <description>Humphrey played something close to a full-time role with Darius Slayton sidelined with a lingering hamstring injury. Last week against the Eagles, Humphrey went for 55 yards on four catches. He’ll face the Eagles again in Week 8, but would only be fantasy viable if Slayton is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff96-d99b-a1dd-ff9ec3650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
