<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested permission to interview Eagles Assistant GM Alec Halaby for their GM vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff2-dc7a-af9b-cfff8ba40000</link>
      <description>They also requested permission to talk to Packers vice president of player personnel Jon-Eric Sullivan, 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams, 49ers vice president of player personnel Tariq Ahmad, and Rams assistant GM John McKay. The fact that there are two 49ers-linked candidates on that list is probably good news for Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel on Black Monday. Halaby had interview requests from the Panthers and Jets the past two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff2-dc7a-af9b-cfff8ba40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed WR Mitchell Tinsley to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff9-d56e-afff-eff91a850000</link>
      <description>He was an exclusive rights free agent. Tinsley pushed former third-rounder Jermaine Burton out of Joe Burrow’s circle of trust in the preseason and managed an 8/116/2 seasonal receiving line, with 15 of those targets coming against the Ravens and Patriots as Tee Higgins was out. Tinsley isn’t exactly a fantasy football sleeper, but Burrow’s rapport with him does make him interesting as a contingency plan. The Bengals also signed these 18 other players to ERFA one-year deals or futures contracts: LB Liam Anderson, C Jacob Bayer, HB Gary Brightwell, QB Sean Clifford, OT Andrew Coker, DT Howard Cross, OT Javon Foster, WR Xavier Johnson, CB Jalen Kimber, CB Bralyn Lux, WR Jordan Moore, LB Antwaun Powell-Ryland, S Russ Yeast, DE Isaiah Foskey, LB Joe Giles-Harris, LB Shaka Heyward, TE Cam Grandy, and S PJ Jules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ff9-d56e-afff-eff91a850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Kevin Stefanski is expected to speak with the Titans, Falcons, and Giants about their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9001-dc7a-af9b-dfbf3a690000</link>
      <description>The Stefanski-Giants connection is one of the most poorly-kept secrets of the last two months of the regular season. It is altogether unsurprising that a coach with his resume would fill up a dance card, even if it is a little surprising at how quickly it appears to have happened. With a relative dearth of offensive-minded head coach candidates making the rounds this year, Stefanski will likely be one of the belles of the ball this silly season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9001-dc7a-af9b-dfbf3a690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said he thinks “there will be competition for our starting quarterback. Who that is and what that looks like remains to be seen.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9008-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd9b90000</link>
      <description>McDaniel, who also added that his understanding is that he is the Dolphins head coach until he is told otherwise, seems to believe there are options both inside and outside of the building that the Dolphins could turn to in 2026. The Dolphins finished out the year letting Quinn Ewers have the reins with Tua Tagovailoa a healthy scratch. Zach Wilson also received some run in Week 18 against the Patriots, though Wilson is an impending free agent. Without much in the way of cap space, the Dolphins might have to get creative at quarterback in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9008-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd9b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX’s Peter Schrager reports the Titans will interview former Falcons HC Raheem Morris for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-900d-d56e-afff-f6ed51d10000</link>
      <description>The Titans have already been linked to six head coaches and we’re not even out of Black Monday yet. Morris was a respectable 16-18 in two years in Atlanta, even if a significant number of those wins came after the Falcons were mathematically eliminated from the playoffs this past month. He had improved the Falcons defense by leaps and bounds in his second year — though it required quite a lot of draft capital to get there. The Titans are clearly casting a wide net in their head-coaching search.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-900d-d56e-afff-f6ed51d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed WR Xavier Restrepo to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9012-dc7a-af9b-dfbf345f0000</link>
      <description>Restrepo had finally gotten elevated just before Thanksgiving before an ankle injury knocked him out for the season. He finished with three catches for 41 yards in two games. The Titans also signed DE David Ebuka Agoha, DB Keydrain Calligan, DT Timmy Horne, LB Nate Lynn, WR Hal Presley III, NT Isaiah Raikes, LB Cam Riley, RB Blake Watson, G Clay Webb and TE Joel Wilson to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9012-dc7a-af9b-dfbf345f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed WR Chris Blair, P Trenton Gill, DB Tysheem Johnson, DT Ben Stille, OT Andrew Stueber, RB Carlos Washington and DB A.J. Woods to reserve/future deals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</link>
      <description>Blair, mostly a special teamer, has played eight games and 48 offensive snaps for the Falcons over the past three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9017-d56e-afff-f6ff08760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Phillip Dorsett to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</link>
      <description>We don’t know how much future there is to reserve for the 33-year-old (happy birthday!), but the Raiders are here for it. The Raiders also signed RB Chris Collier, G McClendon Curtis, LB Jamin Davis, DT Treven Ma’ae, T Joshua Miles, TE Albert Okwuegbunam (remember him?), WR Brenden Rice, G Layden Robinson, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, and T Dalton Wagner to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9019-d56e-afff-f6f9c0830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed TE Sal Cannella, G Jack Conley, WR Luke Floriea, RB Ahmani Marshall, T Tyre Phillips and TE Caden Prieskorn to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</link>
      <description>Cannella had a four-target game against the Steelers in Week 17 after Harold Fannin left early due to a groin injury, catching two balls for 11 yards. The 29-year-old UFL star is merely a depth piece.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9020-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdd230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed WR Malik Cunningham to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</link>
      <description>The former Louisville quarterback made his first career appearance in an NFL game in 2025. He ran the ball against the Cowboys in Week 14 one time and gained one yard. OL Devin Cochran, DE Ahmed Hassanein, TE Zach Horton, WR Jackson Meeks, OL Mason Miller (not the Padres reliever), RB Jabari Small, DL Chris Smith and S Loren Strickland were also all signed to reserve/future deals by the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9024-dc7a-af9b-dfbfe5a80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
