<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired Matt Ryan as President of Football.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a84d-d35e-a1bf-edcfcb010000</link>
      <description>Ryan spent 14 of his 15 years in the NFL as a player with the Falcons, winning the MVP in 2016 and making four Pro Bowls. He signed a one-day contract to retire with the organization and was inducted into the Falcons’ ring of honor in 2024. Ryan is putting his reputation on the line in taking a job many believe was created specifically for him as the Falcons’ President of Football. He’s been granted full control with final say over all football decisions, including leading the search for the team’s next head coach and general manager. Ryan will pause his broadcasting career at CBS while he takes over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a84d-d35e-a1bf-edcfcb010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers are expected to pick up QB Bryce Young’s fifth-year option this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a87a-d56e-afff-eefa9d500000</link>
      <description>Young improved a lot in his third year after a rough first two seasons with the Panthers. The 24-year-old quarterback led Carolina to eight wins, a division championship and the playoffs. Young orchestrated four fourth quarter comebacks and six game-winning drives. He threw for over 20 touchdowns for the first time without increasing his interceptions and lowered his sack percentage. Young led the league in deep ball accuracy with a catchable percentage of 75 percent on passes that traveled at least 20 yards in the air. While Young still has work to do to be a top-15 fantasy quarterback, the Panthers are committed to him for at least the next two years now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a87a-d56e-afff-eefa9d500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested permission to interview 49ers DC Robert Saleh for the head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a912-d35e-a1bf-edd26dc90000</link>
      <description>It’s the fifth interview request for the former Jets head coach as the 2026 coaching carousel continues trudging on. Saleh has also drawn interest from the Cardinals, Ravens, Falcons, and Titans after interviewing with the Cowboys and Jaguars ahead of the 2025 season. The veteran defensive mastermind coach could be on the move once more this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a912-d35e-a1bf-edd26dc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed WR Joshua Palmer (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a918-d968-a19b-f9f9213c0000</link>
      <description>Palmer failed to practice all week before initially drawing the questionable tag, eventually ruled out on Saturday for the team’s Wildcard Round game against the Jaguars. He was then placed on injured reserve, ending his season. Keon Coleman is expected to be active due to the absence for a team in desperate need of play makers behind quarterback Josh Allen and running back James Cook. The team elevated DE Andre Davis and RB Frank Gore Jr. in an associated move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a918-d968-a19b-f9f9213c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for the head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a91f-d968-a19b-f9ff310e0000</link>
      <description>Shula, the grandson of legendary Dolphins coach Don Shula, will have a chance to bring the family full circle in Miami after his Rams ranked 17th in total defense and 10th in points allowed per game in his second season in Los Angeles. The 39-year-old defensive coach has coached with the Rams under head coach Sean McVay since 2017 after coming up at the collegiate level. He would be amongst the five youngest head coaches in the NFL should he land a head-coaching gig this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a91f-d968-a19b-f9ff310e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared TE Terrance Ferguson, OL Kevin Dotson, CB Josh Wallace, CB Derion Kendrick, CB Darious Williams, and WR Jordan Whittington inactive for the Wildcard Round against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a926-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2700000</link>
      <description>Ferguson came into the weekend listed as questionable and will ultimately be held out for the team’s Wildcard Round game against the Panthers. The Rams come into the contest listed as 10-point favorites on the road after losing to the Panthers in Carolina earlier in the season. Wide receivers Konata Mumpfield, Xavier Smith, and Tutu Atwell get the nod over Whittington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a926-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared LB Krys Barnes, C Nick Samac, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, WR David Moore, and DE LaBryan Ray inactive for the Wildcard Round against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a993-d968-a19b-f9f357470000</link>
      <description>No real surprises from one of the healthier teams entering the postseason as the Panthers attempt to knock off the Rams at home as 10-point underdogs. It is the franchise’s first home playoff game since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a993-d968-a19b-f9f357470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) for the Wildcard Round against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a998-d35e-a1bf-edda40cb0000</link>
      <description>Jordan injured his ankle in Week 18 and failed to practice all week, eventually ruled out with the ailment. That leaves very little depth behind starting rookie Woody Marks, who could find himself in a workhorse role for the team’s Wildcard matchup against the Steelers. Nick Chubb appears likely to operate as the primary change of pace option while Dare Ogunbowale could rotate in on obvious passing situations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a998-d35e-a1bf-edda40cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated ILB Drew Sanders (foot) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9a0-d35e-a1bf-ede20b480000</link>
      <description>The No. 1 seeded Broncos get the luxury of an additional week of preparation as they await their Division Round opponent, giving Sanders a legitimate chance to return for the team’s first postseason game. The third-year linebacker spent the entirety of the 2025 regular season on injured reserve after complications from a torn Achilles suffered in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9a0-d35e-a1bf-ede20b480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9bd-dc7a-af9b-efbf0c2a0000</link>
      <description>Gordon made only three appearances for the Bears during the regular season but gives a struggling secondary a tangible boost as they prepare to host the Packers Saturday evening. The two teams split the season series but meet in the Wildcard Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9bd-dc7a-af9b-efbf0c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
