<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 23:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 15-of-21 passes for 136 yards and one interception, adding three rushes for 12 yards and one fumble lost, before being benched in Week 8 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2285-d245-adfb-b7dfadf50000</link>
      <description>Rattler was also sacked three times for 19 yards, which was the running theme for the former starter in this one. The Buccaneers’ pass rush haunted Rattler from the jump, keyed by a standout showing from fill-in starter, OLB Anthony Nelson. On the opening drive, Rattler was hit low, on a scramble, before Nelson jumped onto his back and punched the ball out with an arching hammer fist strike, which Buccaneers defenders successfully recovered. The Saints began their third drive from their own one-yard line. On the second play, Rattler threw a poorly aimed pass at TE Payne Durham, which Nelson successfully batted and caught, before waltzing into the end zone for a pick-six. Rattler’s time as the Saints’ 2025 starter appears to be over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2285-d245-adfb-b7dfadf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley had three rushes for two yards in the Eagles’ Week 8 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2290-dab4-a3fb-bbf064000000</link>
      <description>Shipley played behind Tank Bigsby after Saquon Barkley left the game with a groin injury. Bigsby ran for 104 yards on nine rushing attempts, most of that production coming in the fourth quarter. Perhaps Shipley can be rostered in some deeper leagues but it would appear Bigsby will be the team’s lead back if Barkley misses any time. The Eagles have a bye next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2290-dab4-a3fb-bbf064000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamari Thrash caught 2-of-3 targets for 31 yards in the Browns’ Week 8 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2290-dab4-a3fb-bbf0e23e0000</link>
      <description>Browns receivers caught a combined 2-of-9 targets against the Patriots, with Thrash bringing in both receptions. Though he was technically the leading wide receiver for the day, the Browns offense with Dillon Gabriel is not good enough to bring any fantasy relevance to any wide receivers. Malachi Corley added a carry for 31 yards, but neither Corley nor Thrash is worth starting. Thrash is only worth adding in the deepest of fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2290-dab4-a3fb-bbf0e23e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos CB Patrick Surtain (shoulder) left Denver’s Week 8 game against the Cowboys and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2297-deb1-a39b-239f12900000</link>
      <description>He didn’t come back to the field after halftime and was originally questionable to return before being downgraded. Surtain was mostly shadowing George Pickens for the first half. Per PFF, Surtain had allowed three catches on four targets for 21 yards while playing 35 of 38 snaps over the first 30 minutes of game time. Kris Abrams-Draine replaced Surtain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2297-deb1-a39b-239f12900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed four times for four yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 8 loss to the Dolphins, adding two catches for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2294-d245-adfb-b7df6e580000</link>
      <description>Allgeier never got the chance to get in a rhythm on the ground in a game Atlanta lost by 24. He did, however, handle some garbage time touches late in the game. Allgeier saw all three of the carries on Atlanta’s penultimate drive, finding the end zone on his last tote of the day. The Falcons will be underdogs on the road in New England next week. That doesn’t bode well for Allgeier’s fantasy outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2294-d245-adfb-b7df6e580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 1-of-4 targets for 11 yards in the Falcons’ Week 8 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-229a-dab4-a3fb-bbfa51360000</link>
      <description>Mooney failed to connect on multiple deep shots from Kirk Cousins in this game and wasn’t particularly involved on short or intermediate routes. He did manage to draw a long defensive pass interference call in the third quarter, which doesn’t show up in the box score. It’s possible Mooney hasn’t fully recovered from the hamstring issue he has been dealing with for a few weeks. Either way, it will be hard to trust Mooney in Week 9 versus the Patriots, even if Drake London remains sidelined with his hip injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-229a-dab4-a3fb-bbfa51360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught all nine of his targets for 59 yards in the Falcons’ Week 8 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22a8-dab4-a3fb-bbf828f90000</link>
      <description>Pitts led the Falcons in all receiving categories with Drake London sidelined this week, though that says more about the state of Atlanta’s passing game than it does about Pitts. Still, a 29 percent target share for a tight end is an elite mark. Pitts operated as an intermediate target for Kirk Cousins in his first start of the year and Cousins had no issues locking on to his tight end. Pitts will sit on the TE1/2 border if London is back next week. If London remains out, Pitts sit comfortably inside the top 12 fantasy tight ends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22a8-dab4-a3fb-bbf828f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KhaDarel Hodge caught 3-of-8 targets for 31 yards in the Falcons’ Week 8 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ae-d5d8-a3ff-fbef5f0e0000</link>
      <description>Hodge was the primary beneficiary of Drake London’s injury-related absence this week. He led the team’s wideouts in targets and only trailed Kyle Pitts by one look. Hodge logged a 26 percent target share. If London misses another week because of his hip injury, Hodge could be in line for a strong target share against the Pats in Week 9. He would be a volume-based WR4 in that scenario, though London’s return would take him off the fantasy menu entirely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ae-d5d8-a3ff-fbef5f0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden is active for Sunday Night Football against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22b8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf91b9b0000</link>
      <description>Golden popped on the team’s injury report late in the week with a hip injury but will give it a go Sunday night against the Steelers. Also active are wide receiver Christian Watson and kicker Brandon McManus. Inactive for the Packers are WR Dontayvion Wicks, K Lucas Havrisik, OL Jacob Monk, OL Donovan Jennings, DL Lukas Van Ness, and DL Warren Brinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22b8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf91b9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Scotty Miller, G Andrus Peat, DT Logan Lee, and DE Demarvin Leal inactive for Week 8 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ba-d245-adfb-b7ff13e60000</link>
      <description>Miller injured his finger in Thursday’s practice and will be unable to go for Sunday Night Football. There aren’t any surprises beyond that for the Steelers, who host quarterback Aaron Rodgers’ former team in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22ba-d245-adfb-b7ff13e60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
