<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed K Zane Gonzalez, formerly of the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fa6-d673-a39e-efb748840000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez is set to be the Falcons’ third kicker of the 2025 season after the team parted ways with John Parker Romo following his Week 9 meltdown against the Patriots. Parker Romo had replaced Younghoe Koo as the team’s starter. Gonzalez last season with Washington made five of his seven field goal attempts and all 19 of his extra point tries. Over six NFL seasons, Gonzalez has converted 80 percent of his field goal attempts. He won’t have much fantasy appeal in Week 10 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fa6-d673-a39e-efb748840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars acquired WR Jakobi Meyers from the Raiders in exchange for fourth and sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fb7-d45b-affe-5fb7f1ab0000</link>
      <description>Meyers finally finds his way out of Vegas four months after requesting a trade to escape Chip Kelly’s offensive scheme. Meyers never gelled with Geno Smith and hardly saw an increase in usage during Brock Bowers’ extended injury absence. Meyers managed 32 catches for 352 yards and zero touchdowns over seven games with the Raiders this season. Jacksonville acquiring Meyers at the trade deadline could mean the team is anticipating a worst-case scenario for Brian Thomas, who suffered a serious ankle injury in Week 9 against the Raiders. The team is already without Travis Hunter, who last week was placed on IR with a knee injury. Meyers’ fantasy prospects likely get a boost in Jacksonville if Thomas is sidelined for a while. Meanwhile, Tre Tucker becomes the de facto WR1 in Vegas, though Bowers should continue dominating targets as he did in Week 9. The Raiders could see what they have in Jack Bech as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fb7-d45b-affe-5fb7f1ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jaguars WR Travis Hunter (knee, IR) “is not expected to be out long-term.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fc2-d1e7-a1fa-5feace420000</link>
      <description>This echoes The Athletic’s reporting that Hunter, who injured his knee last week during a practice session, avoided “long term damage” to his knee. Hunter will miss at least the next three weeks and possibly more if the Jaguars want to be careful with the No. 2 overall pick in the 2025 NFL Draft. The Jaguars could also be without Brian Thomas, who sustained an ankle injury during the team’s Week 9 win against the Raiders. Jacksonville on Tuesday acquired Jakobi Meyers from the Raiders. Meyers could immediately see significant playing time if Hunter and Thomas are sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fc2-d1e7-a1fa-5feace420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Ryan McFadden reports Raiders TE Michael Mayer could see an increased role after the team traded Jakobi Meyers to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fe7-d45b-affe-5ff73bf40000</link>
      <description>Mayer saw seven targets last week against the Jaguars, second on the team behind Brock Bowers (13). Mayer logged a pass route on 70 percent of the Raiders’ drop backs as the team used two tight end sets at one of the highest rates of Week 9. Meyers’ absence from the Vegas offense should make Mayer somewhat interesting in deeper fantasy leagues, especially if the Raiders are continually forced into pass-heavy game scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4fe7-d45b-affe-5ff73bf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts acquired CB Sauce Gardner from the New York Jets for AD Mitchell and two first-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ffe-d1e7-a1fa-5ffe4db40000</link>
      <description>Chris Ballard has paid the first-round pick freight for a defender before, when he added DeForest Buckner to the Colts ahead of the 2020 season. It’s a stunning repudiation of the Jets’ plan to have Gardner in their core, but then again they probably never pictured they would be able to get two first-round picks for him before signing him to a long-term extension. Indianapolis’ cornerback room has been in dire need of an upgrade like this on paper for a long time. The problem is that it’s mostly on paper at this point, as Gardner has posted back-to-back PFF coverage grades of 68.1 in 2025 and 73.1 in 2024, a far cry from his 2022 and 2023 seasons. He has not taken to Aaron Glenn’s aggressive system quite as well as expected, and perhaps not as well as the Jets expected either. So the Jets will take the rebuilding road here. For the Colts, even if Gardner isn’t who he was in his first two seasons, he’s a massive upgrade as they attempt to hold on to the AFC South and prime playoff seeding. Their starting cornerbacks last week were Jaylon Jones and Mekhi Blackmon, and once Charvarius Ward is healthy they could throw out Ward, Gardner, and Kenny Moore come playoff time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ffe-d1e7-a1fa-5ffe4db40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired WR AD Mitchell from the Colts, along with two first-round picks, for CB Sauce Gardner.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5007-d713-ad9e-7c571b720000</link>
      <description>Mitchell was buried on the Colts depth chart after he fumbled a touchdown away before the goalline, costing Indianapolis a win against the Rams. He played only 24 offensive snaps in four games afterwards. This could not be any better of a situation for him to rebound ... except for the fact that the Jets have no real quarterback. Mitchell should quickly become the Jets No. 2 wideout opposite of Garrett Wilson. He’s not worth a huge pre-emptive strike in FAAB or anything given the Jets’ circumstances, but Mitchell does have big time talent and it is exciting to see him in an opportunity where he has a chance to realize it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5007-d713-ad9e-7c571b720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks acquired WR Rashid Shaheed from the Saints in exchange for fourth and fifth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5001-d673-a39e-f49197740000</link>
      <description>The trade reunites Shaheed with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak, who held the same role in New Orleans last year. Shaheed has continued his success as the Saints’ deep ball specialist in 2025, racking up 499 yards and two scores through nine games. A drastic improvement in quarterback play should do wonders for his already strong efficiency, even if there is less volume to go around in Seattle. His presence will likely knock Tory Horton out of the starting rotation once Cooper Kupp is healthy. Horton, who has five receiving scores this year, is only worth holding in deeper fantasy leagues. Shaheed will be an extremely boom/bust WR3 once he gets up to speed in Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5001-d673-a39e-f49197740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears acquired EDGE Joe Tryon-Shoyinka and a seventh-round pick from the Browns for a sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-501a-d713-ad9e-7c5e773b0000</link>
      <description>Tryon-Shoyinka has played just 31 defensive snaps for the Browns this year after being signed as a rotational EDGE player. He’ll try to fill in the hole left by Dayo Odeyingbo’s torn Achilles for the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-501a-d713-ad9e-7c5e773b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) is “dealing with a low-grade high ankle sprain” but has a chance to play this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5025-d45b-affe-55b7e70e0000</link>
      <description>You won’t believe how low this high-ankle sprain is, folks. It’s practically in the ground itself. Any time a high-ankle sprain comes to light we mentally budget for the worst and even if the Jaguars don’t want to admit it, it probably helped drive the acquisition of Jakobi Meyers in the short term. We’ll monitor Thomas’ practice reports this week but it sounds like he’s on the pessimistic side of questionable heading into the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5025-d45b-affe-55b7e70e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5030-d673-a39e-f4b14b950000</link>
      <description>This is team three for MVS this year after spending time in Seattle and San Francisco. He doesn’t appear to be a threat to playing time right away — it is a practice squad contract — but it’s not like the Steelers have much beyond DK Metcalf and Calvin Austin in the receiver room that has proven to be better than MVS. We wouldn’t be surprised if he eventually became a low-volume part of the offense. You don’t need to spend FAAB on him unless you’re in a 20-team league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5030-d673-a39e-f4b14b950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
