<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 18:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Drake London (knee) is doubtful for Week 13 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c113-d6c4-abfb-d7133d040000</link>
      <description>The Falcons seem intent on playing it safe with their superstar wideout during the final weeks of another lost season. It wouldn’t be a surprise if London doesn’t see the field again in 2025 after sustaining a knee injury in Week 11. Look for Darnell Mooney to continue functioning as the Falcons’ de factor WR1 with London sideline. Mooney had 71 yards and a touchdown on three targets last week against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c113-d6c4-abfb-d7133d040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c126-d6c4-abfb-d7270f140000</link>
      <description>Kincaid could be on his way to missing yet another game while recovering from a hamstring injury. With Kincaid sidelined, Dawson Knox will function as the team’s TE1. Knox has run a route on 76 percent of the Bills’ drop backs over the past two weeks and have four catches on seven targets. He’s viable in deeper fantasy formats if Kincaid misses Buffalo’s Week 13 game against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c126-d6c4-abfb-d7270f140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LT Dion Dawkins (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c12c-d90e-a9da-df2fd1900000</link>
      <description>Dawkins appears unlikely to suit up in Week 13 against the Steelers after entering the NFL’s concussion protocol and missing Wednesday’s practice. That would leave the Buffalo offense without both starting tackles against an aggressive Steelers pass rush. It could mean another outing full of pressures and hits for Josh Allen, who was banged up last week against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c12c-d90e-a9da-df2fd1900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs TE Noah Gray (concussion) has been ruled out for Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c133-d90e-a9da-df3fe5bd0000</link>
      <description>Gray sustained a head injury last week against the Colts and entered the league’s concussion protocol. He won’t suit up on a short week. It could mean a slight target bump for TE Travis Kelce. Gray had five receptions on seven targets over his past two games as a rotational tight end in the KC offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c133-d90e-a9da-df3fe5bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed DT Malcolm Roach to a three-year contract extension worth up to $29.25 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c137-d82c-a79a-f3b7d5f50000</link>
      <description>Roach has been a key part of the Denver defensive line and will remain with the team for the foreseeable future. His new deal comes with $14 million guaranteed. Roach is is his seventh NFL season. He signed with Denver in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c137-d82c-a79a-f3b7d5f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Teddy Bridgewater will get most of the first-team practice snaps this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c13c-db57-afda-d73e7ace0000</link>
      <description>Bridgewater could get the start in Week 13 against the Cardinals if Baker Mayfield is unable to play through his shoulder injury. Mayfield still has a shot to suit up, however. Bridgewater was miserable in relief of Mayfield last week against the Rams, completing eight of 15 attempts for 62 scoreless yards, with an average depth of target of 6.4, well short of Mayfield’s aDOT of 8.5. Bowles said Monday that the Bucs would have to change their offense to suit Bridgewater if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c13c-db57-afda-d73e7ace0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c140-d90e-a9da-df4f30200000</link>
      <description>McLaurin hasn’t played since late October after re-injuring his quad in a loss to the Chiefs. A full week of practice should mean McLaurin returns for Washington’s Week 13 game against the Broncos, the league’s best pass defense. He has 13 receptions for 203 yards and a touchdown over four games this season and could have some fantasy value in the regular season’s final weeks if Jayden Daniels is able to return from his elbow injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c140-d90e-a9da-df4f30200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said WR Noah Brown (groin) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c143-d6c4-abfb-d743f6000000</link>
      <description>Brown hasn’t practiced since he suffered a severe groin injury in Week 2 against the Packers. The team opened his 21-day practice window on November 24, which means he could play as soon as this week against the Broncos. He would likely function as Washington’s WR3 and should remain on waiver wires, even in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c143-d6c4-abfb-d743f6000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed CB Kaiir Elam, formerly of the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c147-db57-afda-d7772fe20000</link>
      <description>Elam is a former first-round pick (23rd overall) of the Bills in the 2022 NFL Draft. He has played in 39 career NFL games, with 19 starts while playing with the Bills and the Cowboys. Elam had 19 solo tackles and one defended pass in seven games for Dallas this season. He’s been credited with 110 tackles and two interceptions in his career. Elam will join a Titans defense allowing the league’s eighth lowest drop back success rate in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c147-db57-afda-d7772fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco does not have an injury designation for Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c14b-d90e-a9da-df4f56b00000</link>
      <description>Pacheco will make his return to the Kansas City lineup after missing a few weeks with a knee injury. He’ll likely split the backfield workload with Kareem Hunt against the Cowboys in the Chiefs’ Thanksgiving Day game in Dallas. Hunt could be a flex option since he remains the team’s preferred red zone back. Pacheco should remain benched in normal sized fantasy leagues this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c14b-d90e-a9da-df4f56b00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
