<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans EDGE Will Anderson (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5648-d673-a39e-f6d91b6b0000</link>
      <description>Anderson is the most notable of several Houston defenders who were held out of Wednesday’s practice. The third-year EDGE has six sacks this season and scored his first career touchdown on a fumble recovery in Week 7. Losing him would be a devastating blow to a Houston team that has already ruled out C.J. Stroud with a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5648-d673-a39e-f6d91b6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) is not expected to participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5652-d45b-affe-57d6fea00000</link>
      <description>Benson has been on injured reserve since Week 4 with a meniscus injury. He is eligible to return Week 10, but head coach Jonathan Gannon said Benson “is not gonna be out there [Wednesday] but he is doing better.” The initial timeline for Benson’s injury was four-to-six weeks, so it looks like he will return on the later end of that. Expect him out for Week 10 with a shot to return Week 11 against the 49ers. Expect Bam Knight and Emari Demercado to lead the backfield committee while Benson remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5652-d45b-affe-57d6fea00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RG Mekhi Becton (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-565b-d673-a39e-f6db0c9f0000</link>
      <description>Becton missed Week 9 due to a knee issue. He has a lengthy injury history and is a key piece for the Chargers’ banged up offensive line. Fellow OL Bobby Hart (knee/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday as the Chargers are reeling from Joe Alt’s season-ending ankle injury. Justin Herbert and company will need Becton and Hart to log practices the rest of the week to have a chance of playing in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-565b-d673-a39e-f6db0c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp (hamstring/heel) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5663-d673-a39e-f6f301150000</link>
      <description>Kupp did not play in Week 9 due to hamstring and heel issues and now starts out Week 10 not practicing. Wednesday was just a walkthrough for the Seahawks, but the DNP estimation indicates Kupp is not trending to play in against the Cardinals. Also DNP were WRs Jake Bobo (calf) and Dareke Young (quad). Newly acquired Rashid Shaheed and rookie Tory Horton will step up next to Jaxon Smith-Njigba with Kupp, Bobo, and Young dealing with injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5663-d673-a39e-f6f301150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5673-d713-ad9e-7e77a1e40000</link>
      <description>Barner popped up with a limited practice estimate on Wednesday. The 23-year-old has been splitting pass-catching duties with rookie Elijah Arroyo, tallying 21 receptions for 236 yards and four scores on the season. A limited estimation in a walkthrough is no cause for concern yet. Expect Barner to still play Week 10 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5673-d713-ad9e-7e77a1e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Max Melton (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-567f-d673-a39e-f6ffb8ab0000</link>
      <description>Melton suffered a hit to the head in the Cardinals’ Week 9 Monday victory over the Cowboys. He is listed as a non-participant on Wednesday with a concussion. It will be difficult for Melton to pass concussion protocol on a short week heading into a Week 10 matchup against the Seahawks. LB Mack Wilson Sr. (ribs) also was listed with a DNP designation. Both players will need practice time later this week to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-567f-d673-a39e-f6ffb8ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (chest) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56a5-d713-ad9e-7ef5dbba0000</link>
      <description>Nacua suffered a chest injury in Week 9 against the Saints and did not return. Head coach Sean McVay after the game explained Nacua suffered a rib injury and could have returned. Nacua was officially listed as a limited participant on Wednesday as McVay said earlier in the day that the 24-year-old is expected to play Week 10 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56a5-d713-ad9e-7ef5dbba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Jordan Whittington (back) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56ab-d673-a39e-f6bb08390000</link>
      <description>Whittington was a non-participant on Wednesday with a back injury. He has 12 receptions for 121 yards this season as a distant No. 3 wide receiver to Puka Nacua and Davante Adams. If Whittington misses Week 10 against the 49ers, Konata Mumpfield and Xavier Smith could see an uptick in routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56ab-d673-a39e-f6bb08390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports the Dolphins view WR Jaylen Waddle as part of their “new future.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56f3-d713-ad9e-7ef7c0b20002</link>
      <description>The Dolphins received calls on the 26-year-old wideout, including from the Denver Broncos. However, Wolfe reports the Dolphins wanted a “Quinnen Williams or Sauce Gardner type return” for Waddle. This would have consisted of at least one first-rounder and another first- or second-round pick, but there was not a market for this kind of return for him. The Dolphins view Waddle as a part of their future, whether that includes the current Tua/Mike McDaniel quarterback-coach combination or not. Trade rumors will certainly resurface in the offseason, though Miami is clearly reluctant to part ways with the speedy former No. 6 overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-56f3-d713-ad9e-7ef7c0b20002</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys announced the passing of Marshawn Kneeland at the age of 24.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-599c-d45b-affe-5d9e6ffc0000</link>
      <description>Kneeland’s agent confirmed the news shortly after Dallas released their statement. From their statement, “It is with extreme sadness that the Dallas Cowboys share that Marshawn Kneeland tragically passed away this morning. Marshawn was a beloved teammate and member of our organization. Our thoughts and prayers regarding Marshawn are with his girlfriend Catalina and his family.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-599c-d45b-affe-5d9e6ffc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
