<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed CB Brandon Codrington, formerly of the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b2c-d629-a1bc-bb3d025b0000</link>
      <description>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Codrington visited the Texans Wednesday and signed with the team. The 25-year-old spent the better part of the last two seasons as a return specialist with the Bills but was released from Buffalo’s practice squad in January. The Texans now have Codrington to evaluate over the course of the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b2c-d629-a1bc-bb3d025b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b5c-d355-a5bd-af5c18220000</link>
      <description>Also limited was LT Charles Cross (foot). Darnold and Cross have been limited in practice for the playoffs, but have played through their respective injuries. The Seahawks’ passing game has operated well in their two playoff games and neither player will be at risk of being limited for the Super Bowl, barring setbacks in practice. Expect both to fire it up in a battle for the Lombardi Trophy against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b5c-d355-a5bd-af5c18220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b62-d355-a5bd-af76e0da0000</link>
      <description>Spillane said Wednesday that he is confident he will play in the Super Bowl, despite missing practice with an ankle injury. The 30-year-old aggravated the injury in the AFC Championship game and has yet to hit the practice field. However, the DNP is early in the week and Spillane’s confidence in playing indicates he will suit up for the Super Bowl. Practice reports the rest of the week will tell if that is indeed the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b62-d355-a5bd-af76e0da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori suffered an ankle injury in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2bd6-d89c-a1be-afdf098a0000</link>
      <description>Emmanwori was listed as limited on Wednesday’s practice report as a result of an ankle injury he suffered in practice. Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told ESPN’s Kalyn Kahler, “we brought him in to look at it, and we’ll kind of go from here and figure out what are the next steps?” The rookie 21-year-old has been a key piece of the Seahawks defense and an absence would be largely impactful for Macdonald’s squad in the Super Bowl. For now, Emmanwori will be getting the ankle checked out and the Seahawks will make a determination on his status as the Super Bowl matchup against the Pats inches closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2bd6-d89c-a1be-afdf098a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane reports Eagles defensive coordinator Vic Fangio will return for next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2be6-d355-a5bd-aff6e6000000</link>
      <description>Fangio contemplated retirement this offseason after two seasons at the helm of the Eagles’ defense. However, McLane reports that the 67-year-old will indeed return to Philadelphia for the 2026 season. Despite major shake-ups to the offensive side of Nick Sirianni’s staff, Fangio remains to coach a defense that ranked fifth in points allowed last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2be6-d355-a5bd-aff6e6000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold (oblique) said he feels “really good” ahead of Super Bowl LX against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ac3-d629-a1bc-badfadba0000</link>
      <description>Darnold has been dealing with the oblique issue throughout the postseason, though it seemingly hasn’t had any effect on his performance. He noted that the extra rest ahead of the Super Bowl has helped him get ready for the final game of the year. With both Darnold and Maye having no issues playing through their respective injuries, Seattle safety Nick Emmanwori is the biggest injury question mark ahead of Sunday’s game. Emmanwori injured his ankle in practice this week and is undergoing testing to determine the severity of the issue. The rookie has 11 pass breakups, 2.5 sacks, and one interception this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ac3-d629-a1bc-badfadba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles hired former Packers wide receivers coach Ryan Mahaffey as their run game coordinator and tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2e50-d629-a1bc-be5d47ee0000</link>
      <description>Mahaffey is following new Philly OC Sean Mannion from Green Bay to Philly. Mahaffey has been working his way up the ranks with the Packers since 2021. The Eagles went from having the league’s best ground game in 2024 to an average (at best) rushing attack in 2025. Mahaffey doens’t need to get them back to the No. 1 spot in his first year on the job, but his biggest task will be finding ways to recreate the explosive running plays that vanished this past year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2e50-d629-a1bc-be5d47ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said S Nick Emmanwori suffered a low-ankle sprain on Wednesday, but he is “confident” that Emmanwori will play in Super Bowl LX against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f03-d629-a1bc-bf1ff0c00000</link>
      <description>The low-ankle sprain diagnosis is good news. Emmanwori was sidelined in Weeks 2-4 after suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 1. Despite the multi-game absence, Emmanwori ranks second on the team in tackles (71), first in pass breakups (12) and ties for third in interceptions (one). He also accounts for 19 quarterback pressures and three sacks, having established himself as an effective blitzer in Macdonald’s creative defensive scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f03-d629-a1bc-bf1ff0c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 49ers will play the Rams in Melbourne, Australia next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f2e-d629-a1bc-bf3f32080000</link>
      <description>This will be the first time that an NFL game has been played in Australia. The NFL announced last year that the league had signed a multi-year commitment to host regular season games in Melbourne, as it expands the international market. The game will be played at the Melbourne Cricket Ground, which boasts a listed seating capacity of 100,024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f2e-d629-a1bc-bf3f32080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
