<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he expects Matthew Stafford (back) to start against the Texans in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ed-db7b-a5dd-a6eda16b0000</link>
      <description>We’re expecting Stafford to continue to be managed through practices, but so far his back injury doesn’t seem like it’ll keep him from setting foot on the field on opening day. Jourdan Rodrigue of The Athletic said recently she believes the injury is going to need to be managed throughout the season, so Stafford is probably best-approached as a risky QB2 in superflex leagues at this time. For a quarterback who is very bound to the pocket, a first-game test against Will Anderson and Danielle Hunter presents a real challenge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ed-db7b-a5dd-a6eda16b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Alaric Jackson returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06c9-de13-afdd-46cb4eb60000</link>
      <description>Jackson was diagnosed with blood clots in June, but has been trending toward being ready for Week 1. The fact that he was able to suit up for a Monday practice suggests he’s still trending in the right direction, and the team said the plan will be to start him in Week 1 against the Texans if all goes well this week. Jackson earned a PFF pass blocking grade of 79.5 last season, allowing just three sacks and 22 pressures on 502 dropbacks. If he is unable to start, D.J. Humphries looks like the most likely candidate to step up in Jackson’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06c9-de13-afdd-46cb4eb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevon Diggs said there’s a 75-80 percent chance he plays in Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0704-d332-a1fd-9736aa9a0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys open the season on the road against the Eagles on Thursday night. The veteran corner’s status was reported as “up in the air” earlier by NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, and that appears to still be the case based on Diggs’ comments. Diggs said earlier that he would be ready to go by Week 4 at the latest, but his practice availability will give us a better look at how he projects for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0704-d332-a1fd-9736aa9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown (hamstring) was not listed on the Eagles’ injury report on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-070e-de13-afdd-47cf16930000</link>
      <description>It would appear that any concerns over Brown’s hamstring injury lingering into the regular season can be laid to rest. The star receiver was not only a full participant in practice, but avoided the injury report altogether, which is a great sign for his Week 1 availability when the Eagles kick off the season against the Cowboys on Thursday night. Brown profiles as a fringe WR1/WR2 against a Cowboys defense that will be without Micah Parsons following his trade to the Packers and may also be short CB Trevon Diggs (knee).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-070e-de13-afdd-47cf16930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OG Landon Dickerson (back) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0732-de13-afdd-47fbc5800000</link>
      <description>Dickerson didn’t practice on Monday, but there seems to be some hope that he will still suit up on Thursday night when the Eagles play host to the Cowboys. Dickerson was listed on the team’s official report with a back injury, but had been missing time after undergoing a minor knee procedure in mid-August. It was reported over the weekend that Dickerson was “trending” toward playing in Week 1, so we won’t read too much into Monday’s DNP just yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0732-de13-afdd-47fbc5800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevon Diggs (knee) was listed as a full participant in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0737-de13-afdd-47ff531d0000</link>
      <description>The day started with Diggs’ Week 1 availability being “up in the air.” Later, the veteran corner said there was a 75-80 percent chance he would suit up. Now, we know that Diggs was a full participant in Monday’s practice, which would seemingly increase his chances of playing in the season-opener. Diggs is definitely trending toward a return, and said on Monday he felt good when speaking to the media. It’s too early to say for certain if Diggs will play, but this is an encouraging start to the week for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0737-de13-afdd-47ff531d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Najee Harris (eye) said he’s ‘ramping up to it’ when asked if he will play Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0749-dbe3-a9bb-375b4ddc0000</link>
      <description>Speaking to reporters Monday, Harris said “I feel good though, and we’ll just see where it leads.” Harris has been on the practice field for almost a week now as he works his way back into football shape following a July 4 fireworks incident. He continues to claim the injuries to be superficial, insisting he is doing everything he can to be on the field Friday in Brazil against the Chiefs. He also noted that his vision has not been affected but did not want to go into details about the circumstances of the incident. While Harris is certainly trending in the right direction to play in the team’s season opener, his potential workload is a topic of another discussion considering the time he has missed during camp and preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0749-dbe3-a9bb-375b4ddc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (ankle) resumed practicing last week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0865-db7b-a5dd-a8658fde0000</link>
      <description>Not much has been made of Shakir’s return to practice last Wednesday, but it’s a very promising development. Shakir suffered a high-ankle sprain on August 1st, and the Bills smartly chose to hold him out for nearly the entire month of practice so the ankle could fully heal. Shakir may have to shake off a little rust but Josh Allen should have his most proven pass catcher on the field with him when the Bills host the Ravens in Week 1. He’s a WR3/4 with decent upside in PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0865-db7b-a5dd-a8658fde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Kendrick Bourne is visiting with the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ab8-dbe3-a9bb-3afb9a490000</link>
      <description>Bourne recently visited with the 49ers, who have struggled with various wideout injuries and enter the regular season bereft of receiver depth. Bourne, who has never surpassed 800 yards in a season and was phased out by the Patriots this offseason, would make sense in Washington, where there’s not much depth behind Deebo Samuel and Terry McLaurin. Bourne, 30, is widely expected to sign with a team ahead of Week 1. He likely won’t see much action, if any, on opening day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ab8-dbe3-a9bb-3afb9a490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas, Jr. said his chemistry with Trevor Lawrence grew throughout the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b14-de13-afdd-4fdf69040000</link>
      <description>It’s good to hear from the second-year wideout after Lawrence struggled in 2024 and missed seven games with shoulder and head injuries. “I feel like we’ve definitely got a lot closer, whether it’s football or off the field, like all the little things,” Thomas said of his relationship with Lawrence. “I feel like our chemistry is growing on the field, and I feel like it’s going to continue to grow throughout the season.” The offseason work between Thomas and Lawrence wasn’t without some hiccups, however. Thomas was seen during training camp “punching a padded wall or kicking a football” after offensive miscues and miscommunications between quarterback and pass catcher. Head coach Liam Coen has said Thomas — who went for 1,282 yards and ten touchdowns as a rookie — will play more from the slot in 2025. That’s a positive development for Thomas, who was the league’s third most efficient pass catcher from the slot in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b14-de13-afdd-4fdf69040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
