<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings hired Ryan Nielsen as defensive run game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported today that Nielsen is being hired as the Vikings’ new defensive run game coordinator, though prior reporting suggested he may also coach the defensive line. He spent the 2025 season as a senior defensive assistant with the Bills. He served as the Jaguars (2024) and Falcons’ (2023) defensive coordinator in recent seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb is reportedly the “leading candidate” for the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy after interviewing for the role on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</link>
      <description>Webb, 31, withdrew from the Raiders’ head-coaching search late last week, after progressing through the second round of interviews. He also received requests to interview for the Ravens, Eagles, and Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancies and was previously linked to the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy. Only the Giants’ respective vacancy remains available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants completed an interview with former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz broke today’s news. He also reported back on January 6th, the same day Kingsbury parted ways with the Commanders, that Kingsbury was a candidate for the Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancy. Kingsbury has successfully schemed up offenses for mobile quarterbacks in the past. Giants QB Jaxson Dart fits the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports that NFL teams searching for a new defensive coordinator are “moving” on 49ers assistant head coach of defense Gus Bradley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers hired Raheem Morris as their new defensive coordinator earlier today, removing one high-profile candidate. Breer notes that either the Titans or Cardinals could hire Bradley as their next defensive coordinator, though the Cardinals’ ability to let Bradley call plays on defense gives them an “edge” over the Titans. He also notes that if the Titans miss out on Bradley, Falcons defensive pass-game coordinator Mike Rutenberg is “a name to watch.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland’s Mary Kay Cabot reports that the Browns plan to hire Jeff Blasko as their new tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1c0d-d89c-a1be-bfdf5da50000</link>
      <description>Blasko spent the 2025 season coaching Jets tight ends. He was hired by the Cowboys in 2020 as an assistant offensive line coach and was later promoted to run game coordinator and running backs coach in 2023. Blasko previously worked as an assistant offensive line coach for the Browns, alongside new head coach Todd Monken, back in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1c0d-d89c-a1be-bfdf5da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced a multi-year deal with the City of Madrid and Comunidad de Madrid to host games beginning in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e81-d355-a5bd-9fd55e3d0000</link>
      <description>The NFL played its first Madrid game during the 2025 regular season and will now return to Madrid on a multi-year deal. The games will be played at Bernabéu Stadium, the home stadium for Real Madrid C.F. The league now has seven international games scheduled for the 2026 regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e81-d355-a5bd-9fd55e3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Steelers will interview Saints QBs coach Scott Tolzien for their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e8b-d355-a5bd-9fdf6c6c0000</link>
      <description>Tolzien joined the Saints for the 2025 season, but spent the previous five seasons with the Cowboys as a coaching assistant (2020 to 2022) and later as their QBs coach (2023 to 2024). His time with the Cowboys overlaps with Mike McCarthy’s tenure with the team, and he also spent three seasons with McCarthy while playing for the Packers. From a relationship standpoint, there’s a lot that makes sense about McCarthy’s interest in Tolzien, but this would be his first role as an offensive coordinator should he land the job, which could prove challenging given the current state of the Steelers’ roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e8b-d355-a5bd-9fdf6c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced the Saints will play in the league’s first game in Paris, France in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f19-d89c-a1be-bfdf800f0000</link>
      <description>The Saints will be the “home” team against an opponent to be named later, and the game will be played in Paris at the Stade de France stadium. The announcement of the 2026 France game brings the league’s international game totals to eight for the upcoming season, with three of those games set to be played in London/U.K.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f19-d89c-a1be-bfdf800f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed HC Sean McVay to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f30-d042-afbc-7ff2ce450000</link>
      <description>One of the premier coaches in the league, McVay will remain with the Rams for the foreseeable future. It was a decision that likely came easily to ownership, who have seen their team go 92-57 under McVay’s leadership while also winning a Super Bowl in 2021. McVay has led the Rams to double-digit wins in seven of his nine years, and had the team within a game of his third Super Bowl appearance. While we don’t know the length of McVay’s extension, he will presumably be under contract when the Rams pursue a new franchise quarterback once Matthew Stafford, who turns 38 later this month, eventually calls it quits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f30-d042-afbc-7ff2ce450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed GM Les Snead to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f31-d042-afbc-7ff3d8780000</link>
      <description>Snead first joined the Rams in 2012 and has been with the team through the lowest of lows and the highest of highs. His fortunes took a turn for the better when he hired Sean McVay in 2017, as the Rams have gone 92-57 in the regular season over that span, making two trips to the Super Bowl and winning a championship in 2021. Snead has hit on recent picks like Puka Nacua, Kyren Williams, and Byron Young — to name a few, and has repeatedly had them in contention for the better part of the last decade. The combination of Snead and McVay, who also received an extension, should continue to terrorize the NFC West for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1f31-d042-afbc-7ff3d8780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
