<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 02:31:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e67e-db57-afda-f67ebd420000</link>
      <description>Smith popped up on the injury report with a foot issues ahead of the Raiders’ Week 14 game against the Broncos. This late in the season, it is likely he is managing some aches and pains and the Raiders are varying his workload. Smith is still on track to play on Sunday, though he is barely a fantasy QB2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e67e-db57-afda-f67ebd420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Dont’e Thornton (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e687-d90e-a9da-ff8fd6770000</link>
      <description>Thornton is not practicing due to a concussion. The 23-year-old has caught just eight passes this season and has become an afterthought in the pass-catching order. Also not practicing was WR Alex Bachman (thumb), who has primarily been a return specialist this season. Thornton’s potential Week 14 absence does not elevate any other Raiders receiver to be an interesting fantasy play against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e687-d90e-a9da-ff8fd6770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mayer (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e68d-d6c4-abfb-f68f8af50000</link>
      <description>Mayer has not been practicing since suffering an ankle injury in Week 12. He missed Week 13 and is not back practicing yet, indicating he is trending to miss Week 14 against the Broncos. Mayer can stay off fantasy radars at this point in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e68d-d6c4-abfb-f68f8af50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers QB Justin Herbert said he is going to “prepare as if [he is] going to play” in Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e695-d6c4-abfb-f69738570000</link>
      <description>Herbert underwent successful surgery on his left hand earlier this week, ahead of a Week 14 matchup on Monday night against the Eagles. According to the Athletic’s Daniel Popper, he said the fracture on his non-throwing hand successfully “stabilized” and he is preparing to play Monday. Official practice reports from later this week will tell just how ready Herbert will be; given the Chargers have a tough matchup against the Eagles, all Chargers pass-catchers are downgraded even if Herbert plays. Herbert is a shaky fantasy QB2 if he does suit up for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e695-d6c4-abfb-f69738570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner (knee/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6a6-db57-afda-f6b66bf50000</link>
      <description>Barner popped up on the injury report nursing both knee and shoulder injuries Wednesday. He was limited, indicating the 23-year-old tight end is still trending to play in Week 14. Barner’s usage makes him a solid TE2 option if he plays against the Falcons on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6a6-db57-afda-f6b66bf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dortch (chest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c1-d6c4-abfb-f6c385ea0000</link>
      <description>Dortch was sidelined Wednesday with a chest injury. The 27-year-old had fantasy viability with Marvin Harrison Jr. out, but saw just two targets in Week 13 with Harrison back. Harrison (heel) also missed practice Wednesday, so the Cardinals’ wide receiver situation is one to monitor heading into Week 14 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c1-d6c4-abfb-f6c385ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c8-d316-abff-f6dba12c0000</link>
      <description>Adams is dealing with a hamstring issue, but it is unlikely to keep him out of the Rams’ Week 14 matchup against the Cardinals. ESPN’s Sarah Barshop reports head coach Sean McVay said he expects all the players with DNP or limited practice designations to play Sunday. Fantasy managers can expect to enjoy Adams’ red zone role yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6c8-d316-abff-f6dba12c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers head coach Dave Canales said Rico Dowdle would remain the team’s primary early-down running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d4-db57-afda-f6f65ee30000</link>
      <description>As the Panthers head into their bye week, Canales said he “likes” the backfield balance the team struck in Week 13’s upset of the Rams, when Dowdle saw 18 rushes to 17 carries for Chuba Hubbard. Hubbard, fully recovered from a calf injury, ran 15 pass routes against LA — catching a touchdown on two grabs — while Dowdle logged six routes and caught both of his targets. “Some of it was third-down opportunities. We’ve been using Chuba primarily as our third-down back, and then he gets series as we go,” Canales said. With his pass game involvement reduced to almost nothing, Dowdle will be a low-ceiling, touchdown-dependent RB3 when the Panthers return from bye in Week 15. Hubbard, meanwhile, will have some value in deeper PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d4-db57-afda-f6f65ee30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d2-d6c4-abfb-f6d31cf20000</link>
      <description>Williams suffered an ankle injury and played through it in Week 13. It looks to be a minor issue, though the Rams are being cautious and keeping him limited to open the week. Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said on Wednesday the team want to keep Williams fresh for the playoffs, so fantasy managers should not be surprised to see more limited practice listings moving forward. Williams is in the RB2 range for Week 14 against the Cardinals, but his potential workload limitations may lead to Blake Corum being a standalone FLEX play as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e6d2-d6c4-abfb-f6d31cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks re-signed RB Myles Gaskin to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e713-d316-abff-f7930c8f0000</link>
      <description>As expected, the Seahawks added Gaskin back to their practice squad after waiving him Tuesday. He saw three carries for six yards in Week 13 as the third back behind Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet. With Cam Akers recently joining the active roster and ready to be active, Gaskin moves down to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e713-d316-abff-f7930c8f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
