<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (knee) is not on Chicago’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84d-d56e-afff-eeed5cdf0000</link>
      <description>He produced a 6/64/1 receiving line against the Packers in the Wild Card round on seven targets and is likely in line for the same kind of volume as the Bears manage Rome Odunze’s foot. Moore will definitely be a DFS consideration this week behind Colston Loveland and Luther Burden in what would figure to be the highest-scoring game of the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84d-d56e-afff-eeed5cdf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones on Saturday for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c877-d56e-afff-eeff96030000</link>
      <description>It’s an in-person interview and Jones’ second with the team, cementing him as either a finalist or semi-finalist depending on how long the Cowboys want to drag this out. Jones has an interesting ascension case to be Vikings defensive coordinator if Brian Flores leaves, so he seems to have good odds of coming out of this cycle with a coordinator job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c877-d56e-afff-eeff96030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers completed an interview with former Titans head coach Brian Callahan for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c87b-d968-a19b-d8fbe9450000</link>
      <description>That’s two OC interviews for Callahan, who per Jeremy Fowler “impressed” Tampa Bay in his earlier interview last Friday. Callahan hadn’t called plays for the Bengals before getting the Titans head-coaching gig, and after watching his Titans head-coaching play calling, we’d be a little squeamish on the fantasy prospects of whatever team he lands with. It does make some extra sense for the Chargers because he’d likely bring along offensive line coach (and father) Bill Callahan with him, which could help a Chargers o-line that was woeful last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c87b-d968-a19b-d8fbe9450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested to interview Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c87f-dc7a-af9b-cfff1fff0000</link>
      <description>This is Brady’s third request, after the Dolphins and Ravens. Brady will reportedly interview for the Ravens and Falcons gigs on Sunday after the Bills play on Saturday. Brady has long been rumored to be a head-coaching candidate — he even got some buzz as far back as 2022 — but he had a rough 2025 regular season as the Bills passing offense fell apart at times. “President of football” Matt Ryan seems unfazed by this, though, and will add him to a busy pool of Falcons candidates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c87f-dc7a-af9b-cfff1fff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets completed an interview with Dolphins CB coach Matt Araujo for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c876-dc7a-af9b-cfffb84a0000</link>
      <description>Araujo signed on with the Dolphins as assistant defensive backs coach in 2022. He was promoted to cornerbacks coach in 2024. Araujo previously coached at Yale (2019-2021), Boston College (2017-2018), Springfield College (2016) and Maine Maritime Academy (2015).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c876-dc7a-af9b-cfffb84a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in the Divisional Round against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c880-d968-a19b-d8f1f1e30000</link>
      <description>Jordan practiced fully on Friday, which is a great sign. He was unable to play in the Wild Card Round after injuring his ankle in Week 18. We expect Jordan to handle No. 2 rushing duties behind starting RB Woody Marks, though Marks could ultimately dominate touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c880-d968-a19b-d8f1f1e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is not on New England’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88c-d35e-a1bf-cdceac290000</link>
      <description>Mike Vrabel said Gonzalez would be questionable before practice, but he cleared protocol and will officially suit up against the Texans on Sunday. The star cornerback is one of New England’s best players and it’s great news for their defense that he’ll not miss any time after leaving Sunday’s win over the Chargers with a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88c-d35e-a1bf-cdceac290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) is questionable for New England’s Divisional Round game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeea6eb0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice today. Landry played 26 snaps against the Chargers last week and would figure to be part of a rotation at EDGE if he were able to go — the Pats have managed him through practices so we’re not surprised to see him on the injury report, but a DNP on Friday is different than the norm for him. Backup RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) is questionable after two full practices on Thursday and Friday and could come off injured reserve tomorrow. Khyiris Tonga (foot) is not on the injury report at all after two full sessions. His return is great news for the New England run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeea6eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said he is “really optimistic” QB Sam Darnold (oblique) “is going to be able to play” in the Divisional Round against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeeca8d0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald adds that there is “a possibility the injury limits [Darnold] physically,” while adding that Darnold “is confident he’ll be able to operate normally.” Per The Athletic’s Mike Dugar, Macdonald “gave a non-answer” when asked if Darnold “threw during the walkthrough.” Macdonald’s obfuscatory responses make it difficult to assess the severity of Darnold’s injury, but we believe Darnold will play even if the oblique injury is bothering him on Saturday. The Seahawks enter their matchup with the 49ers averaging a below-average 62.5 plays per game, methodically picking up yardage while running out the clock. If they can control the game’s pace, they may be able to keep Darnold’s workload at a manageable, moderate level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeeca8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (knee) is not on New England’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c891-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcad40000</link>
      <description>As expected, Henry will play his usual role. He hooked up with Drake Maye for Maye’s lone touchdown last week against the Chargers and should be in DFS consideration this weekend despite playing in a game with the lowest scoring total on the slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c891-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcad40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
