<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Taylor (shoulder) is questionable to return to the 49ers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49b-df63-a199-fdbb92cf0000</link>
      <description>Taylor drew the start in the backfield in the absence of Christian McCaffrey, Isaac Guerendo, and Jordan James, losing six yards on four carries prior to departing with a shoulder injury. While listed questionable to return, it would stand to reason that his day is done. Corey Kiner was the next back up Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49b-df63-a199-fdbb92cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers OL Dominick Puni (knee) was ruled out for preseason Week 2 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-df63-a199-fdbfefaa0000</link>
      <description>Puni is in line to start at right guard for a team looking to return to the top five in scoring after a down 2024 regular season. He was immediately ruled out for the remainder of the contest, making his situation worth monitoring during the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-df63-a199-fdbfefaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Corey Kiner was carted from the field in Saturday’s preseason game due to an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-d45c-a7fc-b69fa3090000</link>
      <description>Kiner is a UDFA from Cincinnati who has been impressing in Niners camp. The rookie broke off a 19-yard run in the second quarter and remained down after the play, only to later be carted from the field. While he’d typically be considered a long shot to make the roster, Kiner may have had an opening given the current state of the 49ers’ backfield. We’ll hopefully know more on his injury soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-d45c-a7fc-b69fa3090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed seven times for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Raiders’ preseason Week 2 game against the 49ers, adding two yards on his lone reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4a2-d45c-a7fc-b6bad0340000</link>
      <description>Jeanty briefly left the contest in the first quarter with what was described as a shoulder injury before returning to the field and running over a San Francisco defender on a 13-yard carry, his longest of the game. He would later display his raw power again while pushed into the end zone while remaining upright from the one. The swift overreaction to his mundane preseason debut a week ago seems silly in retrospect, with his performance today reinforcing his status as a top tier selection in the early rounds of fantasy drafts this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4a2-d45c-a7fc-b6bad0340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught his only target for 28 yards in the Raiders’ preseason Week 2 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4af-d45c-a7fc-b6bffae10000</link>
      <description>Bowers displayed his elite athleticism while hauling in a 28-yard bomb down the right sideline over a defender in tight coverage against the 49ers Saturday, reinforcing his status as fantasy’s top tight end off the board for the 2025 season. He played on two drives with the starters, the second of which ended in an Ashton Jeanty touchdown plunge from one yard out. The Raiders offense looked much better than it did a week ago, calming some of the offseason nerves for fantasy managers in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4af-d45c-a7fc-b6bffae10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 6-of-8 passes for 55 yards in the Raiders’ preseason game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4ae-d90d-a5bd-b6ff410f0000</link>
      <description>Smith started things off with a deep throw to the outside to Brock Bowers, who “mossed” his defender in single coverage to haul in a 28-yard reception. Smith has now completed 7-of-11 preseason passes for 70 scoreless yards and has looked in command of the offense in limited action. He’ll profile as a QB2 for most weeks for fantasy, but could have some upside as a matchup-based streamer in the right situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4ae-d90d-a5bd-b6ff410f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said he’s not concerned about De’Von Achane’s (soft tissue lower-body injury) Week 1 availability against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b8-d05a-adda-beba0ca10000</link>
      <description>It’s a nondescript soft tissue lower-body injury for the Dolphins’ RB1. McDaniel said Achane could be out between “days and weeks,” to further add to the mystery, making his status one to watch until he officially returns to action. Second-year back Jaylen Wright would be the immediate favorite to replace Achane on most downs, but rookie sixth-rounder Ollie Gordon could also see some work in short-yardage and goal-line situations. The Dolphins kick off the 2025 season in 22 days, which will hopefully prove to be enough time for Achane to get right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b8-d05a-adda-beba0ca10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said ZDT Zach Sieler (unspecified) will be out “between days and weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4d0-d90d-a5bd-b6dbabf90000</link>
      <description>McDaniel said that Sieler likely would have suited up for Saturday’s preseason game against the Lions if it were a regular season game. The veteran lineman who signed a three-year extension this offseason now has 22 days to get right before the Dolphins visit the Colts in Week 1. While the timeline for Sieler’s return is murky, McDaniel said he is not concerned about his Week 1 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4d0-d90d-a5bd-b6dbabf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said he’s “very close” to a decision on the starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b3-d05a-adda-beb326610000</link>
      <description>Speaking to media following the team’s preseason loss to the Packers, Colts head coach Shane Steichen said he would like to make a decision on the starting quarterback soon, adding that he was “very close.” We should see a decision made in the coming days to give the winner enough camp and in-game reps during the two weeks before the regular season starts. Both Anthony Richardson and Daniel Jones have traded sinusoidal reports, with both seemingly shifting between standing out and struggling in camp to this point. Steichen has continually mentioned consistency when speaking to the quarterback competition, and while Jones appears to give his team more consistent play, Richardson continues to demonstrate tantalizing upside if he can get his decision making process tighter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b3-d05a-adda-beb326610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Gardner (calf) won’t play Saturday in the Jets’ preseason game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4fd-d45c-a7fc-b6ffc5160000</link>
      <description>Per Jets beat writer Rich Cimini, Gardner’s injury is “not believed to be serious,” but the Jets won’t risk anything with their star corner. We’ll see if head coach Aaron Glenn offers a different take after the game, but for now, it sounds like this is a non-issue as far as his Week 1 availability is concerned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4fd-d45c-a7fc-b6ffc5160000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
