<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay was “optimistic” that TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) will play in the Divisional Round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36a-d35e-a1bf-f7eace810000</link>
      <description>McVay added that G Kevin Dotson also has a good chance to return against the Bears. With all four of his tight ends healthy, the Rams’ 13-personnel set will become a more complicated situation to read for fantasy purposes. Ferguson seemed to be coming on late in the season before injuring his hamstring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36a-d35e-a1bf-f7eace810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36f-d56e-afff-f7ef8e590000</link>
      <description>That’s the Browns, Falcons, Ravens and Titans with interviews scheduled or completed for McDaniel, who has taken exclusively head-coaching interviews so far. (The Lions have reached out to McDaniel about their offensive coordinator vacancy, but he hasn’t taken the interview as far as we can tell.) McDaniel is probably one of the most valuable 32 head coaches in the league given what he managed to squeeze out of the Dolphins in the Tua Tagovailoa Era, but he doesn’t exactly have widespread appeal amongst the eight head-coaching vacancies. He’s one of the more fascinating coaching free agents this go-around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36f-d56e-afff-f7ef8e590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b37d-d968-a19b-fbfdcc820000</link>
      <description>This was actually one of the expected names that surfaced up in the immediate moments after John Harbaugh was fired, so the only surprising thing is that it took this many days for the request to formally be submitted. Minter has interview requests from the Browns and Titans for their head-coaching vacancies as well, and has some time to set up those interviews now that the Chargers have been eliminated from the playoffs despite holding Drake Maye’s high-flying show to 16 points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b37d-d968-a19b-fbfdcc820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b380-d35e-a1bf-f7c22b1c0000</link>
      <description>That’s the first completed interview for Weaver, who was also requested by the Cardinals and Falcons last week. The 45-year-old Dolphins defensive coordinator mostly has a recent reputation of making something out of nothing as the Dolphins were given little chance on defense last year with a rough secondary and finished 24th in defensive DVOA. Weaver played for the Ravens and also coached them for quite a bit, rising as high as Assistant Head Coach to John Harbaugh before taking the Dolphins job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b380-d35e-a1bf-f7c22b1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b385-d968-a19b-fbf5ee8b0000</link>
      <description>So have the Raiders. The McVay assistant coaching tree continues to be well-plumbed. Scheelhaase stayed put this year after nearly signing on as Jaguars offensive coordinator in 2025 silly season. It’s possible that he leaps to an offensive coordinator gig this year, but the fact that he’s already drawing head-coaching interviews shows his name is on the rise. The Ravens have a crowded board right now, about 10-15 candidates deep, and the Raiders have requested just six names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b385-d968-a19b-fbf5ee8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b388-dc7a-af9b-ffbf8e140000</link>
      <description>They’re joined by the Cardinals and Raiders, adding to the initial two names of the Titans and Dolphins from over the weekend. Shula’s defense has faded down the stretch, but finished fourth in defensive DVOA during the regular season. It should not be lost on anybody that Shula is doing this despite almost no investment on that side of the ball — the Rams have the lowest defensive payroll in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b388-dc7a-af9b-ffbf8e140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders requested an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b395-d968-a19b-fbf5b9110000</link>
      <description>That makes four interview requests for Minter, who already has heard from the Ravens, Titans, and Browns. He’s the seventh name on Las Vegas’ interview request list, joining Packers DC Jeff Hafley, Broncos DC Vance Joseph, Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak, Chiefs OC Matt Nagy, Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase and Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb. Minter’s defense did great work last night against Drake Maye, even if it ultimately didn’t lead to a win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b395-d968-a19b-fbf5b9110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Bailey Zappe to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b398-d56e-afff-f7f8e3e40000</link>
      <description>Zappe has the roster-joining ability of a young Tim Boyle. The Jets will hope to never have to go to Plan Zappe in a real game, though until they solve the position we guess we’re at “anything is possible.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b398-d56e-afff-f7f8e3e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ad-d35e-a1bf-f7efd05a0000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury has only been connected to the Titans and Ravens so far after the Commanders unceremoniously dumped him to elevate David Blough to offensive coordinator. We have not yet heard about any itinerary for Thailand for Kingsbury. It seems more likely that he finds a spot as an offensive coordinator than a head coach based on the early interest, but we’re not quite at the section of the offseason where Kingsbury is in danger of running out of spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3ad-d35e-a1bf-f7efd05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers interviewed Lions assistant special teams coach Jett Modkins for their special teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3b0-d35e-a1bf-f7f229010000</link>
      <description>It’s the second interview for Jett Modkins in the coveted special teams coordinator cycle. We have blurbed both of them because it’s very pleasing to type Jett Modkins. Try it. The Buccaneers fired Thomas McGaughey after a season that concluded with them kicking the ball into the end zone because they were scared of returns (Todd Bowles’ actual words) and are likely hoping that Jett Modkins has answers for that. Jett Modkins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b3b0-d35e-a1bf-f7f229010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
