<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 04:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Elijah Mitchell is inactive for Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</link>
      <description>Mitchell’s deactivation suggests the Chiefs will roll with Isiah Pacheco, Kareem Hunt and rookie Brashard Smith, who notably took a few first-team reps in preseason play last month. He might be worth stashing on benches before kickoff. The Chiefs also declared WR Jalen Royals (knee), TE Jared Wiley, DT Omarr Norman-Lott, OL Hunter Nourzad and DE Malik Herring inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c10-de13-afdd-5edb20240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c24-dbe3-a9bb-3c776e3c0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ wide receiver corps will not be at full health, with Christian Kirk sidelined, but it’s still great news for the Rams, who will have their hands full in trying to cover Nico Collins. Witherspoon broke up six passes and recorded one interception last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c24-dbe3-a9bb-3c776e3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c63-de13-afdd-5eebef8a0000</link>
      <description>Worthy collided with Travis Kelce on a crossing route on the Chiefs’ first drive and stayed on the ground for a few beats before walking off while holding his arm. He almost immediately left for the locker room with a towel draped over his head. According to the broadcast, Worthy is currently undergoing X-rays on his shouler. We should get an update on his status soon, but it doesn’t look like he will be back tonight. That leaves Hollywood Brown as the team’s top wideout with JuJu Smith-Schuster and Tyquan Thornton also in the mix for routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c63-de13-afdd-5eebef8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will not return in Week 1 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c89-d332-a1fd-9ebfd7380000</link>
      <description>Worthy left the opening game of his second season in the first quarter after colliding with Travis Kelce on a crossing route. He was checked out by trainers before walking off the field and into the locker room. Worthy went in for X-rays and was ruled out shortly after. It might be a day or two before we know the nature of the injury, but the mechanism was that of a dislocated shoulder. With Rashee Rice sidelined for the first six weeks while serving a suspension, the Chiefs are down the Hollywood Brown as their No. 1 receiver. Travis Kelce will also be heavily involved until one of Worthy or Rice is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c89-d332-a1fd-9ebfd7380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c8f-d332-a1fd-9ebff3990000</link>
      <description>Perryman went down in the first half and was replaced by backup linebacker Troy Dye. Perryman appeared in 11 games for the Chargers last year, totaling 55 tackles and one sack. Dye has primarily played on special teams throughout his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1c8f-d332-a1fd-9ebff3990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 5-of-7 targets for 79 yards and two touchdowns in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1cfe-d332-a1fd-9efe79d50000</link>
      <description>Johnston got on the board in the first quarter with a short touchdown catch from five yards out. His second touchdown came in the fourth quarter and ultimately iced the game. Johnston turned things around after a dreadful rookie season with eight touchdowns in 2024. Though he appears to be third in the pecking order for targets behind Ladd McConkey and Keenan Allen, his nose for the end zone is undeniable. Johnston will be in the FLEX mix for his Week 2 matchup with the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1cfe-d332-a1fd-9efe79d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 7-of-10 targets for 68 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d04-de13-afdd-5fcf4cd70000</link>
      <description>Allen was left for dead by the NFL after a disappointing 2024 season. He didn’t see much interest as a free agent but eventually found an opening in LA after Mike Williams retired. It was unclear how much he had left in the tank after posting career lows across the board in Chicago. He emphatically silenced the doubters in his first game back in LA by leading the Chargers with 10 targets. Though Allen largely operated as a check-down option for Justin Herbert, that is more than enough to rack up PPR points on a team that looks willing to maintain a high-volume passing attack. Allen will push for a WR3 ranking next week versus Las Vegas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d04-de13-afdd-5fcf4cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 24-of-39 passes for 258 yards and one touchdown in the Chiefs’ 27-21, Week 1 loss to the Chargers, adding six carries for 57 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d0a-de13-afdd-5fcb24240000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs entered the 2025 season in desperate need of a revitalization on offense. While Mahomes has had no issues grinding out wins as a check-down merchant, he’s at his best when attacking opponents downfield. That was the focus of Kansas City’s offseason and it all fell apart on the third play of the night when Xavier Worthy collided with Travis Kelce and suffered a serious shoulder injury. He did not return and his status for Week 2 is questionable at best. Mahomes failed to get much going downfield after Worthy left and was forced to dump the ball off to Hollywood Brown and JuJu Smith-Schuster, the team’s leading target-earners of the night. Despite the disastrous outcome, Mahomes still flashed his signature play-making magic with a scrambling heave to Brown for a 49-yard gain late in the fourth quarter. The Chiefs ultimately settled for a field goal on the drive and never got the ball back. Mahomes saved his fantasy backers with a strong rushing line, but it’s hard to envision him posting weekly QB1 numbers with Rashee Rice suspended for another five games and Worthy’s status up in the air. Mahomes will sit on the QB1/2 border for his Week 2 Super Bowl rematch with the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d0a-de13-afdd-5fcb24240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed 15 times for 48 yards in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs, adding two receptions for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d12-d332-a1fd-9f36eb690000</link>
      <description>The good news is that the first-round rookie drew the start over Najee Harris and out-carried him 15-1. Harris was only targeted once and totaled 10 yards from scrimmage. The bad news is that Kansas City bottled up Hampton with ease, limiting him to 3.2 yards per carry with a long of 11. The Chargers were also stunningly pass-heavy in this game despite their offseason investments at running back. Justin Herbert attempted 34 passes compared to just 22 total rush attempts for the team after removing three Herbert kneel-downs. Hampton’s dominance of the backfield touches will keep him in the RB1 ranks for his Week 2 matchup with Las Vegas, but another pass-first plan from Jim Harbaugh could keep a true breakout from the rookie at bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d12-d332-a1fd-9f36eb690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 25-of-34 passes for 318 yards and three touchdowns in the Chargers’ 27-21, Week 1 win over the Chiefs, adding seven carries for 32 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d19-d332-a1fd-9f3f2ae00000</link>
      <description>The Chargers invested heavily in their running back room this offseaosn, leading many to think Jim Harbaugh was finally going to establish it after leaning on his quarterback in 2024. That couldn’t have been further from the truth as Herbert came out swinging versus Kansas City with three straight dropbacks on his first drive. He marched LA down the field and capped the drive with a five-yard toss to Quentin Johnston in the end zone. Herbert dropped back on 16-of-26 first downs and was successful more often than not. Given how well this approach worked, it’s hard to imagine Jim Harbaugh pulling back when the Chargers square off against the Raiders in 10 days. Herbert should work his way into the QB1 ranks for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d19-d332-a1fd-9f3f2ae00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
