<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 02:25:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a01-dfde-a1bd-5e8d41fd0000</link>
      <description>Also out was EDGE Chase Young (knee). Both Fuaga and Young did not practice last Wednesday, either. However, Fuaga did practice later in the week and went on to play in Week 2 while Young was sidelined again while still not practicing. Between the two, Fuaga is more likely to work his way back to play Week 3 against the Seahawks while it seems Young will still need more time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a01-dfde-a1bd-5e8d41fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a05-d93f-ad9d-5ac7305a0000</link>
      <description>An ineffective showing in Week 2 is now followed up by a foot injury for Charbonnet. He has led Kenneth Walker in touches the first two weeks of the season off the strength of his pass-blocking, but that could change quickly if his foot injury is major. Fantasy managers should stay tuned as we find out more information about the severity of Charbonnet’s foot while Kenneth Walker fantasy managers are on track to get a boost in Week 3 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a05-d93f-ad9d-5ac7305a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a14-dfde-a1bd-5e9d68550000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon missed Week 2 against the Steelers with a knee injury and now starts out Week 3 not practicing. Also out on Wednesday were S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) and S Julian Love (hamstring). Emmanwori has an ankle sprain that seems like a multi-week issue stemming from Week 1, while Love played through a groin injury last week and is now dealing with a hamstring. Needless to say, the Seahawks secondary is banged-up heading into Week 3 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a14-dfde-a1bd-5e9d68550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a18-d1b3-a5dd-5b794ca50000</link>
      <description>Horton caught his first career touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 2 win over the Steelers and has operated as the No. 3 wide receiver for the first two weeks of the season. He pops up on the injury report with a groin issue, though he did get in limited work on Wednesday. Horton is still tracking to play in Week 3, though he is not on fantasy radars yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a18-d1b3-a5dd-5b794ca50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder/ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a1e-d6a5-adff-fedf78d60000</link>
      <description>Jennings has been dealing with the shoulder injury since Week 1 and played through it in Week 2, but it is notable that an ankle issue was added to his designation. He began last week not practicing as well, but wound up playing to the tune of 10 targets and a touchdown in Week 2. With several offensive skill players hurt for the 49ers, Jennings is in the WR3 range if he plays in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a1e-d6a5-adff-fedf78d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf/rest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a26-d1b3-a5dd-5b776ed10000</link>
      <description>Also out was OT Trent Williams (knee/rest). As we mentioned when McCaffrey sat with a calf/rest designation last week, it is likely he will continue to show up with the same designation for the foreseeable future. As for Williams, he hurt his knee in Week 1 and played through it in Week 2. It is likely the same deal this week as the 49ers let the veteran rest and heal as much as possible before he plays in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a26-d1b3-a5dd-5b776ed10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a2e-d93f-ad9d-5aef509c0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ rookie second-round pick missed Wednesday’s practice session with a groin issue. Through two games, the 22-year-old has a 75.0 PFF grade, good for No. 18 among cornerbacks. If he cannot go on Sunday, Elijah Jones is in line for the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a2e-d93f-ad9d-5aef509c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Garrett Williams (knee) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a36-d93f-ad9d-5af7746c0000</link>
      <description>Williams suffered the knee injury in Week 2 against the Panthers and will be sidelined for the near future. Head coach Jonathan Gannon said Williams will be placed on injured reserve with a chance to return. Meanwhile, CB Max Melton (knee) was a limited practice participant. Losing Williams and potentially Will Johnson (groin) for Week 3 is a tough blow to the secondary, but Melton at least has a shot to play against an equally banged-up 49ers receiving group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a36-d93f-ad9d-5af7746c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>According to Broncos beat reporter Zac Stevens, head coach Sean Payton said RB RJ Harvey is “an important piece of what we’re doing.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a3b-dfde-a1bd-5ebf444b0000</link>
      <description>Harvey was a second round pick by the Broncos this year, but has seen just 11 carries and three targets through the first two games of the season. Veteran J.K. Dobbins has been the lead back, but Payton was insistent that Harvey is a key piece of the offense when speaking to the press Wednesday. We have yet to see Harvey utilized like an “important piece”, but rookies often require patience. Payton can be frustrating for fantasy managers with his skill player rotations, but more usage is on the horizon for Harvey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a3b-dfde-a1bd-5ebf444b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports’ Greg Auman reports Buccaneers OG Cody Mauch will require knee surgery that is expected to end his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a5f-d93f-ad9d-5adfc3ae0000</link>
      <description>Mauch, the Bucs’ starting right guard, injured his knee in the Week 2 victory over the Texans. Auman now reports the knee will require surgery, which is expected to sideline the 26-year-old for the remainder of the 2025 season. It is another brutal blow to the Bucs’ offensive line with Tristan Wirfs and Luke Goedeke also sidelined. Mauch will aim to come back for 2026 while the Bucs signed Dan Feeney off the Bills’ practice squad for depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a5f-d93f-ad9d-5adfc3ae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
