<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Velus Jones Jr. to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca1f-dd4c-afb9-efdfa0670000</link>
      <description>The Saints released Jones just two days ago. His presence on the practice squad gives them an emergency option for backup running back and kick return duties. He is not fantasy-relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca1f-dd4c-afb9-efdfa0670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) will not practice today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca35-def2-abdb-df7565000000</link>
      <description>Worthy practiced in full on Wednesday. This is likely just a rest day for Worthy, but his Friday participation level is obviously worth following. Worthy has logged WR2 and WR4 finishes since fully tearing his labrum during a shoulder dislocation in Week 1. If active, he will be a WR2 with upside in what should be a high-scoring game against the Lions on Sunday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca35-def2-abdb-df7565000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca3c-d94a-a79d-cb3d91650000</link>
      <description>The Falcons face the Bills on Monday night, so Thursday is the team’s first Week 6 practice. Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Mooney is still day-to-day despite having more than a full week to rehab the muscle strain. The Falcons were on bye in Week 5. Mooney injured his hamstring on September 28th, and initial reports suggested he is not expected to miss any time. He should be considered questionable to play at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca3c-d94a-a79d-cb3d91650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Taysom Hill has “been taking reps in that position certainly plenty through the last couple weeks and so he’s definitely available to be a backup quarterback.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca56-d94a-a79d-cb5fe9d10000</link>
      <description>In other words, should Spencer Rattler get hurt or benched, Hill could be a factor in what happens — it’s not just Tyler Shough anymore. We’d expect Hill’s work to grow a little this week, perhaps enough to cannibalize Kendre Miller and Alvin Kamara’s ceiling cases. It seems like Moore doesn’t have a limitation yet on the number of ways he’s envisioning using Hill and that makes him fantasy-interesting even if last week’s line is not exciting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca56-d94a-a79d-cb5fe9d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OC Greg Roman said he does not have a lead back between Hassan Haskins and Kimani Vidal for Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca52-d94a-a79d-cb5f13cf0000</link>
      <description>Per Roman, both Haskins and Vidal are going to be “big factors in the game,” though Roman also said, from a snap count standpoint, things “can go a bunch of different ways.” That fails to reassure. Our best guess is that Haskins will get a chance to establish himself as the team’s north-south rusher, while Vidal primarily handles passing down duties while mixing in as a rotational rusher. Fortunately, the Dolphins’ pushover defense could help both players produce usable FLEX results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca52-d94a-a79d-cb5f13cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) practiced in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca77-db72-a199-fa7f0ec40000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from the limited session he got in on Wednesday. Sanders looks to be trending towards playing against the Cowboys after missing Weeks 4 and 5. A horrific Cowboys pass defense makes him a defensible TE2, but it’s hard to recommend him coming off the injury until we see how the target share shakes out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca77-db72-a199-fa7f0ec40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Curtis Samuel (neck/ribs) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca7b-d94a-a79d-cb7f067f0000</link>
      <description>Samuel has been a bit of a nuisance for Buffalo’s main receivers, playing 41.7 percent of the snaps since returning in Week 4 and contributing three catches for 35 yards and a score in four targets. For fantasy purposes, it would be great if he’d sit. We have a hard time believing that will happen off a limited tag on the Thursday before Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca7b-d94a-a79d-cb7f067f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f7-dd4c-afb9-eff7f8250000</link>
      <description>Kincaid was seen wearing a red non-contact jersey at Thursday’s practice. While we would prefer Kincaid to be healthy, he has consistently played through injuries in the past and his early-week participation is promising for his Week 6 availability. The Bills face the Falcons on Monday night, giving Kincaid an extra day to rehab the injured muscle. He remains a TE1 if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f7-dd4c-afb9-eff7f8250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca7d-d94a-a79d-cb7d60d80000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back full practices seem to have Pierce in line to be removed from the injury report tomorrow, we’ll see if there are any steps left on the protocol after he missed two weeks to a concussion suffered in Week 3. Pierce does have some FLEX appeal against the Cardinals in a bye-week shortened slate should he be active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca7d-d94a-a79d-cb7d60d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Jalen Ramsey (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca32-d94a-a79d-cb3f8fa90000</link>
      <description>Ramsey is looking like a long shot to play in Week 6 against the Browns. He sat out Wednesday’s practice as well. The Steelers’ defense was thought to be a team strength entering the season, but myriad injuries and age are beginning to take their toll. If Ramsey can practice tomorrow, he will have a chance to play, though that seems unlikely at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca32-d94a-a79d-cb3f8fa90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
