<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Willis (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 17 against the Ravens. He completed 18-of-21 passes for 288 yards with a touchdown while rushing for 60 yards and two scores before exiting.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6309-dc7a-af9b-efbfc7ab0000</link>
      <description>Willis appeared to aggravate the shoulder injury that he suffered in Week 16 against the Bears. The signal-caller was playing exceptionally well prior to the injury, but looked to be in significant pain after stretching the arm on a throw to the outside. Clayton Tune has taken over at quarterback. It did appear that Willis was set to return to this contest, but with the game out of hand, Tune remained in the game. He could start in Week 18 against the Vikings with that game having no meaning, but it’ll be at least somewhat dependent on Jordan Love (concussion) and his health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6309-dc7a-af9b-efbfc7ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Huntley completed 16-of-20 passes for 107 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ 41-24, Week 17 win over the Ravens, adding eight rushes for 60 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631a-d56e-afff-e7faa9d30000</link>
      <description>Huntley got the start with Lamar Jackson’s back contusion keeping him from playing, and his main goal was handing the football to Derrick Henry (36/216/4) and getting out of the way. Mission accomplished. He did do a nice job connecting on his short-yardage passes, and was rewarded with a touchdown pass to Zay Flowers late in the contest. Huntley will be tasked with being a game manager in Week 18 against the Steelers if Jackson can’t go, and there’s a smidgen of upside because of his ability to make some plays as as a runner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631a-d56e-afff-e7faa9d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 36 times for 216 yards and four touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-630f-d56e-afff-e7effa670000</link>
      <description>Henry now has more 200 yard rushing games (7) than any player in NFL history. He wasn’t targeted in the passing game, because why would you need to? Three of his touchdowns came in the first half, and he routinely ran over completely overmatched Green Bay defenders in yet another impressive effort for the 31-year-old. Keaton Mitchell was somehow able to get nine carries for 31 yards as his (beyond) clear backup on a day where Baltimore rushed for 307 total yards in Lambeau Field. Even if Lamar Jackson (back) returns for Week 18 against the Steelers, Henry is going to be the focal point of the Ravens’ offense for that contest. He has to be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-630f-d56e-afff-e7effa670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 17 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</link>
      <description>Flowers was just able to get across the pylon on a connection with Tyler Huntley in the fourth quarter. The 25-year-old was a bit of an afterthought during Saturday’s contest, but that was true for every Raven not named Drrick Henry. He should again be the top option in the passing attack whether it’s Huntley or Lamar Jackson (back) throwing him the ball in Week 18 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 4-of-4 targets for 28 yards in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</link>
      <description>Andrews’ biggest play was drawing the Packers offsides while lining up under center on a fourth-and-inches play late in the contest. The Ravens only threw the ball for 107 yards in this contest, so there wasn’t much chance for Andrews, Isaiah Likely (3/27) or any of the Baltimore receivers in this one. He’ll be back in Week 18 against the Steelers in a game that’s meaning will be determined by what happens in Week 17 between Pittsburgh and the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins didn’t catch his only target in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-632d-d56e-afff-e7ed87bb0000</link>
      <description>Hopkins got a target in the end zone from Tyler Huntley that wasn’t partciularly close. The Ravens’ passing game did almost nothing in this contest, but didn’t need to with Derrick Henry scoring four times and rushing for 216 yards. Hopkins likely will have a similiar amount of chances in Week 18 against the Steelers even if Lamar Jackson (back) returns to action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-632d-d56e-afff-e7ed87bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 5-of-6 targets for 113 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6331-d56e-afff-e7f9580d0000</link>
      <description>Watson scored on a 39-yard connection with Malik Willis on the Packers’ first drive of the game. The two made a few more connections in the contest in a solid effort where Watson didn’t appear to be bothered by his shoulder or the illness he picked up earlier in the week. Watson and the Packers get a game with essentially zero playoff ramifications against the Vikings in Week 18 to end the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6331-d56e-afff-e7f9580d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed four times for three yards in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens while adding one catch for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6336-d56e-afff-e7fe790a0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was off the injury report after dealing with knee and ankle issues in previous weeks, but whether it was due to those ailments, a faltering offensive line or a great effort from the Baltimore front — likely a combination of all three — the 27-year-old tailback was able to get nothing done. The Packers have nothing to play for in Week 18 against the Lions, so no one should be surprised if it is Emmanuel Wilson (3/16) who gets most of the touches in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6336-d56e-afff-e7fe790a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 3-of-3 targets for 62 yards in the Packers’ Week 17 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633b-dc7a-af9b-efbf3b3b0000</link>
      <description>Doubs did most of the damage on a 40-yard connection in the first quarter with Malik Willis that set up a touchdown pass to Christian Watson. The 25-year-old played fiddle between Watson and Jayden Reed for the rest of the contest, but fantasy managers at least got the one long reception. He’ll be back at it in Week 18 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633b-dc7a-af9b-efbf3b3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed caught 4-of-4 targets for 41 yards in the Packers’ Week 18 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633d-d968-a19b-7bfd29170000</link>
      <description>Reed picked up the overwhelming majority of the yards on a 30-yard pass from Malik Willis. The 25-year-old was second among Packers’ receivers in targets behind the six to Christian Watson, but he picked up just 11 yards on his other three receptions. Reed and the Packers will finish off the regular season against the Vikings in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-633d-d968-a19b-7bfd29170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
