<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Hollywood Brown (ankle) is “taking it slow and we don’t want any setbacks” when asked about Brown playing in Kansas City’s final preseason game on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be6f-d45c-a7fc-be7fbccd0000</link>
      <description>Brown returned to practice today and all the starters are tentatively planning to play at least a little bit in Kansas City’s third preseason game. It looks like Brown should be fully healthy for the start of the regular season, even if he doesn’t chance playing on the ankle on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be6f-d45c-a7fc-be7fbccd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Commanders and Brian Robinson have mutually decided he will not play in Monday’s preseason game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be71-d05a-adda-bef3ced50000</link>
      <description>This comes a day after it was announced that the Commanders have explored potential trades for the fourth-year back. Robinson is seemingly being phased out of the offense in favor of rookie seventh-rounder Jacory Croskey-Merritt and veterans like Austin Ekeler, Jeremy McNichols, and Chris Rodriguez, and struggled late last season. During the final seven games of the regular season, Robinson rushed 86 times for 338 yards (3.9 YPC) and two touchdowns, and managed just 129 yards on 36 carries in the postseason. Croskey-Merritt has turned in an impressive camp and has been touted by some beat writers as the potential favorite to lead the backfield at some point in the season. Should Robinson be traded or cut, that could pave the way for JCM to see a meaningful workload early on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be71-d05a-adda-bef3ced50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said Justin Jefferson (hamstring) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be9d-d90d-a5bd-bedf23700000</link>
      <description>Jefferson hasn’t done much since suffering a mild hamstring strain at the start of camp. The Vikings are doing everything to ensure their WR1 is in good health before the start of the season, but will begin ramping him up with Week 1 less than a month away. O’Connell said last week that Jefferson was “definitely progressing” in his recovery, so Monday’s return marks another step in the right direction. His absence during camp due to a soft-tissue injury is concerning, but the Vikings could have just been exercising extreme caution in this instance. It sounds like he’ll be on track to start in Week 1 barring any setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be9d-d90d-a5bd-bedf23700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (abdominal) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be9e-d90d-a5bd-bedfa26c0000</link>
      <description>The offseason Steelers hype for Austin as a No. 2 wideout was derailed in training camp by an abdominal injury. Austin is working at returning punts today and likely is not 100 percent just yet, but should be by the end of the season. He’s nothing more than a late-round dart throw in standard drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be9e-d90d-a5bd-bedfa26c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said Jalen Nailor (hand) is “week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea0-df63-a199-ffabfede0000</link>
      <description>He did not rule out the possibility of surgery when asked. Nailor was set up to have a big role in Minnesota’s first few games with Jordan Addison suspended, but it sounds like this hand injury has put that in jeopardy. If Nailor does miss time, the Vikings might have to volume-load T.J. Hockenson in early-season action as they likely can’t rely on anyone else in their non-Justin Jefferson receiver room to play well right away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea0-df63-a199-ffabfede0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Tetairoa McMillan (hamstring) might not play on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea6-d90d-a5bd-beff95bd0000</link>
      <description>McMillan did not practice today and it is regarded as a “minor” hamstring ailment, but it would make no sense for the Panthers to risk his health in the third week of the preseason anyway. We have no concerns about McMillan’s status for Week 1 at this point. The volume he’s set to command in what could be an improved Carolina passing attack should make him a viable WR3 in his rookie season, at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea6-d90d-a5bd-beff95bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Andy Dalton (elbow) is dealing with a “muscle issue” and “could play if this was the regular season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea9-d90d-a5bd-befb132b0000</link>
      <description>Sounds like Bryce Perkins was just signed to sop up some reps on Thursday ahead of cutdowns with Dalton and Bryce Young unlikely to play. Dalton should carry on as Young’s backup again in 2025 assuming Canales’ forecast for his injury holds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea9-d90d-a5bd-befb132b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said De’Von Achane (calf) is unlikely to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea9-d05a-adda-beabdee90000</link>
      <description>It’s important to note that McDaniel said the decision to keep Achane out of practice this week is “preventative in nature,” which seemingly downplays the severity of this injury. Achane was reported last week to have suffered a “soft tissue lower-body injury” that would keep him out between “days and weeks,” but it doesn’t sound like he’ll be at risk of missing Week 1 based on McDaniel’s update. We’ll have to revisit this the next time McDaniel provides an update on his RB1’s availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bea9-d05a-adda-beabdee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said there’s a chance Darren Waller could return to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beab-d90d-a5bd-befb18730000</link>
      <description>McDaniel said 12 days ago that Waller was a week away from practicing, so we won’t expect too much here. The veteran tight end came out of retirement to join the Dolphins in late July and was reported to be in “tremendous shape,” but his camp-long absence suggests there’s some work to do to get him ready for the season. Waller’s fantasy outlook is tough to predict, but there’s little reason to think he’ll be more than a league-average tight end at this point in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beab-d90d-a5bd-befb18730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Barrows believes that “if [Christian McCaffrey] is not back to his 2023 form, he’s pretty close to it.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beb1-d45c-a7fc-bebb4d780000</link>
      <description>With a lot of uncertainty in the wideout corps due to injuries, Barrows expects the 49ers “will lean on” McCaffrey and George Kittle early in the passing game. That is music to the ears of fantasy managers. McCaffrey being in tip-top shape is also huge news — though we’re sure we’ll see plenty of him on the injury report as always this year. The fact that he objectively looks close to 2023 form after a short 2024 comeback where he didn’t appear to be himself is great news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-beb1-d45c-a7fc-bebb4d780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
