<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 5-of-7 targets for 55 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf919af0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was flagged for a personal foul in the second half after poking a Packers defender in the eye through the face mask, an act that continued to spur heated interactions between the two teams. He was also flagged for offensive pass interference on a comeback screen in the first quarter, overshadowing his touchdown for real-world football in the process. Metcalf remains a low-volume WR2 that is heavily reliant on touchdowns, but the Steelers simply have very little competition to targets at the moment. That could change as the trade deadline approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23f8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf919af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 2-of-3 targets for 17 yards in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23fc-d245-adfb-b7ffa4ae0000</link>
      <description>Smith saw sparse usage throughout as the team continued its four-man rotation at tight end. He narrowly missed connecting with quarterback Aaron Rodgers on a deep seam in the fourth quarter that could have padded his counting stats for fantasy managers, but the ball fell to the turf just out of the sprawling reach of the veteran tight end. Smith remains off fantasy radars in all but the deepest formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23fc-d245-adfb-b7ffa4ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 3-of-4 targets for 13 yards in the Steelers’ Week 8 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ff-d5d8-a3ff-fbffb2ec0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth came down hard on his neck and head on the first play from scrimmage in the third quarter and had to be helped to the sideline, ultimately returning two series later to finish the game. It is unclear if he was checked for a concussion as it appeared to be his neck that bore the brunt of the fall. It remains difficult for Freiermuth to carry legitimate fantasy value while splitting time with three other tight ends in Pittsburgh, even after his two-touchdown showing a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-23ff-d5d8-a3ff-fbffb2ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports free agent WR Tyler Lockett is expected to sign with the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-259c-dab4-a3fb-bffc79330000</link>
      <description>The Raiders were considered a potential landing spot for Lockett earlier in the offseason after the team went out and hired Pete Carroll and traded for Geno Smith. Lockett caught 10 passes for 70 yards in seven games with the Titans and requested his release after being slowly phased out of the offense. In his final game with the team, he ran just nine routes, even with Calvin Ridley sidelined. Lockett’s chemistry with Geno should bode well for the offense, and it wouldn’t be surprising if he eventually earned snaps over Dont’e Thornton and Jack Bech, who have struggled out of the gate. Even if he earns a significant role, from a fantasy perspective, Lockett won’t have more than WR4/WR5 upside at this stage in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-259c-dab4-a3fb-bffc79330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Saquon Barkley’s groin injury is not believed to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-25ac-deb1-a39b-25ae21ae0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport said his understanding of Barkley’s injury is that “had the game been a little closer, it is likely that Saquon would have returned” in the Week 8 win over the Giants. It’s a good sign for Barkley, who now heads into a Week 9 bye before returning in Week 10 to face the Packers. We’ll see if we get a clearer update from the team during the bye, but it sounds like there’s little to worry about here. If Barkley were to miss time, Tank Bigsby, who erupted for 104 yards on nine carries after Barkley exited Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-25ac-deb1-a39b-25ae21ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Cam Skattebo will miss the remainder of the season with a dislocated ankle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-25c7-d5d8-a3ff-fde73cd40000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport confirmed on Monday what we already expected after Skattebo exited Week 8’s game against the Eagles. The rookie running back who underwent surgery on his ankle yesterday will be out for the remainder of the season, but according to Rapoport, if all goes according to plan, Skattebo should be back “with no issues for next year.” It’s a brutal blow for a Skattebo and a Giants team that was beginning to enjoy some offensive success under the rookie running back and fellow rookie, QB Jaxson Dart. Skattebo’s season ends with a rushing line of 101-410-5 and a receiving line of 24-207-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-25c7-d5d8-a3ff-fde73cd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Bills fear DT Ed Oliver suffered a torn biceps in Week 8’s win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2625-d245-adfb-b77f21580000</link>
      <description>If the worst is confirmed, this injury would likely end Oliver’s regular season and perhaps his postseason. The veteran lineman will undergo an MRI to confirm, but this is shaping up to be a tough blow to the Bills’ defensive unit. Oliver had just worked his way back from injury in Week 6, and was playing at a high level in the three games he appeared in. On the year, Oliver has totaled 12 tackles, seven TFLs, and three sacks to go with one forced fumble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2625-d245-adfb-b77f21580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions designated LB Malcolm Rodriguez (knee) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2631-dab4-a3fb-bf7136cd0000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz was first to report the decision. The fourth-year linebacker, affectionately known as “Rodrigo,” suffered a torn ACL in Week 13 of last season and continued rehab throughout the offseason. Head coach Dan Campbell said back in June that Rodriguez was most likely looking at a November return, and with his 21-day window now open, the team will be poised to activate him some time over the next three weeks. Rodriguez totaled 43 tackles, two sacks, and one pass breakup in 10 games last season for the Lions while making six starts. Once he returns, he should step in to a significant role for a Lions defense that currently ranks 11th in points allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2631-dab4-a3fb-bf7136cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports tests confirmed a high-ankle sprain for Browns LB Carson Schwesinger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-263c-d5d8-a3ff-ff7d43350000</link>
      <description>Now that we have the diagnosis, it’s safe to assume the rookie second-rounder is likely looking at a multi-week absence. Schwesinger has stepped in to make an immediate impact for the Browns’ defense this season, leading the team with 64 tackles while also tallying one interception, one sack, and four TFLs. The Browns are now entering their Week 9 bye. If they believe Schwesinger,who will be reevaluated after the bye, can return inside of the four-game minimum he would be required to miss on injured reserve, it’s possible they opt to keep him on the roster in hopes of a return in 2-3 weeks. Regardless, his loss is a massive one for a defensive unit that has been among the league’s best despite their 2-6 record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-263c-d5d8-a3ff-ff7d43350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars HC Liam Coen said the team has “no plans on moving Brian Thomas Jr. at all.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2661-deb1-a39b-276ffa840000</link>
      <description>Coen is looking to clear the air after The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reported on Sunday that the Jaguars are “listening to calls” for the second-year receiver. Even if true, Russini also noted that it was “highly unlikely” the team would trade BTJ after a rookie season that featured a 87-1,282-10 line, but after a slow start to his 2025 campaign, partly due to injuries, there could be something to the idea of the team being open to trading him should a “godfather offer” come across the table. With the NFL trade deadline just over a week away, we should have our answer on BTJ’s future with the Jaguars soon, but Coen’s remarks on Monday sound pretty concrete. We wouldn’t expect the Jags to trade Thomas this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2661-deb1-a39b-276ffa840000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
