<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid told reporters to “move on from it” when pressed about the status of Josh Simmons (personal).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029f-da18-a39a-da9f3a480000</link>
      <description>We don’t want to trivialize whatever Simmons is going through, the only information that has surfaced so far is that he returned home to San Diego. Reid’s words make it clear that Simmons should remain sidelined for the forseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029f-da18-a39a-da9f3a480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said David Njoku (knee) remains “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02a2-df81-ab9b-7ee7aa2c0000</link>
      <description>Njoku’s practice status will be the guiding light here regarding Week 8’s game against the Patriots, but he called Njoku day-to-day before last week and Njoku did not practice once. Until we see positive news here, it should be assumed that Harold Fannin will continue to operate as Cleveland’s No. 1 tight end and be in line for low-end TE1 duties against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02a2-df81-ab9b-7ee7aa2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs DT Omarr Norman-Lott suffered a torn ACL in Week 7’s win over the Raiders and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b2-df81-ab9b-7ef71d190000</link>
      <description>Norman-Lott exited in the third quarter of Sunday’s game. He remained down on the field for several minutes before eventually being helped to the sideline by teammates, but now the rookie second-rounder will set his sights to a return in 2026. Norman-Lott appeared in five games for the Chiefs this season, totaling five tackles, one sack, and one TFL. Assuming his recovery goes as planned, he should be ready to go around the time training camp starts up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b2-df81-ab9b-7ef71d190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Darren Waller (pectoral) is “week to week” and isn’t expected to require surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b7-df81-ab9b-7ef7c8f40000</link>
      <description>Waller is reportedly dealing with a pectoral strain. It’s all fun and games when Waller is catching touchdowns, but the cost of what it does to his body is: We have to blurb him 15 more times before he gets on the field again. Oh, it’s probably not fun for him either, we shouldn’t minimize that. Anyway, given Waller’s injury history, this will probably take multiple weeks. The passing game tree in Miami is already pretty concentrated — maybe this pushes Malik Washington into a few more six-yard catches, enough to be a PPR scam as a FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b7-df81-ab9b-7ef7c8f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said the team will continue using a two-back approach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</link>
      <description>Chuba Hubbard outsnapped Rico Dowdle 38-33, but Dowdle out-touched Hubbard 18-16. Six teams on bye probably squeezes each of them into the low-end RB2 ranks against the Bills in Week 8, though perhaps the Bills can squeeze the box tight enough to create an Andy Dalton pass funnel coming out of the bye. It’s clear that Carolina’s best approach is through the ground, and that Dowdle is here to stay as either a pest (complimentary) or a pest (derogatory) depending on who you have rostered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Brock Bowers (knee) and Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) should be “ready to go” after the team’s Week 8 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02cc-df81-ab9b-7ecfb0730000</link>
      <description>It was a reasonable expectation after both were mostly shut down in practice all week. Viewers who tuned into watch Vegas play the Chiefs were treated to what happens without the two as Vegas struggled to even do elementary offensive concepts. While it’s good that both players seem healthy enough to come back in Week 9, neither player profiles as a top-tier option while working for this inconsistent offense. Bowers is probably a mid-tier TE1 until we see his 2024 form again, and Meyers is closer to a WR3 than a WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02cc-df81-ab9b-7ecfb0730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colts EDGE Samson Ebukam “is expected to miss multiple weeks with an MCL injury.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02d8-da18-a39a-dadb01a70000</link>
      <description>According to Fowler, Ebukam is seeking a second opinion, but it doesn’t sound like he’ll be on track to play any time in the coming weeks. The 30-year-old pass rusher was injured in Sunday’s win over the Chargers, and has tallied two sacks and and 14 tackles this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02d8-da18-a39a-dadb01a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports Commanders DE Dorance Armstong “will be out indefinitely” after suffering a knee injury in Week 7’s loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02dc-d651-a9df-6bddaf0d0000</link>
      <description>Armstrong, who is seeking a second opinion on his injury, has been playing well for the Commanders this season, totaling 24 tackles, seven TFLs, and 5.5 sacks in just seven games. His loss is a tough blow to a Commanders defense that has been among the league’s worst through the first month and a half, as they currently rank 21st in points allowed and have allowed the sixth-most yards. We’ll likely get a more definite timeline on Armstrong’s absence in the coming days but it sounds like he could be looking at a multi-week absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02dc-d651-a9df-6bddaf0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said Tua Tagovailoa will remain the Dolphins starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02da-df81-ab9b-7edf86320000</link>
      <description>It’s not like he has any better options with Zach Wilson demoted to third string and the green Quinn Ewers behind Tagovailoa. After back-to-back three-pick games, including a late-game benching in a blowout on Sunday, the seat is hot for both McDaniel and Tagovailoa. In-game benching is certainly a possibility in a matchup against what has been a stellar Falcons secondary in Week 8. Tagovailoa is only a marginal superflex starter this week with the added risk, even with six teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02da-df81-ab9b-7edf86320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans activated DL Denico Autry (knee) from the reserve/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02de-da18-a39a-dadf3c590000</link>
      <description>He’ll play in tonight’s game against the Seahawks, as will rookie safety Jaylen Reed, who was also activated off PUP today. Autry is no spring chicken at 35, but he should give the Texans some additional inside pass rush ability going forward and make their defense a little harder to work against on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02de-da18-a39a-dadf3c590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
