<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released RB Ke’Shawn Vaughn.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e23d-db7b-a5dd-e23d936f0000</link>
      <description>The veteran back didn’t play in the preseason at all despite the amount of injuries the 49ers running back room dealt with. He’s a likely practice squad candidate after playing with the 49ers last season. The 49ers also waived/injured QB Carter Bradley and QB Tanner Mordecai, while waiving (regular) DL Jaylon Allen and DL Shakel Brown. Finally, they sent OL Isaiah Prince to injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e23d-db7b-a5dd-e23d936f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (foot) resumed practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e240-de13-afdc-e6cbca1d0000</link>
      <description>Great news. Jackson is practicing as scheduled. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters on Saturday that Jackson was expected to return today, “unless he doesn’t want to.” Evidently, he wanted to. Fantasy managers can continue drafting Jackson as an overall QB1 candidate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e240-de13-afdc-e6cbca1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings (calf) missed practice again on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e23e-db7b-a5dd-e23e72e60000</link>
      <description>While there have been reports Jennings could be placed on IR while his contract dispute with the 49ers and calf injury remain, the team made a flurry of roster moves Monday without placing the 28-year-old receiver on injured reserve. Still, Jennings isn’t practicing with less than two weeks before the 49ers’ first game. While it doesn’t have to be dramatic, this saga needs a conclusion sometime soon. Jennings is still in line for a big role in the 49ers’ passing game if he and the 49ers can get on the same page before the season starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e23e-db7b-a5dd-e23e72e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said, QB Will Howard (hand) will practice in full “soon.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e21c-d332-a1fd-f63e31b80000</link>
      <description>Howard is “moving in the right direction” as he rehabs the broken bone in his throwing hand. He currently sits in the QB3 spot on the Steelers’ unofficial depth chart. Tomlin reportedly “doesn’t know yet” if LB Nick Herbig (hamstring) will be ready for Week 1. ESPN’s Brooke Pryor adds that LB Alex Highsmith (groin) said he is playing Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e21c-d332-a1fd-f63e31b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Bengals have restarted negotiations with DE Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e240-d332-a1fd-f6767e300000</link>
      <description>Schultz adds that the two sides are exploring “a more unique avenue” and that there is “cautious optimism” the two sides can get a deal done on an extension in short order. This has been one of the more befuddling contract negotiations of the offseason as the two sides have been seemingly far off from any real headway. The Bengals have gone so far as exploring trade options for their All-Pro defensive end, with the Patriots reportedly offering a premium pick for his services. Through it all, Hendrickson remains on the Bengals’ payroll, for the time being, and the two sides have reportedly reignited negotiations with an aim on keeping Hendrickson in Cincinnati this season. Schultz also stated that the Bengals have explored giving Hendrickson more money in 2025 while still allowing his contract to expire after the season. Stay tuned, this one could drag on further.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e240-d332-a1fd-f6767e300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews (undisclosed) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e25c-db7b-a5dd-e25c21460000</link>
      <description>Andrews reportedly missed practice on Sunday as well. On Monday, he was seen working with a trainer off to the side, running routes and at times sprinting half the field’s length. The Ravens tend to share injury details minimally, so info may be difficult to come by. There is no reason to think he will miss Week 1 at this time. He’s a TE1 until further notice. Isaiah Likely (foot), Jaire Alexander (knee) and Chidobe Awuzie (undisclosed) also sat out team drills. Awuzie was seen working alongside Andrews, off to the side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e25c-db7b-a5dd-e25c21460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said OT Alaric Jackson will progress to team drills next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e25b-dbe3-a9bb-f25b24020000</link>
      <description>Jackson has been a massive question mark for the Rams this offseason after developing blood clots in June but avoided the PUP and NFI lists last month. The most recent update indicates he could be ready for the start of the regular season, which would be a significant boost to the protection of reeling veteran quarterback Matthew Stafford. Stafford has been dealing with back issues all offseason with the team recently stating the intent is to “keep him upright” in Week 1 against the Texans. Jackson could go a long way in accomplishing that goal. It’ll still be a “wait and see” approach with Jackson but he currently appears to be trending in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e25b-dbe3-a9bb-f25b24020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans waived WR Jha’Quan Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e249-d332-a1fd-f67f6dfc0000</link>
      <description>The 2024 sixth-round pick was crowded out by a new GM who brought in a pair of fourth-round picks. Jackson did not play in the preseason. The Titans also waived: WR TJ Sheffield, DT Josiah Bronson, DT TJ Smith, OLB Desmond Evans, ILB Amari Burney, CB Jalen Kimber, CB Clarence Lewis, CB Jermari Harris, CB Davion Ross, S Julius Wood, and S Joshuah Bledsoe. They released DE Joe Gaziano, G Arlington Hambright, and C Sam Mustipher while putting a waived/injured designation on Matt Landers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e249-d332-a1fd-f67f6dfc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Chad Graff believes TreVeyon Henderson could get “half the carries, if not more” in the Patriots’ backfield.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e276-dbe3-a9bb-f2778ec50000</link>
      <description>Henderson is cited by Graff in this piece as already being New England’s best offensive weapon and also notes that Henderson’s ability to run between the tackles “has surprised even the highest levels of the team brass.” It’s hard to believe the Patriots won’t find a way to make Henderson a real fantasy football contributor this year, perhaps as early as Week 1. A big role for Henderson would make the road to fantasy viability much tougher for Rhamondre Stevenson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e276-dbe3-a9bb-f2778ec50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released RB Royce Freeman.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e27b-dbe3-a9bb-f27bec040000</link>
      <description>Freeman had only joined the Bears last week — the veteran will probably find a practice squad by the time the week is over. The Bears also waived DB Millard Bradford, DL Xavier Carlton, DB Alex Cook, LB Power Echols, DB Kaleb Hayes, QB Austin Reed, RB Ian Wheeler, and TE Joel Wilson. Additionally they released DB Tre Flowers and OL Joshua Miles, and placed DB Zah Frazier on the NFI list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e27b-dbe3-a9bb-f27bec040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
