<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released DT Casey Rogers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e755-db7b-a5dd-e75544830000</link>
      <description>Rogers was signed in May after being waived by the Giants. He’s a practice squad candidate who could see time with the Bills if he doesn’t procure a job with a new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e755-db7b-a5dd-e75544830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released S Darrick Forrest.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-db7b-a5dd-e7868cd60000</link>
      <description>Forrest played extensively throughout the preseason, which was a bad sign. He registered four tackles for his efforts. Forrest will likely sign onto a practice squad, if not an active roster elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-db7b-a5dd-e7868cd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Raiders aren’t looking to trade Jakobi Meyers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e78d-dbe3-a9bb-f7dfd6200000</link>
      <description>Meyers, who requested a trade yesterday, apparently remains a heavy part of Las Vegas’ plans for the season. Perhaps he’ll get a contract adjustment in the coming days. Schefter said that a team reached out to discuss Meyers and the Raiders weren’t willing to pick up salary and aren’t looking to trade their talented slot receiver. We’ll see how the situation unfolds but it sounds like Meyers can still be drafted as if he’ll be Vegas’ slot receiver for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e78d-dbe3-a9bb-f7dfd6200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints placed TE Foster Moreau (knee) on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e791-de13-afdc-e7db20370000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four games, as expected. Moreau didn’t participate in the preseason or training camp and is no guarantee to come back when first eligible. He started 17 games last year and had 32 catches for 413 yards and five scores. Juwan Johnson figures to be New Orleans’ starting tight end this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e791-de13-afdc-e7db20370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers released OG Michael Jordan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e793-de13-afdc-e7db41800000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers also released WR Garrett Greene and DL Adam Gotsis and waived LB Antonio Grier, DL C.J. Brewer and Tyrek Funderburk. FOX Sports’ Greg Auman reports, “Grier, Funderburk should have injury designations.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e793-de13-afdc-e7db41800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers released WR Hunter Renfrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b4-db7b-a5dd-e7b4b3350000</link>
      <description>Renfrow looked healthy in training camp, but ultimately couldn’t crack the Panthers roster. Entering his age-30 season after recovering from a bout of colitis, Renfrow has a chance to catch on elsewhere. It wouldn’t be surprising if he found a 53-man roster spot by the end of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b4-db7b-a5dd-e7b4b3350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints announced QB Spencer Rattler as the Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e775-db7b-a5dd-e775e0e60000</link>
      <description>The second-year quarterback wins the preseason quarterback battle over second-round rookie Tyler Shough, although he’ll need to improve on the lowly 57% completion rate and four-to-five touchdown-to-interception ratio he held in his rookie campaign in order to hold the job deep into the season. Either way, the league’s final quarterback battle comes to an end less than two weeks until the 2025 regular season kicks off. The Saints could be in trouble offensively this year considering the state of the quarterback depth chart, with a potential opportunity on tap to “tank for Archie.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e775-db7b-a5dd-e775e0e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers released RB Nyheim Miller-Hines.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e70d-de13-afdc-e7cf3b240000</link>
      <description>Miller-Hines played in all of the Chargers’ preseason games, including the Hall of Fame game. He rushed 21 times for 65 yards and one fumble, caught 3-of-6 targets for 13 yards, averaged 25.7 yards per kick return and 4.7 yards per punt return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e70d-de13-afdc-e7cf3b240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks released WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-dbe3-a9bb-f7d3e5800000</link>
      <description>Not a big surprise, as Valdes-Scantling didn’t impress in camp after signing his one-year deal, and rookie WR Tory Horton had usurped the wideout to be the third wide receiver to begin the 2025 campaign. The 30-year-old will likely find a new club in the coming days, but at a salary nowhere close to the $4 million he signed for with Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e782-dbe3-a9bb-f7d3e5800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers waived RB Raheem Blackshear.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b9-de13-afdc-e7fb0ca40000</link>
      <description>A good kick returner hits the wire with an injury settlement. The Panthers will move forward with Trevor Etienne and Jimmy Horn Jr. for punts and kickoffs this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7b9-de13-afdc-e7fb0ca40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
