<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) was limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeda-da18-a39b-fedbcc010000</link>
      <description>Harrison was limited yesterday as well. Today, Harrison sported a yellow non-contact jersey while participating in team drills, as is standard for players in phase four (club-based, non-contact drills) of the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol. Harrison is close to returning, but he must remain setback-free and graduate to full football activity before he can retake the field. He should be considered questionable at this time, though today’s limited, yellow-jersey session is encouraging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeda-da18-a39b-fedbcc010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Michael Wilson (foot) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eed7-d651-a9df-efd731210000</link>
      <description>Wilson is now in position to handle No. 2 wide receiver duties in Week 7 against the Packers. Fellow WR Zay Jones (knee) has not yet practiced this week and No. 1 WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) is making his way through the NFL’s concussion protocol. Wilson’s target-earning ability is unreliable, though, rendering him just a dart-throw FLEX in the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eed7-d651-a9df-efd731210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eee7-df81-ab9b-fee71ed30000</link>
      <description>Knight is now on track to handle lead-back duties for the Cardinals in Week 7 against the Packers. The Packers’ defensive front has dealt with a number of injuries this season, though the defense remains strong as a whole. Knight’s role warrants RB3/FLEX consideration, though a ceiling game may be difficult to come by.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eee7-df81-ab9b-fee71ed30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB JJ McCarthy (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eedb-df81-ab9b-fedfa2b30000</link>
      <description>That makes two straight limited sessions for McCarthy while QB Carson Wentz (shoulder) continues to practice in full. It sure looks like Wentz will be the Vikings’ Week 7 starter against his former team, the Eagles. Wentz can be viewed as a QB2 this week while McCarthy remains a worthwhile bench stash in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eedb-df81-ab9b-fedfa2b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (heel) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef05-d651-a9df-ef151bd70000</link>
      <description>On the plus side, fellow DT Jordan Davis (shoulder) continues to practice in full and LG Landon Dickerson (ankle) at least remained limited rather than experiencing a downgrade. Hopefully, this is just a pre-planned rest day for Carter, who sat out in the Eagles’ Week 6 upset loss to the Giants. The G-Men ran the ball aggressively, totaling 172 yards and four touchdowns on 48 carries. The Vikings could employ a similar game plan with RB Jordan Mason if Carter is again out this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef05-d651-a9df-ef151bd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed WR Treylon Burks, formerly of the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eefa-da18-a39b-fefbe6c20000</link>
      <description>Burks joins the Commanders’ practice squad on the same day that WRs Terry McLaurin (quad) and Deebo Samuel (heel) miss practice. McLaurin practiced on Wednesday but Samuel has remained sidelined at both practices. Burks has a chance to be called up on game day this weekend, though we imagine he would only be in on a small number of snaps. Burks does not need to be rostered at this time, though managers with ample bench space can stash him if they wish. Commanders WR Noah Brown (groin) was recently placed on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eefa-da18-a39b-fefbe6c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef05-d99b-a1dd-ff0da0060000</link>
      <description>Evans’ potential return comes at the right time. Fellow WRs Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) and Chris Godwin (fibula) are both dealing with injuries of their own, and Godwin has already been effectively ruled out. The Buccaneers face the Lions on Monday night, giving Evans an extra day to prepare. He will be a high-end WR2 this week, assuming his hamstring responds positively to his return to action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef05-d99b-a1dd-ff0da0060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (hamstring) said he “fully plans” to play in Week 7 against the Falcons after practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef18-da18-a39b-ff1b13e10000</link>
      <description>Kittle also told reporters that he fully tore his hamstring in Week 1 against the Seahawks. No wonder he was quickly ruled out in-game and placed on injured reserve two days later. While Kittle expects to play this week, he acknowledges it will ultimately be up to head coach Kyle Shanahan whether he makes his return. The 49ers’ pass-catching corps has been plagued by injuries this season, yet the 49ers are 4-2, with a 3-0 record against NFC West foes. If active, Kittle is an elite TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef18-da18-a39b-ff1b13e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef28-df81-ab9b-ffef266b0000</link>
      <description>Purdy remained limited while Mac Jones (knee/oblique) was upgraded to full on Thursday. Unless Purdy can practice in full tomorrow, Jones appears to be in line for another start this week. Jones has now thrown for more than 340 yards in consecutive games and gives the 49ers decent odds of holding the top spot in the NFC West. The 49ers face the Falcons on Sunday. Jones will be a QB2 if he is the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef28-df81-ab9b-ffef266b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared EDGE Trey Hendrickson, CB Cam Taylor-Britt, C Matt Lee, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Tanner Hudson and DT McKinnley Jackson inactive for Week 7 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef1d-d651-a9df-ef1dd1a20000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson is sidelined by a hip injury, though the Bengals fortunately get EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) back after a four-game absence. The Bengals’ offense lost two tight ends last week, with Hudson suffering a concussion and Mike Gesicki suffering a pectoral injury that landed him on injured reserve this week. Bengals TE Noah Fant is suddenly on the streaming TE1 radar as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef1d-d651-a9df-ef1dd1a20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
