<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed QB Sean Clifford, formerly of the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52d9-d051-a3df-7ef9d61c0000</link>
      <description>Clifford will join newly signed Mike White on the Cincy practice squad as Jake Browning takes over at quarterback for the remainder of the season following Joe Burrow’s season-ending toe injury. Brett Rypien is expected to be the team’s backup to Clifford. Either White or Clifford will serve as QB3. Clifford completed 9-of-17 attempts for 44 scoreless yards in three preseason outings for Green Bay last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52d9-d051-a3df-7ef9d61c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reports there’s “no guarantee” LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) plays in Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52f6-d606-a5db-5ef61b250000</link>
      <description>The Vikings offensive line has struggled mightily through two games with Darrisaw out and C Ryan Kelly dealing with a head injury. J.J. McCarthy, who’s out for multiple weeks with an ankle sprain, has been pressured on 40 percent of his drop backs through Week 2, the eighth highest rate in the NFL. No Darrisaw for Minnesota would be a potential problem for QB Carson Wentz as he takes over the Vikings offense in McCarthy’s absence. Pro Football Focus grades the Bengals’ pass rush as the 13th best in the league through two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-52f6-d606-a5db-5ef61b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) is “questionable at best” for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-533b-d654-a19b-d37b4ea90000</link>
      <description>Porter missed last week’s loss to the Seahawks while recovering from a hamstring injury and could sit out this week against the Patriots. The Steelers’ secondary has struggled to start the season, allowing the NFL’s sixth highest adjusted yards per attempt and the seventh highest accuracy rate. Porter’s absence could be a boon for Drake Maye in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-533b-d654-a19b-d37b4ea90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs DT Calijah Kancey is out for the remainder of the season with a torn pec.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-537c-dfa0-a9bb-dbfea9e30000</link>
      <description>Kancey sustained the injury on Monday night against the Texans. He’ll undergo surgery and miss the rest of the season. Kancey has 11.5 sacks over the past two seasons and has been a critical piece of Tampa’s stifling rush defense. The Bucs could be a little more vulnerable to opposing rushers with Kancey sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-537c-dfa0-a9bb-dbfea9e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OC Kevin Patullo said designed quarterback runs and keepers for Jalen Hurts “are coming.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5379-d051-a3df-7ff923450000</link>
      <description>Patullo said that they haven’t gotten to use Hurts like this because of how they’re being defended. He added: “Don’t worry.” It would go a long way towards avoiding disastrous lines such as Sunday’s if Hurts could actually get more involved in the running game, and with Saquon Barkley also struggling to generate space, perhaps that would help matters. The Eagles have already run 32 plays against eight or men in the box this year per TruMedia — they may need to prove that they can pass their way out of it before things get better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5379-d051-a3df-7ff923450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed C Nick Samac off the Ravens practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-537e-d606-a5db-5ffe5fdc0000</link>
      <description>Reinforcements are on the way for Carolina after they had to place Austin Corbett and Robert Hunt on the practice squad. Samac will back up Cade Mays and Chandler Zavala, who will get the first crack at starting roles on the interior line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-537e-d606-a5db-5ffe5fdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said he “expects” to get Christian Kirk (hamstring) back in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5392-d654-a19b-d3f2def90000</link>
      <description>We’ll monitor the practice status ahead of Week 3’s #RevengeGame against the Jaguars for Kirk, but it’s a promising sign that the coach is already declaring strongly that he’s expecting Kirk back. Braxton Berrios (also hamstring) is also expected back for the Texans, potentially forecasting a shakeup on a wideout depth chart that hasn’t given anything but Nico Collins incompletions (and one touchdown) to talk about so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5392-d654-a19b-d3f2def90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said OL Ben Bartch (ankle) will be out “for a while.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53b1-dfa0-a9bb-dbb79d660000</link>
      <description>Bartch suffered a high-ankle sprain and was replaced by Connor Colby, a seventh-round pick from Iowa who played fairly well in his debut. It sounds like Bartch will be headed to injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53b1-dfa0-a9bb-dbb79d660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (knee/PUP) said he anticipates returning to practice “in some capacity” when his window to do so opens up in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53bf-dfa0-a9bb-dbbfa9490000</link>
      <description>“I feel like if it was the NFC Championship Game tomorrow, I would be able to go out there and feel confident, for sure,” Watson told The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman. Watson’s window to return, whenever it opens, would be 21 days long. So reading between the lines, it sounds like Watson could be ready for a return sometime before Week 10. That’d be great news for the Packers, who are now sans Jayden Reed for the short-term future and haven’t gotten much from first-round pick Matthew Golden in the early going.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53bf-dfa0-a9bb-dbbfa9490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes Tyrone Tracy’s involvement as a kick returner “suggests a reduced offensive role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53c7-d606-a5db-5fd741dd0000</link>
      <description>“Tracy returned three kickoffs as a rookie, but that role ceased once he became the No. 1 running back in Week 5,” Duggan writes. Cam Skattebo appears to have taken over the top spot on the depth chart in Week 2. It’s hard to call Skattebo a sure fantasy weapon given how poorly the Giants are run blocking, but he sure seems like he’s at the head of a committee already. Skattebo should be a popular waiver wire target in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-53c7-d606-a5db-5fd741dd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
