<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 02:40:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bub Means was carted away from the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers after suffering an apparent lower-leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-964d-df63-a199-df6fd1ca0000</link>
      <description>A high-ankle sprain ended Means’ 2024 rookie year prematurely. Hopefully, this is unrelated. Before exiting, Means caught 1-of-2 targets for 12 yards. He is competing for the Saints’ No. 3 wide receiver role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-964d-df63-a199-df6fd1ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said Luther Burden “is working his tail off behind the scenes.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-965a-d05a-adda-beda6ba60000</link>
      <description>Johnson acknowledges that Burden’s play is “not where it needs to be yet,” but he “loves how hard” Burden is working. That’s encouraging. Burden is a talented, young player. If he can get up to speed, after missing significant practice time due to a strained hamstring, he could return flex value in year one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-965a-d05a-adda-beda6ba60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 7-of-11 passes for 53 yards and rushed three times for 22 yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9661-d05a-adda-bee3f5550000</link>
      <description>Rattler got the start but did little with it, producing two glaring low points. The Saints’ second drive started on the Chargers’ 17-yard line after the returner muffed the Saints’ punt. The drive stalled out with a turnover on downs at the Chargers’ one-yard line. Rattler later added a lost fumble to the box score when he was sacked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9661-d05a-adda-bee3f5550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Shough completed 15-of-22 passes for 165 yards, one touchdown and one interception and rushed once for three yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9647-d05a-adda-bec7aa420000</link>
      <description>Shough bounced back after throwing a bad pick-six by linking up with WR Mason Tipton, streaking down the left side of the field, for a 54-yard touchdown. Shough telegraphed his pass on the interception by staring directly at his intended receiver, which allowed Chargers CB Eric Rogers to easily jump the route. All in all, Shough outplayed Spencer Rattler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9647-d05a-adda-bec7aa420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OG Landon Dickerson was carted away from practice after suffering an apparent right leg injury on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9676-d90d-a5bd-b67fdf1b0000</link>
      <description>Dickerson underwent surgery to fix an injury in his left knee last year. This is unrelated, but it’s not good. Dickerson remained down for some time and was ultimately transported to the locker room via the cart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9676-d90d-a5bd-b67fdf1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendre Miller rushed six times for 15 yards and caught 1-of-1 targets for nine yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9684-d05a-adda-be86c6060000</link>
      <description>Miller added one kickoff return for 36 yards. It was an uninspiring performance but no one played better. He notably surrendered two snaps on the opening drive to WR-to-RB convert Velus Jones. Jones rushed once for minus-one yards, caught 4-of-4 targets for 16 yards and returned two kickoffs for 73 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9684-d05a-adda-be86c6060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden II caught 2-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Chargers’ preseason Week 1 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9681-d45c-a7fc-969b3f950000</link>
      <description>Gadsden and Tyler Conklin both logged three first-drive snaps and Conklin failed to secure his lone target. Gadsden has a long way to go before he becomes re-draft-relevant but he’s getting reps alongside Conklin, which is a good start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9681-d45c-a7fc-969b3f950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 0-of-1 targets in the Chargers’ preseason Week 1 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9695-d05a-adda-be97bff70000</link>
      <description>Not much to go on here. Harris played 28 snaps, including 5-of-6 on the first drive. Harris must make his mark if he wants to lock up the X-receiver role pre-Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9695-d05a-adda-be97bff70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeAndre Lambert-Smith caught 0-of-2 targets in the Chargers’ preseason Week 1 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-969c-df63-a199-dfbfeafc0000</link>
      <description>Lambert-Smith led the Chargers’ wide receiver corps with 30 snaps, and played 5-of-6 on the first drive. The intriguing rookie needs a bounce-back showing next week if he wants to earn an early-season role in the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-969c-df63-a199-dfbfeafc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Khalil Herbert (undisclosed) missed practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96e8-d90d-a5bd-b6fb1ae30000</link>
      <description>This is Herbert’s second missed practice. The Indy Star’s Nate Atkins commented on the matter, saying this is a “setback” for Herbert “in the RB3 battle.” Herbert is not worth stashing on fantasy benches at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-96e8-d90d-a5bd-b6fb1ae30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
