<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 21:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out QB Brock Purdy (toe) for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a162-d95b-addb-e96680760000</link>
      <description>The 49ers will also be without WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) and WR Ricky Pearsall (knee). All three failed to practice this week. Backup QB Mac Jones (knee) promisingly practiced in full every day. In Jones’ two prior starts this season, he completed 53-of-80 passes for 563 yards, four touchdowns and one interception and rushed seven times for five yards. He belongs on the QB2 radar against the Rams on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a162-d95b-addb-e96680760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) will not play in Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a166-d6e9-af9d-abf6c5390000</link>
      <description>Jauan Jennings was also ruled out. Pearsall is dealing with a nagging knee injury that flared up in his Week 4 matchup with the Jags. Per Kyle Shanahan, he felt “instability” in his knee after the game. Pearsall hasn’t practiced since. Kendrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson are now the team’s top receivers. Christian McCaffrey will look to set the record for targets by a running back tomorrow. Bourne is familiar with the Shanahan system and was already playing a part-time role before this week. He can be started as a WR5 for fantasy purposes, while Robinson and any other 49ers wideouts are best left on the bench.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a166-d6e9-af9d-abf6c5390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) will not play in Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a16d-deb6-a7fd-f3ff7dc40000</link>
      <description>Brock Purdy and Ricky Pearsall will both miss Thursday’s game versus the Rams as well. 49ers fans will be treated to Mac Jones peppering Kenrick Bourne and Demarcus Robinson with targets tomorrow. Jennings did not practice at all this week, putting his availability for Week 6 in question as well. The mini-bye after Thursday Night Football might be enough for some of the injured 9ers to get back on the field for next week’s game, but it’s simply too early to say right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a16d-deb6-a7fd-f3ff7dc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a178-d6e9-af9d-abf86cf40000</link>
      <description>Njoku had his reps monitored in practice because of the knee issue last week and was cleared from the injury report entirely on Friday. We expect the same routine this week. Coming off a three-target game, it will be next to impossible to trust Njoku in Dillon Gabriel’s first career start. Both he and Harold Fannin Jr. are TE2s for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a178-d6e9-af9d-abf86cf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that some league executives don’t expect the Eagles “to trade Brown in-season but said that it could be something to entertain in the offseason.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a16e-d95b-addb-e96ebd080000</link>
      <description>Per Fowler, “Brown’s contract comes with a dead cap hit of nearly $90 million,” which makes a trade difficult, “though not impossible if designated as a post-June 1 trade.” Brown’s “love-hate” relationship with the Eagles’ passing game is reportedly one of the league’s “worst-kept” secrets, and Brown’s frustration with the state of things is apparently “boiling over.” Fowler notes that “a few early-game connections” could assuage Brown’s concerns, but the relationship could be heading for a split down the road. For now, we are left hoping that the Eagles feature Brown early in the game against the Broncos this weekend. A sell-high opportunity could present itself soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a16e-d95b-addb-e96ebd080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a17b-d6e9-af9d-abfb428f0000</link>
      <description>Taylor tweaked his ankle in Week 1 but managed to play through the issue in Week 2. He was then off the injury report entirely for two weeks but is back on it as a limited participant today. This doesn’t appear to be something that will prevent him from playing on Sunday, but it’s clear the ankle injury is going to be a lingering issue for the rookie tight end. Taylor posted a breakout game of sorts in Week 5 with five grabs for 65 yards. He gets another good matchup in Dallas this week, keeping him in the TE2 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a17b-d6e9-af9d-abfb428f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a184-deb6-a7fd-f3dfbbc80000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as Lamb is reportedly expected to miss at least two weeks because of the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. He did not practice last week and it would be a surprise to see him on the practice field at all this week. George Pickens stepped up on Sunday with eight catches for 134 yards and two scores. He will once again be tasked with WR1 duties versus the Jets this week. Pickens will flirt with a fantasy WR1 ranking for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a184-deb6-a7fd-f3dfbbc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a188-deb6-a7fd-f3df631b0000</link>
      <description>Sanders left Week 4 with the ankle injury in the first half and did not return. His absence from Wednesday’s practice puts him on the wrong side of questionable for Week 5 against the Jets. Assuming he can’t suit up, rookie Jaydon Blue will be in line to finally see some action after being a healthy scratch for the first month of the year. Blue is worth stashing in deeper leagues, though he isn’t going to threaten Javonte Williams for the starting role anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a188-deb6-a7fd-f3df631b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KaVontae Turpin (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a18b-deb6-a7fd-f3df059a0000</link>
      <description>Turpin ran as the Cowboys’ No. 3 receiver on Sunday. CeeDee Lamb isn’t expected to be back for Week 5, meaning Turpin was in line for the same role versus the Jets. That is now in question based on Wednesday’s injury report. Ryan Flournoy would seemingly be in line for extra snaps if Turpin can’t suit up this week, though he is a cut too deep for even dynasty managers to care much about.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a18b-deb6-a7fd-f3df059a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints TE Juwan Johnson (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a187-deb6-a7fd-f3df6b900000</link>
      <description>Johnson seemingly tweaked his ankle while attempting a cutback along the sideline on Sunday. He reportedly made multiple visits to the training staff but remained in the game. His absence comes at a tough time. The Saints activated TEs Tayson Hill (knee) and Foster Moreau (knee) from the physically unable to perform list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a187-deb6-a7fd-f3df6b900000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
