<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said De’Von Achane (ribs) was feeling better on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff57-d8cf-affb-ff7f76860000</link>
      <description>McDaniel said on Sunday that it was his decision to hold out Achane after he exited in the second quarter with his rib injury. Speaking on Monday, McDaniel again reiterated that Achane could have re-entered the game if needed, but that moment never came. Achane is hoping to play in Week 15’s game against the Steelers, but this situation is setting up to be a headache for fantasy managers. With the Dolphins not playing until Monday night, fantasy managers may need to figure out a backup plan for Achane if he isn’t cleared or ruled out before the weekend. Achane’s status will be one to monitor throughout the week, but it sounds like he’ll at least have a chance to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff57-d8cf-affb-ff7f76860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Mike Evans (collarbone) has a chance to play in Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff63-da9b-a9bf-ff6ffcdd0000</link>
      <description>It was reported on Sunday that Evans was already pushing to play in Week 15 after being held out against the Saints. Evans practiced all of last week and is clearly trending toward a return, which could not come at a better time for the Bucs. After an unprecedented loss to the 2-10 Saints, the Buccaneers are 7-6 and need all hands on deck as they look to secure a playoff berth and/or NFC South title in the coming weeks. In addition to Evans, Bowles also said WR Jalen McMillan (neck) has a chance to return this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff63-da9b-a9bf-ff6ffcdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Tristan Wirfs (oblique) is “in play” for Tampa Bay’s Week 15 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff4f-d005-a9bf-ff7fe5d40000</link>
      <description>Wirfs missed last week’s game with an oblique, but he was questionable and got in a limited practice on Friday of last week. We expect the injury report to show him with another rest day today — anything better would be great news for his return. But Tuesday and Wednesday should be days where his participation trends up if the Buccaneers are serious about Wirfs playing against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff4f-d005-a9bf-ff7fe5d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said the Broncos have “got to continue to find more touches for” Marvin Mims “on the offensive side of the ball and we’ll do that.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff67-d8cf-affb-ff6f812a0000</link>
      <description>Mims has just four targets since October 19. The meaning of “more” would appear almost limitless when weighed against that. Still, for those of you holding on in dynasty leagues as the third-year receiver fell behind Pat Bryant, this could be the little bit of hope you needed to realize “wait, Marvin Mims was still on my roster?”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff67-d8cf-affb-ff6f812a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) avoided a serious injury and is day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff78-d005-a9bf-ff7c4e230000</link>
      <description>We’ll keep an eye out for the practice reports this week, but Mitchell should have a shot to play in Week 15 based on this news. He’ll be a viable FLEX option, if he plays, in what amounts to an elimination game between the Bengals and Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff78-d005-a9bf-ff7c4e230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said “the hope” is that Riley Leonard (knee) will play against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff7b-da9b-a9bf-ff7f18080000</link>
      <description>Leonard has a knee injury that was diagnosed after the game that Steichen said he is “working through.” He played to the very end of the Colts snaps against the Jaguars, so either he played on it or injured it on his final run to the end zone. The lone remaining quarterback on the roster is, you guessed it, Brett Rypien. We’ll probably get a better sense of how much urgency the Colts have based on how many quarterback workouts get scheduled this week, but this is getting dire in a hurry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff7b-da9b-a9bf-ff7f18080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders CB Kyu Blu Kelly suffered a ruptured patellar tendon in Week 14’s loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff78-d77b-adfa-fffbb0d60000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo, Blu Kelly did not suffer any ligament damage, which is a good sign. The former fifth-round pick from the 2023 draft class played his way into a starting role for the Raiders this season and has totaled 40 tackles, three interceptions, and six pass breakups while making eight starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff78-d77b-adfa-fffbb0d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said CB Charvarius Ward is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff7f-d005-a9bf-ff7f4a2c0000</link>
      <description>Again. As in: For the third time this season. Woof. It would not be surprising if this was a season-ender for Ward. He did play 61 of 64 snaps against the Jaguars, so he apparently either played through symptoms or they developed after the game. It’s become a lost season for Ward, one of the Colts big-money signings this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff7f-d005-a9bf-ff7f4a2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said Anthony Richardson (eye/IR) won’t be activated from injured reserve this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff83-d8cf-affb-ffab70050000</link>
      <description>“From the sounds of it,” Indy Star’s Joel A. Erickson reports, “Richardson hasn’t been cleared to return yet.” It’s possible based on this update that Richardson could play later in the season for those of you looking to superflex stash a rushing quarterback. But there’s obviously no guarantee that he’ll return at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff83-d8cf-affb-ffab70050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said Drake London (knee) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff89-d8cf-affb-ffab739d0000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if London practiced today based on this quote, but the Falcons don’t need to release the injury report yet. With a Thursday game coming to lead off Week 15, London will get some star-level benefit of the doubt if he’s anywhere close, but the inability to even practice since suffering the injury leads us to believe he starts the week on the pessimistic side of questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff89-d8cf-affb-ffab739d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
