<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 2-of-5 targets for 17 yards in the Bears’ Week 13 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccca-d90e-a9da-dfcf7c690000</link>
      <description>Moore did have one rush for 10 yards, but it’s still another unimpressive line for the 28-year-old wideout. It’s disappointing after his two-touchdown effort the previous week against Pittsburgh, and a little more understandable considering the Bears ran for 281 yards with swirling winds affecting the passing game. Nevertheless, these types of games have been all too common for Moore, and he’s a risky WR3 against the Packers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccca-d90e-a9da-dfcf7c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ravens are expected to place LB Chandler Martin on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccca-db57-afda-defa6ae40000</link>
      <description>The undrafted rookie suffered a season-ending knee injury against the Bengals on Thursday. It is an unfortunate development for the special teams contributor. Chandler has been active for the last three games, logging three tackles in punt and kick coverage duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccca-db57-afda-defa6ae40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 13 times for 56 yards in the Eagles’ Week 13 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cccc-d90e-a9da-dfcfcd3a0000</link>
      <description>Barkley didn’t catch either of his two targets, with one being a clear drop and the other a pass that he just didn’t get his head turned around in time to bring in. The 56 yards are more than double the ugly 22-yard game he had against the Cowboys in Week 13, but still a massive disappointment. Unfortunately, this has been far more common than could have been anticipated, and while there are five weeks to go, this appears to be a lost season for the 28-year-old. He’s back in action after an extended rest against the Chargers on Monday Night Football in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cccc-d90e-a9da-dfcfcd3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 5-of-8 targets for 48 yards in the Eagles’ Week 13 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd1-d82c-a79a-ffd535350000</link>
      <description>Smith and Jalen Hurts connected on a 30-yard pass early in the contest, and after that, it was all dink-and-dunk between the two. It’s been a feast or famine type year for the wideout in 2025, with this one squarely in the middle at best. Smith will remain a high-end WR3 — if there is such a thing — for Week 14 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd1-d82c-a79a-ffd535350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 2-of-4 targets for 27 yards in the Eagles’ Week 13 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd4-db57-afda-def6434b0000</link>
      <description>Goedert was held to just two catches for the third consecutive weeks as the Eagles’ offense continues to disappoint at unanticipated — before the season, anyway — levels. The 30-year-old tight end is now off the TE1 radar going forward, including a Week 14 bout against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd4-db57-afda-def6434b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cairo Santos hit his only field goal attempt and went 3-for-3 on extra points in the Bears’ Week 13 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd6-d6c4-abfb-ded7b1d80000</link>
      <description>Santos had no trouble dealing with the swirling winds in Philadelphia and connected on a 30-yard attempt to give Chicago a 10-3 lead. The veteran kicker has been solid in 2025 while making 18-of-22 of his attempts and not missing an extra point this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd6-d6c4-abfb-ded7b1d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said OC Kevin Patullo will continue calling plays.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccaf-d90e-a9da-dfafd8ad0000</link>
      <description>Sirianni adds that “if he thought Kevin Patullo was the issue, he’d make the change.” It is fair to point out that the Eagles’ offensive health has been an issue this season, which is not helping things, but the play calling clearly needs work. For now, Sirianni is sticking with his guy. Despite the offensive woes, the Eagles sit atop the NFC East at 8-4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccaf-d90e-a9da-dfafd8ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that an “MRI and other tests confirmed” Amon-Ra St. Brown suffered “a low-ankle sprain with no structural damage and a quick return” is expected.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd2-db57-afda-def28a740000</link>
      <description>Rapoport deemed it a “1-2 week injury,” yet adds that St. Brown will “push to play.” St. Brown regularly plays through injuries, so it would be unsurprising to see him out there next Thursday against the Cowboys. The team could handle it conservatively by keeping him sidelined for the recommended recovery window, though. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ccd2-db57-afda-def28a740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cd86-d6c4-abfb-df87cba70000</link>
      <description>Mayfield suffered a sprained AC joint in his non-throwing shoulder and left the game in the first half of Week 12’s loss to the Rams. The 30-year-old quarterback has progressed throughout the week, taking all of the first-team reps in practice on Friday. Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Mayfield was trending towards playing, which is confirmed by Fowler’s report. It’s good news for fantasy managers and the Buccaneers as Teddy Bridgewater seemed borderline disinterested in playing quarterback in relief of Mayfield last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cd86-d6c4-abfb-df87cba70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports there’s a “solid chance” Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (illness) plays in Week 13 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d014-d90e-a9da-df1f65fd0000</link>
      <description>Harrison is recovering from appendicitis. The 23-year-old wide receiver practiced in a limited capacity all week. While Harrison had seen an uptick in production with Jacoby Brissett under center, it was nothing compared to what Michael Wilson did in the last two weeks with Harrison out. Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon made no guarantees that those targets will automatically go back to Harrison this week, making him a WR2/WR3 for the Week 13 matchup against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d014-d90e-a9da-df1f65fd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
