<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:04:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle underwent surgery to repair his ruptured Achilles tendon and it “went very well.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a8-d968-a19b-dbf93ec40000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan adds that Kittle “is in good spirits,” post-op. That is good to hear. Kittle, 32, ruptured his Achilles tendon in San Francisco’s Wild Card win over the Eagles. He is under contract through 2029, having signed a four-year extension in April 2025. The procedure was notably performed by Dr. Neal ElAttrache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3a8-d968-a19b-dbf93ec40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos DL John Franklin-Myers (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Denver’s Divisional Round game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b2-d35e-a1bf-c7f271f10000</link>
      <description>Franklin-Myers boasts 39 quarterback pressures and eight sacks this season. The impactful interior defender’s return comes at the right time. The Broncos will also get LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) back in the lineup on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b2-d35e-a1bf-c7f271f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos ruled out LB Drew Sanders (ankle) for Denver’s Divisional Round game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b0-d56e-afff-e7f89d540000</link>
      <description>The Broncos designated Sanders to return from injured reserve on January 10th, but he is not yet ready to play. He spent the regular season on injured reserve due to complications from a torn Achilles suffered in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3b0-d56e-afff-e7f89d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs QB Patrick Mahomes (knee) said his doctor told him he “could be” ready to play in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3bf-d968-a19b-dbfff8de0000</link>
      <description>Mahomes said that his rehab is going “great” so far. He is “hitting all the checkpoints” in terms of regaining “strength” and “range of mobility.” He said he should be able to do “some stuff” during organized team activities and hopes to do “a lot” in training camp. Overall, this is a positive first update from Mahomes as he returns from ACL and LCL tears in his knee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3bf-d968-a19b-dbfff8de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks ruled out TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) for Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3c6-d35e-a1bf-c7c6e7a50000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks designated Arroyo to return from injured reserve on January 7th, opening his 21-day practice window. Evidently, he is not yet ready to resume playing, though he was able to practice fully all week. If the Seahawks beat the 49ers and advance to the NFC Championship Game, Arroyo seemingly has decent odds of making a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3c6-d35e-a1bf-c7c6e7a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring/knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3bb-d968-a19b-dbfbc9c50000</link>
      <description>Cross’ availability was seemingly jeopardized by a knee injury he suffered on Wednesday, but he resumed practicing in full today and is good to go. The Seahawks’ handsomely paid left tackle has been sidelined since injuring his hamstring in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3bb-d968-a19b-dbfbc9c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with 49ers OC Klay Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3f3-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e30000</link>
      <description>This is Kubiak’s first reported invitation to interview for a new role of any kind. Good for him. The 49ers’ offense is averaging 5.5 yards per play as it heads into a matchup against the division-rival Seahawks this weekend. The unit continues to perform very well despite missing key players for multi-game stints throughout the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3f3-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fb-d56e-afff-e7fb4ab20000</link>
      <description>Earlier this week, Rams head coach Sean McVay said he was “optimistic” about Ferguson returning to action. Ferguson’s continued full participation puts him firmly on track to play in the Divisional Round against the Bears. Rams RG Kevin Dotson (ankle) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fb-d56e-afff-e7fb4ab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager reports that former Ravens OC Todd Monken is one of five candidates “linked” to the Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c403-d35e-a1bf-c5c3e9380000</link>
      <description>Schrager puts Monken at the top of the list. Earlier today, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reported that Monken is “among the leading candidates” for the role. He should probably be considered the favorite. However, the four remaining candidates are Giants interim head coach Mike Kafka, Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase, former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury and Browns OC Tommy Rees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c403-d35e-a1bf-c5c3e9380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Peter Schrager links Giants interim DC Charlie Bullen and four other candidates to the Giants’ defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fd-d56e-afff-e7fd13a40000</link>
      <description>Per Schrager, Bullen has a chance to remove the “interim” part of his title, which makes sense. He significantly improved the Giants’ defensive performance after receiving the in-season promotion in Week 13, improving their quarterback pressure rate from 32.9 to 39.9 percent and lowering their yards allowed per play average from 6.1 to 5.1. The remaining four candidates include former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon, Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver, Ravens DC Zach Orr and Browns DC Jim Schwartz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c3fd-d56e-afff-e7fd13a40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
