<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders will interview with 49ers OC Klay Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8fa-d56e-afff-eefa0c200000</link>
      <description>Only two days ago, Kubiak had zero reported interview invites. Now he is slated to interview for both the Steelers and Raiders’ head-coaching vacancies. Good for him. Kubiak’s offense has helped propel the 49ers into the Divisional Round, with the defense’s front-seven being hampered by injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8fa-d56e-afff-eefa0c200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver believes it is “untenable” for the Eagles to “stay the course” with WR A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff56bb0000</link>
      <description>Silver notes that Brown’s talents are not being maximized. After this season, we tend to agree. Were the Eagles to trade him, though, it would create more than $72 million in dead money. Silver believes that “the team and potential suitors might need to find a more creative solution, such as a preemptively reworked contract.” Of course, hiring a brilliant offensive coordinator could always fix things. Brown’s discontent is well documented, but revamping roles may simply be the best and easiest fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff56bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c926-d35e-a1bf-cde639e70000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that Gannon had interviewed with the Cowboys earlier this week, ostensibly via video. The Cowboys are reportedly set to host two more in-person meetings, one with Eagles DB coach and pass game coordinator Christian Parker and the other with Vikings DB coach and pass game coordinator and Daronte Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c926-d35e-a1bf-cde639e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Giants are still expected to sign former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh to a five-year contract to be their next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c929-d35e-a1bf-cdeb63530000</link>
      <description>Over the last few hours, multiple reports have indicated that the two sides are still expected to come to an agreement. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “seems like something was lost in translation” during early negotiations, specifically regarding the “reporting structure” and decision-making powers. He adds that the Titans are still “interested and waiting” to find out what happens, while noting that former Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski could be “the one” for the Giants if things fall through with Harbaugh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c929-d35e-a1bf-cdeb63530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers will interview former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c971-d35e-a1bf-cdf3eb620000</link>
      <description>This would be a fun pairing. The Chargers’ offense stagnated this season, with veteran WR Keenan Allen operating as the No. 1 target earner. One imagines McDaniel would draw up some fantasy-friendly concepts for QB Justin Herbert and WR Ladd McConkey if he were to be offered and accept the role. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the interview “will likely happen early next week.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c971-d35e-a1bf-cdf3eb620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “remains to be seen” whether the Eagles want to keep WR A.J. Brown on the roster for the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c916-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0370000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, there are questions as to whether Brown and QB Jalen Hurts “can be together for another season.” He also states bluntly that if the team wishes to trade him away, they will take a cap hit to do so. Earlier today, The Athletic’s Mike Silver reported something similar, though he believes the Eagles and a potential trade partner “might need to find a more creative solution, such as a preemptively reworked contract.” Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c916-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c975-d56e-afff-effd47980000</link>
      <description>Shula, 39, will also interview for the Titans, Steelers, Giants, Cardinals and Raiders’ head-coaching vacancies. The Rams face the Bears’ explosive offense on Sunday, in a contest that will determine one of the two representatives in the NFC Championship Game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c975-d56e-afff-effd47980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers are working on contract extensions for head coach Matt LaFleur and general manager Brian Gutekunst.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ca1a-d968-a19b-dafbad430000</link>
      <description>Reporting among the top NFL news-breakers that Green Bay is expected to workout a contract extension with LaFleur has been consistent over the last week. The 46-year-old Packers coach has one year left on his contract, but Green Bay intends to extend LaFleur and avoid lame-duck status. The same appears to be true of Gutekunst, who Schefter reports is also more likely than not to receive a contract extension soon. The Packers are 76-40-1 and have made the playoffs six times in seven years under LaFleur, who was hired by Gutekunst in 2019. Gutekunst helped usher in a new era of Packers football by drafting Jordan Love, trading future Hall of Fame quarterback Aaron Rodgers and acquiring three-time All-Pro pass rusher Micah Parsons. Packers President Ed Policy was spotted with LaFleur and Gutekunst earlier this week, according to Schefter. While no deal is done yet, Green Bay continues to trend towards keeping the band together.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ca1a-d968-a19b-dafbad430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan speculates the holdup with John Harbaugh’s five-year contract to be the Giants next head coach involves the organization’s chain of command.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc56-d56e-afff-eefef02c0000</link>
      <description>Duggan reports that while Harbaugh coached the Ravens for 18 seasons, the 63-year-old head coach reported directly to owner Steve Biscotti and not the general manager. While that has not been the Giants’ chain of command historically, it appears Harbaugh prefers that same setup rather than reporting to Giants GM Joe Schoen. Harbaugh is the first major domino to fall in this offseason’s coaching carousel, which gives the Giants some options if this deal were to fall through, though that’s not seen as likely at this point. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the negotiations are heading in the right direction, according to a source, and the Giants hope to introduce Harbaugh at a press conference on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cc56-d56e-afff-eefef02c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
