<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports Jets OC Tanner Engstrand is not expected to call plays in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb8f-dc7a-af9b-ffbfdafe0000</link>
      <description>An offensive coordinator not calling plays for a defensive-minded head coach certainly evokes a strong whiff of “what would you say you do here?” Hughes added that former Colts and Panthers HC Frank Reich is “among the names” he’s heard linked to the Jets. This is certainly an out-of-left-field development as the Jets’ run game was mostly praised last year despite what looked to be a pretty elementary passing game. Perhaps they’re trying to find someone who can assist with the passing part.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fb8f-dc7a-af9b-ffbfdafe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams OC Mike LaFleur is scheduled to have a second interview with the Cardinals for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba7-d35e-a1bf-ffe7a4920000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, LaFleur will meet in-person with the Cardinals on Monday and Tuesday. The 38-year-old has spent the last three seasons as the Rams’ offensive coordinator after a failed two-year stint with the Jets. LaFleur has not called plays with the Rams, but his time with the Jets wasn’t exactly a resumé builder. The Raiders also requested an interview with LaFleur, who is now available to speak with after the Rams loss in the Conference Championship game to the Seahawks this past weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba7-d35e-a1bf-ffe7a4920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports the price for Murray “starts with a third-round pick.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba6-d56e-afff-ffee98340000</link>
      <description>“That source compared Murray’s situation with Geno Smith’s when he was traded from Seattle to Las Vegas last March for a third-round pick. The source pointed out that Smith was more consistent during his last season with Seattle than Murray was in his five games with Arizona this season, however, the source added that Murray ‘is a more talented player,’” Weinfuss writes. He quotes another source that believes the Cardinals can get a second-round pick for Murray due to a down quarterback draft. It wouldn’t be exceptionally surprising to see Murray fetch a Day 2 pick in trade given desperation around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fba6-d56e-afff-ffee98340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Michael DiRocco believes “early indications” are that Travis Hunter is primarily going to be a cornerback and have a package of plays on offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbb4-d56e-afff-fffc178a0000</link>
      <description>This would, obviously, be bad for his fantasy football value. Whether it’s the right move or not for the Jaguars is open to interpretation. It looked like Hunter had just started to scratch the surface of his talent before his season-ending knee injury. But with Jakobi Meyers, Parker Washington, and Brian Thomas Jr. seemingly locked in as the team’s three main receivers, this role makes a lot of sense for how things currently stand in Jacksonville. Hunter’s status as an offensive player will be something we spend a lot of time monitoring this offseason, but if he only has a package of plays, it’d be hard to endorse him as more than a WR4/WR5 flier in redraft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbb4-d56e-afff-fffc178a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newark Star-Ledger’s Art Stapleton said Raiders DC Patrick Graham is a “possible defensive coordinator” for the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc4-d56e-afff-ffec8f2a0000</link>
      <description>Graham worked for Mike McCarthy in Green Bay. The Steelers let all of Mike Tomlin’s staff out of their contracts, so they’ll likely need to fill the role with someone new. It wouldn’t be surprising if Graham was choosing from a few different options — including remaining Raiders defensive coordinator — once all the head-coaching seats are settled. He did interview for the Dolphins head-coaching gig last week before it went to Jeff Hafley, and he had an interview request from Washington a few weeks ago for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc4-d56e-afff-ffec8f2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Kuharsky reports the Titans will interview former Buccaneers QB coach Thad Lewis for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc9-d35e-a1bf-ffcb8f290000</link>
      <description>The list of names linked to the Titans OC role so far are Kliff Kingsbury, Brian Daboll, Adam Stenavich, and now Lewis. Lewis got interviewed by the Texans for their OC vacancy in the 2025 offseason, as well as an in-house look from the Buccaneers. He also was interviewed for Buffalo’s OC vacancy in 2024. The Buccaneers fired Lewis earlier this offseason and this is his first known interview since that happened — we bet he’ll pick up a lower-level role elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc9-d35e-a1bf-ffcb8f290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Titans will interview former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury and Packers OC Adam Stenavich for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd1-dc7a-af9b-fffff26d0000</link>
      <description>We can imagine Stenavich being someone that appeals to Robert Saleh’s defensive coach instincts, though Stenavich has not called plays under Matt LaFleur. Kingsbury had head-coaching interest from the Titans — as well as several other teams — so it’s not surprising they’re interested in pursuing him for this role as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd1-dc7a-af9b-fffff26d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins interviewed Eagles defensive line coach Clint Hurtt for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd6-dc7a-af9b-ffff5e6e0000</link>
      <description>Hurtt coordinated Seattle’s defense in 2022 and 2023 before being swept away in the Pete Carroll firing. He had formerly been Carroll’s defensive line coach and worked with Seattle from 2018-2023. He was previously Chicago’s linebackers coach under Vic Fangio. Hurtt’s coordinating experience wasn’t positive, but he’s potentially worthy of a second chance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd6-dc7a-af9b-ffff5e6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Giants interim coach Mike Kafka will join the Lions in a “high-ranking offensive staff role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</link>
      <description>He’s not the offensive coordinator — that’s Drew Petzing — but Kafka will apparently be another offensive mind in the room for Dan Campbell. It’s a coup for the Lions considering Kafka had interviewed to be an offensive coordinator in Detroit, Philadelphia, Tampa, and with the Giants this offseason. He’ll hope to rehab his coaching image after a fairly benign interim coach showing after Brian Daboll was swept out of power in New Jersey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested permission to interview Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase is reportedly meeting with the Browns right now in Los Angeles and Cleveland beat writers are picking out words carefully so they aren’t the ones saying he’s the favorite for the job despite the long interview, so perhaps this is a leverage play. It’s certainly no surprise to see the Bills interested, and they’ll reportedly have an in-person interview with Scheelhaase tonight. Scheelhaase also completed interviews with the Ravens, Raiders and Steelers this offseason. Scheelhaase would be yet another Sean McVay coaching tree disciple wherever he lands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
