<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed CB Amani Oruwariye to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94f5-d56e-afff-f6fd7bc70000</link>
      <description>The former Lions starter has bounced around between the Jaguars, Cowboys, and Ravens the last three seasons. He’ll be cornerback depth for Baltimore in 2026. The Ravens also signed T Gerad Christian-Lichtenhan, WR Cornelius Johnson, DT David Olajiga, G Jared Penning, DB Marquise Robinson, DE Kaimon Rucker and RB Lucas Scott to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94f5-d56e-afff-f6fd7bc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Chargers assistant GM Chad Alexander for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9502-d968-a19b-ddf334e60000</link>
      <description>Alexander, who came over from the Jets to join former Ravens charge Joe Hortiz, interviewed for the Raiders and Jaguars jobs in the 2025 offseason. The Dolphins continue to grow their general manager interview pool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9502-d968-a19b-ddf334e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested permission to interview Ravens OC Todd Monken for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-950b-d56e-afff-f7eb8caa0000</link>
      <description>It’s probably a little more surprising than it would have been at this time last year, as Monken’s offense struggled while Lamar Jackson dealt with injuries. Still, Monken has a good reputation as an offensive play-caller and the Browns would definitely seem to be leaning in the direction of either a CEO coach or offensive mind so they could retain DC Jim Schwartz. The Ravens finished 11th in offensive DVOA despite Jackson’s injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-950b-d56e-afff-f7eb8caa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested to interview 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9512-dc7a-af9b-dfbf40370000</link>
      <description>It’s the first request for Saleh this year. For a brief shining moment ahead of the firing of Jaguars GM Trent Baalke, Saleh was the favorite there in 2025 after interviewing well. He also interviewed for the Cowboys vacancy in the 2025 offseason. The 49ers have been besieged with defensive injuries in 2025, losing stars Nick Bosa and Fred Warner for most of the season, but have been respectable in spite of that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9512-dc7a-af9b-dfbf40370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested permission to interview Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9516-d35e-a1bf-d5d658a30000</link>
      <description>It is Weaver’s second request of the cycle after he drew one from the Falcons yesterday. Miami’s defensive coordinator has been a finalist for the Saints, Commanders, and Falcons over the past couple of offseasons. Weaver certainly seems worthy of a chance to be a head coach at this point. We’ll see if he can become a favorite for anyone else this offseason. The Dolphins finished 24th in defensive DVOA last year with a skeleton crew defensive backs room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9516-d35e-a1bf-d5d658a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived QB Clayton Tune.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9523-dc7a-af9b-dfbf4e640000</link>
      <description>Over three seasons with the Cardinals and Packers, Tune is 21-of-38 for 112 scoreless yards, three interceptions, and has taken 12 sacks. On the bright side, he still has his youth. The Packers decided to add Desmond Ridder to the playoff roster over Tune. We don’t think anything we can say would be meaner than that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9523-dc7a-af9b-dfbf4e640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed LB Kyzir White off the Titans practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9525-d56e-afff-f7edc56d0000</link>
      <description>White gives the 49ers some emergency depth for the playoffs with Tatum Bethune hurt. The 49ers finished Week 18 with Eric Kendricks and Garret Wallow at linebacker and won’t get Fred Warner back until the NFC Championship, at earliest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9525-d56e-afff-f7edc56d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed K Matthew Wright to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-952a-d35e-a1bf-d5ea1e220000</link>
      <description>Your latest Matt Prater potential replacement has arrived. Wright will kick against the Jaguars in the Wild Card round should Prater be unavailable. Wright is 5-for-5 on field goals and 4-of-4 on extra points between three teams this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-952a-d35e-a1bf-d5ea1e220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions fired OC John Morton.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954d-d35e-a1bf-d5cfa4da0000</link>
      <description>Just five days ago, Morton said he wanted to say with the team even in a lesser role. Dan Campbell, who took over playcalling duties from Morton midseason, apparently did not agree to this arrangement. Morton will probably catch on elsewhere lower on the ladder in 2026, perhaps back in Denver with Sean Payton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954d-d35e-a1bf-d5cfa4da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants, Cardinals, and Raiders have all requested an interview with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954f-d35e-a1bf-d5cff3850000</link>
      <description>These are in addition to a Falcons interview we heard about yesterday, making Kubiak one of the hottest head-coaching candidates of the offseason. Seattle’s 10th-ranked DVOA offense with Sam Darnold, as well as Kubiak’s ability to scheme so much of his offense around star wideout Jaxon Smith-Njigba, have apparently drawn plenty of attention. Kubiak, on bye, is also available to interview right away, which doesn’t hurt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954f-d35e-a1bf-d5cff3850000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
