<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 7-of-9 targets for 65 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-df81-ab9b-7edfbc7c0000</link>
      <description>Otton and the rest of the Tampa Bay offense struggled in the first half, managing only 52 yards of total offense before the break. They would then be thrust into a negative game environment following a 78-yard rushing score from Jahmyr Gibbs, which led to Otton seeing a boost in targets in the second half against the prevent defense of the Lions. Alpha wide receiver Mike Evans also departed in the second quarter, forcing the secondary options through the air to step up as Mayfield was tasked with 50 pass attempts. Otton won’t return meaningful volume in most weeks and he remains nothing more than a TE2 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-df81-ab9b-7edfbc7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans is expected to miss “most of the year” after suffering a broken collarbone in Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-d99b-a1df-3e9c7b750000</link>
      <description>Evans entered the 2025 season hoping to record his 12th straight 1,000-yard season. It appears as though achieving that goal is no longer possible. Evans became the first NFL wide receiver to total 1,000 receiving yards in each of his first seven seasons, back in 2020. He continued extending that record every year through 2024. Despite another 1,000-yard season potentially being out of reach, phrasing regarding the injury suggests Evans has a chance to return later this season. The Buccaneers (5-2) should still be in the playoff hunt when early-to-mid December rolls around, which NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports is in line with the “regular” recovery timeline for a broken collarbone. Evans will likely be placed on injured reserve in the short term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-d99b-a1df-3e9c7b750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-12 targets for 58 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049f-df81-ab9b-7edf822d0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka saw his snap rate monitored in the first half but a second quarter injury to Mike Evans forced him into increased snaps and routes after the break. Quarterback Baker Mayfield continually missed Egbuka high, part of the reason he managed only four receptions on a team-leading 12 targets. Even so, fantasy managers can take solace in the fact he once again led the team in targets, this time while playing through a hamstring strain suffered in Week 6. Egbuka could once again function as the otp option through the air when the Buccaneers travel to New Orleans to face the Saints in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049f-df81-ab9b-7edf822d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tez Johnson caught 4-of-9 targets for 58 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04a1-df81-ab9b-7ee7f8660000</link>
      <description>Johnson saw an increased snap rate throughout due to the team managing the workload of fellow rookie Emeka Egbuka in the first half and veteran receiver Mike Evans’ departure in the second quarter. He appears to be worthy of a waiver addition considering the state of the wide receiver corps, with Evans likely to miss the team’s Week 8 meeting with the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04a1-df81-ab9b-7ee7f8660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 20-of-29 passes for 241 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Lions’ 24-9, Week 7 win over the Buccaneers, adding seven yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04cc-d651-a9df-6dddacc30000</link>
      <description>Goff set the tone from the opening kick, leading the Lions down the field to score their fourth opening possession touchdown of the season. Running back Jahmyr Gibbs would add a touchdown from 78 yards out in the second quarter that allowed the team to take a more conservative approach on offense, leading to the modest 29 pass attempts from Goff. The veteran quarterback managed a lofty 8.31 yards per attempt against the pass-funnel Tampa Bay defense, doing most of his damage through alpha wide receiver Amon-Ra St. Brown and Gibbs, with the two combining for 168 of Goff’s 241 yards through the air. The win vaults the Lions to 5-2, a record that is currently tied with four other teams (potentially another added, pending the result of the Seahawks game Monday) just 0.5 games behind the Conference leading Packers in the NFC. The Lions get another tough test in Week 8 when they host the 3-3 Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04cc-d651-a9df-6dddacc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 17 times for 136 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 7 win over the Buccaneers, adding 82 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04d2-da18-a39a-ded3a5e30000</link>
      <description>The 218 yards from scrimmage were the most by a Lions skill position player since Calvin Johnson’s record setting 329 yards in 2013, also going down as the third most yards from scrimmage of a Detroit running back in the team’s storied history. Much of Gibbs’ damage came on a 78-yard second quarter touchdown scamper up the gut, his first of two trips to the paint against an opponent that has been one of the stingier defenses to run on over the previous five seasons. Gibbs dominated the backfield work until the second half, ceding a total of 16 opportunities to David Montgomery - the vast majority of which came after the break with the game in hand. But that also makes the outburst that much more impressive considering Gibbs did his damage on only 20 touches. Up next for Gibbs and the Lions is a divisional matchup with the Vikings in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04d2-da18-a39a-ded3a5e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed 13 times for 21 yards in the Lions’ Week 7 win over the Buccaneers, adding 18 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04d8-d99b-a1df-3edcc14a0000</link>
      <description>Montgomery was vastly overshadowed by the 218 yards from scrimmage from backfield mate Jahmyr Gibbs, the latter of whom put up the third most yards from scrimmage for a back in franchise history. Even so, Montgomery remains an integral part of the one-two punch in Detroit and he should return better counting stats moving forward. Continue treating Montgomery as an RB3 ahead of a Week 8 matchup with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04d8-d99b-a1df-3edcc14a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 6-of-10 target for 86 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 7 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04da-da18-a39a-dedbc7290000</link>
      <description>St. Brown has now seen seven or more targets in all six games since the team’s opening weekend loss to the Packers, hitting double-digits three times in that span as the clear top dog through the air for the Lions. His first quarter touchdown went down as his seventh trip to paint in 2025, a mark that now stands alone atop the league - one ahead of Jake Ferguson, Davante Adams, and George Pickens. He’ll look to keep the momentum going in a Week 8 meeting with the division rival Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04da-da18-a39a-dedbc7290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught all three targets for 15 yards in the Lions’ Week 7 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04de-d651-a9df-6ddf6f660000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Jared Goff attempted only 29 passes in a night headlined by the team’s defense and running back Jahmyr Gibbs, with no pass-catcher other than alpha wide receiver Amon-Ra St. Brown notching more than three targets. The talented fourth-year tight end will look to get back on track in the fantasy streets when the Lions host the Vikings in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04de-d651-a9df-6ddf6f660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams failed to catch either target in the Lions’ Week 7 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04e0-da18-a39a-def37d760000</link>
      <description>Williams was targeted only twice and failed to come down with either look on a night Kelvin Sheppard’s defense and running back Jahmyr Gibbs stole the show. The significantly positive game environment led to only 29 pass attempts from quarterback Jared Goff, and no pass-catcher other than Amon-Ra St. Brown saw more than a modest three targets. Williams has yet to live up to the offseason hype in fantasy circles, a trend he will look to buck in Week 8 when the Lions host the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04e0-da18-a39a-def37d760000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
