<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports that “the NFL has begun a review of the recent domestic violence allegations against Dolphins receiver Tyreek Hill.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3558-d93a-abbb-7d5a06a00000</link>
      <description>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel also indicated that the “in-house disciplinary process,” which involves “an effort” to interview the alleged victim, has been activated. Hill was recently accused of eight instances of domestic violence “in a court filing submitted in connection with a divorce case.” Florio notes that Hill pleaded guilty to “domestic assault and battery by strangulation” 10 years ago, which could count as “an aggravating factor in connection with any punishment Hill may face,” if the league deems he violated the Personal Conduct Policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3558-d93a-abbb-7d5a06a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RT Morgan Moses (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3566-dbe3-a9bb-357720260000</link>
      <description>The last thing Drake Maye needed was to lose one of the bookends to his offensive line. Moses was brought in as a free agent to help improve one of the league’s worst lines in 2024. Though the veteran tackle is a few years past his prime, he was still set to be a stabilizing force for the unit. Losing Moses would be a tough blow for a New England offense that already came out flat-footed in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3566-dbe3-a9bb-357720260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Quinshon Judkins (personal) did not practice Wednesday but is expected to return on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-356e-d93a-abbb-7d7ee2030000</link>
      <description>Judkins is meeting with league officials in New York today as part of their investigation into him under the personal conduct policy. Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, he should be on the field for the remaining two practices of the week, though that doesn’t guarantee he will suit up on Sunday. Fellow rookie Dylan Sampson led the Browns with 12 carries in Week 1, though he only turned in 29 yards on the ground. Sampson looked exciting as a pass-catcher, reeling in eight balls for 64 yards. He will have a standalone role even once Judkins returns and could be in line for an RB2 fantasy outing if Judkins misses Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-356e-d93a-abbb-7d7ee2030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB DaRon Bland (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3577-d332-a1fd-b77762360000</link>
      <description>It’s a concerning development for Bland, who missed 10 games in 2024 because of a foot injury. However, it’s not clear if the two issues are related. Bland played on every single snap in Week 1 and recorded three tackles. Losing him to a recurring foot issue would be a massive blow to a Dallas defense that began the season by shipping off their star EDGE defender in Micah Parsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3577-d332-a1fd-b77762360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-357b-d332-a1fd-b77f2f080000</link>
      <description>Waller missed all of training camp while regaining his conditioning after being away from the NFL for a year. He was then added to the Week 1 injury report with a surprise hip issue and did not play. It doesn’t look like he will be out there for Week 2 either. The Dolphins don’t have a tight end of note for fantasy purposes behind Waller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-357b-d332-a1fd-b77f2f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-357d-db7b-a5dd-b57d0fb40000</link>
      <description>Waddle took a big hit in the third quarter of Miami’s Week 1 loss to the Colts and briefly left the game. He was checked out by trainers on the sideline and managed to return later in the contest. Though seeing him on the injury report this early in the year is slightly ominous, there’s no indication that he is at risk of missing Week 2. Waddle and the Dolphins will be looking to rebound versus the Patriots after a dismal outing against Indianapolis. Waddle will be stuck in the WR3 ranks until his team turns things around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-357d-db7b-a5dd-b57d0fb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Hunter Renfrow (ribs) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3581-d93a-abbb-7ddb74e10000</link>
      <description>Renfrow took multiple hard hits that left him shaken up in Week 1, though he was never given an injury designation and managed to play through the pain. A limited practice to open the week means he isn’t at much risk of missing Week 1. However, the veteran wideout may see his snaps reduced in an effort to keep him healthy. After catching two passes in Week 1, Renfrow is not on the fantasy menu for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3581-d93a-abbb-7ddb74e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3598-d332-a1fd-b7be92c40000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said yesterday that he was hopeful Porter Jr. will play this week. The team called up cornerback James Pierre from the practice squad this morning, indicating at least a slight level of concern on JPJ’s availability. Thursday’s practice report will be more telling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3598-d332-a1fd-b7be92c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35bf-dbe3-a9bb-35fffcfd0000</link>
      <description>Engram left the Broncos’ Week 1 game against the Titans with a calf injury. He caught three passes for 21 yards before exiting in the fourth quarter. Getting in a limited practice to start the week is a good sign his injury is not major, but fantasy managers should monitor his status throughout the week. Engram is a low-end TE1 for Week 2 against the Colts if he plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35bf-dbe3-a9bb-35fffcfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35c5-dbe3-a9bb-35d7433a0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw is dealing with a quad issue that has lingered from the summer. The 28-year-old is no stranger to leg injuries, having suffered an Achilles rupture in the Super Bowl back in February 2024. He has yet to practice this season, indicating he is not close to returning for Week 2. Also sidelined on Wednesday was DE John Franklin-Myers (knee). Franklin-Myers did play in Week 1 but now begins Week 2 by missing the first practice of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35c5-dbe3-a9bb-35d7433a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
