<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants ruled out WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) for Week 11 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83d0-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa7d2a0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate, but it was expected. Slayton aggravated his nagging hamstring injury after catching 4-of-4 targets for 89 yards in Week 10 against the Bears. Watching the Giants’ downfield wide receiver work with the cannon-armed QB Jameis Winston would have been fun. Slayton’s absence against the Packers condenses the Giants’ reliable pass catchers to slot WR Wan’Dale Robinson and the tight ends. Robinson is a strong bet to lead the team in targets and can be started as a WR3 in an albeit tough matchup. No. 1 TE Theo Johnson warrants TE1 treatment. No. 2 TE Daniel Bellinger (groin) is best-suited to deep leagues as a touchdown-dependent bet. Keep an eye on possession WR Isaiah Hodgins, who the team brought back earlier this week. He is not worth starting this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83d0-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa7d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Taron Johnson (groin) is questionable for Buffalo’s Week 11 game against Tampa Bay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83d8-d713-ad9e-efdcd4700000</link>
      <description>He downgraded to a limited session on Friday after going full on Thursday. Buffalo used Cam Lewis as their slot replacement against the Dolphins in Week 10, but Lewis (calf) is also questionable. Tampa should be able to get some explosives by isolating their best on Buffalo’s slot corners. Johnson hasn’t played since Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83d8-d713-ad9e-efdcd4700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (back) is not on Chicago’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e0-d713-ad9e-eff4d73f0000</link>
      <description>He’ll be more of a thorn in Colston Loveland’s side than anybody fantasy managers will want to dial up this week. Kmet is effectively only a TE2, and not one with an especially strong usage case. He has more than two targets in just two of eight games this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e0-d713-ad9e-eff4d73f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (ankle) isn’t on Chicago’s final Week 11 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e2-d673-a39e-a7f3548b0000</link>
      <description>Odunze has been managed at practice each of the last three weeks and the pattern stayed intact here: He’ll play against the Vikings and remain on the WR2 line. Odunze went for 6/37/1 in Chicago’s first meeting with the Vikings in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e2-d673-a39e-a7f3548b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants ruled out OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder) for Week 11 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83dc-d1e7-a1fa-dbfe36600000</link>
      <description>Thibodeaux was visibly in pain last weekend, so his absence is unsurprising. The Giants also ruled out his backup, OLB Chauncey Golston (neck), and listed starting DT Rakeem Nunez-Roches (toe) as doubtful. Two more starters, LB Bobby Okereke (shoulder) and CB Paulson Adebo (knee) are listed as questionable. Good news for the Packers’ offense, which has been heavily scrutinized in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83dc-d1e7-a1fa-dbfe36600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) won’t play in Chicago’s Week 11 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e5-d673-a39e-a7f577720000</link>
      <description>Edwards hasn’t played since Week 9, and he’s been banged up enough that he’s already missed half of Chicago’s games this season. Noah Sewell manned the middle next to Tremaine Edmunds last week and has been one of the worst cover linebackers in the league this year per PFF data, with a 30.0 coverage grade. The Vikings should see some success over the middle of the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e5-d673-a39e-a7f577720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e4-d1e7-a1fa-dbee8b2a0000</link>
      <description>After sitting out on Wednesday, Moore upgraded to limited on Thursday before practicing fully on Friday. The veteran wide receiver is good to go after injuring his right shoulder in a fall last weekend. Moore has largely finished in the WR3/WR4 range this season and can be treated accordingly this week against the Vikings’ top-notch, blitz-based defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e4-d1e7-a1fa-dbee8b2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 11 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e9-d673-a39e-a7f96c060000</link>
      <description>It remains to be seen when Hendrickson will play again, as he did not practice all week. Shemar Stewart (knee) also remains out with a long-term injury. Pittsburgh’s offense should be able to get back on track against one of the NFL’s weakest defenses this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e9-d673-a39e-a7f96c060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 11 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e5-d713-ad9e-eff57fac0000</link>
      <description>Swift was limited on Wednesday and practiced fully on Thursday and Friday. He retook the Bears’ lead back role in Week 10 against the Giants and can be treated as an RB2 against a Vikings defense that admittedly corralled him for half-PPR RB28 results in Week 1, as the Bears were working out a few offensive kinks. Swift enters the rematch on firmer footing, in an established rotation with talented backup RB Kyle Monangai.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83e5-d713-ad9e-eff57fac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Samaje Perine (ankle) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 11 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83eb-d673-a39e-a7fbe7f40000</link>
      <description>Perine suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 9 and has not practiced since. Tahj Brooks has assumed backup duties, but the Bengals went back to last year’s “All Chase Brown All The Time” plan in Week 9. We’ll see if they have any more faith in Brooks in Week 11 after their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-83eb-d673-a39e-a7fbe7f40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
