<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 16:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared RB Jaylen Wright, QB Quinn Ewers, CB Ethan Bonner, CB Storm Duck, TE Darren Waller, WR Tahj Washington, and DT Benito Jones inactive for Week 2 against the Patriots</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48d7-d86f-abdd-4dffd5460000</link>
      <description>Wright is set to miss his second straight game due to a knee injury. He practiced in a limited fashion to end the week, but is still not ready to return to game speed, making Ollie Gordon the primary No. 2 running back for Week 2. Waller (hip) was ruled out earlier this week while Duck (ankle), Bonner (hamstring), and Jones (obique) will be missing for a defense that is already struggling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48d7-d86f-abdd-4dffd5460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declare RT Jack Conklin (eye) inactive for Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-dc44-a9d9-4fff6b6d0000</link>
      <description>Cornelius Lucas is expected to draw the star in place of Conklin, who is somewhat of a surprise scratch after practicing in a limited capacity all week. In addition to Conklin, the Browns also declared QB Shedeur Sanders, RB Raheim Sanders, DT Mike Hall Jr., and OG Zak Zinter inactive for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-dc44-a9d9-4fff6b6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared QB Case Keenum, CB Kyler Gordon, WR Jahdae Walker, OT Ozzy Trapilo, OL Kiran Amegadjie and DT Shemar Turner inactive for Week 2 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48de-d86f-abdd-4dff0fde0000</link>
      <description>It’s a quiet list for a road-tripping Bears squad on a short week coming off a rough Monday evening home loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48de-d86f-abdd-4dff0fde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared EDGE Chase Young, WR Trey Palmer, DB Rejzohn Wright, OL Trevor Penning, OL Xavier Truss, DT Khristian Boyd and EDGE Jonathan Bullard inactive for Week 2 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e0-d294-a19b-ecf0f7e60000</link>
      <description>Young is officially week to week. He seemed like he gave it a legitimate go this week before being ruled out on Friday. He should be considered genuinely questionable for Week 3 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e0-d294-a19b-ecf0f7e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared CB Joey Porter Jr., S DeShon Elliott, G Max Scharping, G Andrus Peat, DE Esezi Otomewo, and DT Derrick Harmon inactive for Week 2 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e2-da67-a99f-ccf797400000</link>
      <description>Porter will miss Week 2 after failing to log a practice this week due to a hamstring injury. Pittsburgh’s secondary should be able to get along without Porter against a toothless Seahawks passing offense. The Steelers proved vulnerable against the rush in Week 1 against the Jets. That could lead the Seahawks to run the ball quite a bit against the Pittsburgh front seven.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e2-da67-a99f-ccf797400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Xavier Worthy “is looking good to play” in Week 3 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-da67-a99f-ccff14b40000</link>
      <description>Worthy is out for the Chiefs’ Week 2 game against the Eagles, leaving the Chiefs without their top two receivers for the Super Bowl rematch. Given how hard of a hit Worthy took from a player who weighs nearly 100 pounds more than him, missing just one week would be an incredible turnaround for the young wideout. Per Rapoport, Worthy suffered a fully torn labrum from the collision. He is expected to play with a harness on his shoulder once he is back on the field. For Week 2, Hollywood Brown, coming off a 16-target game, will serve as the team’s No. 1 receiver. The volume alone will put him in the WR2 ranks versus Philly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-da67-a99f-ccff14b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Curtis Samuel, NCB Taron Johnson, S Jordan Hancock, LB Shaq Thompson. T Chase Lundt, DT Ed Oliver, and DE Landon Jackson inactive for Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48cb-d294-a19b-ecfbe6b00000</link>
      <description>We already knew Oliver was missing this week with an ankle injury but there had been hope that Johnson (quad) would suit up. Those are two big losses for this Bills defense heading into a showdown with a Jets offense that seemed live in week one. The good news is that Tre’Davious White (groin) will make his season debut across from Christian Bedford.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48cb-d294-a19b-ecfbe6b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) active for New York’s Week 2 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e3-d86f-abdd-4dff41580000</link>
      <description>He’ll see plenty of action against the Cowboys and is a worthwhile PPR scam FLEX option. Inactive for the Giants are: QB Jameis Winston, LT Andrew Thomas (foot), OL Evan Neal, DL Rakeem Nunez-Roches (foot), WR/KR Xavier Gipson, TE Thomas Fidone, and LB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e3-d86f-abdd-4dff41580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared WR Efton Chism, CB Christian Gonzalez, DT Eric Gregory, EDGE Keion White, OG Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 2 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-dc44-a9d9-4fffa4c50000</link>
      <description>Chism was dealing with a knee injury and was ruled out for Week 1 with what was technically a healthy scratch. Though he was not listed on the injury report for Week 2, he is again a healthy scratch against the Dolphins. Gonzalez (hamstring) was ruled out earlier this week while White (illness) did not practice this week. Their absences will create a softer Pats defense for a Dolphins offense that struggled last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48df-dc44-a9d9-4fffa4c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared DE Tyler Baron, TE Jelani Woods, OT Esa Pole, RB Kene Nwangwu, WR Josh Reynolds, and DT Jay Tufele inactive for Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e6-d86f-abdd-4dff4b410000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here for the Jets. Reynolds figures to operate as the team’s number two wide receiver whenever he’s healthy enough to take the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-48e6-d86f-abdd-4dff4b410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
