<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said that most starters will play in preseason Week 2 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aacc-df63-a199-fbef46610000</link>
      <description>Mike Evans and Lavonte David are the only starters who will not play. This game could provide insight into Baker Mayfield’s connection with rising rookie WR Emeka Egbuka, as well as the Buccaneers’ backfield usage with Rachaad White (groin) likely sidelined. Mayfield did not play last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aacc-df63-a199-fbef46610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed FB Wesley Steiner, formerly of the Raiders, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aad4-d90d-a5bd-aadf31ea0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders briefly rostered Steiner after he went undrafted earlier this year. Steiner will technically be listed as the FB3, with standout rookie FB Robbie Ouzts penciled in as the starter and FB Brady Russell spending half his time at TE. The signing reinforces the notion that Seattle is committed to establishing the run this season, which is good news for both Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet. The team correspondingly waived LB Michael Dowell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aad4-d90d-a5bd-aadf31ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reports Rashee Rice’s hearing and potential suspension could impact “the back half of the Chiefs’ season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aae2-d45c-a7fc-aafa894f0000</link>
      <description>Rice’s case regarding a multi-car crash will be heard by independent arbitrator Judge Sue L. Robinson, who issued Deshaun Watson’s initial six-game suspension after considering the matter for more than a month in 2022. Two weeks later, the NFL appealed Robinson’s suspension and agreed to an 11-game suspension with the NFLPA. Judge Robinson’s lengthy previous deliberation period could be an issue for Rice and the Chiefs. The NFL has again shown a willingness to operate on the Judge’s time, scheduling Rice’s hearing for September 30th because that is when her schedule allowed it. The Chiefs face the Ravens on September 28th, in Week 4. Should a similar timeline play out, it is possible Rice’s potential suspension is not imposed until after the Chiefs’ Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aae2-d45c-a7fc-aafa894f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Broncos and Cardinals will sit most of their starters, when the two teams play their preseason Week 2 game this weekend.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab17-d90d-a5bd-ab5ff19a0000</link>
      <description>Broncos head coach Sean Payton adds that five or six starters who currently “have a lack of reps” will play on an “eight-play pitch count.” Those five or six players will be worth watching, namely to determine if the group includes players like RJ Harvey, Marvin Mims, Troy Franklin and/or Pat Bryant. Should any of those players take the field, it would be nice to see them get the start and leave quickly thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab17-d90d-a5bd-ab5ff19a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that the Dolphins “never showed any genuine interest in moving [Tyreek] Hill during the offseason.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab27-d45c-a7fc-ab3fc6d00000</link>
      <description>Howe cites “several high-ranking league sources” in the report. Recent buzz around Hill has not been great and he is now nursing an oblique injury. Still, the Dolphins do not appear to be interested in allowing the 31-year-old wide receiver to play elsewhere and Howe thinks that “there’s reason to believe [the distractions have] been left in the past.” If Hill really is turning a corner in his commitment to football, and the Dolphins can get him back to performing at an elite level, it would be a boon to the offense as a whole.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab27-d45c-a7fc-ab3fc6d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said, after reviewing the tape of today’s practice, he has decided to sit Baker Mayfield for the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab2b-d90d-a5bd-ab7b497c0000</link>
      <description>Bowles initially told reporters that all starters, aside from Mike Evans and Lavonte David, would play on Saturday. Per The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Mayfield “played so well today in the joint workout with the Steelers” that Bowles changed his mind. It’s unfortunate for fantasy managers who were hoping to catch a glimpse of Mayfield’s connection with WR Emeka Egbuka but the game should still give us a look at the Buccaneers’ running back rotation with Rachaad White sidelined by a groin injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab2b-d90d-a5bd-ab7b497c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said A.J. Brown (hamstring) is “working through some things” when asked if Brown suffered a setback after missing practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab52-d45c-a7fc-ab5a7f8d0000</link>
      <description>Brown was sidelined by a hamstring strain in early August. He briefly resumed practicing before being sidelined once again. Team reporters are listing Brown as being sidelined by a hamstring injury, though Sirianni’s comments on the matter are vague. For what it’s worth, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo said, “it feels like the hope is” that Brown resumes practicing “sometime in the near future,” adding that he doesn’t “sense any great concern” from the team, regarding the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab52-d45c-a7fc-ab5a7f8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said “sooner rather than later would be nice” when asked about when he would like to name the QB1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-adfa-d90d-a5bd-affbec7a0000</link>
      <description>Speaking Thursday, Steichen said he doesn’t “have an exact timetable” on when he will name the Colts’ QB1, but with the Colts’ second preseason set to take place on Saturday against the Packers, it wouldn’t be surprising if Steichen came to a decision on his QB1 before the preseason finale in order to avoid starting him in a meaningless game. Anthony Richardson played only seven snaps last week against the Ravens before exiting the game with a dislocated pinky finger. Steichen will undoubtedly want to get a longer look at him this weekend as he looks to cement his decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-adfa-d90d-a5bd-affbec7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Akron Beacon Journal’s Chris Easterling reports Browns LB Devin Bush’s trial for his domestic violence case has been scheduled for December 2nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae18-d05a-adda-ae9a571a0000</link>
      <description>Bush was arrested in May and faces charges of assault and harassment. The late trial likely means Bush will be available for the Browns for much of the season, as their regular-season schedule concludes on January 4th when they face the Bengals in Week 18, but a late-season suspension, or one to kick off the 2026 campaign, could be on the table should the league pursue one after the trial has concluded. Bush signed a one-year contract with the Browns this offseason after totaling 76 tackles, one sack, and eight TFLs for them last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae18-d05a-adda-ae9a571a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Stone (soft tissue) returned to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae5f-df63-a199-ff7fa59c0000</link>
      <description>Stone was listed as week-to-week last weekend after dealing with an unspecified soft tissue injury. Instead, the veteran safety missed less than a full week of practice and was spotted on the field Friday with the rest of the team. Stone totaled 81 tackles and four interceptions for the Bengals last season and signed a restructured deal this offseason. Barring any setbacks, it sounds like he’ll be good to go for Week 1 when the Bengals take on the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae5f-df63-a199-ff7fa59c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
