<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OT Joe Alt (ankle) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0349-d99b-a1df-3b4d47a20000</link>
      <description>He was limited twice last week in practice before being called doubtful and scratched on Sunday. The Chargers also had Austin Deculus (ankle) and Trey Pipkins (knee) limited on Monday, leaving Foster Sarell and Bobby Hart as their current healthy alternatives on the roster. Hart started last week, and Deculus was relieved by Sarell with both Alt and Pipkins inactive. It would be nice if Alt could be ready for Week 8, but it doesn’t feel like something we can count on at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0349-d99b-a1df-3b4d47a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots claimed LB Caleb Murphy off waivers from the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-035a-d651-a9df-6b5fe8770000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old former Titans UDFA had been a rotational pass rusher for the Chargers this year, seeing 88 pass rush snaps of his 129 total snaps in six weeks with the team. He’ll likely be tried in the same role in New England, now reunited with former head coach Mike Vrabel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-035a-d651-a9df-6b5fe8770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills designated CB Maxwell Hairston (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0364-d651-a9df-6b751e570000</link>
      <description>His 21-day practice window will open, so the Bills will have three weeks to see him in practice before they have to activate him. Hairston sprained his knee early in training camp and, whenever he makes his Bills debut, it will be the first time we have any film of him on an NFL field. We’d bet on the Bills taking a conservative approach with the rookie first-rounder during his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0364-d651-a9df-6b751e570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) will play in Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-034e-d99b-a1df-3b4ef5b30000</link>
      <description>It was reported over the weekend that Egbuka had “a real chance to play” after returning to practice for a limited session on Saturday. Now, according to Rapoport, Egbuka’s pregame workout “went well,” putting him in position to suit up for a clash between to NFC titans. After suffering his injury in Week 6 against the 49ers, the initial fear was that Egbuka would miss at least one game. Given what we know about soft-tissue injuries, it’s hard to know how effective Egbuka will be without a full week of rest. Fantasy managers choosing to play him in what is undoubtedly a plus matchup do so at their own risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-034e-d99b-a1df-3b4ef5b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roquan Smith (hamstring) said he expects to play in Week 8 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0382-d651-a9df-6b97797e0000</link>
      <description>Smith has missed the last two games with a hamstring injury but was able to log a practice in his return from the Ravens bye week. With several days to go until Sunday’s game against the Bears, Smith is clearly trending in the right direction heading into a pivotal matchup with the Ravens’ season on the line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0382-d651-a9df-6b97797e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin, OG Luke Haggard, S Sebastian Castro, DL C.J. Brewer, CB Kindle Vildor, and RB Josh Williams inactive for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038a-df81-ab9b-7fcf743b0000</link>
      <description>The two key fantasy players here, Irving and Godwin, were ruled out long before Monday. While they are both out, rookie Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) who suffered an injury a week ago, is able to suit up and will play opposite Mike Evans in a game that should be ripe for fantasy scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038a-df81-ab9b-7fcf743b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions OT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is active for Week 7 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038d-d99b-a1df-3b8dd4960000</link>
      <description>Decker was questionable entering the week and was a DNP on Saturday after logging limited practices the previous two days. The veteran tackle hasn’t played since Week 4’s game against the Browns, and should provide an immediate boost to the passing game and protecting Jared Goff. While Decker is active, the Lions have declared CB Terrion Arnold, DL Quinton Jefferson, S Kerby Joseph, CB Avonte Maddox, S Jammie Robinson, RB Sione Vaki, and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Monday night’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038d-d99b-a1df-3b8dd4960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans (hamstring) is active for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</link>
      <description>Evans was trending in this direction all week, but will officially return on Monday night against the Lions. The veteran receiver will pair up with rookie Emeka Egbuka, who is going to attempt to play through a hamstring injury of his own after going down in Week 6 against the 49ers. Assuming they’re both in top shape, Evans and Egbuka should give Baker Mayfield plenty to work with in a game that is expected to feature a lot of scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed J.J. McCarthy (ankle) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</link>
      <description>Just over 24 hours ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said “don’t be surprised” if Carson Wentz starts in Week 8. The decision to start Wentz will be spun as one that came down to the health of McCarthy’s ankle, but ever since McCarthy was unexpectedly diagnosed with a high-ankle sprain after a Week 2 loss to the Falcons, questions have been raised about the team’s commitment to him as their starter. McCarthy was limited in all of practice last week. Another week of limited practices would suggest he is close to a return even if Wentz draws another start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz (shoulder) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</link>
      <description>The injury is to Wentz’s non-throwing shoulder, which should be a good sign for his availability overall. Whether or not Wentz plays in Week 8 against the Chargers likely comes down more to the health of J.J. McCarthy (ankle) than his own and whether or not the Vikes are ready to hand the keys back to the 2024 first-rounder. Wentz has thrown for 1,072-5-4 in four games for the Vikings this season but struggled mightily in his last outing against the Eagles (313-0-2). He’ll be a fantasy QB2 if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
