<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers (hand) is questionable to return in Week 11 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4c-d673-a39e-aedd878d0000</link>
      <description>What was initially believed to be a left wrist injury is now being classified as a left hand injury. Rodgers did not return to the field in the second half of Sunday’s game, leaving Mason Rudolph to take over for the time being. We will be sure to provide an update if Rodgers returns and/or is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4c-d673-a39e-aedd878d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared WR Tory Horton, QB Jalen Milroe, WR Jake Bobo, LB Jared Ivey, LB Connor O’Toole, and T Mason Richman inactive for Week 11 against the rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4e-d1e7-a1fa-deeea7b80000</link>
      <description>Horton will miss a second straight game with injuries to his groin and shin. That will mean Cooper Kupp and Rashid Shaheed will function as the Seahawk’s No. 2 and No. 3 receivers, respectively, against the Rams. Kupp is a usable WR3 in PPR formats while Shaheed is a high-variance flex option in deep fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4e-d1e7-a1fa-deeea7b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Penix (knee) is questionable to return in Week 11 aganist the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e51-d673-a39e-aed1d1fd0000</link>
      <description>Penix took a hit to the knee in the third quarter and was slow to get up. He went to the sideline for a look by the medical staff and was later seen on the bench with his helmet off. Kirk Cousins has taken his place in the lineup and will likely be under center for the remainder of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e51-d673-a39e-aed1d1fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dulcich caught 2-of-4 targets for 18 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 11 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4c-d45b-affe-dfde01600000</link>
      <description>Dulcich earned a healthy 20 percent target share but managed just 3.8 PPR points. Fellow Miami tight end Julian Hill was targeted just once. Dulcich will barely hit the TE2 ranks when he returns from the Dolphins’ upcoming bye to face the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e4c-d45b-affe-dfde01600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 10-of-18 passes for 81 yards, zero touchdowns and an interception in the Chargers’ Week 11 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e55-d45b-affe-dfd7ccb30000</link>
      <description>With the Chargers inconceivably down 35-6 early in the fourth quarter, Herbert headed to the showers early. It was, as you can see, an inexplicably disastrous performance, one where Herbert at least managed to tack on three carries for 21 yards. Dealing with a nonexistent rushing attack and shaky offensive line, Herbert just couldn’t get anything going even as the Jags’ offense was nothing special. His interception was a fourth quarter air mail before his benching. Herbert and the Bolts have been all over the map this year, but a common denominator is that they have not been the same without LT Joe Alt, who is now done for the season. Herbert does have the Bolts’ Week 12 bye to lick his wounds before a Week 13 date with the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e55-d45b-affe-dfd7ccb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims is active for Denver’s Week 11 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e5d-d1e7-a1fa-deffd2660000</link>
      <description>He’ll try to get his WR3 role or a split back from Pat Bryant today. Inactive for the Broncos are CB Patrick Surtain (pectoral), LB Alex Singleton (illness), LB Jonah Elliss (hamstring), T Geron Christian, DL Jordan Jackson, and DE Sai’vion Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e5d-d1e7-a1fa-deffd2660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Isiah Pacheco (knee) is inactive for Kansas City’s Week 11 game against Denver.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e60-d673-a39e-aef1185c0000</link>
      <description>Ruled out on Friday, Pacheco is the only player with an injury status for the Chiefs this weekend. They also healthy scratched: CB Joshua Williams, WR Jalen Royals, TE Jared Wiley and OL Hunter Nourzad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e60-d673-a39e-aef1185c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DB Jalen Ramsey was ejected in the fourth quarter of Week 11’s game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e57-d1e7-a1fa-deff7ab90000</link>
      <description>Ramsey had been jawing with Ja’Marr Chase throughout the day, but things finally escalated in the fourth quarter on back-to-back plays. The two had previously been flagged for unsportsmanlike conduct, and on the following play, Ramsey could be seen getting in the face of Chase before grabbing his helmet and throwing a punch. We’re less than a week removed from Commanders DT DaRon Bland being suspended for throwing a punch on Amon-Ra St. Brown, and it wouldn’t be surprising if a one-game suspension was handed down to Ramsey in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e57-d1e7-a1fa-deff7ab90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mecole Hardman has ruled out for the remainder of Week 11 with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de4-d1e7-a1fa-dfeef7640000</link>
      <description>Hardman was signed to Buffalo’s practice squad this week and then signed to the active roster on Saturday night. His Bills career began with an electric 61-yard kickoff return. He later fumbled on a punt return where he should have called a fair catch. That was his last play of the game, but the Bills ruled him out with a calf injury. It does make you wonder how long his Bills tenure will last.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8de4-d1e7-a1fa-dfeef7640000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
