<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e04-d95b-addb-7e46a6910000</link>
      <description>Ricard has not practiced the entire season and continues to be held out of practice with a calf issue. The Ravens had not placed him on injured reserve, but the injury seems to be a lengthier issue than expected. Ricard is a key part of the Ravens’ blocking schemes, which have struggled at times without the 31-year-old. Also out was OT Ronnie Stanley (ankle). The Ravens are banged-up in the trenches heading into Week 4 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e04-d95b-addb-7e46a6910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Will Dissly (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e0b-deb6-a7fd-7fdf336c0000</link>
      <description>Dissly continues to miss time with a knee issue that kept him out for Week 3. Rookie Oronde Gadsden took over at tight end with Dissly sidelined while veteran Tyler Conklin did not catch any of his targets against the Broncos. Fantasy managers should expect another Gadsden boost should Dissly miss Week 4. WR Derius Davis (knee) also missed practice on Wednesday. He is primarily a returner, so there is little impact for fantasy managers if Davis misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e0b-deb6-a7fd-7fdf336c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OG Mekhi Becton (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e13-dca3-a9fb-7f9be92d0000</link>
      <description>In addition to Becton, center Bradley Bozeman (back) also did not practice Wednesday. The Chargers’ interior offensive line is banged up to start the week and will have a couple days to return to practice ahead of a Week 4 showdown against the Broncos. Should Bozeman and Becton miss time, Omarion Hampton will have a tough time finding running lanes against the Denver defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e13-dca3-a9fb-7f9be92d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) is doubtful for Week 4 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e1d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2eb0000</link>
      <description>Johnson did not practice all week after already missing Week 3. He is listed as doubtful to play Thursday against the Seahawks. Meanwhile, fellow CB Darren Hall (ankle) is listed as questionable. Also questionable are LB Akeem Davis-Gaither (elbow) and OL Kelvin Beachum (knee), Evan Brown (heel), Paris Johnson Jr. (knee), and Will Hernandez (knee). Missing Johnson and Brown especially would deplete the left side of the Cardinals’ offensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e1d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfc2eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OT Josh Jones (ankle) is out for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e23-dca3-a9fb-7fbb263e0000</link>
      <description>Jones did not practice all week with an ankle injury and is out for Thursday’s game against the Cardinals. He has played sparingly in the Seahawks’ three games as depth for the offensive line. OG Anthony Bradford (back) and LB Boye Mafe (toe) are both listed as questionable while S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) is doubtful for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e23-dca3-a9fb-7fbb263e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants K Graham Gano (groin) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e38-d6e9-af9d-feb836850000</link>
      <description>Gano seemed to strain his groin in warmups on Sunday prior to the Giants’ game against the Chiefs. The team signed Younghoe Koo to the practice squad and now Gano starts out the week not practicing. Gano is trending to miss Week 4 with Koo likely kicking in his place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e38-d6e9-af9d-feb836850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e39-deb6-a7fd-7ffff5260000</link>
      <description>Tuten was listed with a shoulder injury for all of last week’s practices, but was ultimately removed from the injury report ahead of the Jaguars’ Week 3 game against the Texans. The rookie carried the ball six times and played just 12 snaps, which could both be a function of the shoulder injury and LeQuint Allen’s rise as the pass-catching back. Tuten is still trending to play in Week 4, but his utilization may still be low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e39-deb6-a7fd-7ffff5260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e3c-d6e9-af9d-febc815a0000</link>
      <description>Adams has a sore hamstring and sat out of Wednesday’s practice, which is generally a rest day for him anyways. Head coach Sean McVay does not anticipate it impacting Adams’ status for Week 4 against the Colts. The 32-year-old has a 13/213/1 stat line through three games and profiles as a fantasy WR2 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e3c-d6e9-af9d-febc815a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e49-dca3-a9fb-7fd9ea4a0000</link>
      <description>Bowers has been dealing with a knee injury since Week 1, but was taken off the injury report after three limited practices ahead of Week 3. He starts out this week as a full participant and is likely to play Week 4 against the Bears. Fellow tight end Michael Mayer (concussion) did not practice after suffering the concussion in Week 3. Bowers has had a pair of middling games since suffering the injury, but he is still a top-three tight end play for fantasy purposes, especially if Mayer is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e49-dca3-a9fb-7fd9ea4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jacory Croskey-Merritt (knee) missing Wednesday’s practice was “precautionary”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e53-d6e9-af9d-fed3f2d10000</link>
      <description>Fowler reports that Croskey-Merritt was “a little sore” after Sunday’s game against the Raiders, but he has felt better and “the hope is that practice rest is precautionary.” Bill’s addition to the injury report is perhaps a result of a violent running style that scored him a touchdown in Week 3. ESPN Commanders beat report John Keim added the injury is “not considered to be anything serious at all.” Expect Bill to play in Week 4 against the Falcons, though he is still in a committee that caps his ceiling in the RB3 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7e53-d6e9-af9d-fed3f2d10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
