<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 2-of-4 targets for 21 yards in the Commanders Week 4 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9230-deb6-a7fd-d3ff40060000</link>
      <description>It was another forgettable performance for Ertz, who remains a touchdown-dependent fantasy option. Ertz has gone for 38 or fewer yards in three games this season and has caught three or fewer passes in the same number of games. There are likely better options available on waivers than Ertz in Week 5 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9230-deb6-a7fd-d3ff40060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed nine times for 12 yards in the Lions’ Week 4 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9229-deb6-a7fd-d3ffb5880000</link>
      <description>Montgomery got his shot at his weekly touchdown in the third quarter. The Lions got the ball inside the five after a Joe Flacco interception and gave it to Montgomery twice in a row. He couldn’t find paydirt and Amon-Ra St. Brown scored on third down. Jahmyr Gibbs has out-carried Montgomery 37-21 over the past two weeks. Both backs can get home because of how many touchdowns there are up for grabs in Detroit, but his dwindling role makes him a riskier bet for Week 5 versus the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9229-deb6-a7fd-d3ffb5880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco completed 16-of-34 passes for 184 yards and two interceptions in the Browns’ 34-10, Week 4 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9238-d6e9-af9d-9ab87a510000</link>
      <description>Flacco earned himself a fewer more starts last week with an upset win over the Packers. He might have given them all back today with a dreadful showing in Detroit. He looked out of sync with his receivers on both of his interceptions. The first was a heave to Cedric Tillman who stopped on his route, resulting in an overthrow of more than 10 yards. The second was a toss to Jerry Jeudy, who was blanketed in coverage by D.J. Reed. Jeudy lobbied for a pass-interference call while Reed sprinted to the goal line, coming up a few yards short of a pick-six. Flacco also took a trio of sacks and gave way to Dillon Gabriel at the end of the game. Flacco will likely start again next week, but his leash grows shorter with every loss. He is a low-end QB2 for Week 5 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9238-d6e9-af9d-9ab87a510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerome Ford rushed one time for a one-yard loss in the Browns’ Week 4 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9246-d6e9-af9d-9ad6965f0000</link>
      <description>Ford caught one of his two targets for four yards He has one carry and five catches over the past two weeks. Even with a clear role on passing downs, there isn’t enough meat on the bones for him to be a viable fantasy option heading into Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9246-d6e9-af9d-9ad6965f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard rushed 10 times for 49 yards in the Panthers’ Week 4 loss to the Patriots, adding three receptions for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9230-d6e9-af9d-9ab0923c0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard’s calf injury didn’t appear to be an issue, but he was held to a season-low 13 touches as the Panthers failed to sustain drives in a blowout loss. That was especially true through the air, where Bryce Young managed just five yards per attempt. Hubbard’s efficiency hasn’t been anything to call home about this year, either, while he has yet to find the end zone on the ground. He does have two scores through the air, preventing outright fantasy disaster. Young is really struggling, but Week 5 might finally be Hubbard’s week vs. the similarly-downtrodden Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9230-d6e9-af9d-9ab0923c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson rushed one time for a two-yard loss in the Browns’ Week 4 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-924d-d6e9-af9d-9add80ea0000</link>
      <description>Sampson has one carry and zero catches in each of his past two games. The return of Quinshon Judkins, who had 21 carries in Week 4, has eliminated Sampson’s role entirely. Sampson could work his way back into a part-time role at some point, but fantasy managers can’t afford to wait this one out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-924d-d6e9-af9d-9add80ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle rushed nine times for 32 yards in the Panthers’ Week 4 loss to the Patriots, adding a -2 yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9251-dca3-a9fb-bfd9386e0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle has now reached 10 touches in back-to-back blowout game scripts. The difference this time being it was the Panthers losing. Severely short-handed at receiver, the Panthers could eventually need Dowdle for more looks out of the backfield, but he isn’t making enough inroads to be currently startable in 12-team leagues even ahead of a soft Week 5 date with the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9251-dca3-a9fb-bfd9386e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Hurts completed 15-of-24 attempts for 130 yards and two touchdowns in the Eagles’ Week 4 win against the Bucs, adding nine rushes for 62 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-924f-d95b-addb-fa4f33cd0000</link>
      <description>Hurts was hot in the first half, making a few superb intermediate throws and connecting with Dallas Goedert for two short touchdowns against the pass-funnel Tampa defense. His first half sharpness faded in the second half, as the Philadelphia offense ground to a halt and Hurts faced consistent pressure from the Bucs’ front seven. Hurts nearly scored on a long rush in the first half but was stopped at the two yard line. He has nine total touchdowns through four weeks. With his rushing production and touchdown equity via the vaunted tush push, Hurts will once again be an elite fantasy play in Week 5 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-924f-d95b-addb-fa4f33cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku caught 2-of-3 targets for 11 yards in the Browns’ Week 4 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9250-d95b-addb-fa5636540000</link>
      <description>Njoku didn’t have any ceiling games heading into Week 4, but his floor as a high-end TE2 had yet to fall out. He had at least three catches for 37 yards but no more than five for 40 through three games. Even the floor evaporated today with a nine percent target share and three PPR points. Harold Fannin Jr. saw six targets, though he also caught just two passes. Njoku continues to descend the TE2 ranks as he prepares to face the Vikings in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9250-d95b-addb-fa5636540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 4-of-8 targets for 62 yards in the Panthers’ Week 4 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9253-d6e9-af9d-9ad3c6540000</link>
      <description>One of McMillan’s missed connections was a deep-ish drop, but he was the least of the Panthers’ problems in Boston. McMillan dominated target share and air yards as the Panthers’ only viable pass catcher. He has posted back-to-back quiet box scores, but his physical dominance remains easy to spot. It’s just a matter of whether Bryce Young can sustain enough drives to get McMillan the proper play volume. Still yet to score, McMillan will have a golden opportunity in Week 5 against the struggling Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9253-d6e9-af9d-9ad3c6540000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
