<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai had 12 rushes for 23 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 11 win against the Vikings, adding one catch for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f09-d713-ad9e-ef5d91750000</link>
      <description>D’Andre Swift once again led the Chicago backfield, this time with 21 carries for 90 scoreless yards as Monangai — the bigger back in the Bears backfield — continued seeing inside-the-ten work. The rookie now has three rushing scores in 2025. Swift logged 12 pass routes on the day while Monangai had 11 — a surprisingly even split considering Swift’s usual role as the clear-cut pass-catching back for Caleb Williams. Monangai will continue to have deep league flex appeal in the Bears’ run-heavy offense. He’ll be a top-30 option next week against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f09-d713-ad9e-ef5d91750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said, “Obviously, there was a chance, but it was not looking good,” when asked about Michael Penix (knee) returning in Week 11 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f0e-d45b-affe-df9e94360000</link>
      <description>Morris added, “It didn’t feel great.” Penix was bent backward while taking a sack in the third quarter. He managed to walk off under his own power and was listed as questionable to return. He never retook the field despite the game making it to overtime. His status for Week 12 is up in the air as of Sunday night. Kirk Cousins will make his second start of the year if Penix can’t suit up versus the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f0e-d45b-affe-df9e94360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coltson Loveland caught 3-of-4 targets for 40 yards in the Bears’ Week 11 win against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f13-d673-a39e-af9362180000</link>
      <description>The efficient Loveland continues to be a tertiary pass catcher in the Bears’ run-heavy offense. He ran 21 routes in Week 11 to 26 routes for Cole Kmet, who two catches for 45 yards on five targets. When Kmet is healthy and in the lineup, Loveland is hardly playable in 12-team leagues. Loveland has 15 receptions over Kmet’s past five healthy outings. He’ll be a desperation streaming play in Week 12 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f13-d673-a39e-af9362180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared CB Terrion Arnold, DL Quinton Jefferson, S Kerby Joseph, WR Tom Kennedy, RB Craig Reynolds, and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Week 11 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f10-d45b-affe-df9620490000</link>
      <description>Both Arnold and Joseph will miss their third games of the season as the Lions prepare to face the Eagles on Sunday Night Football. The Lions have dropped two of their previous four games after starting the season 4-1 as the aim to keep pace with the Lions and Packers atop a congested NFC North.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f10-d45b-affe-df9620490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs LG Kingsley Suamataia (concussion protocol) left Kansas City’s Week 11 game against the Broncos and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d673-a39e-af972e8f0000</link>
      <description>He was ruled out early in the second half. Mike Caliendo is getting snaps in his stead at left guard. Suamataia has been a much better player in his second season at left guard after a rough rookie season at left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d673-a39e-af972e8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy rushed 19 times for 88 yards in the Giants’ Week 11 loss to the Packers, adding four receptions for 51 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d1e7-a1fa-dffe03170000</link>
      <description>The 88 yards rushing were the fourth most of Tracy’s career, and a new season high. His 51 receiving yards were the second most of his career. So naturally he continued to lose goal-line work to Devin Singletary, who produced two touchdowns on his 16 carries. Frustrating, though Tracy has now firmly moved ahead of Singletary as the Giants’ 1A back as they look to mix and match their backfield down the stretch. With Jaxson Dart (concussion) likely back for Week 12 against the Lions, Tracy will be an upside RB2/FLEX option for what could be a high-scoring game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d1e7-a1fa-dffe03170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (knee) is active for Week 11 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d673-a39e-af9725650000</link>
      <description>Jurgens returns to the Philadelphia offensive line after missing the previous two games with a knee injury sustained in Week 7, just in time for one of the more difficult rushing matchups in the league against the Lions. Inactive for the Eagles are QB Sam Howell. RB A.J. Dillon, CB Mac Williams, G Drew Kendall, and NT Ty Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f16-d673-a39e-af9725650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney caught 3-of-7 targets for 34 yards in the Falcons’ Week 11 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f15-d45b-affe-df9742fa0000</link>
      <description>Mooney caught three passes in his previous three games combined. Reeling in three balls in this game is an improvement, but it was still a rough day for Mooney. He continued to struggle with drops and averaged an inefficient 4.9 yards per target. Drake London got injured late in this game and could miss Week 12. Mooney will cling to WR4 life if London is out. He will otherwise be off the fantasy radar entirely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f15-d45b-affe-df9742fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson rushed 11 times for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 11 win over the Giants, adding a nine-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f19-d45b-affe-df9f46b60000</link>
      <description>With Josh Jacobs lost to a second quarter knee injury, Wilson was thrust into No. 1 duties for the final two-plus quarters. Wilson’s churning 11-yard touchdown run was nice in the second frame, but he was otherwise low on highlights as the Pack just tried to survive and advance in Jersey. They must now await Jacobs’ MRI results. Coach Matt LaFleur was not forthcoming with updates after the game. If Jacobs is sidelined for Week 12 against the Vikings, Wilson will be a workload-based RB2, one likely backed up by Chris Brooks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f19-d45b-affe-df9f46b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 2-of-3 targets for 14 yards in the Falcons’ Week 11 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f1b-d45b-affe-df9f58990000</link>
      <description>Drake London missed Week 9 and Pitts popped for 59 yards on nine grabs. London has been active for the past two weeks. Pitts, in turn, has four catches for 52 yards in his previous two outings. He is not on the fantasy radar when London is healthy, but that may not be the case in Week 12. London left today’s game with a knee injury and was ruled out. Pitts would sit on the TE1/2 border if London isn’t able to play against the Saints next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f1b-d45b-affe-df9f58990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
