<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:04:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (illness) practiced fully on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a9-d56e-afff-e6e9425f0000</link>
      <description>Warren should be good to go for the Steelers’ Wild Card Round game against the Texans on Monday. The Texans field a top-tier defense, so having the backfield at full strength is helpful. Warren has been splitting work with RB Kenneth Gainwell and can be safely expected to continue doing so in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a9-d56e-afff-e6e9425f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ae-d968-a19b-fcff5c5b0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall did not practice at any point this week. We’d characterize Pearsall as on the pessimistic side of questionable, though we’re sure the 49ers will give him every chance to get active in a must-win playoff game. The 49ers wideout has not played since aggravating his PCL sprain in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ae-d968-a19b-fcff5c5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Jonnu Smith (glute) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-d56e-afff-e6ee0c5c0000</link>
      <description>Mid-week appearances typically indicate that a player suffered an injury in practice. With TE Darnell Washington (arm) sidelined, the Steelers’ tight end group is suddenly looking quite thin. Steelers TE Pat Freiermuth would warrant TE1 treatment if Smith is also sidelined on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-d56e-afff-e6ee0c5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (hamstring) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card matchup against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b1-d35e-a1bf-e5f399b90000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session on Thursday and was seen practicing again today. We’d be surprised if Williams didn’t go on Sunday. He said he feels “confident” he that will play, though it likely wouldn’t be at 100 percent. Austen Pleasants is the reserve tackle that’d be called on if Williams faced an in-game reaggravation of his injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b1-d35e-a1bf-e5f399b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) is not on San Francisco’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b3-d56e-afff-e6fb45f00000</link>
      <description>Kittle got in limited work on Wednesday and Thursday and was spotted practicing again on Friday. He did play against the Seahawks in Week 18 so it’s not much of a surprise that he’ll be ready here. Kittle’s output will be paramount as the 49ers try to find a non-Christian McCaffrey trick over the middle against a fierce Eagles defense. He should make for a top-of-line DFS or Playoff Best Ball play at TE this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b3-d56e-afff-e6fb45f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (ankle) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</link>
      <description>Winters did not practice Wednesday or Thursday and was not seen by media on Friday. The 49ers will give him every hour he can to be healthy as he’s the main incumbent with a chance to play this week. If not, the 49ers will have to turn to Eric Kendricks, Garret Wallow, and possibly new signing Kyzir White in the middle against the Eagles. CB Renardo Green (foot) and DE Keion White (groin/hamstring) are also questionable for the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Bears assistant GM Ian Cunningham for their “president of football” position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4c7-d968-a19b-fcf71f0c0000</link>
      <description>We assume that Cunningham is a front runner to be whatever they want to call him in the front office in Atlanta, we’ll stick with “guy who picks the players” next to Matt Ryan’s Tony Boselli-esque role with the club. Cunningham had been reported to be interviewing for the GM job, not the “president of football” gig. Regardless, he’s a front runner for a job in this front office and the Falcons are the last GM gig still available after the Dolphins filled their vacancy earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4c7-d968-a19b-fcf71f0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions scheduled an interview with Seahawks passing game coordinator Jake Peetz for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-dc7a-af9b-efbf48df0000</link>
      <description>Peetz spent the 2022 season working under Rams head coach Sean McVay as an offensive assistant before being promoted to passing game assistant in 2023. He has served in his current role with the Seahawks since 2024. Lions executive vice president and general manager Brad Holmes spent 2003-2020 as a member of the Rams’ personnel department before accepting his current role in Detroit. Peetz is a natural fit for this job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-dc7a-af9b-efbf48df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions and Commanders scheduled interviews with Ravens QB coach Tee Martin for their offensive coordinator vacancies next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</link>
      <description>Per Jordan Schultz, “has done extensive work for Baltimore’s passing game as a whole” over the last three seasons, “helping propel Lamar Jackson to the 2023 NFL MVP.” Martin coach the Ravens’ wide receivers in the two prior seasons. These are the first reported interviews scheduled for Martin this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders hired David Blough as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</link>
      <description>The former NFL quarterback was on the Lions’ practice squad as recently as 2023. Blough, 30, has just two years of coaching experience, both with the Commanders as their assistant quarterbacks coach. The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala notes that Blough “helped fill in when QBs coach Tavita Pritchard left for Stanford” in November. The Commanders were evidently impressed with Blough’s ability to rise to the occasion. He also interviewed for their vacant offensive coordinator position earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
