<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 21:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Carroll told reporters Sunday that the Raiders are in the market for a backup quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd90-dbe3-a9bb-fdd369c30000</link>
      <description>No surprise, as the raiders will be without QB Aidan O’Connell for up to eight weeks with his fractured wrist. One name that has been floated as a potential replacement is Ryan Tannehill, and even with the 37-year-old sitting out the 2024 season, it would make sense to acquire a player with his experience/relative success rather than roll with Cam Miller as the backup for Geno Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd90-dbe3-a9bb-fdd369c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings waived WR Silas Bolden.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd97-de13-afdc-dfdf40d50000</link>
      <description>Even with the Vikings in need of receiving bodies, Bolden didn’t do enough in camp to justify a roster spot. The Vikings also waived CB Reddy Steward, CB Keenan Garber, RB Tre Stewart, S Mishael Powell, T Logan Brown, OL Zach Bailey, WR Robert Lewis and DL Travis Bell to go along with the previously announced releases of QB Brett Rypien and OLB Cam Gill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd97-de13-afdc-dfdf40d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released DB Tre Herndon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7b-d332-a1fd-df7f7ee70000</link>
      <description>Herndon took preseason snaps with both the Bills and Colts this month. He spent the 2018-2023 seasons with the Jaguars, after signing on with them as an undrafted free agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd7b-d332-a1fd-df7f7ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns waived TE Sal Cannella.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</link>
      <description>Cannella thrived in the UFL over the last two seasons, but didn’t produce enough in the preseason to justify a roster spot; at least to the Browns. Along with Cannella, Cleveland also waived CB Chigozie Anusiem, G Javion Cohen, T Sebastian Gutierrez, DE K.J. Henry, DT Ralph Holley, CB Christian Holmes, CB Keenan Isaac, T Jason Ivey, DE Titus Le, LB Marvin Moody, CB Darius Rush, LB Charlie Thomas III, T Lorenzo Thompson, G Dartanyan Tinsley, TE Mitchell Van Vooren and C Bucky Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots waived OL Layden Robinson with an injury designation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddb2-dbe3-a9bb-fdf356a30000</link>
      <description>Robinson was the fourth-round pick of the Patriots in 2024, but the former Texas A&amp;M standout was unable to stay on the field in his brief time with New England. He could be a candidate for the practice squad if he goes unclaimed/doesn’t find a new job on a 53-man roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddb2-dbe3-a9bb-fdf356a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears placed CB Terell Smith on injured reserve with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd94-de13-afdc-dfdf6b2e0000</link>
      <description>We already knew Smith would miss the 2025 season, but this move makes it official. It’s a terribly unfortunate development for the talented former fifth-round pick. The Bears waived LB Swayze Bozeman, OL Chris Glaser, TE Thomas Gordon, S Mark Perry and DB Jeremiah Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd94-de13-afdc-dfdf6b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles waived QB Dorian Thompson-Robinson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbb-de13-afdc-dffbbe710000</link>
      <description>Even with the injury to Tanner McKee (thumb), the Eagles feel confident enough in their depth at quarterback to let Thompson-Robinson hit the waiver wire. It’s certainly feasible that the team could bring back DTR on the practice squad, but it’s just as likely that he’ll be looking for a new organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbb-de13-afdc-dffbbe710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets waived QB Adrian Martinez.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</link>
      <description>Martinez is a practice squad candidate, but the Jets may choose to go with Brady Cook as the third quarterback behind Josh Fields and Tyrod Taylor. New York also waived LB Jamin Davis, DE Michael Fletcher, T Liam Forandel, TE Zach Kuntz, DB Tanner McCalister and RB Lawrance Toafili.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s John Shipley believes “the Jaguars will look to unload” either Travis Etienne Jr. or Tank Bigsby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</link>
      <description>Shipley adds that if the Jaguars’ trade efforts are unsuccessful, he thinks they will carry Etienne, Bigsby and rookies Bhayshul Tuten and LeQuint Allen Jr. on the final roster and make “one of the two rookies inactive on game day.” Etienne regularly took passing down snaps during preseason play. While Tuten’s explosive traits make him an all-around breakout candidate, it’s possible Allen could sneak into a specialized passing down role if Etienne ends up being traded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Archer of ESPN reports that the Cowboys are releasing OT La’el Collins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</link>
      <description>Collins was signed at the start of August to add depth, but the 32-year-old didn’t do enough in his limited time with Dallas to make the 53-man roster. Collins could be of interest for a team in need of depth, but is unlikely to be more than one of the last few players on the roster as long as he’s still playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
