<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Jayden Daniels (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8280-dca3-a9fb-bf9973530000</link>
      <description>Daniels is on track to play in Week 4 against the Falcons, but this will ultimately come down to whether team doctors clear him. Daniels is said to be feeling good after going through some drills. The 2-1 Commanders will, of course, take the long view with Daniels’ health. If he is ready to play, he will be out there and can be started as a QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8280-dca3-a9fb-bf9973530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8284-d6e9-af9d-8a9424a70000</link>
      <description>He successfully played through the injury in Week 3 and we have no doubts he’ll be able to do so with an extra day ahead of Monday’s game against the Jets. Waddle will be a WR3 in a matchup against a surprisingly-flammable Jets defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8284-d6e9-af9d-8a9424a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8285-dca3-a9fb-bf9d8aca0000</link>
      <description>Mike McDaniel said last week that he expects Waller to make his debut in Week 4, but it’s hard to read much into Waller’s injury status because he’s been limited for most of the last two weeks. Luckily, he’s far enough off the fantasy radar that this is less “annoying for everyone who plays fantasy football” and more “a personal attack solely on the Rotoworld blurbing staff.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8285-dca3-a9fb-bf9d8aca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8288-d95b-addb-eace8b650000</link>
      <description>Titans CB L’Jarius Sneed pretended not to know who Collins was on Wednesday, so Collins decided to actually practice in full. Can this be a smash spot? Well, probably not, the Texans offense is rough. But it can be a WR1 game for Collins coming off a 8/104/1 line against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8288-d95b-addb-eace8b650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans QB Cam Ward (ankle/calf) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828a-dca3-a9fb-bf9badff0000</link>
      <description>There was little doubt that he’d play against the Texans in Week 4 — the entire purpose of the Titans organization is to win two games against the Texans — but this all but confirms it. Ward will be a tough superflex start against a good defense with his rough supporting cast, but he’s shown enough that we can’t rule out the idea of him having a big game entirely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828a-dca3-a9fb-bf9badff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Noah Fant (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828b-d95b-addb-eacfb4b10000</link>
      <description>The Bengals play on Monday night, so Fant has an extra day to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol. Beginning the practice week with a DNP designation is a bad sign though. The Bengals are likely to be without their positional target leader (14) against the Broncos this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828b-d95b-addb-eacfb4b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (toe) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828c-d6e9-af9d-8a9c9d120000</link>
      <description>Pitts was removed from the injury report ahead of Week 3 with this same toe injury and we expect that to remain the case going forward until the pattern changes. Pitts will be an interesting TE2 play against the Commanders, but until we see him featured in the red zone it’s going to be hard to trust him as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828c-d6e9-af9d-8a9c9d120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Samaje Perine (thumb) is practicing in full for Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828e-d95b-addb-eacee33a0000</link>
      <description>The team officially lists Perine with a finger injury, though prior reports specify the thumb. The Bengals’ pass-catching specialist is evidently expected to play this week, though his pass-catching efficacy is in question. The Bengals need all the help they can get if they hope to win games this season. He does not need to be rostered in fantasy though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-828e-d95b-addb-eacee33a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82a5-d6e9-af9d-8ab595180000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner helpfully shared a video of Pearsall and WR Demarcus Robinson, whose three-game suspension recently came to a close, leading positional drills. Pearsall can be seen wearing a white sleeve on his left leg, perhaps to reduce swelling. His participation today puts him on track to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars. He is a low-end WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82a5-d6e9-af9d-8ab595180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82c8-d95b-addb-eace735a0000</link>
      <description>The Saints’ right tackle is now firmly on track to suit up in Week 4 against the Bills. Fuaga entered Week 2 with a knee injury and exited Week 2 with a back injury as well. The 23-year-old was unable to play in Week 3 against the Seahawks. Saints EDGE Chase Young (calf) and OG Dillon Radunz (toe) remain sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82c8-d95b-addb-eace735a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
