<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:01:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d0c-deb1-a39b-2d0ee4dd0000</link>
      <description>Collins suffered the concussion on Monday night versus Seattle. He went down in the fourth quarter and did not return. A significantly short week will make it even harder for him to clear the league’s concussion protocol by Sunday. With Christian Kirk also sidelined, Xavier Hutchinson appears to be the team’s top wideout heading into Week 8. Rookie Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins should both see more work as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d0c-deb1-a39b-2d0ee4dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1c-deb1-a39b-2d1efb850000</link>
      <description>Kirk suffered a hamstring injury in practice last week and was downgraded to a DNP on Friday. The team ruled him out before the weekend. A DNP to start the week suggests Kirk will also miss Week 8’s game against the 49ers. Kirk also missed time to start the year because of a hamstring issue. Fantasy managers can cut ties with him once he is officially ruled out later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1c-deb1-a39b-2d1efb850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed WR Ray-Ray McCloud, formerly of the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d21-d245-adfb-9d7f906b0000</link>
      <description>McCloud has been signed to the Giants’ practice squad. The move reunites McCloud with Giants head coach Brian Daboll. The two spent McCloud’s 2018 rookie season with the Bills, where Daboll served as the offensive coordinator. McCloud barely played that year, catching 5-of-6 targets for 36 yards, but the 29-year-old wide receiver has become a capable returner and can fill in as a rotational receiver as needed. Injuries have thinned out the Giants’ perimeter wide receiver corps, so a Week 8 call-up from the practice squad is in the cards for McCloud. He is not on the FLEX radar in 12-team re-draft leagues, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d21-d245-adfb-9d7f906b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) was seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1a-dab4-a3fb-9f7aeeff0000</link>
      <description>Austin could end up being officially listed as limited today, but his return to practice is a good sign overall. The Steelers’ diminutive wide receiver was taken to the hospital after injuring his shoulder in Week 4 against the Vikings and has not practiced since then. The Steelers (4-2) sit atop the AFC North, and face a talented Packers (4-1-1) team with playoff aspirations. Austin would enter the FLEX conversation if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1a-dab4-a3fb-9f7aeeff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler and Dan Graziano report that they expect the Jets to “consider dealing veterans to acquire draft capital” and “probably will be active sellers.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d51-dab4-a3fb-9f716e410000</link>
      <description>In a linked article, Fowler identifies the Chargers, Chiefs and Texans as the best fits for Jets RB Breece Hall and puts Hall’s odds of being traded at 35.0 percent, for what that’s worth. The 24-year-old running back is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year, and the Jets currently have RB Braelon Allen (knee, injured reserve) and RB Isaiah Davis under contract through 2027. Davis can be stashed, speculatively, at this time. Acquiring draft picks in exchange for Hall makes sense from a team-building perspective. Should he land with the Chargers or Chiefs, Hall’s fantasy-scoring ceiling could rise considerably, operating as a featured player in a high-scoring offense. Things could become complicated upon Chargers RB Omarion Hampton’s (ankle) return from injured reserve in the former scenario. Hall would undoubtedly become the Texans’ lead running back but the positional rotation gets a bit murkier. The ESPN reporters also list EDGE Jermaine Johnson and CB Michael Carter II also potential trade candidates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d51-dab4-a3fb-9f716e410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d27-d5d8-a3ff-fd6744b90000</link>
      <description>Swift was played through this issue and ran for 124 yards and a score on 19 attempts. The team managed his reps in practice but didn’t have any issues with him hitting 20 touches on Sunday. It’s possible the groin injury is getting worse, or this could just be a maintenance day. Thursday’s practice will be more revealing. Fantasy managers will need to make contingency plans if Swift remains out tomorrow. With Roschon Johnson also missing practice because of a back issue, Kyle Monangai could be in line for a massive workload this week. Mongangai should be rostered in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d27-d5d8-a3ff-fd6744b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d4c-d245-adfb-9d5f84400000</link>
      <description>Kincaid sat out the Bills’ Week 6 loss to the Falcons after practice in a limited capacity all week. Their Week 7 bye gave him an extra week to get right, and today’s limited session puts him on track to face the Panthers this weekend, though it would have been nice to see him practice in full today. As long as he upgrades to full participation, fantasy managers can expect to have their TE1 back on the field this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d4c-d245-adfb-9d5f84400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Kmet (back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d75-deb1-a39b-2d7f7e380000</link>
      <description>Kmet suffered the back injury in Week 7’s win over the Saints and did not return. A DNP to start the week already has him on the questionable. If he does miss Week 8, Colston Loveland will finally get the chance to take on a starting role. Loveland has been rotating with Kmet since returning from an injury of his own. The first-round rookie would immediately vault to the top of the TE2 ranks if Kmet is ruled out for Sunday’s game versus the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d75-deb1-a39b-2d7f7e380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d7a-deb1-a39b-2d7e5c310000</link>
      <description>Moore was listed as a DNP on Wednesday last week as well. He was upgraded to a limited session on Thursday and then went full-go for the final practice of the week. We expect a similar practice routine for the veteran wideout this week. With one game over 50 yards all year and 68 serving as his high-water mark, fantasy managers should be treating a banged-up Moore as a WR4 for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d7a-deb1-a39b-2d7e5c310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Joshua Palmer (knee/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d78-dab4-a3fb-9f78fbc10000</link>
      <description>Palmer was forced from play after injuring his knee and ankle while being tackled by a Falcons defender in Week 6. His continued sidelining post-bye indicates he may need another week to rehab the two injuries. Fellow Bills WR Curtis Samuel (ribs) was limited on Wednesday. WR Tyrell Shavers should see increased opportunities this weekend. He is not a reliable FLEX option, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d78-dab4-a3fb-9f78fbc10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
