<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed six times for 27 yards in the Lions’ Week 11 loss to the Eagles, adding 10 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-902b-d1e7-a1fa-daeb5af10000</link>
      <description>The seven opportunities paled in comparison to the 20 of Jahmyr Gibbs, with much of that likely attributed to consistently negative game script as the Lions played from behind throughout. That also included the team being stuffed on five fourth down attempts, the first time they turned the ball over on downs five times since 2022. Montgomery is no stranger to having his workload be tied to game environment, typically much better in a fantasy setting when the Lions are able to control the trajectory of the game. That’s important considering the Lions host the Giants in Week 12, against whom he could return to fantasy relevancy in short order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-902b-d1e7-a1fa-daeb5af10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 4-of-7 targets for 88 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 11 loss to the Eagles, adding nine yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9030-d673-a39e-b4b17e540000</link>
      <description>The Lions felt the impact of playing without tight end Sam LaPorta in this one, particularly considering the lockdown coverage throughout on alpha wide receiver Amon-Ra St. Brown. Williams found paint from 40 yards out in the second quarter on an in-breaking route, simply outrunning coverage up the middle of the field after beating his man inside. It was otherwise a rather quiet showing for the speedy receiver, who caught four of quarterback Jared Goff’s 14 completions. Regardless of the team’s performance, Williams has now recorded back-to-back fantasy relevant outings after the team shook up offensive play caller against the Commanders last week. He has another stellar chance to record solid counting stats for fantasy managers against a Giants team allowing explosive plays through the air at one of the highest rates in the league in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9030-d673-a39e-b4b17e540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 2-of-12 targets for 42 yards in the Lions’ Week 11 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9035-d713-ad9e-fc755f8a0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown was held without a catch in the second half as quarterback Jared Goff completed just two of his final 18 pass attempts. The Lions were also stopped on five fourth down attempts as they struggled through unrelenting pressure and lockdown coverage against an Eagles defense that has now allowed just 16 points to the Packers and Lions their last two games. St. Brown will look to return to fantasy stardom his next time out when the Lions host the Giants in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9035-d713-ad9e-fc755f8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught 1-of-2 targets for nine yards in the Packers’ Week 11 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9038-d45b-affe-d5be33ed0000</link>
      <description>Wicks ran ahead of a returning Matthew Golden (shoulder) but caught the same amount of passes and drew one fewer target. Even as Romeo Doubs dropped everything in sight, the Pack never seemed to consider getting Wicks more involved. Although he is only 24 years old, it is getting late early on Wicks’ dynasty league career. He has no current demonstrated path to 2025 re-draft appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9038-d45b-affe-d5be33ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savion Williams caught a 33-yard pass in the Packers’ Week 11 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903a-d673-a39e-b4bbb8780000</link>
      <description>The third-round rookie’s lone reception was his fourth quarter grab which came against extremely tight coverage on 3rd-and-10. It was a highlight-reel level play, and the longest reception of his young career. Williams is playing extremely few snaps even as the Packers hunt for playmakers, but the rare times he’s on the field, he seems to command targets. Six days shy of his 24th birthday, Williams’ advanced age limits his long-term dynasty appeal, but he remains worth an end-of-bench spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903a-d673-a39e-b4bbb8780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Hurts completed 14-of-28 passes for 135 yards in the Eagles’ 16-9, Week 11 win over the Lions, adding 31 yards and a touchdown on 10 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9038-d673-a39e-b4b9410d0000</link>
      <description>Hurts continues to average the lowest yards per carry of his standout career, still sitting below the 3.7 yards per carry he averaged against the Lions. Much of that can be attributed to being stopped on four tush push attempts on consecutive drives in the fourth quarter after scoring on the same play earlier in the game, the last of which gave the Lions the ball already in field goal position while down 10 with just over two minutes left to play in the fourth quarter. That also marks consecutive games in which head coach Nick Sirianni’s end-game play calling anc lock management came into question. Even so, a retooled defense at the trade deadline has ceded just 16 combined points to the Packers and Lions in their previous two games, something that continues to mask an underperforming offense. Hurts and the rest of the offense seemed to cater to the squeaky wheel in this one, feeding A.J. Brown 11 targets on only 28 pass attempts. The Eagles improve to 8-2 with the win ahead of a meeting with the division rival Cowboys in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9038-d673-a39e-b4b9410d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 26 times for 83 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903e-d713-ad9e-fc7ee0ae0000</link>
      <description>Barkley struggled to get the wheels turning in the first half but made multiple nice runs in the fourth quarter to help the Eagles put the game away, coming close to ripping off chunk gains on multiple occasions in the final frame. Even so, fantasy managers that sunk a first round pick into the veteran are assuredly left wanting more as Barkley now has only two carries of 20 or more yards after amassing 17 such carries during his historic 2024 season. Of note, the Eagles lost center Cam Jurgens and offensive tackle Lane Johnson to aggravated injuries in this one, which is something to keep an eye on ahead of a Week 12 matchup with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903e-d713-ad9e-fc7ee0ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 7-of-11 targets for 49 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9042-d713-ad9e-fc5656b60000</link>
      <description>Brown saw just two downfield targets while primarily working the short areas with slants and outs, an interesting approach considering the Lions were once again down multiple starters in the secondary. The increased targets appear to be more than coincidence after Brown was seen telling fantasy managers to drop him on a livestream of him playing Madden earlier in the week. The outspoken receiver is averaging the lowest yards per game of his standout career, and yet, the Eagles currently sit at an 8-2 record and in the driver’s seat for the only bye out of the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9042-d713-ad9e-fc5656b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 2-of-5 targets for 24 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9046-d673-a39e-b4d71b7b0000</link>
      <description>That now makes seven of nine appearances in which Goedert has managed four receptions or fewer while playing for a seemingly dysfunctional offense now ranked 16th in points per game. Goedert derives the bulk of his fantasy value from an elite red zone role, meaning his weekly range of outcomes remains one of the widest at the position, of current TE1s. That doesn’t change ahead of a divisional tilt against the Cowboys in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9046-d673-a39e-b4d71b7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 1-of-5 targets for eight yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9049-d673-a39e-b4d98fed0000</link>
      <description>Smith doesn’t get a complete pass as he dropped his first target on the first play from scrimmage, but it is noteworthy that quarterback Jalen Hurts peppered A.J. Brown with 11 targets after the outspoken wide receiver was seen telling fantasy managers to drop him on a livestream of him playing Madden earlier in the week. The explosive receiver will look to get back on track in Week 12 when the Eagles face off against the porous defense of the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9049-d673-a39e-b4d98fed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
