<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) is not on Chicago’s final injury report for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f4c-d86f-abdd-7ffd92c20000</link>
      <description>He’ll be active for the first time this season after missing Week 1. Kyler Gordon (hamstring) remains sidelined for the Bears defense. It’s good news for Chicago ahead of their date with the Lions, with Detroit certainly be looking to be more effective in the passing game after Week 1’s blunder in Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f4c-d86f-abdd-7ffd92c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears DT Grady Jarrett (knee) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 2 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f4f-d86f-abdd-7fff09b60000</link>
      <description>Jarrett was able to get in a limited session on Friday after missing each of the first two practices of the week. Jarrett played 46 of the 56 snaps in Week 1 and will likely be dialed back a little even if he is active in Week 2. Andrew Billings and Chris Williams will pick up more slack against Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f4f-d86f-abdd-7fff09b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Roschon Johnson (foot) is not on Chicago’s final injury report for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f52-dc44-a9d9-3f767ffa0000</link>
      <description>It remains something of a mystery how highly the new coaching staff thinks of Johnson since he’s been sidelined for the entirety of training camp with this foot injury. He got in a full practice on Friday for the first time this week. We’d tentatively expect him to be behind Kyle Monangai in the pecking order at running back for Chicago, but we can’t really say that with any certainty. Johnson operated as a goal-line back for the Bears last year and looked better than D’Andre Swift, so that’s a role he could claim if he has the coaching staff’s trust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f52-dc44-a9d9-3f767ffa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out OT Christian Darrisaw (knee) for Week 2 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f33-da67-a99f-fff7d5530000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw’s participation status on Friday is not yet known but he did manage to practice in full on Wednesday before being downgraded to limited on Thursday. He could return in Week 3. The Vikings also ruled out LB Andrew Van Ginkel and CB Jeff Okudah. Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) is questionable to play against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f33-da67-a99f-fff7d5530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Mike Reiss believes the Patriots RB snap distribution could be changing in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f5a-da67-a99f-fffffa310000</link>
      <description>Implied, but not explicitly said, is that this probably will cut in favor of rookie TreVeyon Henderson as the Patriots rushed for only 60 yards in Week 1. Reiss quotes coach Mike Vrabel as saying: “We have to evaluate everything to make sure we’re getting it right based on volume, who’s playing, who’s getting the ball, who’s trying to get the ball.” Henderson could find himself in a nice spot with more volume after Miami’s defense imploded in Week 1. He’ll be on the RB2/RB3 borderline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f5a-da67-a99f-fffffa310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f58-d294-a19b-fff85acd0000</link>
      <description>Boutte was limited on Wednesday but practiced in full on Thursday and Friday. The Patriots’ third-year wide receiver bagged WR2 results last week, carrying over a strong end-of-season streak from 2024. It remains to be seen whether he will prove himself as a weekly fantasy starter. Boutte has strong odds of delivering a fantasy-friendly stat line in Week 3 against a Dolphins pass defense that allowed the fourth-most yards per pass play (9.38) in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f58-d294-a19b-fff85acd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RB Sione Vaki (hamstring) is doubtful for Detroit’s Week 2 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f78-dc44-a9d9-3f7eb7870000</link>
      <description>Vaki got in three limited practices this week, but looks unlikely to be available. When healthy, he’s debatably the RB3 on the team, in a heat with Craig Reynolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f78-dc44-a9d9-3f7eb7870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions DB Kerby Joseph (knee) is questionable for Detroit’s Week 2 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f7a-dc44-a9d9-3f7e41c60000</link>
      <description>Joseph was a surprise add to the injury report with a limited Friday session after practicing in full for each of Detroit’s first two sessions of the week. Late adds are never a good sign. The last thing the Lions need is another defensive injury, but it looks like they might be getting one. We’ll undoubtedly hear more about Joseph over the next couple of days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f7a-dc44-a9d9-3f7e41c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions T Taylor Decker (shoulder) is questionable for Detroit’s Week 2 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f7c-d86f-abdd-7ffd96910000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week and Decker may not be in Terron Armstead territory where we can confidently forecast he’ll play. He appears to be truly questionable and perhaps on the pessimistic side of it. Decker played all 67 snaps last week and 2024 fourth-rounder Giovanni Manu appears to be the backup if the Lions need help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f7c-d86f-abdd-7ffd96910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) will not play in Pittsburgh’s Week 2 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f80-d294-a19b-fff01c170000</link>
      <description>Harmon didn’t practice all week and doesn’t look close to playing yet. The Steelers opted not to place him on injured reserve, but he may only narrowly beat the four-week window at this point. Harmon has to be considered a question mark for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f80-d294-a19b-fff01c170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
