<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:29:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said Luther Burden (ankle) is a “day-by-day” situation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23dc-d8cf-affb-bffe42c40000</link>
      <description>Burden’s availability for Saturday night’s game against the Packers seems to be in some question by this update. We’ll start getting practice reports for that game on Tuesday. It wouldn’t be surprising if Burden wasn’t ready for a short week after leaving Week 15’s game in the third quarter and not returning, but the practice report will give us more of an idea of where he’s at.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23dc-d8cf-affb-bffe42c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Matt Prater (quad) will not play in Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23dd-d1bc-a3fb-a7fdac170000</link>
      <description>The Bills will also be without DT Jordan Phillips. Prater suffered a quad injury in the Bills’ Week 15 win over the Patriots and will miss at least one game with the injury. He was already filling in this season for Tyler Bass (hip/groin), which means the Bills will be in search of their third kicker heading into this weekend’s game against the Browns. The Bills don’t currently have a kicker on their practice squad, so they’ll have to try out a handful of guys this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23dd-d1bc-a3fb-a7fdac170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said “all options are on the table” when asked about Rome Odunze (foot) and intimated they may need to “protect him from himself.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23df-d8cf-affb-bfff28a80000</link>
      <description>The full quote from Johnson was: “There may be a case that we need to protect him from himself a little bit so he can help us down the road.” It doesn’t sound like he’s especially likely to be ready to go against the Packers in Week 16. And the idea of a shut down possibly being in play should have Odunze-reliant managers (assuming they survived last week’s bagel) making other plans for the remainder of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23df-d8cf-affb-bfff28a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots waived LB Caleb Murphy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23e9-d005-a9bf-fbfda2760000</link>
      <description>The Patriots claimed Murphy off waivers from the Chargers in October. The 26-year-old linebacker totaled just two tackles in the five games he appeared in for the Patriots and became expendable after the team signed Chad Muma earlier on Monday. Murphy will now head back to waivers where he can be claimed by any team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23e9-d005-a9bf-fbfda2760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed S Isaiah Oliver (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23ed-d8cf-affb-bfefc0b30000</link>
      <description>Oliver’s season will come to an end with this IR designation. The eighth-year safety has appeared in 14 games for the Jets this season, totaling 55 tackles and three pass breakups while also making two starts. Oliver earned a 49.1 PFF coverage grade this season and spent some time in the slot. He signed a one-year contract with the Jets this offseason and will likely enter free agency next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23ed-d8cf-affb-bfefc0b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said EDGE Jonathan Greenard (shoulder) will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23fd-d8cf-affb-bfff2d1c0000</link>
      <description>Greenard will be a candidate for an offseason extension/restructure with a $22.3 million cap hit and the Vikings entering the offseason over the cap. Greenard finishes his age-28 season with just three sacks after back-to-back seasons of 12.5 and 12 in 2023 and 2024, but the Vikings simply didn’t force as many pass-rush situations in 2025 as the defense struggled to contain the run. He was trying to play through his shoulder injury, but with the Vikings officially out of the playoff picture, Greenard can recuperate ahead of the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-23fd-d8cf-affb-bfff2d1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said “there is a concern” about Ricky Pearsall’s knee and ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2415-d8cf-affb-bc3f9c9f0000</link>
      <description>It’s quite the change in tune from last night when Shanahan said he thought Pearsall would “be alright.” Speaking on Monday, Shanahan said the combination of injuries for Pearsall complicates things, but also said they “shouldn’t rule him out [for Week 16].” This is already shaping up to be something to watch for when the team releases its first injury report on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2415-d8cf-affb-bc3f9c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed S Brandon Jones (pectoral) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2427-d005-a9bf-fc373e4c0000</link>
      <description>Jones suffered the injury in Sunday’s win over the Packers. The decision to place Jones on IR came after an MRI, which could indicate something more serious, although the team has not suggested that at this time. Jones has totaled 78 tackles, seven pass breakups, and one interception in 14 games for the Broncos this season. Safety Devon Key is listed behind him on the depth chart and will presumably take over in Jones’ absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2427-d005-a9bf-fc373e4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewers, DB Elijah Campbell, A.J. Green III, OL Larry Borom, WR Tahj Washington, and DT Matthew Butler inactive for Week 15 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2460-d1bc-a3fb-a564a6230000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here as the Dolphins look to pick up their fifth consecutive win on Monday Night Football against the Steelers. Numerous key injuries to the Pittsburgh side should allow the Dolphins to continue forward with a ground-heavy attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2460-d1bc-a3fb-a564a6230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (illness) is active for Monday Night Football in Week 15 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-246c-d8cf-affb-bc6e199b0000</link>
      <description>Warren was a surprise addition to the team’s injury report earlier Monday but avoided inactivity after going through pre-game workouts. It remains to be seen if he will assume a normal workload, although fantasy managers are likely forced to start Warren with this the final game of Week 15. Inactive for the Steelers are WR Roman Wilson, QB Will Howard, OL Andrus Peat, DT Brodric Martin-Rhodes, OLB T.J. Watt, and DT Derrick Harmon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-246c-d8cf-affb-bc6e199b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
