<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:05:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on Monday Mornings with Mitch, Bills TE Dawson Knox said Dalton Kincaid played the entire 2025 season with a torn PCL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-eb69-d968-a19b-fbf937000000</link>
      <description>Bills beat writer Ryan Talbot notes that “a source close to Kincaid confirmed what Knox said” on the podcast. This certainly comes as a bit of a surprise. Kincaid, who popped up on multiple injury reports this season due to a knee injury, apparently played through the entire season with a PCL injury he suffered in 2024, which caused him to miss some time. We would assume that surgery will be in Kincaid’s future to correct the issue after he was limited to just 253 routes run this season on a career-low 368 offensive snaps, but we’ve yet to see anything from the team to suggest that. Kincaid averaged an impressive 2.70 yards per route run in his limited action, but the Bills offense will be better off in 2026 if they can have him on the field for a full assortment of snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-eb69-d968-a19b-fbf937000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Titans requested an interview with Cowboys DL coach Aaron Whitecotton for their defensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-eba4-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1340000</link>
      <description>Whitecotton also had an in-house interview with the Cowboys to fill their defensive coordinator vacancy, but it’s worth noting that the veteran coach has never served as a defensive coordinator. Whitecotton worked with the Jets under Robert Saleh in the past, so this interview with the now Saleh-led Titans shouldn’t come as much of a surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-eba4-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Titans have spoken to Steelers OC Arthur Smith about their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebae-d56e-afff-efee96f30000</link>
      <description>Smith was with the Titans from 2011 until 2020, when he left to take the role of the Falcons’ head coach. The veteran offensive play-caller has fielded several requests from other teams regarding their offensive coordinator vacancies, and was most recently passed on by the Chargers in favor of Mike McDaniel. Smith’s run-loving ways could pair well in Tennessee for a team short on receiver talent, but he would have his work cut out for him to help turn around what was one of the worst offenses in the league last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebae-d56e-afff-efee96f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Bills are interviewing former Colts QB Philip Rivers for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebb4-dc7a-af9b-efbf69930000</link>
      <description>Rivers is the current coach at St. Michael Catholic High School. The future Hall of Famer, who came out of retirement to try to keep the Colts in the playoff hunt this season, again retired after the Colts were eliminated, but has reportedly been researched by several teams as a head-coaching fit,per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. Rivers is reportedly close with Josh Allen, who is sitting in on head-coaching interviews with the team. Rivers does not have any experience as an NFL coach, and would join the ranks of former Colts interim head coach Jeff Saturday should be land the gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebb4-dc7a-af9b-efbf69930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Todd Monken is “the clear favorite at this point” to land the Giants’ offensive coordinator job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebca-d968-a19b-fbfbf7390000</link>
      <description>Fowler notes that Monken “is still sorting through options” and remains in the mix for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy, but the long-time Harbaugh assistant would make for a natural fit in New York. Monken’s ability to get the most out of his team’s pass attack has been his calling card throughout his career, and he helped lead Lamar Jackson to his second-MVP in 2023 during his first year as the Ravens’ offensive coordinator. With a talented young group of Jaxson Dart, Malik Nabers, and Wan’Dale Robinson already in place, Monken would have plenty to work with out of the gate should he re-join Harbaugh with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebca-d968-a19b-fbfbf7390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders interviewed Steelers DC Teryl Austin for the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebf5-d56e-afff-effd6d110000</link>
      <description>You won’t find many defensive coordinators on the market more qualified than Austin, who has led as the Steelers’ defensive coordinator since 2022 while also holding the same role with the Lions (2014-2017) and the Bengals (2018). Since Austin took over as the Steelers’ defensive play-caller, the team finished in the top-10 in points allowed three times, while ranking in the top-15 in yards allowed twice. This is the first reported interview for Austin, who may or may not be back with the Steelers once they solidify their next head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ebf5-d56e-afff-effd6d110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said EDGE Harold Landry (knee) will not play in the AFC Championship game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1b-dc7a-af9b-efbf109c0000</link>
      <description>Landry didn’t practice all week and played just 11 snaps against the Texans. New England’s backup ends will once again be counted on to make some big splash pressures against the Broncos on Sunday. Landry’s status for the Super Bowl, should the Pats advance, would appear to be questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1b-dc7a-af9b-efbf109c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said WR Mack Hollins (abdomen/IR) and CB Carlton Davis (concussion protocol) are questionable for the AFC Championship game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1c-d35e-a1bf-eddef4920000</link>
      <description>Hollins was just designated to return yesterday, so we’d be a little surprised if he was instantly activated but this gives him a chance. Davis was spotted shedding a non-contact jersey in practice on Friday and would seem to have a real chance to go against Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1c-d35e-a1bf-eddef4920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Bears assistant GM Ian Cunningham for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1f-d968-a19b-fcff0cfe0000</link>
      <description>Cunningham is one of two candidates who are considered the favorites to land the Falcons’ general manager vacancy. Cunningham was hired as the Bears’ assistant general manager back in 2022 and has been on the radar as a potential GM hire for the last several seasons. The Bears’ success undoubtedly makes Cunningham the most attractive he’s ever been as a candidate, as the decision to pair head coach Ben Johnson with second-year quarterback Caleb Williams paid immediate dividends for the Bears, and the emergence of young talents like Colston Loveland and Luther Burden also make for good points. Whether it’s now or in the future, Cunningham’s days with the Bears could be numbered as he continues to generate interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec1f-d968-a19b-fcff0cfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks activated TE Elijah Arroyo from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec3c-d35e-a1bf-edfe20ad0000</link>
      <description>He’ll play in the NFC Championship game, though his role might be small. Arroyo has been sidelined since Week 14 and hasn’t drawn more than two targets since Week 7’s win over the Texans. Perhaps the Seahawks will scheme up some downfield shots to him — the fact that they’re barely doing that with a healthy Rashid Shaheed probably makes Arroyo a stay-away in DFS contests this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ec3c-d35e-a1bf-edfe20ad0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
