<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 12:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields completed 15-of-26 passes for 116 yards and one touchdown in the Jets’ 27-14, Week 11 loss to the Patriots, adding 11 carries for 67 additional yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8094-d713-ad9e-ecd468450000</link>
      <description>Fields and the Jets got off to a strong start to open the game. Picking up one first down after another with primarily his legs, Fields led a lengthy 14-play, 72-yard drive, which he capped with a five-yard rush touchdown to give the Jets the early lead. Unfortunately for Fields, the offense would three-and-out on its next three drives, and didn’t add any additional points until late in the third quarter when Fields connected with John Metchie for a 22-yard score after a Patriots defender slipped in coverage. Fields would fumble a snap in the fourth quarter that resulted in a turnover and a Patriots field goal three plays later, but his conservative play continued to limit turnovers through the air. He took two sacks late in the fourth quarter with the game already out of reach, but Fields’ struggles through the air were noticeable. It doesn’t help that his pass-catchers, specifically Adonai Mitchell, failed to haul in a few catchable passes. Fields entered halftime with just 25 passing yards and continues to fall well short of the passing yard totals we’ve grown accustomed to seeing from a modern-day QB. He’ll be hard to trust as anything more than a dart throw in 2QB/Superflex leagues in Week 12 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8094-d713-ad9e-ecd468450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 19 times for 62 yards and two touchdowns in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets, adding five receptions for 31 additional yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-809d-d673-a39e-a49d29da0000</link>
      <description>The drum beat for Henderson to regain the team’s lead only grows louder. In his second-straight game sans Rhamondre Stevenson, Henderson handled 19 of the team’s 22 running back carries and punched in two seven-yard touchdowns in Thursday’s win. Henderson also saw significant work in the passing game, hauling in all five of his targets for 31 yards and a score that came in the third quarter to put the Patriots up two possessions late in the third quarter. Henderson has now scored five times in the last two weeks and has looked like the better, more explosive back compared to Stevenson. If Stevenson (toe) is unable to play in Week 12 against the Bengals, Henderson will be locked in as a volume-based RB1 against a defense that has struggled all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-809d-d673-a39e-a49d29da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall rushed 14 times for 58 yards in the Jets’ Week 11 loss to the Patriots, adding two receptions for six additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80a2-d713-ad9e-ecf66bbd0000</link>
      <description>Four straight three-and-outs in the second quarter didn’t do much to help Hall’s fantasy upside in Thursday’s loss. The Patriots held Hall to just 58 yards (4.1 YPC) on the day, and he was kept out of the end zone in the first quarter when Justin Fields topped off the Jets’ first possession of the day with a five-yard rushing touchdown. Hall’s volume will continue to keep him in the RB1 mix for Week 12 against the Ravens, but it’s hard to view him as anything more than a boom-or-bust fantasy asset who remains prone to underwhelming weeks given the Jets’ offensive struggles. Hall will be a fringe RB1/RB2 in Week 12 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80a2-d713-ad9e-ecf66bbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adonai Mitchell caught 1-of-6 targets for 10 yards in the Jets’ Week 11 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80a8-d673-a39e-a4b906800000</link>
      <description>Mitchell made his debut with the Jets on Thursday night after being acquired from the Colts in the deal that sent Sauce Gardner to Indy. The second-year speedster did step in to lead the Jets with six targets, but it was an otherwise forgettable day for Mitchell, who was responsible for a whopping three drops in the loss, per PFF. Mitchell let a deep pass slip through his hands in the second quarter and later let another ball slip by him in the third. Fantasy managers in need of a deep stash can add Mitchell off waivers next week, but he shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a WR4/WR5 in Week 12 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80a8-d673-a39e-a4b906800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Metchie caught 3-of-3 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 11 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80af-d673-a39e-a4bf3ab70000</link>
      <description>Metchie’s three targets aren’t anything to write home about, but the third-year receiver made the most of one of his looks when safety Craig Woodson slipped in coverage, allowing Metchie to secure a wide-open target for a 22-yard touchdown late in the third quarter. Metchie is finally on the board for the 2025 season, but is a long way from being a reliable fantasy option. Metchie led the Jets with 23 routes run in Thursday’s contest, but we need to see a little more target volume before we can consider starting him as a deep play. We’ll see if he has any more to offer in Week 12 when the Jets take on the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80af-d673-a39e-a4bf3ab70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 4-of-4 targets for 30 yards in the Jets’ Week 11 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80b6-d45b-affe-d5b626de0000</link>
      <description>It was business as usual for Taylor, who has now gone for 34 or fewer yards in three of his last four games. The rookie tight end is a reliable safety blanket for Justin Fields, but has seen his fantasy stock slip a bit since his 12-target game against the Cowboys in Week 5 against the Cowboys. Fantasy managers in desperate need of help at tight end should continue to avoid Taylor, who has averaged just 4.8 targets per game since Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80b6-d45b-affe-d5b626de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 9-of-11 targets for 105 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80bb-d45b-affe-d5bf93b80000</link>
      <description>Diggs posted his third 100-plus yard game of the season in Thursday’s win over the Jets while also turning in his second double-digit target performance of the year. The veteran receiver was involved early in this one, hauling in three receptions on the Patriots’ opening drive that ended with a seven-yard touchdown run by TreVeyon Henderson. He later popped up for back-to-back gains of 21 and 18 yards in the third quarter on another drive that ended with a Henderson score, and also hauled in a 22-yard reception early in the fourth quarter. Diggs has gone for 14-151-1 in his last two games on 19 targets and will face a porous Bengals defense in Week 12. He’ll be firmly on the WR2 radar in next week’s game, which should be ripe for fantasy points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80bb-d45b-affe-d5bf93b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught 4-of-5 targets for 64 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c1-d45b-affe-d5d753bb0000</link>
      <description>It wasn’t the 106-yard effort we saw from Hollins in Week 10’s win over the Buccaneers, but the veteran receiver continues to be a reliable target for Drake Maye with Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) sidelined. Hollins made back-to-back big plays on the Patriots’ second possession, ripping off gains of 19 and 20 yards to help set TreVeyon Henderson up for his second rushing score in as many possessions. Hollins has gone for 10-170-0 on 15 targets over the last two weeks and has been targeted on 24.6 percent of his routes over that span. He’ll remain hard to trust outside of deep leagues, but in a plus Week 12 matchup against the Bengals, he’ll have some appeal as a WR4 if Boutte misses a third-straight game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c1-d45b-affe-d5d753bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 3-of-3 targets for 36 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c6-d673-a39e-a4d7b2910000</link>
      <description>Douglas’ three targets were good for fifth-most on the team, as both Hunter Henry and TreVeyon Henderson out-targeted him in this one. The third-year slot receiver converted a key fourth-and-short early in the game, but saw his longest gain of 26 yards come on a third-down catch after a defender failed to touch him once he fell to the ground. Douglas is a reliable, sure-handed slot receiver who is on pace for his worst statistical season since entering the league in 2023. There’s just not enough consistent production to make him a reliable option, meaning fantasy managers can continue to fade him in Week 12 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c6-d673-a39e-a4d7b2910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 4-of-6 targets for 45 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80cc-d45b-affe-d5deb2330000</link>
      <description>It’s just the second time since Week 5 against the Bills that Henry has surpassed 40 yards, and he has only one touchdown to show for it over that span. Henry remains good for his weekly 4-to-6 targets per game, but could have a chance at a decent Week 12 matchup against a Bengals defense that is allowing the third-most targets per game (9.8) and fourth-most receptions per game (6.8) to opposing tight ends since Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80cc-d45b-affe-d5deb2330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
