<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:02:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 3-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Texans’ Wild Card win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b5d4-d968-a19b-fdf5a3210000</link>
      <description>Schultz fell victim to a defensive struggle as the game entered the fourth quarter with the Texans nursing a 7-6 lead before two defensive scores broke things wide open. The veteran tight end has a good chance to step into increased usage considering the concussion suffered by alpha wide receiver Nico Collins, particularly considering the tight end-funnel matchup against the Patriots in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b5d4-d968-a19b-fdf5a3210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans will interview former Giants head coach Brian Daboll for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b792-dc7a-af9b-ffbf136b0000</link>
      <description>It’s Daboll’s first head coaching interview request since being fired by the Giants in November following a 2-8 start to the season. Daboll’s tenure with New York got off to a solid start but quickly crumbled, turning into one of the NFL’s most toxic situations. Perhaps his work with a young Josh Allen in Buffalo is appealing to a Titans franchise looking for a head coach who can maximize Cam Ward after an uneven rookie season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b792-dc7a-af9b-ffbf136b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs will interview Ravens offensive coordinator Todd Monken for the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b7a5-dc7a-af9b-ffbf252d0000</link>
      <description>Monken hasn’t parted ways with the Ravens quite yet, but there’s no way he’ll stay on with the team after John Harbaugh was fired in part for refusing to fire Monken. Monken’s Ravens offense was one of the league’s most efficient units over the past few seasons. His work with Baker Mayfield in Cleveland for one season could make Monken an appealing hire for a Bucs team looking to right the offensive ship after a rocky second half of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b7a5-dc7a-af9b-ffbf252d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio believes it’s “hard to imagine” Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin not coaching in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b809-dc7a-af9b-ffbf121f0000</link>
      <description>Tomlin said after the Steelers’ Wild Card loss to the Texans that he was not in the “mindset” to make a decision on whether he’ll return to Pittsburgh in 2026. “I’m more in the mindset of what transpired in this stadium, and certainly what we did and didn’t do. Not a big-picture mentality as I sit here tonight,” Tomlin told reporters after yet another first-round playoff exit for his Steelers. Florio points out that Tomlin, who will turn 54 in March, has been coaching since the mid-90s when he started at Virginia Military Institute following his playing career. He’s won 63 percent of his games over 19 years as Steelers head coach. “For now, the question is whether Tomlin wants to spend a 20th year with the Steelers,” Florio said. “On one hand, why wouldn’t he? On the other hand, hearing the ‘fire Tomlin!’ chants during the Week 13 loss to Buffalo may have caused him to rethink sticking around in a place where, come next year, those chants could get louder.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b809-dc7a-af9b-ffbf121f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panther general manager Dan Morgan said a long-term contract for QB Bryce Young is “up in the air.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b838-d56e-afff-fef8127c0000</link>
      <description>“We’re still talking through the roster,” Morgan said of a long-term extension for Young, whose play improved in 2025 as the Panthers made the postseason for the first time since 2018. “It’s up in the air and we’re still working through it.” Young in 2025 had a career-high 45 percent drop back success rate, in line with Caleb Williams and Tyler Shough. He also posted a career-best 6.3 adjusted yards per attempt. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported reported the Panthers are expected to pick up Young’s fifth-year option this offseason. It would be surprising if Carolina committed to Young, 24, long term in the coming months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b838-d56e-afff-fef8127c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins interview former Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b83e-d35e-a1bf-fdfe15c70000</link>
      <description>Stefanski, the two-time head coach of the year during his tenure with the Browns, could have his choice of open head coaching gigs. He’s interviewed with the Falcons, Giants, Ravens, and Titans, and now is in talks with a Dolphins team that recently fired Mike McDaniel. Stefanski during his time with Cleveland was a creative offensive play designer and play caller who was hamstrung by ownership with a Deshaun Watson contract that ranks among the worst in the history of pro sports. His history of quarterback development will be appealing to any team looking to get the most out of their young QBs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b83e-d35e-a1bf-fdfe15c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers picked up QB Bryce Young’s fifth-year contract option.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b850-d35e-a1bf-fdd2bb120000</link>
      <description>Carolina general manager Dan Morgan said Tuesday that the team would exercise Young’s option. Young in 2025 showed signs of life as a viable starting NFL quarterback, posting career highs in drop back success rate (45 percent) and adjusted yards per attempt (6.3). Young now has 49 touchdowns to 30 interceptions over three NFL seasons. Morgan added Tuesday that the Panthers were “up in the air” about a long-term deal for Young, 24. He’ll be the team’s starter for at least the next two years in any case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b850-d35e-a1bf-fdd2bb120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said the team would be “very aggressive” in retaining defensive coordinator Brian Flores.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b868-d968-a19b-f8f9e85a0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings are reportedly working on a new contract for Flores, one of the game’s best defensive minds who headed a Minnesota defense that allowed the league’s third lowest EPA per play in 2025. Flores, who once served as Dolphins head coach, could be a head coaching candidate for some of the teams looking to hire in the coming days and weeks. The Commanders are in talks with Flores about their defensive coordinator vacancy. It appears the Vikings are ready to do whatever it takes to keep Flores for 2026 and beyond, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b868-d968-a19b-f8f9e85a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Commanders are hoping to interview Vikings defensive coordinator Brian Flores for the team’s defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b86d-d56e-afff-feedc0f10000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear if the Commanders have formally requested an interview with Flores, whose Minnesota defense terrorized opposing passers and allowed the NFL’s third lowest EPA per play in 2025. In Washington, Flores would be taking over a talent-bereft defense that was among the league’s worst against the rush and the pass in 2025. Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said Tuesday that the team would be “very aggressive” in retaining Flores for 2026 and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b86d-d56e-afff-feedc0f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper believes the “tenor surrounding [Chargers offensive coordinator Greg] Roman has very clearly changed” after the team’s Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b879-d56e-afff-fef9c5940000</link>
      <description>A dejected Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh was non-committal about Roman’s return as OC following LA’s blowout loss to the Patriots on Sunday night — a loss that saw Justin Herbert have one of his worst games as a pro as the Chargers scored just three points. The team’s offensive lineman, including Bradley Bozeman, were circumspect when asked whether Roman should return as the team’s OC in 2026 and call plays. “That’s their call upstairs,” Bozeman told The Athletic. Widely considered a run-first coordinator, Roman’s Bolts offense in 2025 ranked eighth in pass rate over expected, ranking 13th in total pass attempts. It would hardly be a shock if the Chargers moved on from Roman after two mediocre seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b879-d56e-afff-fef9c5940000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
