<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (abdomen/groin) and CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) were estimated full participants in Wednesday’s walk-thru practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363b-d332-a1fd-b63f5bd10000</link>
      <description>Moore took a big hit towards the end of the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings, giving fantasy managers concerns over his health status. He finished out the game and is now estimated as a full participant in Wednesday’s walk-thru, indicating he is good to go. Meanwhile, Johnson sat out Week 1 with his injuries and appears to be a step closer to returning with a full practice estimation on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363b-d332-a1fd-b63f5bd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363f-db7b-a5dd-b63f2e8a0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter had reported yesterday that Jennings was “day-to-day” with a shoulder issue. The 28-year-old was hurt in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks, but and MRI did not show extensive damage to his shoulder. He starts out the week missing practice, putting his status to return immediately for Week 2 in jeopardy. With George Kittle on IR and Brock Purdy likely out, the 49ers are running out of fantasy-relevant offensive players early on in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363f-db7b-a5dd-b63f2e8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf/rest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3649-d332-a1fd-b67fd0a90000</link>
      <description>There’s a chance we see McCaffrey pop up with the calf/resting player designation several times throughout the season as the 49ers try to manage his workload and prevent aggravation of his prior calf injury. His limited practice last week had fantasy managers concerned, but he took on a large workload in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks. Expect McCaffrey to play in Week 2 while continuing to take on a large offensive workload with nearly every other offensive skill player hurt for the 49ers..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3649-d332-a1fd-b67fd0a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Brock Purdy is expected to miss 2-5 weeks “with a turf toe variant.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-38c2-d3c5-a9f9-3cf7b77b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport specifically said his “understanding is that Purdy is out 2-5 weeks.” We will likely get a more definite timeline from Kyle Shanahan in the coming days, but it sounds like Purdy is a near lock to miss Week 2’s game against the Saints and is also unlikely to play in Week 3 against the Cardinals. Purdy is reportedly dealing with a ligament injury that is affecting the bottom of his foot, and his absence will pave the way for Mac Jones to make his first start in a 49ers uniform since being acquired by the team this offseason. All fantasy expectations for all pass-catchers in the Niners’ offense should be scaled back a bit in Jones’ first start. However, Jauan Jennings’ (shoulder) Week 2 status is murky and George Kittle (hamstring) is on injured reserve, which could result in a busy day for Ricky Pearsall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-38c2-d3c5-a9f9-3cf7b77b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports Cowboys CB DaRon Bland (foot) could miss multiple weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3938-d903-afbd-fdfc2fbd0000</link>
      <description>Bland suffered a right foot injury in Monday’s practice and was a DNP on Wednesday. Bland suffered a stress fracture to his left foot last season that required surgery and resulted in him missing seven games last season. Archer reports this new injury is not considered as serious as last year’s, which leads us to believe surgery is not on the table at this time. However, his Week 2 absence against the Giants could prove costly for a Cowboys secondary that is still working Trevon Diggs (27 snaps in Week 1) back into the mix. We’ll likely get an official word on Bland’s availability by the end of the week, but it’s possible a stint on the IR could be in his future if the team believes his recovery will stretch beyond four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3938-d903-afbd-fdfc2fbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chris Godwin (ankle) is expected to practice in a limited capacity on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3940-d903-afbd-fdec78750000</link>
      <description>Godwin is recovering from a second surgery he underwent in the spring to repair some hardware he had put in his ankle. It was reported earlier that Godwin and the Bucs are targeting a Week 5 return, but Rapoport reports “Week 6 is also possible” as a return date. The Buccaneers made the decision to keep Godwin off injured reserve to start the season, and now appear ready to ramp him up for a return next month. If all goes well, Godwin is likely looking at multiple weeks of practice before he takes to the field. He avoided injured reserve to start the year, but there’s little reason to expect an early return, keeping the fantasy stocks for Mike Evans and rookie Emeka Egbuka high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3940-d903-afbd-fdec78750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers beat writer Rick Stroud reports Tristan Wirfs (knee) is expected to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3962-d903-afbd-fdee89160000</link>
      <description>Wirfs and Chris Godwin (ankle) are both making their practice debuts on Thursday as the team plans to ramp them up for a return. Wirfs underwent knee surgery in July but avoided a stay on short-term IR to open the season, indicating he could have a shot at returning before Week 5 if all goes well. Second-year lineman Graham Barton drew the Week 1 start against the Falcons in Wirfs’ absence and allowed three pressures and three hurries, on 38 pass-blocking snaps, per PFF. Wirfs will likely practice in a limited capacity on Thursday and seems unlikely to play in Week 2 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3962-d903-afbd-fdee89160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns OC Tommy Rees said the team will “take it day to day to see how (Quinshon Judkins) continues to progress in practice.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-397a-d8e3-affd-7bfab2e00000</link>
      <description>Judkins is finally set to practice with the Browns for the first time since his July arrest. The rookie second-rounder could have a chance to suit up in Week 2 against the Ravens, but it doesn’t sound like the team is rushing to put him on the field after missing all of training camp. Even if he is active, expectations for Judkins should be low out of the gate, as the team will likely have him on a snap/touch count as he continues to get up to speed. Rookie Dylan Sampson will be the only fantasy viable running back for the Browns in Week 2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-397a-d8e3-affd-7bfab2e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on KNBR Thursday, 49ers GM John Lynch said Brock Purdy (foot) will not play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-398c-d903-afbd-fdec1c930000</link>
      <description>In addition to ruling Purdy out for Week 2’s contest against the Saints, Lynch also declined to put a timeline on his QB1’s recovery. Hours after NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported Purdy would be looking at a 2-5 week absence, Lynch said the information the team has received from doctors has them viewing it as “a week-to-week thing.” With Purdy already confirmed as out for Week 2, the 49ers will shift to Mac Jones as their starter and lean on him throughout the duration of Purdy’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-398c-d903-afbd-fdec1c930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones is slated to start in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39a9-d903-afbd-fdedb2400000</link>
      <description>The team did not officially confirm Jones as the Week 2 starter, but speaking on KNBR radio early Thursday morning, General Manager John Lynch confirmed Brock Purdy (foot) would not play in Week 2, leaving Jones as the next man up. Jones signed a two-year, $7 million contract with the 49ers this offseason and was the rumored target of head coach Kyle Shanahan during the 2021 NFL Draft when the Niners used the No. 3 overall pick to select Trey Lance. Viewed as an ideal fit in Shanahan’s system, Jones completed 17-of-23 passes for 209 yards and two interceptions this preseason, and will have his work cut out for him with George Kittle (hamstring) on injured reserve and Jauan Jennings (shoulder) at risk of also missing Week 2. Jones shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a low-end QB2/high-end QB3 in his Niners debut and can be avoided altogether outside of 2QB and superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39a9-d903-afbd-fdedb2400000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
