<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “the belief around the league” is that the Raiders will “move on” from head coach Pete Carroll.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e5-d968-a19b-d9f580970000</link>
      <description>The smoke on Carroll’s impending firing has been out of control all week, with the embattled 74-year-old head coach being a consensus pick to lose his job following today’s game against the Chiefs. The Raiders will have to eat the final two years of Carroll’s contract to fire him. The Raiders definitely haven’t done enough to give Carroll any benefit of the doubt, but it’s still a little surprising that the Raiders will become the first team to one-and-done consecutive coaches since the 2021-22 Houston Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e5-d968-a19b-d9f580970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there is a feeling from many” that Mike Tomlin will remain the Steelers’ head coach through 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89de-d35e-a1bf-cdde39160000</link>
      <description>Tomlin is under contract for one more season. The Steelers haven’t fired a head coach since the 1968 season, and they aren’t likely to break that streak with Tomlin, the league’s longest-tenured boss. Pittsburgh faces Baltimore tonight with the AFC North crown on the line. Fans and pundits will call for Tomlin to be fired if they lose, but we suspect the organization will let him see the end of his contract even if the Steelers miss the postseason. Then Tomlin will have a prove-it year with the team in 2026. He is all but guaranteed his job for next year if Tomlin and the Steelers topple Baltimore tonight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89de-d35e-a1bf-cdde39160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared RB Aaron Jones, WR Myles Price, QB John Wolford, CB Dwight McGlothern Jr., QB Brett Rypien Sr., T Walter Rouse, and TE T.J. Hockenson inactive for Week 18 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e8-d56e-afff-efe8cbed0000</link>
      <description>Facing defensive backups for the Packers, Jordan Mason will likely get a starter’s workload in the Minnesota backfield with Jones sidelined. JJ McCarthy, dealing with a hand injury, will start the regular season’s final game. Look for Justin Jefferson to be peppered with targets as QB-WR combo try to get on the same page ahead of an uncertain offseason for McCarthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e8-d56e-afff-efe8cbed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the “feeling around the league” is that Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon’s job is “safe.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89ea-d56e-afff-efea1f2e0000</link>
      <description>We’re not sure what else Gannon would have to do to lose his job at this point. They’ve reeled off eight straight losses to fall to 3-13 and will face a motivated Rams team today to likely fall to 3-14. Despite massive monetary investments in their defense this offseason, the former Eagles defensive coordinator Gannon has the Cardinals 27th in defensive DVOA. They’ve allowed 40 points four different times during their losing streak, and allowed 37 to the Bengals in Week 17 before they mercifully pulled Joe Burrow. Despite these results, Gannon is apparently viewed as safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89ea-d56e-afff-efea1f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared LB DeMarvion Overshown, CB Shavon Revel Jr., S Alijah Clark, DT Jay Toia, and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive for Week 18 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f990000</link>
      <description>Clark is inactive for personal reasons, but the rest of the inactives are not a surprise. This will end the season for all five defenders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “the feeling ultimately around the league” is that Shane Steichen will remain the Colts’ head coach for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e7-d35e-a1bf-cde7f20e0000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, the same is true of GM Chris Ballard. It’s never entirely fair to blame a single injury for a team’s struggles, but the Colts were the AFC’s No. 1 seed when Daniel Jones suffered a season-ending Achilles injury. Even with Jones’ play dropping off in the second half of the season, he was still doing enough to keep the team in the playoff mix. The Colts would almost certainly be competing for the AFC South title this week had Jones stayed healthy. After watching Steichen turn around Jones’ career en route to an 8-4 record before his injury, there was no way the team could move on from him at the end of the season. The Colts will now be tasked with bringing Jones, an impending free agent, back on a deal that works for both sides. The 2026 season will likely tie together the fates of Steichen, Irsay, and Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e7-d35e-a1bf-cde7f20e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bills head coach Sean McDermott is “safe for now” to return in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89f0-d56e-afff-eff8bf0c0000</link>
      <description>Schefter said McDermott’s job status for 2026 could hinge on winning at least one postseason game in the midst of Josh Allen’s career prime. McDermott since he was hired as Buffalo’s head coach in 2017 is 104-57, mostly dominating a weak AFC East. The Patriots’ rise to prominence with Drake Maye at quarterback has pushed the Bills out of the top spot in the division, and the Bills’ offensive struggles in 2025 raise real questions about whether the team is squandering Allen’s best years. McDermott could be out if the Bills lose in the Wild Card round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89f0-d56e-afff-eff8bf0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared TE Theo Johnson, S Jevón Holland, WR Ryan Miller, WR Jalin Hyatt, RB Dante Miller, OLB Caleb Murphy, and QB Russell Wilson inactive for Week 18 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89f1-d35e-a1bf-cdf358f00000</link>
      <description>Johnson was courtside at the Knicks game on Friday night and was featured on the Jumbotron, but is apparently not feeling well enough to suit up on Sunday. The Giants are no longer likely to earn the first pick in the draft after their win over the Raiders in Week 17, but they could still nab a top-three selection with a loss today and some help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89f1-d35e-a1bf-cdf358f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Davante Adams (hamstring) is not expected to play in Week 18 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e6-d56e-afff-efeed4cf0000</link>
      <description>Adams returned to practice on Thursday for some light practices to close the week. He was listed as questionable, though that seemed like an optimistic designation at the time. The Rams are playing their starters this week in an effort to get the No. 5 seed, but they don’t need to rush Adams back to take down Arizona. Adams will get the week off and should be ready for the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89e6-d56e-afff-efeed4cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) is expected to return for the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a03-d56e-afff-eeeb7f650000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are resting their starters this week, likely netting them the No. 3 seed. Johnson hasn’t played since Week 11 and has reportedly been a week away from returning for the past month. We suspect this time it does indeed count. The Eagles will be roughly at full strength on offense when they open the playoffs at home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a03-d56e-afff-eeeb7f650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
