<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Gunnar Helm (toe) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5208-d56e-afff-f6e876140000</link>
      <description>The Titans have been distributing the ball across the skill position corps in recent weeks, and we see no reason for that to change in Week 17 against the Saints. Helm is a touchdown-dependent fantasy-starter in re-draft formats. His rookie season showings have been encouraging overall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5208-d56e-afff-f6e876140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Watt (lung) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520b-d35e-a1bf-57cb554d0000</link>
      <description>It’s a really good sign for Watt, who hasn’t played since Week 14 after suffering a partially collapsed lung. He was hospitalized just before the team’s Week 15 game and has been out ever since. Watt may still need another week or two before he is ready to return, but it looks like, at worst, he will be back for the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520b-d35e-a1bf-57cb554d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51fd-d35e-a1bf-55ffdc340000</link>
      <description>Njoku’s absences continue to benefit rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr., who leads the team in targets (102), receptions (70), receiving yards (701) and receiving touchdowns (five). Fannin has also been given a carry in consecutive games and scored a one-yard rushing touchdown last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51fd-d35e-a1bf-55ffdc340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (hand) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520f-d968-a19b-5affbf810000</link>
      <description>Sampson should be rostered wherever he is available. With RB Quinshon Judkins joining RB Jerome Ford (hamstring) on injured reserve after fracturing his fibula and dislocating his ankle, Sampson could operate as the Browns’ featured running back, if healthy, in Week 17. Among NFL RBs with 25-plus targets, Sampson (2.07) is the only player to average 2.00 yards per route run or more. He forces missed tackles as a rusher, 0.18 per attempt, at the same rate as Judkins, albeit via a much smaller sample. Sampson’s only competition for backfield touches is UDFA rookie RB Raheim Sanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520f-d968-a19b-5affbf810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520f-dc7a-af9b-dfbfa74d0000</link>
      <description>Austin left Week 16’s game with the hamstring injury. He went down in the second half and was listed as questionable to return but never did. A DNP today stacks the odds against him to suit up on Sunday. With DK Metcalf suspended for the remainder of the regular season, Adam Thielen is seemingly the team’s top wideout for Week 17. Aaron Rodgers will also lean heavily on his tight ends versus the Browns, putting Darnell Washington and Pat Freiermuth in the TE2 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-520f-dc7a-af9b-dfbfa74d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (knee) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51f4-dc7a-af9b-dfff1bbe0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported earlier today that St. Brown is expected to play through what has been described as “a little irritation” in his knee. We believe him. The Lions’ No. 1 wide receiver regularly plays through ailments. He remains a fantasy football WR1 for Week 17 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-51f4-dc7a-af9b-dfff1bbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5212-d968-a19b-5af3d29b0000</link>
      <description>A limited practice to open the week is more or less maintenance for Warren. He should have no issues suiting up for Week 17’s game against the Browns. Coming off a two-score, 143-yard performance on Sunday, Warren is flirting with an RB2 ranking for the final week of the fantasy football season. He is still splitting work with Kenneth Gainwell, but both backs could get home in a run-heavy win over Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5212-d968-a19b-5af3d29b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5217-d56e-afff-f6ff03ab0000</link>
      <description>Montgomery missed Tuesday’s practice with the illness but was back for a limited session today before being listed as questionable. We fully expect him to suit up this week. The Lions are a long-shot to make the playoffs, but they aren’t entirely eliminated just yet. Montgomery only carried the ball four times last week, but he should get more opportunities with the Lions expected to roll over the Max Brosmer-led Vikings this week. He will cling to RB3 life one last time when the Lions take on Minnesota on Christmas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5217-d56e-afff-f6ff03ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is questionable for Week 17 agianst the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-521e-dc7a-af9b-dfbf55b40000</link>
      <description>He’s playing. Decker has played through the shoulder issue for weeks despite being listed as questionable. Fellow offensive lineman Christian Mahogany is also listed as questionable. He got in three limited practices this week and should be good to go as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-521e-dc7a-af9b-dfbf55b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said George Kittle (ankle) has “a chance” to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5223-d35e-a1bf-57e39a790000</link>
      <description>Kittle did not practice on Wednesday. The 49ers can get the No. 1 seed in the NFC and a bye to open the playoffs with wins in their final two contests. He could push through the ankle issue now to get a chance at a week of rest in the Wild Card Round. If he doesn’t suit up, backup tight end Jake Tonges would take his spot in the lineup. Tonges was a viable TE2 with Kittle sidelined earlier in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5223-d35e-a1bf-57e39a790000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
