<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Raheem Mostert (knee/ankle) inactive for Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1c80000</link>
      <description>Mostert entered Week 17 questionable to play due to knee and ankle injuries. He is not fantasy-relevant on his own. His absence could result in a few late-game touches for RB Zamir White and RB Dylan Laube. Neither player should be anywhere near fantasy lineups, though. Starting RB Ashton Jeanty could feasibly handle all backfield touches against the Giants today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins EDGE Chop Robinson (concussion) exited Week 17 against the Buccaneers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6691-d35e-a1bf-67d3e6030000</link>
      <description>Robinson entered concussion protocol in the second quarter against the Buccaneers and was promptly ruled out. He suffered a concussion in Week 9 and missed a game before returning in Week 11. Robinson’s season is likely over with the Dolphins eliminated and this being his second concussion of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6691-d35e-a1bf-67d3e6030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins LB Jordyn Brooks (hamstring) exited Week 17 against the Buccaneers and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6697-d35e-a1bf-67d720030000</link>
      <description>Brooks left in the third quarter against the Buccaneers and went to the locker room. The 28-year-old is the Dolphins’ leading tackler and one of the team’s better offensive players. He is questionable to return with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6697-d35e-a1bf-67d720030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Keon Coleman, TE Dalton Kincaid, OT Tylan Grable, DT DaQuan Jones, DT Jordan Phillips, S Jordan Poyer, and K Matt Prater inactive for Week 17 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6698-d35e-a1bf-67da49010000</link>
      <description>Kincaid was listed as questionable with a knee injury, and he will not be able to play, which is a significant blow to the Bills’ offense. It’s also a big blow to Kincaid’s future status in Buffalo. Early on this season, he looked to be headed towards a breakout season, but this is now the second year in a row he’s been hard to rely on because of injuries. That may cause Buffalo not to pick up his fifth-year option. Dawson Knox (knee) will be active and could take on a big role in a rain-soaked game, and Gabe Davis will be active, with Keon Coleman a healthy inactive yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6698-d35e-a1bf-67da49010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner (calf) left Indianapolis’ Week 17 game against the Jaguars and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a0-d56e-afff-e6e8b6600000</link>
      <description>It’s not all that surprising after Gardner barely practiced all week before being made active. The Colts have no incentive to push him. It wouldn’t be surprising if this were the last game he played in this year. Gardner had three tackles and a pass defensed before leaving in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a0-d56e-afff-e6e8b6600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared OT Lane Johnson, LB Nakobe Dean, LB Josh Uche, QB Sam Howell, CB Michael Carter, and RB A.J. Dillon inactive for Week 17 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a0-d35e-a1bf-67e231040000</link>
      <description>None of this is overly surprising. They will get DT Jalen Carter back for this one, but Dean being out is tough in a game that figures ot be run-heavy. It would also have been nice to get Lane Johnson back, but the Bills don’t have a ferocious pass rush, so it may not be a huge issue in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a0-d35e-a1bf-67e231040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow completed 24-of-31 passes for 305 yards and two touchdowns in the Bengals’ Week 17 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a2-dc7a-af9b-efbf4dac0000</link>
      <description>We can’t write “in the Bengals’ Week 17 win over the Cardinals” because there was actually 12:06 remaining when Burrow took a seat with the Bengals leading 37-7. Doing whatever he wanted against one of the league’s worst defenses — including finding Ja’Marr Chase for a pair of touchdowns, his first since Oct. 16 — Burrow’s two scores brought him to 154 for his career, tying him with Carson Palmer for fourth in Bengals franchise history. Burrow could have had a 4-5 score day, but the Bengals kept advancing inside the Cardinals’ five-yard line then punching it on the ground. Healthy and dealing, Burrow should be out there to put the finishing touches on his 2025 box scores against the Browns in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a2-dc7a-af9b-efbf4dac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers CB Jamel Dean (shoulder) exited Week 17 against the Dolphins and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6699-d56e-afff-e6f95a6d0000</link>
      <description>Dean left in the third quarter against the Dolphins and was getting his shoulder tested on the sidelines. The Buccaneers officially declared him as questionable to return. Jacob Parrish will be in the game to replace Dean in the secondary rotations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6699-d56e-afff-e6f95a6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NFL’s Jay Glazer reports the Steelers will not void the guaranteed money in DK Metcalf’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-661f-dc7a-af9b-efbf82d30000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was suspended for two games after throwing a punch at a Detroit fan in Week 16. That suspension allowed the Steelers to void $45 million in future guarantees on Metcalf’s contract. The Steelers, however, are doubling down on Metcalf by letting the guarantees stand. Glazer has a copy of a security report filed by Metcalf last year, complaining about the same fan while he was playing for Seattle. The history of repeated harassment by the fan certainly paints Metcalf’s actions in a different light, even though they were still worthy of a suspension. Metcalf is eligible to return in the playoffs, assuming the Steelers go on to win the AFC North and secure the No. 4 seed in the AFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-661f-dc7a-af9b-efbf82d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (ribs) returned in Week 17 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a4-d56e-afff-e6ec857e0000</link>
      <description>Waddle exited in the second quarter and went to the locker room with a rib injury. He returned at the end of the third quarter with the Dolphins holding a lead and looking to secure a win. Missing about a quarter-and-a-half worth of time made Greg Dulcich a more significant target in the Dolphins offense while Waddle was out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-66a4-d56e-afff-e6ec857e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
