<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:06:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Shough completed 12-of-20 passes for 102 yards in the Saints’ preseason game against the Broncos, adding two carries for 20 yards and a touchdown on the ground.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85d-dbe3-a9bb-f85f3d3f0000</link>
      <description>Shough played on five drives in this one. The rookie outperformed Spencer Rattler in the box score, but also lost a fumble on a strip sack in the third quarter. Shough would rebound to lead arguably his best drive of the season, driving the Saints 77 yards downfield on 6-of-8 passing for 57 yards and found pay dirt on an 11-yard quarterback keeper to cap the drive. Shough is hoping to beat Rattler for the rights to be named the Saints’ QB1 for Week 1 when they take on the Cardinals. Head coach Kellen Moore has some time before preparing for the first week of the season, but this will be the last test until then. We would expect to get a final word on the starter soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85d-dbe3-a9bb-f85f3d3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shedeur Sanders completed 3-of-6 passes for 14 yards in the Browns’ preseason Week 3 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85c-db7b-a5dd-f85cd3e10000</link>
      <description>Sanders’ returns have progressively gotten worse as the preseason has labored on, capped off by the poor showing against the Rams, during which the rookie quarterback took a ridiculous five sacks on 11 drop backs against third and fourth stringers. Even so, recent reports have surfaced indicating the team intends to keep all four quarterbacks on the initial 53-man roster, with general manager Andrew Berry saying Saturday that he “sees no problem with keeping four quarterbacks.” Whether or not those sentiments will hold true through roster cuts remains to be seen. Dillon Gabriel shined against the Rams, completing 12 of 19 passes for 129 yards and a score after Joe Flacco completed nine of his ten attempts for 71 yards and a touchdown. Gabriel has a good shot at starting the season as Cleveland’s No. 2 quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85c-db7b-a5dd-f85cd3e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings hosted QB Carson Wentz for a visit Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d88c-de13-afdc-decf46dd0000</link>
      <description>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell had continued to sing the praise of current backup Sam Howell throughout the offseason, with today’s actions seemingly contradicting those words. Wentz has played for five different teams during the previous five seasons after leaving the Eagles following the 2020 season. There is also a foundational connection here between Wentz and quarterbacks coach Josh McCown, who played together for the Eagles in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d88c-de13-afdc-decf46dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught 1-of-2 targets for 29 yards in the Packers’ preseason Week 3 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d8e3-db7b-a5dd-f8e736450000</link>
      <description>Golden drew the start at wide receiver alongside Romeo Doubs, with Christian Watson and Jayden Reed both unable to suit up for the third straight preseason game. Watson is reportedly set to begin the regular season on the PUP list while Reed recently shed his walking boot but failed to appear in any preseason game, setting the stage for Golden to begin the season as the team’s top pass-catcher. He certainly has looked the part throughout the offseason, something Packers fans and fantasy managers are hoping continues once games start to count.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d8e3-db7b-a5dd-f8e736450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught all three targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 3 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d909-db7b-a5dd-f90d77790000</link>
      <description>Washington was targeted on three of quarterback Tua Tagovailoa’s eight pass attempts from the first three drives of the team’s final preseason contest, the final of which went for a nifty touchdown from 25 yards out. It was a simple crossing route on a quarterback bootleg, with Washington catching it in the flat before putting on the breaks and leaving his defender in the dust. The obvious caveat here is that both Tyreek Hill and DeVon Achane remained out of the lineup, but Washington has surely shown the same on-field connection with Tagovailoa this preseason that has been reported in camp, making him a viable late-round dart in best ball contests the rest of the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d909-db7b-a5dd-f90d77790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel completed 12-of-19 attempts for 129 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 3 preseason game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9f9-de13-afdc-dffbf3ec0000</link>
      <description>Gabriel once again looked sharp, throwing accurately in the short and intermediate areas like he did in college. The rookie has played efficiently in his limited preseason action, outplaying fellow rookie QB Shedeur Sanders throughout the summer. Gabriel is well positioned to start the regular season as the Brown’s QB2 behind Joe Flacco. He could be an interesting late round pick in superflex formats in case Flacco gets benched or dinged up this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9f9-de13-afdc-dffbf3ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson had two rushes for three yards in the Browns’ Week 3 preseason game against the Rams, adding one catch for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9fe-d332-a1fd-dffe712c0000</link>
      <description>Sampson started the game with the Browns’ first-team offense following a Friday report from ESPN that the rookie would “push” veteran RB Jerome Ford for touches out of the backfield early in the regular season. Sampson had a nice catch against the Rams, shedding two tacklers to pick up a few extra yards. Sampson appears to have a shot at the RB1 role in the Cleveland backfield, though Ford will likely figure in until the coaching staff has total confidence in the rookie. Quinshon Judkins, meanwhile, has not participated in training camp and has yet to sign his rookie deal. Judkins is likely weeks away from getting up to speed. Look for Sampson, who had nearly 1,500 rushing yards and 22 rushing scores last year at Tennessee, to play an outsized role in the Cleveland offense in Week 1 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9fe-d332-a1fd-dffe712c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright is “week to week” with a left leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb497c0000</link>
      <description>The “week to week” tag is via coach Mike McDaniel. Wright’s injury has been unclear, but the Miami Herald reported he had a compression sleeve on his left leg for Saturday’s preseason finale. Wright, of course, did not dress for that one. Sixth-round rookie Ollie Gordon did and had an impressive night. It’s been a rough August for Wright, who seemed to be at risk of losing work to replacement-level veteran Alexander Mattison before the vet suffered a serious neck injury. It would appear he might now actually be in some danger of Gordon coming for the No. 2 spot behind De’Von Achane. Fantasy managers need to follow this one closely between now and Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb497c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon had eight rushes for 43 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 preseason game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb8b250000</link>
      <description>Gordon ends the preseason averaging almost five yards per carry, logging a few impressive runs along the way and possibly carving out a spot in the Miami backfield. Gordon has been an efficient producer this preseason while Jaylen Wright has struggled mightily as a rusher and as a pass catcher. Wright is deal with a leg injury that has been described as “week to week.” De’Von Achane, meanwhile, has a calf injury that could keep him sidelined until Week 1. Head coach Mike McDaniel said the team would be cautious with Achane leading up to the season opener. Gordon, a hyper-productive college back who had 1,721 rushing yards and 21 touchdowns at Oklahoma State in 2023, should be drafted in most 12-team fantasy leagues in case Achane and Wright continue struggling through injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb8b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said Brian Robinson will be the team’s No. 2 running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc2a-db7b-a5dd-fc2efa0b0000</link>
      <description>After missing several weeks with a shoulder injury and apparently falling out of favor with the Niners’ coaching staff, Isaac Guerendo will enter the season as the team’s RB3 behind Christian McCaffrey and Robinson, who was acquired on Friday in exchange for draft compensation. “We brought him here to be our (No.) 2 back,” Shanahan said of Robinson, who last year in Washington had 799 rushing yards and eight touchdowns as the Commanders’ lead back. “I’ve always been a big fan of Brian. Loved him coming out college... We were pumped that he was available and pumped that we were able to get him.” That’s as much confirmation as fantasy managers are going to need in understanding the San Francisco backfield pecking order. Robinson should be drafted in all fantasy formats in case McCaffrey misses time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc2a-db7b-a5dd-fc2efa0b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
