<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared LB Krys Barnes, C Nick Samac, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, WR David Moore, and DE LaBryan Ray inactive for the Wildcard Round against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a993-d968-a19b-f9f357470000</link>
      <description>No real surprises from one of the healthier teams entering the postseason as the Panthers attempt to knock off the Rams at home as 10-point underdogs. It is the franchise’s first home playoff game since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a993-d968-a19b-f9f357470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) for the Wildcard Round against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a998-d35e-a1bf-edda40cb0000</link>
      <description>Jordan injured his ankle in Week 18 and failed to practice all week, eventually ruled out with the ailment. That leaves very little depth behind starting rookie Woody Marks, who could find himself in a workhorse role for the team’s Wildcard matchup against the Steelers. Nick Chubb appears likely to operate as the primary change of pace option while Dare Ogunbowale could rotate in on obvious passing situations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a998-d35e-a1bf-edda40cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated ILB Drew Sanders (foot) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9a0-d35e-a1bf-ede20b480000</link>
      <description>The No. 1 seeded Broncos get the luxury of an additional week of preparation as they await their Division Round opponent, giving Sanders a legitimate chance to return for the team’s first postseason game. The third-year linebacker spent the entirety of the 2025 regular season on injured reserve after complications from a torn Achilles suffered in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9a0-d35e-a1bf-ede20b480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears activated CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9bd-dc7a-af9b-efbf0c2a0000</link>
      <description>Gordon made only three appearances for the Bears during the regular season but gives a struggling secondary a tangible boost as they prepare to host the Packers Saturday evening. The two teams split the season series but meet in the Wildcard Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9bd-dc7a-af9b-efbf0c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (knee) left Carolina’s Wild Card game against the Rams and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9ed-db1c-a7ff-a9ffdb2c0000</link>
      <description>Josiah Stewart ran right over Ekwonu as his leg buckled. The fact that he was almost immediately ruled out likely foreshadows that he would have problems playing if the Panthers advanced. We can’t rule out a serious injury that requires surgery, either. Ekwonu played 950 regular-season snaps as Carolina’s starter at left tackle. Yosh Nijman took over at left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a9ed-db1c-a7ff-a9ffdb2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa34-d35e-a1bf-eff6a9d90000</link>
      <description>That makes six for Kubiak: Falcons, Giants, Cardinals, Raiders, Ravens, and now the Dolphins. What the Seahawks OC did to offend the Titans, we’ll never know. Gary Kubiak’s son stands a solid chance of picking up a job this cycle given how many openings there are and how many he’s already interviewed for. Things will slow down a bit with his market as the Seahawks start playing playoff games next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa34-d35e-a1bf-eff6a9d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders interviewed Titans DC Dennard Wilson for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa3d-d968-a19b-fafd61290000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s work was often overlooked toiling behind Brian Callahan’s horrific offense over the past two years, but the Titans played well on run defense and at least came up with some exotic blitz looks to deal with their lack of pass-rush surge. Still under contract with the Titans, Wilson would likely be allowed to walk as the Titans new head coach wouldn’t necessarily want to retain him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa3d-d968-a19b-fafd61290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (shoulder) left Los Angeles’ Wild Card game against the Panthers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa43-dc7a-af9b-efff42d40000</link>
      <description>He injured the shoulder in the first quarter, briefly returned, and has now been ruled out. Witherspoon played 12 snaps before leaving. The 30-year-old veteran started two games this regular season, appearing in six, while dealing with a shoulder injury that sent him to injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa43-dc7a-af9b-efff42d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared OL Zach Tom inactive for Green Bay’s Wild Card game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa46-d968-a19b-faf7752d0000</link>
      <description>Tom is the only one of Green Bay’s questionable players that will sit, which means Malik Willis (hamstring/shoulder) is active as Jordan Love’s backup. Also inactive for Green Bay are: WR Dontayvion Wicks, QB Desmond Ridder, CB Jaylin Simpson, DL Collin Oliver and WR Jakobie Keeney-James.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa46-d968-a19b-faf7752d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) is active for Chicago’s Wild Card game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa49-d35e-a1bf-efcb74b10000</link>
      <description>He was the only questionable Bears player, but after being activated from injured reserve earlier today it would have been surprising if he hadn’t gone. Inactive for the Bears are: QB Case Keenum, DB CJ Gardner-Johnson, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, DL Joe Tryon-Shoyinka, WR Jahdae Walker and OL Luke Newman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aa49-d35e-a1bf-efcb74b10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
