<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 17:02:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White (groin) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-990e-d05a-adda-bb8e1ec70000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on an official update on White’s injury, but he was seen in shorts for the start of Monday’s practice. White suffered a groin injury in Saturday’s preseason game against the Titans and was reportedly going to undergo further testing to determine the severity of it, so it’s possible we have an update after practice. Regardless, this situation remains one to monitor, and would make Sean Tucker an interesting late-round dart throw as a handcuff to Bucky Irving if White were to miss any time in the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-990e-d05a-adda-bb8e1ec70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Renfrow (hamstring) returned to practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-995a-d05a-adda-bbda75f60000</link>
      <description>Renfrow missed nearly two weeks of practice with a hamstring injury, but will now resume his comeback attempt. The veteran receiver had been impressing early in training camp and was sounding like a safe bet to make the roster before going down. Renfrow was back in full pads on Monday and could have a chance to suit up for the Panthers’ next preseason game, which is set for Saturday against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-995a-d05a-adda-bbda75f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaycee Horn (car crash, thumb) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-997c-d45c-a7fc-9b7eb9b60000</link>
      <description>Horn was involved in a car crash last week and reportedly suffered a thumb injury that required stitches. He was listed as day-to-day with his injury, and was not sporting pads in Monday’s practice, but Horn will hopefully be up to full speed later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-997c-d45c-a7fc-9b7eb9b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Robert Longerbeam suffered a torn patella tendon and will miss the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9986-df63-a199-d9afecc10000</link>
      <description>Longerbeam becomes the second Ravens rookie CB to be lost for the season due to a knee injury. Fellow rookie Bilhal Kone suffered a torn ACL and MCL in last Thursday’s preseason win over the Colts. Longerbeam, who was selected in the sixth round of this year’s draft, will now land on injured reserve and work toward returning next season. With two corners now out for the season, we can expect the Ravens to add a few new names to their secondary in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9986-df63-a199-d9afecc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jon Machota believes “no one has come close to running away with the No. 1 job” in the Cowboys’ backfield.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99b3-d05a-adda-bbb36a830000</link>
      <description>Machota notes that Javonte Williams has seen “the most reps with the starters,” but also points out the fact that Miles Sanders (knee) and Jaydon Blue (ankle) have both been sidelined with injuries. The fact that there are no standouts in Dallas’ backfield shouldn’t come as a surprise, considering the veterans of the group both underperformed in the previous season with their respective teams. Williams is a surefire bet to open as the team’s starter if both Sanders and Blue are unable to go, but there’s a good chance this backfield remains in flux early into the season until a clear-cut starter emerges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99b3-d05a-adda-bbb36a830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent RB Jamaal Williams is working out for the Dolphins on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</link>
      <description>Williams has now met with two teams since the weekend, as the veteran running back was also brought in by the Bears on Saturday. Williams blew up for 262-1066-17 in 2022 but has totaled just 470 yards and two touchdowns on 154 carries since 2023 despite playing in 27 games. Williams’ workout comes a day after Alexander Mattison suffered a neck/shoulder injury in preseason action against the Bears. Now entering his age-30 season, Williams won’t have much to offer outside of a rotational and/or short-yardage role, which would make him unreliable for fantasy wherever he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99c5-d05a-adda-bbc7382e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Alexander Mattison underwent neck surgery on Sunday and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99e1-d45c-a7fc-9bfbca940000</link>
      <description>Mattison left the field under his own power in Sunday’s game, and it was reported after the game that the veteran running back had suffered a neck injury. We now know that Mattison was taken by ambulance to the hospital after the injury and underwent surgery the same day.ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reportsMattison had a full range of motion, but he will now land on season-ending injured reserve after reportedly carving out a role for himself in camp. It’s a tough end to the season for a player who was hoping to bounce back following a disappointing 2024 season with the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99e1-d45c-a7fc-9bfbca940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Alec Pierce is day-to-day with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99eb-df63-a199-d9ebe9f20000</link>
      <description>Groin exited Sunday’s practice with an apparent leg injury that has now been diagnosed as a groin injury. Per Fowler, Pierce’s injury is not expected to be serious, and the day-to-day diagnosis suggests he could return before the end of the week. Pierce is being pushed in camp by second-year receiver Adonai Mitchell for a role as the team’s primary deep threat, and can ill-afford to miss time as Mitchell continues to impress in camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99eb-df63-a199-d9ebe9f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarShawn Lloyd (groin) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99f7-df63-a199-d9ff079a0000</link>
      <description>Per Packers beat writer Matt Schneidman, Lloyd and fellow running back Emanuel Wilson (knee) both practiced “in some capacity.” It doesn’t sound like either back got in a full workload, but it’s an encouraging sign for a backfield that was down its top two backs last week. Wilson is currently listed as the team’s RB2, with Lloyd backing him up as the RB3. Assuming both backs are back in 11-on-11s soon, look for the battle for the RB2 role to ramp up over the final few weeks of camp and the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-99f7-df63-a199-d9ff079a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) was spotted in street clothes during Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</link>
      <description>Stafford threw upwards of 60 passes on Saturday in preparation for his return to the field on Monday. Instead, his much-anticipated return has again been delayed due to a back injury that required an epidural last week. Head coach Sean McVay said last week that Stafford was feeling well enough to play in games, which may still be the case, but the decision to hold him out on a day he was set to return is somewhat alarming. Hopefully, we’ll get more clarification on his status after practice, but this remains a story to monitor with Week 1 less than a month away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
