<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:25:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Matt Milano (pectoral) won’t practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4efb-dc44-a9d9-4fff17ed0000</link>
      <description>Milano played only 23 snaps against the Jets before leaving and being spotted with a wrap on his right arm on the sideline. Joe Andreessen played 10 snaps behind Milano and would seem to be the logical replacement. Milano is no longer the star he was in his prime and took a paycut this offseason, so this is not a huge short-term loss for the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4efb-dc44-a9d9-4fff17ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Packers worked out free agent QB Dorian Thompson-Robinson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f3a-da67-a99f-cfffefd90000</link>
      <description>Our best guess here is that the Packers are meeting with DTR due to the minor thumb injury Jordan Love is dealing with. Love was spotted at Monday’s practice with his left thumb taped, but there’s been little mention about the injury, leaving us to believe it’s a near non-issue. Thompson-Robinson has appeared in 15 games in his NFL career while making five starts, and has a career passing line of 880-1-10. He has also rushed 35 times for 187 scoreless yards. Thompson-Robinson is unlikely to be anything more than a practice squad QB for the Packers if he were to sign with the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f3a-da67-a99f-cfffefd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared TE Devin Culp, WR Chris Godwin, WR Tez Johnson, RB Josh Williams, T Tristan Wirfs, and S Rashad Wisdom inactive for Week 2 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4a-d294-a19b-effa48580000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here after both Godwin and Wirfs were ruled out earlier in the week. The Buccaneers enter Week 2 in a similar situation to their first game of the season, a game that saw rookie Emeka Egbuka and veterans Mike Evans and Sterling Shepard dominate targets from quarterback Baker Mayfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4a-d294-a19b-effa48580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Dameon Pierce is inactive for Week 2 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4c-da67-a99f-cffda1640000</link>
      <description>The Texans carried four running backs and a fullback on their active roster in Week 1, with Pierce now the lone man out in the equation for Week 2. Expect Dare Ogunbowale to serve as the third-down back while Woody Marks mixes in for change of pace duties behind lead rusher Nick Chubb. Also inactive for the Texans are WR Christian Kirk, WR Braxton Berrios, QB Graham Mertz, C Jake Andrews, and DT Tommy Togiai.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4c-da67-a99f-cffda1640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield completed 25-of-38 passes for 215 yards and two touchdowns in the Buccaneers’ 20-19, Week 2 win over the Texans, adding 33 yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5043-dc44-a9d9-576797940000</link>
      <description>Mayfield put the team on his back when it mattered most, leading a successful touchdown drive with under two minutes to play after the Texans took the lead on a late Nick Chubb rushing score. Fighting through mounting pressure from a tenacious Houston pass rush, Mayfield escaped the pocket on fourth down to extend the game-winning drive with a 15-yard carry up the middle. The two-minute, game-winning drive went down as his fifth such occurrence since being drafted in 2018 and sent the Buccaneers to a 2-0 record for the fifth consecutive season. Up next for Mayfield and the Buccaneers is a home meeting with a Jets team potentially without starting quarterback Justin Fields in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5043-dc44-a9d9-576797940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving rushed 17 times for 71 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans, adding 50 yards on six receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5049-d86f-abdd-55fd4ad40000</link>
      <description>Irving played almost every first half down in a gritty victory that went down to the wire, adding work through the air throughout. He padded his counting stats for fantasy managers on the game-winning two-minute drive by catching four passes with the game on the line, eventually ceding the winning touchdown to backfield mate Rachaad White from two yards out. Even so, fantasy managers have to be happy with the returns absent a score. Up next is another difficult test against the Jets at home in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5049-d86f-abdd-55fd4ad40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White rushed 10 times for 65 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans, adding one yard on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-504c-dc44-a9d9-576e53010000</link>
      <description>White played sparingly in the first half behind unquestioned starter Bucky Irving, but it was White that sealed the win at the end of a two-minute drive from two yards out. White isn’t likely to return consistent fantasy production on what amounts to change-of-pace snaps, but fantasy managers in a bind with bye weeks looming could do worse than stashing him at the end of their bench. White will be a difficult start in Week 3 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-504c-dc44-a9d9-576e53010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans caught 5-of-11 targets for 56 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-504e-dc44-a9d9-576ecec50000</link>
      <description>Evans was shadowed by All-Pro cornerback Derek Stingley for the duration of the game, which explains the modest production although he saw 11 targets. He narrowly led the team in yardage in a game quarterback Baker Mayfield managed just 215 yards on 38 pass attempts. Even so, Evans remains a locked-in fantasy WR2 for as long as he remains healthy. Evans could be in for another shadow in Week 3 opposite Sauce Gardner when the Buccaneers host the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-504e-dc44-a9d9-576ecec50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-7 targets for 29 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5051-d294-a19b-f4f1a6100000</link>
      <description>Egbuka’s fantasy returns could have been even bigger had he come down with one of two deeps targets, the second of which could have gone for 50 yards or more on a scramble drill late in the fourth quarter. His second quarter touchdown from 15 yards out gave the Buccaneers their first lead of the game, which they would hold until just over two minutes remaining in the game. Fantasy managers must be excited about the early returns for the electric rookie after scoring three times in his first two professional outings. He could again see heavy usage in Week 3 with Mike Evans likely to draw shadow coverage from Sauce Gardner when the Buccaneers host the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5051-d294-a19b-f4f1a6100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 3-of-4 targets for 25 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5055-d86f-abdd-55fd27690000</link>
      <description>We wrote Otton’s Week 1 returns off due to positive game script, but it’s harder to do so in a game Baker Mayfield attempted 38 passes. He should continue to play heavy snaps for the Buccaneers but is difficult to trust in managed leagues, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5055-d86f-abdd-55fd27690000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
