<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants will visit with Colts OC Jim Bob Cooter to discuss their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b3e-d042-afbc-7ffe40fd0000</link>
      <description>Cooter has also been linked to the Eagles this offseason and has interviewed with them twice. As a non-playcaller behind Shane Steichen in Indianapolis, it’s natural that he’d accept a lateral move that allows him to call plays. It’s also possible this is a leverage interview to try to draw an offer from Philadelphia, though that would just be speculation on our part.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b3e-d042-afbc-7ffe40fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills general manager Brandon Beane said he expects to pick up TE Dalton Kincaid’s fifth-year option.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b40-d355-a5bd-8f54f9e20000</link>
      <description>Specifically, Beane said he does not “see any reason why we wouldn’t pick that up,” adding that the Bills’ mission is to help Kincaid stay healthy. We expect them to follow through, but this falls short of a firm commitment. Kincaid has been plagued by injuries during his three years in the NFL and told reporters earlier today that he does not plan to undergo surgery to correct the PCL tear in his knee, instead opting for more rehab. He initially suffered the injury in 2024 and “continued to tweak it in different situations” this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b40-d355-a5bd-8f54f9e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Ben Baby reports Bengals RB Chase Brown is “in talks” with the Bengals regarding an extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b41-dfd7-a5dc-0f6300820000</link>
      <description>Brown had an uneven fantasy season as he was disastrous pre-Joe Flacco and the Bengals simply couldn’t get the ground game going, but came on strong in the second half of the season and wound up with a 69/437/5 receiving line. Entering his age-26 season and the final year of his rookie contract, an extension would seem to make sense given the Bengals don’t exactly have anyone waiting in the wings. 2025 sixth-rounder Tahj Brooks is the closest thing Cincinnati has to a prospect at the position, and he only managed 47 offensive snaps in his rookie season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b41-dfd7-a5dc-0f6300820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Joe Brady said WR Keon Coleman “is not done being a Buffalo Bill.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b5c-d355-a5bd-8f5c1c850000</link>
      <description>Last week, Bills owner Terry Pegula blamed former head coach Sean McDermott for the second-round pick spent on Coleman in 2024, absolving general manager Brandon Beane along the way. Brady said that he spoke with Coleman after being named the Bills’ new head coach, telling the young wide receiver that he fully supports him. Day 2 picks are rarely traded or released just two years into their career, but Brady’s comments help clarify Coleman’s status on the roster following Pegula’s strong remarks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b5c-d355-a5bd-8f5c1c850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Jonathon Brooks said he was “hopeful” to attend minicamp but “there is no set date” on his full return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b52-d355-a5bd-8f569ac10000</link>
      <description>Brooks missed the entire 2025 season after tearing his ACL for the second time in 2024. He’s still entering his age-23 season and the third year of his rookie contract, so we can’t rule out that he’ll see a real role with the Panthers in 2026. How the Panthers treat Rico Dowdle (or a replacement for Dowdle) in free agency will likely tell us a lot about how they view Brooks’ recovery, but Panthers GM Dan Morgan did praise how he was attacking his rehab and said he’s “looking great.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b52-d355-a5bd-8f569ac10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall believes Bijan Robinson’s heavy workload will continue “and perhaps even increase” under new head coach Kevin Stefanski.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b72-dfd7-a5dc-0f73a1ac0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons gave Robinson 366 touches in 2025, third in the league behind Jonathan Taylor (369) and Christian McCaffrey’s league-leading 413. Tyler Allgeier is a free agent and Stefanski’s teams have heavily emphasized the run. While we’re not saying that Robinson is a sure bet for an increase — it’s hard to call any player with 366 touches as “due” for more work — it does appear to at least be on the table. That would only strengthen his case to go 1.1 in most standard drafts in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b72-dfd7-a5dc-0f73a1ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall and Jeff Howe report Kirk Cousins is expected to be released.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b77-d042-afbc-7ff717710000</link>
      <description>The way the Falcons re-structured Cousins’ contract earlier in the offseason pointed to this, but Kendall also reports that Cousins could be brought back by the Falcons on a less-expensive contract. Cousins will likely have his share of suitors in the offseason despite entering his age-38 season, so it’s no lock he’d be back in Atlanta if released. Kevin Stefanski notably didn’t say much when asked about Cousins at his opening press conference earlier in the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b77-d042-afbc-7ff717710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Bears assistant general manager Ian Cunningham for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b76-d355-a5bd-8f76f95e0000</link>
      <description>Cunningham previously interviewed for the Falcons’ president of football position, and has now completed two interviews for their general manager vacancy. Reports continue to list him as a favorite for this role. Texans assistant GM James Liipfert is also considered a finalist for the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b76-d355-a5bd-8f76f95e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Colts pass-game coordinator Alex Tanney for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b7b-d355-a5bd-8f7fb48b0000</link>
      <description>The long-time journeyman quarterback had worked as Eagles quarterbacks coach before packing up to Indianapolis with Shane Steichen. It’s his first offensive coordinator interview. Tanney is most famous for posting several trick-shot videos on YouTube in the early 2010s. He attempted just 15 professional passes from 2012-2020, spending the 2018-2020 seasons with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b7b-d355-a5bd-8f7fb48b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills hired Pat Meyer as their new offensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b82-d355-a5bd-8fd6d20e0000</link>
      <description>Meyer served as the Panthers’ offensive line coach from 2020-2021, while new Bills head coach Joe Brady served as the Panthers’ offensive coordinator. Meyer spent the following five seasons serving in the same role with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b82-d355-a5bd-8fd6d20e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
