<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 19:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys T Tyler Guyton (concussion) will not play in Dallas’ Week 5 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdd-d6e9-af9d-abdd51cb0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys could have four backup linemen starting with Cooper Beebe on IR, Tyler Booker (ankle) already ruled out, and G Tyler Smith (ankle) extremely questionable for Week 5. Neither Guyton, Booker, nor Smith practiced all week for the Cowboys. While OC Klayton Adams has made great results out of subpar ingredients, this is going to be a big ask for Dallas as they take on a rough Jets defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abdd-d6e9-af9d-abdd51cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (knee) will play in Week 5 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abf6-deb6-a7fd-fbffdb7f0000</link>
      <description>Daniels was seemingly held out as a precaution last week, letting him get closer to full strength for his return this time around versus the Chargers. The reigning offensive rookie of the year will wear a brace on his knee on Sunday. While his rushing output might dip slightly in his first game back, we still expect the young quarterback to do plenty of damage on the ground. Daniels is immediately back in the upper echelon of the fantasy QB1 ranks for a potential shootout with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abf6-deb6-a7fd-fbffdb7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel (heel) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 5 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abfd-d6e9-af9d-abfde9fe0000</link>
      <description>Samuel missed the first two practices of the week with the heel issue, but the Commanders generally do a good job of giving their veterans rest during the week. He was back on the practice field on Friday and even avoided a questionable designation, suggesting he won’t be limited by the heel issue on Sunday. With Terry McLaurin out for Week 5, Samuel will once again operate as the team’s top receiver, this time with Jayden Daniels throwing him the football. He sits in the WR2 ranks heading into his date with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abfd-d6e9-af9d-abfde9fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (knee/biceps) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac01-dca3-a9fb-bd999f040000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was listed as a DNP for Wednesday’s walkthrough but returned for a full session on Thursday and Friday. He was never at any risk of missing his Week 5 date with the Seahawks. The same can’t be said of Bucky Irving and Mike Evans, who were both ruled out for Sunday’s game. A road trip to face Mike Macdonald’s stalwart defense isn’t ideal for Mayfield’s fantasy outlook, but injuries and bye weeks have him just inside the QB1 ranks despite a poor matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac01-dca3-a9fb-bd999f040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers admits his play is being affected by the knee injury that held him out of Thursday and Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac05-dca3-a9fb-bd9dc88d0000</link>
      <description>Although Bowers is officially questionable to face the Colts, coach Pete Carroll has said he is “planning to play.” In theory, that’s good news, but speaking Friday, Bowers painted the picture of a player who is currently playing at maybe 60 or 70 percent health. “I want to be back to going full speed, being able to separate from guys,” Bowers said. “I feel like I can’t really do that to the best of my abilities right now.” He certainly sounds like someone who would benefit from a missed game or two. The problem for fantasy managers is, tight end just isn’t deep enough right now to give Bowers a week or two on the bench. If he makes the effort to play, you still have to start him and hope for 5-6 targets and a touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac05-dca3-a9fb-bd9dc88d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs WR Sterling Shepard (foot) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac08-d6e9-af9d-ae98ae250000</link>
      <description>Shepard was listed as a DNP for Wednesday’s walkthrough but returned for two full practices to close the week. It was just a maintenance day for the veteran wideout. With Chris Godwin back in the lineup last week, Shepard’s role was reduced and he was targeted just four times. He is nothing more than a WR5/6 heading into Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac08-d6e9-af9d-ae98ae250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen is uncertain if Adonai Mitchell will dress for Week 5 against the Raiders after his Week 4 miscues.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac0b-d6e9-af9d-ae9bca6a0000</link>
      <description>“Working through that,” was Steichen’s Friday update. It must be said, Steichen’s quote was delivered before Alec Pierce (concussion) was again ruled out. Mitchell probably “has” to play, but it’s clear the team isn’t just moving on from his Week 4 mistakes that cost Indy two long touchdowns. If Mitchell suits up, it could only be on an emergency basis behind Ashton Dulin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac0b-d6e9-af9d-ae9bca6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks DB Devon Witherspoon (knee) has been ruled out for Week 5 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac14-deb6-a7fd-ffdf70ad0000</link>
      <description>The same is true of FS Julian Love (hamstring) and EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence (quad). Seattle’s banged up defense is a break for the Bucs’ equally-injured offense. The Hawks’ primary slot corner, Witherspoon hasn’t played since Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ac14-deb6-a7fd-ffdf70ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Eagles wide receivers A.J. Brown and Devonta Smith are frustrated with their roles in the offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb0-d6e9-af9d-afb02c1b0000</link>
      <description>You didn’t need a paid subscription to the Athletic to figure out Brown was unhappy this year, he made that clear in the postgame press briefing after totaling seven yards on nine targets in Week 4. Smith hasn’t been as vocal, but his underwhelming numbers this year have come on even less targets (20) than Brown has received (28). The Eagles are 4-0 and there’s been no indication Philadelphia intends to lean more towards the pass going forward. They face the Broncos’ top secondary in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb0-d6e9-af9d-afb02c1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell will be active for Week 5 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb8-d6e9-af9d-afb83e350000</link>
      <description>Mitchell impressed in the preseason with reports that he solidified himself as the No. 3 back in the Ravens’ offense. Once the season began, coach John Harbaugh made it clear that wasn’t a valued role as Mitchell was deemed a healthy scratch since the opening week. With Lamar Jackson sidelined for Week 5 and the Ravens turning to Cooper Rush, Mitchell is going to be active and could provide a spark in Lamar’s absence. He still doesn’t have much fantasy value as a contingent back or otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-afb8-d6e9-af9d-afb83e350000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
