<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 02:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said C.J. Stroud (concussion) will not play in Houston’s Week 12 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</link>
      <description>This did seem to the way it was going for most of the week, even with Stroud returning to practice today. The good news is that a return against the Colts in Week 13 seems plausible for Stroud, who has now missed three full games with this concussion suffered against the Broncos in Week 9. Davis Mills will shepherd the Texans through Thursday Night Football against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said he’s “optimistic” about Jaylen Warren (ankle) playing in Week 12 but said he’ll be limited early in the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</link>
      <description>He added that Warren was cleared to return to the game by trainers, but that the Steelers opted not to chance anything. The story here seems to be the Steelers just taking it easy on their best back. We’ll probably see him limited on Wednesday, possibly Thursday as well, but we’re expecting him to play in Week 12 based on everything we’ve seen to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said “we’ll see where the week goes” when asked about Will Howard getting first-team reps in practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-989d-d45b-affe-dd9fa7f40000</link>
      <description>Howard missed the entire preseason thanks to a fractured pinkie finger, so the Steelers probably would like to evaluate him to some extent with the extra time that Aaron Rodgers (wrist) vacates in practice. There’s no indication that Mason Rudolph won’t be the starter in Week 12 if Rodgers is ruled out, but it probably says something about how the Steelers feel about Howard’s long-term projection that there’s discussion about him seeing some first-team reps in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-989d-d45b-affe-dd9fa7f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions activated LB Malcolm Rodriguez (knee) from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98cb-d45b-affe-dddf2f760000</link>
      <description>His 21-day window was up, so Rodriguez had to be activated today or lost for the season. Rodriguez practiced in full all last week on the injury report and should be a good bet to be active right away in Week 12 for the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98cb-d45b-affe-dddf2f760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (ankle) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98d2-d1e7-a1fa-dafae1240000</link>
      <description>He’ll more than likely be good to go for the Texans on Thursday night. Collins was limited on Monday. He’ll be on the WR1/WR2 borderline against the Bills after being the target on 36 Davis Mills passes over the last three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98d2-d1e7-a1fa-dafae1240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (shoulder) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e7-d713-ad9e-fcf7e7880000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be removed from the injury report on Wednesday. Schultz was limited on Monday and has been managed for most of the last three weeks with shoulder soreness. He’ll be in line for a low-end fantasy TE1 role against the Bills on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e7-d713-ad9e-fcf7e7880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans G Ed Ingram (knee) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e9-d713-ad9e-fcfd26760000</link>
      <description>After missing each of the last two games with a knee injury, Ingram looks likely to go on Thursday night. Ingram has posted back-to-back full practices this week. Tytus Howard (ankle/knee) and Trent Brown (hand/knee) were both limited participants on Monday and Tuesday and also look to be trending towards playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e9-d713-ad9e-fcfd26760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived LB Damone Clark.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98ef-d673-a39e-bcff84450000</link>
      <description>The 2022 fifth-rounder had solid PFF coverage and tackling grades before the Cowboys absolutely lost confidence in him the past two seasons, playing him just 251 snaps between 2024 and 2025. He might find a home on waivers. Still just 25, he should at least find a practice squad spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98ef-d673-a39e-bcff84450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed WR Brenden Rice to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9944-d45b-affe-ddd66e370000</link>
      <description>Rice, the son of NFL Hall of Famer and former Seattle Seahawk Jerry Rice, was most recently on the Patriots’ practice squad. The Seahawks add him to their practice squad as depth to the pass-catching corps. The 23-year-old Rice appeared in three NFL games for the Chargers last season, but has not recorded a target on offense. The Seahawks also added RB Velus Jones to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9944-d45b-affe-ddd66e370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard said, “when I came back from my calf, I wasn’t maybe quite where I wanted to be.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9986-d45b-affe-dd9659a10000</link>
      <description>Hubbard missed two games due to a calf injury he suffered prior to Week 5. He has not been efficient since returning, losing his lead back role to Rico Dowdle and averaging under 4.0 yards per carry since Week 7. Via Kassidy Hill on the Panthers’ team website, Hubbard said he “maybe rushed it back a little sooner.” The 26-year-old was paid like the team’s lead back at the beginning of the season but the veteran Dowdle has outplayed him as Hubbard deals with his calf injury. For the rest of this season, Hubbard is an RB4 at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9986-d45b-affe-dd9659a10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
