<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught both of his targets for 74 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</link>
      <description>Kupp, returning from a hamstring injury that kept him sidelined in Week 9, had an electric 67-yard catch and run in the second quarter before the Seahawks shut down the passing offense up 35-0 on the hapless Cards. Kupp ran a route on 10 of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs on the day. He should hold some PPR value coming down the stretch of the regular season. Kupp will be a top-36 play in Week 11 against a vulnerable Niners secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Knight had 10 rushes for 28 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding one catch for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b99-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbe0a90000</link>
      <description>Knight couldn’t get anything going with his team-leading ten rushes while Emari Demercado was efficient with his touches, racking up 104 yards on just seven touches (four carries). Knight will be an entirely touchdown-dependent RB3/4 option in Week 11 against the 49ers. Demercado would seem to be the superior weekly fantasy play in the Arizona backfield until Trey Benson returns from IR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b99-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbe0a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) was seen in a walking boot after the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b9d-d45b-affe-7f9f29ff0000</link>
      <description>Bateman reportedly suffered a high-ankle sprain in Sunday’s victory after being taken down by an illegal hip-drop tackle that was not flagged. Bateman appeared fine after the play and walked off under his own power, but reports of his injury began surfacing following the game. If he’s unable to play in Week 11 against the Browns, DeAndre Hopkins or Devontez Walker would potentially be in line for more work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b9d-d45b-affe-7f9f29ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught both of his targets for three yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bbd-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb0310000</link>
      <description>Barner ran a route on five of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs. The Seahawks shut down their passing attack after the team seized a 35-0 lead in the second quarter. Barner, who has seen some involvement near the goal line as the Hawks’ tush push quarterback, has had more than three receptions in a game just once in 2025. He’ll be a thin streaming option in Week 11 against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bbd-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb0310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker had 14 rushes for 67 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals, adding one catch for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc2-d713-ad9e-6fd650890000</link>
      <description>Walker once again split the backfield with Zach Charbonnet in one of the least appealing backfields in all of fantasy football. Charbonnet also had 14 rushing attempts (for 83 yards) and scored on a short touchdown. Charbonnet’s inside-the-ten domination has left Walker with little to no weekly touchdown upside. Sunday marked Walker’s fourth highest carry total of the season, thanks mostly to the Seahawks entering clock-killing mode early in the second half. Walker, who ran eight routes on 13 Seattle drop backs in Week 10, profiles as a top-30 running back play for Week 11 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc2-d713-ad9e-6fd650890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught his lone target for three yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals, adding two rushes for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc6-d713-ad9e-6fd665620000</link>
      <description>Shaheed’s usage was quite extensive just five days after the Seahawks acquired him in a trade with the Saints. Shaheed ran a pass route on 10 of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs before the Hawks effectively shut down the offense with a 35-0 lead over Arizona. His involvement in the run game suggests the team is committed to getting Shaheed involved in the offense going forward. Shaheed’s role as the main downfield threat for Sam Darnold — the league’s best deep ball passer — should give him plenty of high-variance WR3 pop. He gets the Rams in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc6-d713-ad9e-6fd665620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet had 14 rushes for 83 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bd2-d45b-affe-7fd6637a0000</link>
      <description>Ken Walker also had 14 rushes (for 67 yards) and ran more pass routes than Charbonnet in a game that saw Sam Darnold log a grand total of 13 drop backs. Importantly, Charbonnet continues to dominate inside-the-ten rushes. He scored on one such opportunity in this game, and now has six rushing scores in 2025. Walker has three touchdowns on the ground and hasn’t scored a rushing TD since Week 3. Charbonnet will be a touchdown-reliant RB3 play in Week 11 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bd2-d45b-affe-7fd6637a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden (knee) questionable to return to Week 10 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bd7-d1e7-a1fa-7bff54340000</link>
      <description>Gadsden suffered a knee-to-knee collision in the third quarter and was taken to the locker room for x-rays following a quick visit to the medical tent. The breakout rookie had been on a torrid stretch the previous three games prior to the injury. Fantasy managers will want to monitor his situation in the coming days. Gadsden managed 13 yards on three receptions but committed two drops prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bd7-d1e7-a1fa-7bff54340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 3-of-7 targets for 34 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6be0-d713-ad9e-6ff4662f0000</link>
      <description>Wilson was once again a full time player and was third in targets behind Trey McBride (13) and Marvin Harrison, Jr. (12). Wilson now has at least three receptions in four straight games as the team’s distant No. 3 option. Wilson will be a desperation 14-team league option next week against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6be0-d713-ad9e-6ff4662f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 5-of-6 targets for 93 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6be7-d1e7-a1fa-7bef55f10000</link>
      <description>Smith-Njigba somehow got there for fantasy purposes in a game that saw Sam Darnold log just 13 drop backs before the Seahawks shut down their offense up 35-0 in the second quarter. JSN accounted for 53 percent of Seattle’s receiving yards and was targeted on a whopping 46 percent of his pass routes. His touchdown was his sixth of the season. Smith-Njigba was checked for a concussion in the second quarter; his practice status should be monitored this week ahead of the Seahawks’ Week 11 game against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6be7-d1e7-a1fa-7bef55f10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
