<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:02:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Chiefs are requesting to interview Bears RB coach Eric Bieniemy for their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6cd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee810000</link>
      <description>Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy’s contract will expire shortly, and he continues to draw interest around the league for head coaching vacancies. Bieniemy, who last worked with the Chiefs in 2022, has bounced around jobs over the last three season, spending 2023 with the Commanders before moving on to UCLA as an assistant head coach and OC in 2024, and landing with the Bears in his current role this season. Bieniemy has a long history with the Chiefs and head coach Andy Reid, and was a part of two Super Bowl-winning teams in 2019 and 2022. The Chiefs never finished lower than sixth in total points scored since Bieniemy took over as offensive coordinator in 2018, but they’ve finished 15th or worse in scoring in every season since his departure. A reunion would make sense for both sides and could help the Chiefs recapture some of what made them one of the most prolific offenses in the league for five-straight seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6cd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons re-signed DC Jeff Ulbrich to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6db-d968-a19b-defb77100000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin Stefanski has officially locked in his defensive coordinator. The newly minted Falcons coach opted to stick with Ulbrich, whose lone season with the team under Raheem Morris yielded a defense that ranked 15th in yards allowed, 19th in points allowed, and set a franchise record with 57 sacks. The Falcons denied a request from the Cowboys’ earlier this month to interview Ulbrich for their defensive coordinator vacancy, which hinted at the team retaining him even through a regime change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6db-d968-a19b-defb77100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills promoted Brandon Bean to President of Football Operations.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6e7-d35e-a1bf-d7e7ad060000</link>
      <description>If the decision to retain Beane for next season came as a surprise, then the decision to promote him to President of Football Operations will evoke similar feelings. Beane joined the Bills in 2017, and while the team has enjoyed plenty of regular-season success with him calling the shots with roster management, his inability to surround Josh Allen with premium talent is a notable red flag. Beane’s first order of work is finding a new head coach to replace the recently fired Sean McDermott, but the Bills can’t continue with the receiving corps they rolled out in Saturday’s divisional round loss to the Broncos. While the likes of Brandin Cooks and Gabe Davis are almost certain to be let go this offseason, 2024 first-rounder Keon Coleman continues to look like a bust, and Khalil Shakir, while solid, can’t carry the passing game as a low ADOT slot receiver. Beane’s promotion will come with added pressure to get premium talent around Allen, who will be 30 at the start of next season. It goes without saying that the 2026 offseason will be one of the most important offseasons for the Bills in recent memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6e7-d35e-a1bf-d7e7ad060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mike McCarthy “has now interviewed twice in recent days for the Titans head coaching job.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6fd-d35e-a1bf-d7ff17530000</link>
      <description>It was reported over a week ago that McCarthy would interview with the Titans on January 17th, but according to Schefter, the team also spoke with McCarthy “once in late December in Green Bay,” while the season was still going on. This certainly throws a bit of a wrinkle in how we should view the Titans’ head-coaching vacancy, as the early decision to speak with McCarthy in-season could hint at him being the favorite in the clubhouse. McCarthy is also expected to speak with the Steelers in the coming days, giving him another potential suitor if things don’t work out with the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d6fd-d35e-a1bf-d7ff17530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed TE Tanner Hudson to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d709-d35e-a1bf-d7cbbeaf0000</link>
      <description>Hudson, 31, was playing on an expiring deal this season but is now locked in for 2026. The veteran tight end played on 148 offensive snaps this season, per PFF, and has never been used as anything more than a backup since entering the league in 2019. He caught 19 passes for 168 yards and two touchdowns this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d709-d35e-a1bf-d7cbbeaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said “I can’t be certain right now” when asked if Mack Hollins (abdomen) could play in the AFC Championship game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d725-d968-a19b-dff5005b0000</link>
      <description>Vrabel said the team is “still working through everything with some of those guys that could be back,’ so it’s unlikely we learn much about Hollins’ availability before the Patriots release their first injury report on Wednesday. Hollins hasn’t played since Week 16 and has yet to practice since going down. The veteran receiver has come up big on various occasions for the Patriots this season and would be a welcomed addition to the offense against a top-flight Broncos defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d725-d968-a19b-dff5005b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland suffered a concussion in Sunday’s Divisional round loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d744-dc7a-af9b-dfffe2c20000</link>
      <description>Loveland was injured late in the fourth quarter in Sunday’s loss to the Rams and was not available for any of the team’s offensive snaps in overtime. Loveland, who caught 58 passes for 713 yards and six touchdowns as a rookie, should make a full recovery in the coming days and will be primed for a breakout 2026 campaign after an impressive rookie year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d744-dc7a-af9b-dfffe2c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Bills HC Sean McDermott plans to continue coaching in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d74e-d968-a19b-dfff1e830000</link>
      <description>The recently-fired McDermott will be one of the hottest names on the market and is now free to speak with other teams. With seven other teams still looking to secure their next head coach, McDermott will have plenty of suitors to consider as interviews start lining up. McDermott led the Bills to eight postseason births in his nine years at the helm, while going 98-50 in the regular season. Even if he’s unable to land a head coaching gig, McDermott will be in high-demand for several defensive coordinator positions that need filled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d74e-d968-a19b-dfff1e830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Ravens will hold a second interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d74f-d56e-afff-f7efd4cd0000</link>
      <description>Weaver now has second interviews scheduled with both the Ravens and Steelers, and is scheduled to meet with the Ravens on Tuesday. Weaver spent four seasons with the Ravens as a player from 2002 to 2005, and also worked under John Harbaugh from 2021 to 2023. He’s received several head coaching interviews in recent years since joining the coaching ranks, and could finally be on the verge of securing his first head-coaching gig this coaching cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d74f-d56e-afff-f7efd4cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed their interview with Lions DC Kelvin Sheppard for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d75b-dc7a-af9b-dfff8eb90000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins were the first team to interview Sheppard this coaching cycle. The first-year defensive coordinator saw his defense rank 22nd in points allowed and 18th in yards allowed in his first year at the helm, but the Lions again dealt with several injuries on the defensive side of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d75b-dc7a-af9b-dfff8eb90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
