<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 25-of-35 passes for 203 yards and one touchdown in the Steelers’ 27-20, Week 9 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-467a-d673-a39e-e6fb850c0000</link>
      <description>The Steelers forced six turnovers in Sunday’s win over the Colts and turned those turnovers into 24 points. Despite entering the fourth quarter with a 24-7 lead, it was anything but a dominant day for Rodgers and the offense, who averaged an underwhelming 3.7 yards per play and converted only four third downs on the afternoon. Rodgers did manage to connect with Pat Freiermuth on a 12-yard score two plays after the Steelers force an interception on Daniel Jones, but the Colts defense did what they could to give Rodgers and company fits despite facing numerous short fields. With DK Metcalf bottled up all afternoon, Rodgers looked to Calvin Austin and Darnell Washington to move the ball, as the two combined for 9-99-0 on 12 targets, with the longest pass of the day coming on a 19-yard strike to Austin that helped setup a short rushing score by Jaylen Warren. Rodgers is averaging just 5.9 YPA over the last two weeks and will need to get more out of his offense in Week 10 when they visit the Chargers on Sunday Night Football on NBC. He’ll be a QB2 in fantasy next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-467a-d673-a39e-e6fb850c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb rushed 11 times for 34 yards in the Texans Week 9 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4682-d673-a39e-e69331ed0000</link>
      <description>Chubb hasn’t gone over 61 yards in any of Houston’s games this year and has caught 10 passes in nine games. He’s a touchdown-or-bust option in a running game that gets stuffed in the red zone regularly. There’s no reason to pretend better things are on the way against the Jags in Week 10 — he’s a low-end FLEX at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4682-d673-a39e-e69331ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 14 times for 45 yards in the Colts’ Week 9 loss to the Steelers, adding two receptions for 12 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4687-d45b-affe-5797977c0000</link>
      <description>Fresh off back-to-back three-touchdown performances, Taylor found little room to operate in Sunday’s defeat. Taylor’s longest play of the game came on a nine-yard run in the third quarter, but the Colts’ six turnovers put a cap on any potential scoring opportunities for the bell cow back. Taylor saw Daniel Jones dive into the end zone for a one-yard score on the team’s opening possession, and the lone garbage time touchdown the Colts scored went to Josh Downs on a four-yard throw. it was a disappointing game for all involved, but Taylor will obviously be on the RB1 radar next week when the Colts face the Falcons in Germany.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4687-d45b-affe-5797977c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 6-of-7 targets for 118 yards and two touchdowns in the Bears’ Week 9 win against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468a-d1e7-a1fa-5eea20710000</link>
      <description>Loveland’s second touchdown was a dramatic 58-yard catch and run touchdown to give the Bears the lead after their defense had given up a late touchdown to Joe Flacco and the Bengals. With Cole Kmet out with a head injury, Loveland took on a more prominent role in this one. The rookie ran a route on 37 of the team’s 45 drop backs and was targeted on nearly 22 percent of his routes. Loveland, like a lot of rookies, has taken on a larger role as the season has worn on. He could be a must-play option in Week 10 against the Giants if Kmet is sideline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468a-d1e7-a1fa-5eea20710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports, “The fear heading into the MRI is that Tucker Kraft tore his ACL.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4686-d1e7-a1fa-5eeecec90000</link>
      <description>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said after the game that Kraft’s knee injury “does not look good.” We fully expect the MRI to confirm a season-ending injury for the young tight end. It’s a devastating blow for the Packers, who had been relying on Kraft as their de facto WR1 this year. Kraft easily led the team with 30 catches for 469 yards and six scores heading into Week 9. Luke Musgrave will take his place in the lineup, though he is unlikely to replace Kraft’s production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4686-d1e7-a1fa-5eeecec90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 14 times for 55 yards in the Patriots’ Week 9 win over the Falcons, adding four catches for 32 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4686-d713-ad9e-6ed6a72d0000</link>
      <description>Henderson got the start with Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) out for the game. The Patriots used him early and often in this game, but Terrell Jennings vultured a touchdown and rotated in frequently when the Pats would enter Falcons territory. Henderson showcased burst on outside runs and found success in space. Encouragingly, the rookie got 51 snaps to Jennings’ 17, but he still wasn’t trusted in high leverage situations. Henderson has low-end RB2 upside as long as Stevenson is out moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4686-d713-ad9e-6ed6a72d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 16 times for 31 yards and two touchdowns in the Steelers’ Week 9 win over the Colts, adding two receptions for negative two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468b-d713-ad9e-6edf52470000</link>
      <description>Warren’s two touchdowns are all that will satisfy fantasy managers in this one. Warren was held in check all day by the Colts stout defensive front, but did manage to punch in scores from one and two yards out. Warren’s rushing volume continues to be reliable, but his lack of targets in the passing game makes him a touchdown-dependent option every week. This will keep him on the RB2 radar in Week 10 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468b-d713-ad9e-6edf52470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 10 times for 27 yards in the Texans’ Week 9 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468d-d673-a39e-e69d29c40000</link>
      <description>The box score won’t show it, but Marks did take a firm share of the workload here with 35 snaps to Nick Chubb’s 26. (The annoying thing is that Dare Ogbunbowale has begun to mix in and hurt them both.) Otherwise, not a lot going on here. Not much running room against one of the league’s best defenses with Davis Mills under center, and a 10-yard run was negated via holding penalty. Marks is probably still a FLEX play at best against the Jaguars next week, especially if Mills starts again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468d-d673-a39e-e69d29c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 25-of-37 passes for 284 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ 27-24, Week 9 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468e-d1e7-a1fa-5eee8c260000</link>
      <description>Goff was also sacked five times for 44 yards, bringing his net passing down to 240 yards. Nevertheless, his official 284 through the air was rather amazingly his second most of the year. It was an accomplishment considering he had just 115 yards at the break. Much of his production came on the opening series with Sam LaPorta, while 37 yards arrived via a late Jameson Williams touchdown where the wideout did most of the work. Goff deserves credit for all of that, of course, but this was not a game where he was consistently making plays. In fact, beleaguered second-year pro J.J. McCarthy somehow made more, and the Lions lost a critical home divisional tilt to a team unhappy with its quarterback situation. Officially just not quite the same without former OC Ben Johnson, the Lions need to figure out what they want to be in the second half of the season. The Commanders could go either way as a Week 10 road matchup. Goff is never a gangbusters fantasy option when the Lions head outdoors away from home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-468e-d1e7-a1fa-5eee8c260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
