<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Mike Evans (collarbone) “has shown everything he needed to show” to play in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0922-d77b-adfb-cba3aae40000</link>
      <description>Evans is practicing this week and — barring a setback — should suit up Thursday night against Atlanta. Evans over the season’s first three weeks led the Bucs offense with a 41 percent air yards share and a 27 percent target share. His return to the Tampa lineup could limit Emeka Egbuka’s opportunities, though the rookie should remain in most 12-team lineups against the Falcons. Evans needs to be started in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0922-d77b-adfb-cba3aae40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Philip Rivers said his Hall of Fame eligibility is “not a factor” in determining if he’ll play in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-092c-d77b-adfb-cbafbf440000</link>
      <description>Rivers’ HOF eligibility will reset if he’s on the Colts’ active roster at any point in the coming weeks. Rivers was set to be eligible for the Hall as early as 2026. “I haven’t been holding my breath on that,” Rivers said during a Wednesday presser. “I haven’t been counting down the years.” If that’s the case, Rivers could be under center in Week 15 against the Seahawks, as QB Riley Leonard deals with a knee injury he sustained in Week 14 against the Jaguars. Rivers reportedly impressed Colts coaches and officials in his workout. Rivers would profile as a desperation superflex play in fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-092c-d77b-adfb-cbafbf440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills EDGE Joey Bosa (hamstring) practiced in a limited capacity Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0931-da9b-a9bf-df3d699e0000</link>
      <description>Bosa was sidelined last week against the Bengals with a hamstring issue but could return for the Bills’ critical Week 15 matchup against the Patriots. Buffalo’s vulnerable defense will need all the help it can get to slow down MVP frontrunner Drake Maye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0931-da9b-a9bf-df3d699e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (personal) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0933-d77b-adfb-cbb3d59a0000</link>
      <description>Knox in Week 14 led the Bills in receiving with six grabs for 93 yards. If he doesn’t return to practice by Friday, Dalton Kincaid could see an expanded role, making him a must play in Week 15 against the Patriots. Twenty-five percent of the Bills’ targets have gone to the tight end position in 2025, the sixth highest rate in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0933-d77b-adfb-cbb3d59a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals did not activate RB Trey Benson (knee) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0936-d8cf-affb-bd3ecd560000</link>
      <description>The season is over for Benson, who never came back from the knee injury he suffered in October. He ends the season with 160 rush yards (5.5 yards per carry) and 13 receptions for 64 scoreless yards. Benson was set to function as the Cardinals’ lead back after James Conner went down for the year. That never materialized, and now Bam Knight serves as the nominal RB1 in the Arizona backfield. Knight, who has 25 touches over the past two games, profiles as a usable flex this week against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0936-d8cf-affb-bd3ecd560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts head coach Shane Steichen said QB Riley Leonard (knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0946-d8cf-affb-bd6e0ec00000</link>
      <description>It’s anyone’s guess for now how much Leonard practices after injuring his knee in Week 14’s loss to the Jaguars. Late-week practice participation for Leonard — who threw for 145 yards and an interception against Jacksonville — would suggest he can suit up in eek 15 against Seattle. Philip Rivers, 44, who signed with the Colts on Wednesday, could get the starting nod if Steichen determines Leonard isn’t ready to play. Both QBs would be big downgrades for every fantasy relevant player in the Colts offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0946-d8cf-affb-bd6e0ec00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said QB Marcus Mariota would start in Week 15 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0951-d8cf-affb-bd7b634f0000</link>
      <description>Daniels did not suffer structural damage to his injured left elbow last week against the Vikings, Quinn added. It appears the listless Commanders are intent on protecting Daniels from further setbacks in a lost season. Mariota, who has a higher drop back EPA than Daniels through Week 14, would profile as a superflex option against the soft Giants defense allowing the league’s fifth highest rate of yards per play this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0951-d8cf-affb-bd7b634f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said the team is not shutting down QB Jayden Daniels (elbow) for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-095d-d8cf-affb-bd7f3b4d0000</link>
      <description>There seems to be no real plan for how to handle Daniels in the final weeks of a disastrous season for Washington. Daniels, after aggravating his elbow injury in Week 14 against the Vikings, has been ruled out for Week 15’s game against the Giants. Quinn said Daniels will practice this week for some reason. Marcus Mariota, who has a higher drop back EPA than Daniels this season, will draw another start and becomes a viable streaming play in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-095d-d8cf-affb-bd7f3b4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0965-da9b-a9bf-df6d56950000</link>
      <description>With Taylor and Justin Fields (knee) sidelined, Brady Cook will get all the first-team practice reps ahead of the team’s Week 15 game against the Jaguars, according to head coach Aaron Glenn. Cook threw for 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions while completing 46.7 percent of his passes against the Dolphins in relief of Taylor last Sunday. He would be a significant downgrade for all New York pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0965-da9b-a9bf-df6d56950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Justin Fields (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0968-d77b-adfb-cbeb3de50000</link>
      <description>Tyrod Taylor was also a DNP on Wednesday after injuring his groin last week against the Dolphins. Undrafted rookie QB Brady Cook is set to see all the first-team practice reps ahead of the Jets’ Week 15 game against Jacksonville. Cook, who had 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions against Miami, would barley be startable even in superflex formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0968-d77b-adfb-cbeb3de50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
