<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 6-of-7 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 16 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4466-dc7a-af9b-cfff35980000</link>
      <description>Henry got the team on the scoreboard in the second quarter from one yard out, shedding his block on a Drake Maye bootleg for an easy score after his defender committed to keeping Maye from the end zone. His solid red zone role has kept his fantasy value afloat this season, even through a modest aDOT and route participation for the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4466-dc7a-af9b-cfff35980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Huntley completed 9-of-10 passes for 65 yards in the Ravens’ 28-24, Week 16 loss to the Patriots, adding two yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4469-d968-a19b-5cf98a2c0000</link>
      <description>Huntley entered the game in the second quarter following a back injury to starter Lamar Jackson. He wasn’t asked to do much through the air as the defense allowed the Ravens to ride Derrick Henry in the second half, ultimately coming up short of the much needed win after the Patriots surged from 11 points down to snatch the victory away. The loss removes control from the team’s path to the postseason, now requiring a loss by the Steelers in Week 17, a win over the Packers, and to beat their divisional opponents in Week 18 to reach the playoffs. They could also be forced to do so without Jackson, pending follow-on testing to his injured back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4469-d968-a19b-5cf98a2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 18 times for 128 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-446e-d35e-a1bf-45eed2120000</link>
      <description>Henry erupted in the second half following the departure of starting quarterback Lamar Jackson, quite literally putting the team on his back as the Ravens built an 11-point lead in the fourth quarter. The veteran bruiser overcame a lost fumble in the first quarter for his second consecutive 100-yard showing, sixth 100-yard outing, and fourth multi-touchdown game of the season. Even so, the Ravens fall to 7-8 with the loss and no longer control their own destiny for a playoff berth. King Henry gets a difficult matchup against the Packers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-446e-d35e-a1bf-45eed2120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught all seven targets for 84 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots, adding 18 yards and a touchdown on once carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4472-d56e-afff-e6fab5050000</link>
      <description>Flowers was the main cog of the offense through the air on a night starting quarterback Lamar Jackson departed in the second quarter with a back injury. His departure contributed to the team attempting only 20 passes, seven of which were directed to the veteran speedster. His returns were sparkling until a game-sealing fumble with just over two minutes remaining cost the Ravens the game and lowered their chances of reaching the playoffs. Flowers gets another difficult matchup against the Packers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4472-d56e-afff-e6fab5050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</link>
      <description>Not one of Hopkins’ four catches was routine as the veteran receiver made several spectacular grabs throughout. Arguably the most impressive was a ball down the sideline that deflected off the defenders hands, which he corralled in time to drag the trailing foot as he headed to the ground. Hopkins doesn’t play enough snaps for the low volume Ravens to warrant weekly fantasy consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4476-d968-a19b-5cf759600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards in the Ravens’ Week 16 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are never a high pass volume offense, but things got worse in this one following the departure of starting quarterback Lamar Jackson in the second quarter. The team shifted to a heavier emphasis on Derrick Henry in the second half, which appeared to be working until they allowed the Patriots to overcome an 11-point fourth quarter deficit to steal the win. Now at the tail end of his career, Andrews rarely returns fantasy utility if he is held out of the end zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4478-d968-a19b-5cf9c6bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lamar Jackson is day-to-day with a back bruise.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-462e-d35e-a1bf-47ee7b190000</link>
      <description>The back injury Jackson suffered in the second quarter of Sunday’s loss to the Patriots ended up sidelining him for the remainder of the game, but it sounds like he’ll have a chance to return in Week 17 against the Packers. The Ravens are hanging onto their playoff hopes by a thread, needing to win out over the final two weeks of the season while also needing the Steelers to lose their final two games. Facing a true do-or-die scenario next week, the Ravens will hope Jackson can return under center come Saturday. If he’s unable to go, Tyler Huntley would draw the start in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-462e-d35e-a1bf-47ee7b190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Little converted both of his field goal attempts in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4448-d35e-a1bf-45ca0ce90000</link>
      <description>The big-footed Little continues to be one of the NFL’s most reliable kickers. He’s missed just four kicks this season — making 88 percent of his kicks — while making 43 of 44 extra point tries. Little has benefited from the neutral and positive game script created by a red hot Jacksonville offense. He’ll be a solid option in Week 17 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4448-d35e-a1bf-45ca0ce90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) was discharged from the hospital on Sunday night.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4638-d968-a19b-5ef9869c0000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Jeff Legwold, Bryant was diagnosed with a concussion “but cleared of other major injuries” after leaving on a stretcher in Week 16’s loss to the Jaguars. Bryant was also tested for a neck injury, but those tests came back negative, per Legwold. Bryant is probably a long shot to clear concussion protocol in time to be ready for Week 17’s game against the Chiefs, but it sounds like he avoided all serious injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4638-d968-a19b-5ef9869c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the league will review the situation between DK Metcalf and a fan in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4642-dc7a-af9b-cfffd1fa0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was seen jawing with a Lions fan in the first half of Sunday’s game, and appeared to throw a punch in the direction of the fan. The fan involved in the incident spoke with a member of theDetroit Free Pressafter the game, and said Metcalf came over to him after he called him by his full name. Metcalf will almost certainly be fined for his involvement with the fan, but a suspension could also be on the table. We would expect to hear a final decision on this later in the day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4642-dc7a-af9b-cfffd1fa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
