<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 04:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed G Ben Powers (bicep) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb8d-db72-a199-fbcf3a110000</link>
      <description>Powers is a massive loss on the interior offensive line for an offense that derives its identity from the unit. The veteran guard is expected to miss the better part of the next two months as he heals from a torn bicep. The team said they hope to get him back for the stretch run in late December.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb8d-db72-a199-fbcf3a110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions HC Dan Campbell said CB D.J. Reed will be “out indefinitely” with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb97-def2-abdb-bff7fe250000</link>
      <description>Fellow cornerback Terrion Arnold is also expected to miss significant time with a shoulder injury, leaving the team extremely shorthanded on the back end ahead of a Week 6 matchup with the Chiefs. Safety Kerby Joseph has been tending to a knee injury as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb97-def2-abdb-bff7fe250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared DE Travon Walker, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Wyatt Milum, DL Danny Striggow, and DT Khalen Saunders inactive for Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb9d-db72-a199-fbdfca370000</link>
      <description>Walker was attempting to play just over a week after having surgery on his wrist but ultimately did not do enough to avoid being inactive. A win against the Chiefs will give the Jaguars more wins through five games than they had in all of the 2024 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb9d-db72-a199-fbdfca370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) is active for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbb9-d94a-a79d-bbbd26960000</link>
      <description>Worthy returned to the lineup in Week 4 following two missed games with a separated shoulder but experienced swelling in his ankle on the flight to Jacksonville, ultimately prompting the questionable tag. He is active and will play against the Jaguars, giving the Chiefs their primary option through the air. Inactive for the Chiefs are CB Kristian Fulton, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, DT Omarr Norman-Lott, OL Hunter Nourzad, and DE Malik Herring</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbb9-d94a-a79d-bbbd26960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) questionable to return to Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbbc-d94a-a79d-bbbdf98f0000</link>
      <description>Strange exited in the third quarter after a hit to the midsection and was labeled questionable to return on the same drive. He managed 22 yards on one reception prior to departing. Expect Johnny Mundt and Hunter Long to fill the void at tight end for the rest of the game against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bbbc-d94a-a79d-bbbdf98f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 29-of-41 passes for 318 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Chiefs’ 31-28, Week 5 loss to the Jaguars, adding 60 yards and a touchdown on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bc6a-dd4c-afb9-ffebdc1f0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs jumped out to an early 14-0 lead but didn’t score again until the fourth quarter. A 99-yard pick-six by Devin Lloyd at the end of the third quarter gave the Jaguars their first lead of the game and served as a 14-point swing, forcing Mahomes into desperation mode in the final frame. Penalties also played a massive role in the defeat, with four special teams infractions routinely leading to poor field position for Kansas City and excellent field position for Jacksonville. Kicker Harrison Butker kicked the ball out of bounds on the kickoff following a Kansas City touchdown with under two minutes remaining, giving the Jaguars the ball at the 40 for their game-winning drive. Mahomes continues to lead the team in rushing through five games, a completely unsustainable trend if they are to return to the AFC Championship game for the eighth consecutive season. In all, it was a poor team performance for the Chiefs that drops them to 2-3 ahead of a Sunday Night Football clash with the surging Lions in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bc6a-dd4c-afb9-ffebdc1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed seven times for 49 yards and two touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars, adding eight yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcb8-dd4c-afb9-fff937990000</link>
      <description>Hunt matched lead back Isiah Pacheco with seven carries and contributred two green zone touchdowns on carries inside the five in the second half. There doesn’t seem to be much fantasy upside from this backfield considering quarterback Patrick Mahomes continues to lead the team in rushing through five games, although Hunt appears to be the back most likely to contribute usable fantasy scores with the more robust red zone role. Hunt remains a touchdown-dependent, desperation FLEX moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcb8-dd4c-afb9-fff937990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed seven times for 36 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars, adding 20 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcca-d94a-a79d-bdcf33730000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers are surely growing tired of seeing Pacheco held to 10 or fewer touches, with Week 5 marking his third such output in five tries, with no game with more than 11 touches. He continues to split work with both Kareem Hunt and rookie Brashard Smith, the former of whom punched in two touchdowns from inside the five against the Jaguars. Fantasy managers are likely stuck with the veteran back in the hopes something changes moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcca-d94a-a79d-bdcf33730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 3-of-5 targets for 90 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bccd-def2-abdb-bded21e20000</link>
      <description>Thornton caught his first three targets in the first half for gains of 24 yards, 32 yards, and 34 yards but failed to catch another ball in the final 42 minutes of play. He saw his snap rate cut drastically with the return of Xavier Worthy in Week 4, something that carried over into the team’s Week 5 loss to the Jaguars. It appears his early-season involvement in the offense ahs gone by the wayside, something unlikely to change course with Rashee Rice’s return looming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bccd-def2-abdb-bded21e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 7-of-8 targets for 61 yards and a touchdown in the Chief’s Week 5 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd0-db72-a199-fedb12510000</link>
      <description>Kelce scored from two yards out on the team’s second possession in the first quarter, padding his fantasy stats the rest of the way with six more short-area receptions. The veteran tight end turned 36 Sunday and lacks the same burst and athleticism he had earlier in his career, but he can still return usable fantasy weeks due to his red zone connection with quarterback Patrick Mahomes. Kelce is teetering on the fringes of TE1 territory but lacks truly elite ceiling in a more conservative role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd0-db72-a199-fedb12510000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
