<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 21:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e987-db72-a199-fbcf64c10000</link>
      <description>Oh, dear. Just a few days after Downs scored his first touchdown of the season, he appeared on the Colts’ injury report with a concussion. The Colts’ slot receiver technically has a chance to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol in time for the team’s Week 7 game against the Chargers, but fantasy managers should plan to be without him and immediately begin making backup plans. Downs’ 14 targets earned over the last two weeks lead all Colts pass catchers. Were Downs indeed unable to play this weekend, it would free up a significant share of the team’s targets for TE Tyler Warren and WRs Michael Pittman Jr. and Alec Pierce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e987-db72-a199-fbcf64c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e988-db72-a199-fbcbd4f00000</link>
      <description>This is likely just a bit of maintenance for the veteran receiver. Jeudy led the league in routes last year and is on pace to do so again. He should be good to go by the end of the week. Jeudy led the Browns with 13 targets in Week 6 but turned them into just five grabs for 43 yards. He is falling into the WR4 ranks heading into his Week 7 date with Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e988-db72-a199-fbcbd4f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 7 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e986-dd4c-afb9-efc7489d0000</link>
      <description>Pierce returned in Week 6 after a two-game absence following his Week 3 concussion. He evidently picked up a minor ankle injury along the way, though he does not appear to be at risk of missing any time. The Colts’ field-stretching wide receiver will be called upon to generate explosive gains against the Chargers this weekend. Colts slot WR Josh Downs (concussion) and rotational WR Ashton Dulin (chest) did not practice on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e986-dd4c-afb9-efc7489d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e994-d94a-a79d-e99d847c0000</link>
      <description>Saints head coach Kellen Moore called it a maintenance day for Kamara and said the ankle injury, which Kamara played through on Sunday, has not gotten worse since last week. We fully expect Kamara to suit up for Week 7 against the Bears. In a great matchup for opposing backs, Kamara will get one more week in the RB2 ranks despite his efficiency once again declining this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e994-d94a-a79d-e99d847c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e998-db72-a199-fbdb42fe0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals have handled Murray’s mid-foot sprain smartly and conservatively thus far, keeping him inactive last week after the quarterback logged a limited session on Friday. While Murray may be feeling the need to return, the Cardinals could be content to let him sit another week. Fill-in starting QB Jacoby Brissett threw for 320 yards last week, beating Murray’s season-high by 100 yards. Murray should be considered questionable to play at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e998-db72-a199-fbdb42fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e99a-d94a-a79d-e99f72c20000</link>
      <description>A limited practice to start the week is typically maintenance for a veteran player. Barring a setback, we expect Olave to suit up for Week 7’s game against the Bears. Olave has been dominating volume in New Orleans but hasn’t turned his absurd target totals into a true spike week. He has five games with at least 50 receiving yards but only one over 60 and no triple-digit performances. A date with Chicago’s porous defense will be his best shot at a breakout performance, keeping him in the middle of the WR2 ranks for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e99a-d94a-a79d-e99f72c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e999-d94a-a79d-e99dce4e0000</link>
      <description>Harrison’s early-week participation is promising, but he still must pass through all five phases of the NFL’s concussion protocol while remaining setback-free before he can be cleared to return. This is a step in the right direction for him, though. Cardinals WR Zay Jones (knee) was sidelined on Wednesday and WR Michael Wilson (foot) was limited, leaving the receiving corps in a precarious place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e999-d94a-a79d-e99dce4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs (chest) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a0-def2-abdb-fde11ea60000</link>
      <description>This is the first we are hearing of this injury, though a limited practice on Wednesday is nothing to be concerned about for a veteran like Diggs. He should be good to go by Friday. Diggs posted back-to-back 100-yard outings before Week 6 but came back to Earth versus the Saints with just 28 yards. He did, however, have a 51-yard catch called back by a penalty. Despite the quiet showing, Diggs will still sit in the WR2 ranks for Week 7 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a0-def2-abdb-fde11ea60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3c6ee0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ passing game is in rough shape. Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot), and WRs Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) and Michael Wilson (foot) were limited today as well. If Jones can suit up in Week 7 against the Packers, he could find himself in a FLEX-worthy role, catching passes from QB Jacoby Brissett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3c6ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Michael Wilson (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a3-def2-abdb-fde388660000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ starting quarterback and starting wide receiver trio is entirely banged up at the moment. QB Kyler Murray (foot) and WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) were both limited today, while WR Zay Jones (knee) did not practice. Wilson has been very unproductive this season and makes for an unreliable FLEX option, though he could see an increase in targets this week, pending his teammates’ availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a3-def2-abdb-fde388660000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
