<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars EDGE Travon Walker (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c263-d90e-a9da-df6fa1220000</link>
      <description>Walker missed Week 12 with the knee issue and looks likely to sit for at least one more game. Walker has just 2.5 sacks this year. His absence doesn’t change much for Cam Ward and the Titans, who are taking on the Jags this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c263-d90e-a9da-df6fa1220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c268-db57-afda-d67a2e330000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor did not practice last week due to a hamstring issue, missing Week 12 against the Seahawks. He returns to practice in a limited capacity to start of the week with the potential to play Week 13 against the Jaguars. Ayomanor has caught 28-of-59 targets for 334 yards and two touchdowns this year, finding some fantasy relevance. With Calvin Ridley out for the season, he has fantasy WR4 viability when healthy. If Ayomanor can ramp up to full practice participation this week, he has a better chance of playing against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c268-db57-afda-d67a2e330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c26e-d82c-a79a-f3fe954d0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo has been dealing with a foot issues for a couple weeks but has been able to play through it. He gets a limited practice on Wednesday and should still be good to go for Week 13 against the Jaguars. Rookie Gunnar Helm has been getting more opportunities at the tight end spot, so fantasy managers are unlikely to be eyeing Okonkwo in a week where no teams are on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c26e-d82c-a79a-f3fe954d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans C Lloyd Cushenberry (foot) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c273-d90e-a9da-df7fad290000</link>
      <description>Cushenberry is the Titans’ starting center and popped up on the injury report with a foot issue. Also not practicing were DT Shy Tuttle (concussion), S Xavier Woods (hamstring), and S Kendell Brooks (concussion). Cushenberry is the primary concern in the middle of the Titans’ offensive line, but the Titans defense is also a bit banged up heading into Week 13 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c273-d90e-a9da-df7fad290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) is questionable for Week 13 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c279-db57-afda-d67b5a540000</link>
      <description>Golden was listed as a limited practice participant in all three Packers practice reports this week. He missed Week 12 against the Vikings and is now listed as questionable for Thanksgiving day against the Lions. The rookie has fallen down the receiving ladder for the Packers, with three targets in each of his last three games played. If Golden does play, he is in the WR5 range, while Dontayvion Wicks and Christian Watson will get boosts if Golden is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c279-db57-afda-d67b5a540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c280-db57-afda-d6b2d9500000</link>
      <description>The Chargers designated Hampton to return from injured reserve this week and he starts out practicing in a limited capacity. Hampton said he was dealing with a fractured left ankle and is waiting for doctors to clear him. Kimani Vidal has been the lead back in the meantime and the Chargers get a plus matchup against the Raiders in Week 13. It will be difficult to keep Hampton on fantasy benches if he is indeed activated for Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c280-db57-afda-d6b2d9500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Tre Tucker (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c287-d82c-a79a-f397eaa40000</link>
      <description>Tucker pops up on the Raiders’ first injury report of the week with a knee issue. He was limited, so little cause for concern thus far and he is still trending to play in Week 13. If Tucker cannot go, Dont’e Thornton and Jack Bech will see more opportunities, though we cannot recommend investing in any Raiders wide receivers outside of Tucker. The veteran Tyler Lockett (ankle) was a full participant in practice and is the best non-Tucker wide receiver option in Las Vegas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c287-d82c-a79a-f397eaa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c28f-d90e-a9da-df8f83200000</link>
      <description>Mayer left Week 12 against the Browns with an ankle injury and did not return. He starts out this week not practicing, putting his status for Week 13 against the Chargers in jeopardy. The Raiders’ passing offense is not fruitful for fantasy purposes, so Mayer’s potential absence only boosts Brock Bowers’ fantasy opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c28f-d90e-a9da-df8f83200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers K Eddy Pineiro (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c291-d82c-a79a-f39597450000</link>
      <description>Pineiro is still not back at practice after suffering a hamstring injury in Week 11. Matt Gay kicked in his stead in Week 12 and is likely to do so again for Week 13 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c291-d82c-a79a-f39597450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c297-d82c-a79a-f397100f0000</link>
      <description>Njoku dealt with the knee issue last week, but played through it to the tune of zero targets in essentially a part-time role in Week 12. Also limited among the offensive skill players were RB Jerome Ford (hamstring) and WR Jamari Thrash (foot). None of these three are crucial producers for the Browns at the moment. Njoku’s absence would give more opportunities for Harold Fannin, though he is still trending to play Week 13 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c297-d82c-a79a-f397100f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
