<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c507-db72-a199-ff4f1fa10000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation, but it’s still good to see Barkley get in a full practice and be cleared from the injury report entirely. His injury was described as “general soreness’ by NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport earlier this week. We don’t expect it to limit him in any capacity versus the Giants. Barkley is off to a slow start this year, but a date with the lowly G-Men should give him a chance to rack up touches and chunk plays. He remains an RB1 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c507-db72-a199-ff4f1fa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (ankle) will not play in Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c513-def2-abdb-dd7369840000</link>
      <description>Dickerson suffered the ankle injury in Week 5 and was always expected to miss at least one game. He could be out another week or two as well. Brett Toth replaced Dickerson in the lineup last week and is presumably in line to do so again versus the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c513-def2-abdb-dd7369840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (heel) is questionable for Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c515-d94a-a79d-cd1d28170000</link>
      <description>Linebacker Nakobe Dean (knee) is also listed as questionable. Carter was added to the injury report on Wednesday as a limited participant before being listed as questionable. A surprise addition to the injury report this late in the week is typically a bad sign, and the fact that the Eagles have a short turnaround to Thursday’s game will only compound the issue. Philly will still be favored by at least a touchdown with or without Carter, but his absence would make life a little easier for Jaxson Dart in his third NFL start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c515-d94a-a79d-cd1d28170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed Kimani Vidal from their practice squad to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c51b-dd4c-afb9-e7db262b0000</link>
      <description>The team also signed Nyheim Miller-Hines to their practice squad. Both running backs were cut at the end of training camp. Vidal re-signed to the team’s pratice squad and is now being called up permanently with both Najee Harris and Omarion Hampton on injured reserve. Vidal will split work with Hassan Haskins this week. Haskins should handle more work on early downs, making him the priority off waivers this week. Vidal will be a high-risk RB4 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c51b-dd4c-afb9-e7db262b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said he believes GM Eric DeCosta “will continue to have discussions about adding a pass rusher ahead of the trade deadline.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c511-def2-abdb-dd7123db0000</link>
      <description>On Tuesday, DeCosta traded away EDGE Odafe Oweh and a seventh-round pick to acquire former Chargers S Alohi Gilman and a fifth-round pick. Oweh is in the fifth and final year of his rookie contract, and DeCosta evidently had no plans to sign the 26-year-old EDGE rusher to a multi-year extension, instead opting to recoup value before Oweh’s scheduled departure. Unfortunately, Oweh’s departure leaves the Ravens’ pass rush worryingly thin. They currently do not have a pass rusher with double-digit quarterback pressures on the active roster. Trading for an affordable pass rusher who can impact the game immediately makes sense. Those, of course, can be difficult to find.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c511-def2-abdb-dd7123db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler does not expect the Raiders to bench QB Geno Smith in Week 6 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c53f-d94a-a79d-cd3f58fe0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler classified the Raiders’ general feeling toward Smith as being “mildly concerned” at the moment, “but there’s no sentiment that Smith is a broken quarterback.” Fowler notes that Raiders head coach Pete Carroll and Smith “have enough sweat equity together from their Seattle days that Carroll could stick with him a little longer as a result.” Fowler’s colleague, Dan Graziano, adds that “for now, it sounds like the Raiders will ride it out with Smith,” though the turnovers must decrease soon. Smith faces the Titans and Chiefs before Las Vegas goes on bye in Week 8. If Smith continues to rack up interceptions over the next two weeks, backup QB Kenny Pickett could be under center in Week 9 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c53f-d94a-a79d-cd3f58fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker (quad) is practicing in full for Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c52b-d94a-a79d-cd2f34ec0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers opened Coker’s practice window this week. A full practice to open the week puts him on track to play on Sunday, but the team will need to see how he responds after two more practices before making a final decision. Coker was a standout performer during the preseason and had likely cemented himself as a starting wideout for the Panthers before going down with the quad injury. He should reclaim his starting role in the next week or two.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c52b-d94a-a79d-cd2f34ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Lions EDGE Aidan Hutchinson “looks destined for a new deal” that will keep him in Detroit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c552-def2-abdb-dd7399820000</link>
      <description>Fowler is unconvinced that Hutchinson will beat the four-year, $186 million deal signed by Packers EDGE Micah Parsons, but it should be plenty lucrative and on par with “quarterback money.” The Lions’ 25-year-old pass rusher currently ties for a positional high in quarterback pressures (31) and ties for second in sacks (six). The Lions face off against the Chiefs in Week 6’s Sunday Night Football game on NBC, and Chiefs EDGE George Karlaftis is the player with whom Hutchinson is tied in the former category. Karlaftis signed a four-year, $93 million extension through 2030 in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c552-def2-abdb-dd7399820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown (wrist) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c55e-db72-a199-ff5f485d0000</link>
      <description>This is the first appearance on the injury report for St. Brown. The Lions do a good job of resting their veterans throughout the week, so fantasy managers shouldn’t panic just yet. It is, however, a situation to monitor throughout the week. Jameson Williams could finally see more work on underneath routes if St. Brown were to miss Week 6. Sam LaPorta would also be asked to step up in a potential shootout with Kansas City. We will get more info when the Lions release their practice report of the week on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c55e-db72-a199-ff5f485d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (knee) is practicing in full for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c55f-d94a-a79d-cd5fb5510000</link>
      <description>The Steelers infamously declared Warren inactive on the morning of their Dublin, Ireland game in Week 4 against the Vikings, setting up West Coast fantasy managers for goose eggs in their RB2 spot. The Steelers’ Week 5 bye appears to have helped Warren put the knee ailment behind him, though his backup, RB Kenneth Gainwell, could take on a decently sized workload in Week 6, after totaling 134 scrimmage yards and two touchdowns in Warren’s stead. Last week, ESPN’s Dan Graziano did list Warren ahead of Gainwell when discussing the backfield’s current state, so Warren should still have access to a fantasy-friendly role this week, even if Gainwell’s touch count does increase. Treat Warren as an RB3/FLEX with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c55f-d94a-a79d-cd5fb5510000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
