<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LT Will Campbell (knee) is active for Week 18 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a9e-d968-a19b-daffb69a0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots’ rookie left tackle is active for the first time since Week 12. He could be on something of a snap count as he looks to get his legs back ahead of the postseason, but the Pats remain in contention for the AFC’s No. 1 seed, if only faintly. Perhaps Campbell will play more than expected if circumstance dictates. Inactive for the Patriots are OT Marcus Bryant, OG Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito, EDGE Harold Landry, LB Robert Spillane, DT Khyiris Tonga and OG Jared Wilson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a9e-d968-a19b-daffb69a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared QB Tyrod Taylor, RB Breece Hall, WR Tyler Johnson, TE Jelani Woods, DL Micheal Clemons, CB Brandon Stephens, and CB Qwan’tez Stiggers inactive for Week 18 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a9e-d968-a19b-daff82fd0000</link>
      <description>We knew that Hall was going to be out with a knee injury, but it seems that Tyrod Taylor will also be out with a knee injury, which means that Justin Fields will be the backup on Sunday. Taylor will finish the season 80-for-104 for 779 yards with five touchdowns and five interceptions in six games (four starts). The 36-year-old will be a free agent this offseason and remains good enough, when healthy, to be an NFL backup if he chooses to continue his playing career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a9e-d968-a19b-daff82fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Brandin Cooks inactive for Week 18 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aa5-d35e-a1bf-cfe733c20000</link>
      <description>Every other player the Bills declared inactive is a key starter, like Dion Dawkins or Greg Rousseau, so this says a lot about how important Cooks is to the Buffalo offense despite only being on the roster for three games. The 32-year-old posted a 100-yard game last week and has emerged as the primary deep threat for Josh Allen and the offense. Expect Cooks to be a key contributor in the playoffs for as long as the Bills can keep winning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aa5-d35e-a1bf-cfe733c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Isiah Pacheco is inactive for Week 18 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aa7-d968-a19b-daf738380000</link>
      <description>Pacheco’s season will end after 17 weeks in which he once again struggled with injuries and on-field effectiveness in the pass-heavy Kansas City offense. Pacheco, with 462 rushing yards and one touchdown over 13 games, was among the NFL’s least efficient running backs for a second straight season. He once again lost valuable work — including goal line touches — to Kareem Hunt and managed a meager 19 receptions on the season. Pacheco, 26, had just six games with double digit touches in 2025, and did little after first contact on his rushes. He heads into the offseason as an undrafted free agent, and could see interest from multiple teams looking for a solid RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aa7-d968-a19b-daf738380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (concussion) is active for Week 18 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a99-d56e-afff-eef9c6df0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers have ruled out starting RB Omarion Hampton (ankle), among other impactful starters, as they prepare for the playoffs. Chargers No. 2 RB Kimani Vidal (neck) will likely get the start this week. While Haskins will rotate in, healthy RB Jaret Patterson will also be in play. It is a muddled situation against a tough Broncos defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8a99-d56e-afff-eef9c6df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught 4-of-7 targets for 132 yards and two touchdowns in Indianapolis’ Week 18 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ab5-dc7a-af9b-cfbf492a0000</link>
      <description>Pierce went nuclear against Houston’s backup cornerbacks, notching a huge deep touchdown over a peeking-in-backfield Tremon Smith. He was ejected after making (light) contact with an official in the third quarter arguing a non-call in the end zone. Setting a career-high in targets and yards in the final year of his rookie deal, Pierce looked to be coming on in the middle of the season. He went from an average of 2.8 catches and 54.8 yards in his first four games to an average of 3.6 catches, 72.4 yards, and all four of his touchdowns from Weeks 7-16. That includes a dud with Philip Rivers and does not include his Week 17 disaster bagel. Pierce proved that he has a future at the top of someone’s route tree this season. He may draw a protective franchise tag or transition tag from the Colts, but if not, Pierce figures to be one of the best free agents on the market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ab5-dc7a-af9b-cfbf492a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared QB Geno Smith, RB Raheem Mostert, OL Dylan Parham, DT Adam Butler, DT Brodric Martin, CB Chigozie Anusiem, and S Terrell Edmunds inactive for Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ab5-dc7a-af9b-cfbf53460000</link>
      <description>Smith is dealing with an ankle injury and won’t suit up for the season finale against the Chiefs. That means Kenny Pickett will get another start for a Raiders team positioned to get the first overall pick in the 2026 NFL Draft. Pickett threw for 64 yards and an interception in a Week 14 start against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ab5-dc7a-af9b-cfbf53460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 8-of-11 targets for 101 yards in the Vikings’ Week 18 win against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ac4-d35e-a1bf-cfc6d30b0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson was 47 yard short of 1,000 receiving yards on the season and eclipsed that marker in the first half with a barrage of targets from J.J. McCarthy before McCarthy left the game with a right hand injury. Plagued by some of the worst quarterbacking in recent NFL memory, Jefferson managed just two touchdowns after ten touchdowns last season without an established starter under center for the Vikings. He had no chemistry whatsoever with McCarthy. Jefferson remains an elite wideout who dominates targets and air yards and will continue to do so in 2026. If he gets some decent quarterback play, Jefferson should bounce back nicely in Kevin O’Connell’s fantasy-friendly offensive scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ac4-d35e-a1bf-cfc6d30b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett recorded his 23rd sack of the 2025 season, giving him the NFL record for sacks in a season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aaf-d56e-afff-eeef0fc70000</link>
      <description>Neither the Browns nor the Bengals were in the playoff race for this game, so all eyes were on Garrett as he chased the record for the second straight week. He made onlookers wait until the final minutes of the game before tracking down Joe Burrow behind the line of scrimmage for an easy takedown. He was previously a half-sack behind T.J. Watt and Michael Strahan for the record, through Strahan accomplished the feat when the NFL played just 16 games in a season. Garrett locked up his second Defensive Player of the Year award several weeks ago, but now he will hold a place in the history books as the most productive pass-rusher the league has ever seen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aaf-d56e-afff-eeef0fc70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
