<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts designated Anthony Richardson (eye) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3254-d8cf-affb-be7e2d470000</link>
      <description>The Colts now have three weeks to officially activate Richardson from injured reserve. Head coach Shane Steichen said he still has some vision limitations. As Rapoport notes, this is largely just to get him back on the practice field. The Colts are rolling with Philip Rivers for now and have Riley Leonard as a backup option in the meantime. Richardson is undoubtedly still at least a few weeks away from returning, if not more. Unless Rivers struggles mightily, Richardson will be relegated to backup duties once fully cleared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3254-d8cf-affb-be7e2d470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3263-d8cf-affb-be6b028a0000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Matt LaFleur, the team will give Jacobs up until gametime before making a call on his status. That means he will be listed as questionable on the team’s final injury report, which will drop later today. Jacobs has not practiced at all this week, which is usually a sign that a player won’t suit up. However, Jacobs has been playing through his knee issues for weeks, and there has been no indication that his injury worsened in Week 15. Fantasy managers should be prepared for him to sit, even if he is truly questionable heading into the weekend. Emanuel Wilson would be in line for a workhorse role and an RB1 ranking if Jacobs can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3263-d8cf-affb-be6b028a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said EDGE Drake Jackson (knee) will be able to play in Week 16 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3270-d8cf-affb-be7a9b630000</link>
      <description>Jackson hasn’t played since suffering a patellar tendon injury with the 49ers in 2023. Though the Commanders’ season is over, Jackson will get the opportunity to get some reps on tape before he heads into free agency in the spring. Jackson has six sacks in 23 career games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3270-d8cf-affb-be7a9b630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (personal) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3286-d087-addf-b3f6a6330000</link>
      <description>Reed missed yesterday’s session while tending to a personal matter. After returning today, he will get cleared for Week 16 when the team releases its final injury report. With Christian Watson trending toward playing this week, expect a messy receiver rotation for the Packers, per usual. Reed will be stuck in the WR4 ranks if Watson plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3286-d087-addf-b3f6a6330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ed2-d005-a9bf-fef67b0c0000</link>
      <description>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans inspired hope when he told reporters that Marks could have returned in Week 15, if the team had needed him. Having missed the first two Week 16 practices, Marks must now be viewed as questionable to play. The Texans (9-5) are in playoff contention, so it is possible that the team is simply giving their featured rookie running back extra time to rest before relying heavily upon him once again on game day. If he can resume practicing tomorrow, he should be good to go. In the meantime, stashing RB Jawhar Jordan is worthwhile. Veteran RB Nick Chubb (ribs) should also be available on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ed2-d005-a9bf-fef67b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (oblique) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32b1-d087-addf-b3f1667d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans face the lowly Raiders this week, so the defense should be okay if Stingley is unable to play. Houston (9-5) currently sits in second in the AFC South and seventh in the AFC playoff picture. Getting him back in time for the team’s Week 17 game against the Chargers would be helpful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32b1-d087-addf-b3f1667d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (illness) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32bb-d35e-a1bf-77fb7b3b0000</link>
      <description>Ironically, Jackson missed practice on Wednesday after a Tuesday media session in which he said he is “feeling better” after dealing with multiple injuries this season. The Ravens’ quarterback has finished as a QB1 just twice since Week 9. He faces the Patriots’ talented defense in Week 16 and can only be viewed as a volatile, borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32bb-d35e-a1bf-77fb7b3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Hendon Hooker, formerly of the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32c0-da28-afbb-f6fdf6360000</link>
      <description>Hooker spent time with the Panthers this season, but spent two seasons with the Lions after they drafted him in the 2023 NFL Draft’s third round. Jets OC Tanner Engstrand served as the Lions’ passing game coordinator from 2023-2024. Adding Hooker to the team’s practice squad makes sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32c0-da28-afbb-f6fdf6360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Rashee Rice (concussion) will not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32c7-d087-addf-b3f7ffe10000</link>
      <description>Rice is on the wrong side of questionable at this point, as is WR Tyquan Thornton (concussion), who will also be sidelined today. The Chiefs will likely attempt to control the game with a run-heavy approach against the Titans, with QB Gardner Minshew under center. Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy and TE Travis Kelce should handle significant portions of the available targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32c7-d087-addf-b3f7ffe10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) will not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32d5-d087-addf-b3f5285b0000</link>
      <description>McDuffie appears unlikely to play at this point. With the Chiefs having been eliminated from playoff contention, there is not need to rush him back. The Chiefs’ defense can still pose problems for Titans rookie QB Cam Ward, even with its No. 1 cornerback sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32d5-d087-addf-b3f5285b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
