<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is questionable for Baltimore’s Week 8 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17a4-deb1-a39b-37ae34ec0000</link>
      <description>Jackson got in a full practice on Friday for the first time since hurting his hamstring, but the questionable listing is curious. The Ravens did not have Jackson talk to the media on Sunday, instead letting Tyler Huntley be interviewed. John Harbaugh said Huntley would start if Jackson could not go. This won’t be the last Lamar Jackson update this weekend, but it does seem like there is some real doubt on his status despite practicing all week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17a4-deb1-a39b-37ae34ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Jerry Jeudy (knee) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1797-dab4-a3fb-9ff727160000</link>
      <description>Jeudy will be active on game day after practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday and Friday. He functions more as a target share dent against TEs David Njoku (knee, questionable) and TE Harold Fannin Jr. than he does as a serious FLEX option. Jeudy is catching just 44.9 percent of his targets and has cleared 60 yards in a game just once. He has not scored a touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1797-dab4-a3fb-9ff727160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins (illness) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17aa-d245-adfb-97ffe81a0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday after a Thursday DNP. Hopkins remains just a FLEX dart throw at this stage of his career and gets massively less appealing if Lamar Jackson (questionable, hamstring) does not play against the Bears in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17aa-d245-adfb-97ffe81a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17ae-dab4-a3fb-9ffe4ed50000</link>
      <description>Neither are CB Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring), ILB Roquan Smith (hamstring), or CB Marlon Humphrey (illness) — and outside of Humphrey missing Wednesday’s practice all four of those players got in full sessions all week. Baltimore’s defense finally looks to mostly be recovered from their early October swoon. Will they actually play better in Week 8? That’s the real question.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17ae-dab4-a3fb-9ffe4ed50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Scotty Miller (finger) will not play in Week 8’s game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17b9-deb1-a39b-37bfb6830000</link>
      <description>He apparently picked up this injury in practice on Thursday, and did not return on Friday. Usually this kind of quick rule out would put Miller at some risk of an IR stint. His absence does not impact fantasy football in the slightest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17b9-deb1-a39b-37bfb6830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) is not on Pittsburgh’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17bc-dab4-a3fb-9ffc84b00000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full all three days this week. Austin profiles as a low-end FLEX play this week, but at least he managed to avoid a trip to IR and the Packers do invite defenses to throw on them. Something something Aaron Rodgers #RevengeGame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17bc-dab4-a3fb-9ffc84b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (hip) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 8 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17c7-dab4-a3fb-9ff777c20000</link>
      <description>Golden wasn’t on the injury report until Friday, when he popped up with a limited session due to a hip injury. We suspect there will be more reporting on this one over the weekend, but late week downgrades are never auspicious news. Golden is a WR3 candidate if he plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17c7-dab4-a3fb-9ff777c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys ruled out CB Trevon Diggs (concussion/knee) for Week 8 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178f-deb1-a39b-378f39720000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys will also be without starting S Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder), rookie CB Shavon Revel (knee) and LB DeMarvion Overshown (knee). Backups S Juanyeh Thomas (migraine) and DE Marshawn Kneeland (ankle) are questionable. The Broncos offense has a fantasy-friendly matchup on its hands this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178f-deb1-a39b-378f39720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (calf) is not on Green Bay’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17c9-d245-adfb-97dfb1bc0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs reportedly had to fight hard with management to be active for Week 7, but three limited sessions this week were apparently enough to keep him up this week. He’ll be on the RB1 line as usual against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17c9-d245-adfb-97dfb1bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers K Brandon McManus (quad) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 8 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cb-d5d8-a3ff-ffeb8d4f0000</link>
      <description>McManus practiced in a limited setting on Thursday and Friday. If he’s not able to go in Week 8, Lucas Havrisik would take the reins as Green Bay’s kicker again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cb-d5d8-a3ff-ffeb8d4f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
