<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 3 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6337-d6a5-adff-f7f743e30000</link>
      <description>Mooney was limited on Wednesday before practicing in full on Thursday and Friday. Facing the Panthers’ relatively soft safety duo bodes positively for the field-stretching wide receiver, but game script could end up working against him in the second half. Overall, it’s a matchup worth targeting. He’s a WR3/FLEX start in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6337-d6a5-adff-f7f743e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) will not play in Week 3’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6339-d93f-ad9d-7bff13860000</link>
      <description>He was ruled out after not practicing a single time all week. The guidance from Jordan Schultz after Week 2’s win was that Stewart will likely be week-to-week. He’ll need to get on the field at some point ahead of Week 4 before we even generate the expectation that he’ll play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6339-d93f-ad9d-7bff13860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) is questionable for Week 3’s game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6345-dfde-a1bd-7fcd56ba0000</link>
      <description>Brian Daboll was optimistic that Thomas would play, but it has the feel of a game-time decision despite three straight limited practices. Thomas would be an enormous upgrade over Marcus Mbow if able to play (and play up to his natural talent) in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6345-dfde-a1bd-7fcd56ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons ruled out CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) for Week 3 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6330-d6a5-adff-f7f502b30000</link>
      <description>Terrell was injured in-game last week and the Falcons replaced him with former slot CB Dee Alford. The secondary will have a tough time containing Panthers rookie WR Tetairoa McMillan with Terrell stuck on the sideline. Falcons backup CB Mike Ford (groin) is also questionable. On the plus side, Pearce (groin) practiced in full on Friday before being removed from the injury report. He is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6330-d6a5-adff-f7f502b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WRs Wan’Dale Robinson (foot) and Darius Slayton (groin/calf) aren’t on New York’s final injury report for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6348-dfde-a1bd-7fcd05c80000</link>
      <description>Both will play against the Chiefs as the Giants hope to avoid falling to 0-3. Robinson makes for a WR3/FLEX option against the Chiefs, while Slayton simply hasn’t generated enough targets with Russell Wilson to be a reliable start at this point of the season. Both receivers participated in all three practices this week on a limited basis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6348-dfde-a1bd-7fcd05c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) and Tyrone Tracy (calf) aren’t on New York’s final injury report for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634a-d1b3-a5dd-637b1fa10000</link>
      <description>Both will play against the Chiefs. Tracy got in three limited practices but appeared to lose his head-of-committee role to Skattebo last week and should be considered a risky start even in deeper leagues. The Chiefs have done an admirable job against the run this year and the Giants have not been able to generate anything on the ground, leaving Skattebo as a FLEX play despite a solid expected volume in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634a-d1b3-a5dd-637b1fa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints ruled out EDGE Chase Young (calf) for Week 3 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634a-dfde-a1bd-7fcf1b530000</link>
      <description>Friday’s injury report has not yet been released but as of Thursday, Young remains a non-participant. The Saints will also be without OG Dillon Radunz (toe), who started in Week 2 against the 49ers. Saints LG Trevor Penning (toe) and RT Taliese Fuaga (knee/back) are both questionable for Week 3 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634a-dfde-a1bd-7fcf1b530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said OL Steve Avila (ankle) is doubtful for Week 3’s game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634d-d6a5-adff-f7cd3b280000</link>
      <description>It’ll likely be Justin Decich at guard for the Rams again on Sunday against Jalen Carter and company. McVay added that Colby Parkinson (ankle) is questionable for the contest. No Rams tight ends currently qualify as major fantasy plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634d-d6a5-adff-f7cd3b280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (quad) is questionable for Week 3 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634c-d6a5-adff-f7cd3dcf0000</link>
      <description>Swift was a limited practice participant all week. He seemingly has decent odds of suiting up, but he might end up being on a snap count. As a result, fantasy managers should quickly add backup RB Kyle Monangai wherever available. It’s possible the rookie back takes on a FLEX-worthy workload in what is expected to be a back-and-forth affair. If he seizes the opportunity, it could earn him more work moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-634c-d6a5-adff-f7cd3dcf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
