<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:43:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet had 14 rushes for 52 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 13 win against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d79c-db57-afda-d7bed5180000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet played behind Ken Walker in the first half and took over as the Seahawks’ primary ball carrier in the third and fourth quarters with Seattle up multiple scores. He scored his eighth touchdown of the season on a nice burst up the middle in the third quarter, and remains the preferred backfield option inside the ten yard line. Though Walker is the Seahawks’ clear-cut pass catching back, Charbonnet will continue as a touchdown-dependent RB3 play in Week 14 against Atlanta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d79c-db57-afda-d7bed5180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught 1-of-3 targets for seven yards in the Seahawks’ Week 13 win against the Vikings. adding one rush for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a5-d82c-a79a-f7b5577d0000</link>
      <description>Shaheed has lost all of his fantasy value since being traded from the Saints to the run-first Seahawks. He now has four receptions over four games with Seattle, and he’s not being used as a downfield threat the way he was in New Orleans. Against the Vikings he ran a pass route on 20 of the team’s 32 drop backs and was targeted on 10 percent of those routes. Shaheed doesn’t need to be rostered in 12-team leagues and won’t be fantasy relevant unless Seattle struggles with wideout injuries in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a5-d82c-a79a-f7b5577d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaret Patterson rushed 11 times for 54 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a9-db57-afda-d7bb01fb0000</link>
      <description>Patterson deserves credit for fighting through contact en route to a two-yard touchdown late in the fourth quarter, but his best play occurred on the Chargers’ fourth drive. Patterson ran to the right, through a crowded box, as Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby dove toward him and landed a clean punch on the football. The rock hardly moved in Patterson’s grip, and he continued on his way to a 22-yard gain, bringing the ball to the Raiders’ 15-yard line. Patterson can be stashed until RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) returns from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a9-db57-afda-d7bb01fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 18-of-23 passes for 165 yards, two touchdowns and one interception in the Raiders’ 31-14, Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ad-d6c4-abfb-d7aff5f80000</link>
      <description>Smith also racked up 40-sack yards on five sacks and rushed twice for minus-six yards. Aside from that, Smith’s day consisted of dump-offs to RB Ashton Jeanty and relying on TE Brock Bowers’ otherworldly talents to score two touchdowns. The duo had one called back by a questionably timed timeout call from Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh, but Smith dutifully went back to Bowers on the next play, resulting in an incompletion and a defensive pass interference call, bringing the Raiders a fresh set of downs. Smith flung another pass in Bowers’ direction after that, and the soon-to-be-perennial first-team All-Pro pass catcher somehow produced a once-handed catch while diving backward against tight coverage. Smith is tough to trust, even as a QB2, against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ad-d6c4-abfb-d7aff5f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 3-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b0-d90e-a9da-dfbfc1740000</link>
      <description>The Chargers’ pass rush consistently impacted Raiders QB Geno Smith’s dropbacks and the secondary covered Tucker well. The speedy wide receiver had a nice 10-yard, sideline snag on a comeback route on the Raiders’ eighth drive. A few plays later, he got open in the red zone by hesitating at the top of his stem before breaking inward. He secured the pass and was tackled at the Chargers’ three-yard line. Tucker is a boom-bust FLEX against the Broncos’ elite defense next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b0-d90e-a9da-dfbfc1740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Bech caught 2-of-3 targets for 22 yards in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a8-d90e-a9da-dfaf22d50000</link>
      <description>Bech missed time with a chest injury in this one, though that hardly impacted his box score relevance. The Raiders scored a touchdown on their fourth drive, and Bech at least helped them get there with a 16-yard pickup. He should not be on fantasy rosters. The Raiders face the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7a8-d90e-a9da-dfaf22d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught 4-of-4 targets for 63 yards and two touchdowns in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b2-d82c-a79a-f7b6e5c90000</link>
      <description>The talented tight end helped bring the ball down to the Chargers’ five-yard line on the Raiders’ fourth drive by ripping off a 24-yard gain on a corner route via play action. Two plays later, QB Geno Smith found him wide open in the back of the end zone for his first touchdown of the day. His second punctuated an unbelievable red zone sequence on the Raiders’ ninth drive. Smith initially connected with Bowers on a four-yard touchdown, but the play was questionably overturned by the refs, seemingly post-snap, who accommodated a last-second timeout call from Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh. Smith targeted Bowers in tight, physical coverage on the next play, and although it resulted in an incompletion, one of Bowers’ coverage defenders was called for defensive pass interference, bringing a fresh set of downs. On the next play, Raiders C Alex Cappa stepped on Smith’s right foot during the dropback. Smith hit the deck, clung to the ball and waited for the sack. Smith went right back to Bowers after that, who somehow secured a one-handed catch by falling backward, to the left, with his left hand outstretched, saving the ball from hitting the ground by inches. Bowers remains an elite TE1 against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b2-d82c-a79a-f7b6e5c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 2-of-6 targets for four yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7aa-d90e-a9da-dfafcec30000</link>
      <description>It was as bleak as ever for Jefferson in a lost season in the prime of his NFL career. The Vikings designed some easy looks for Jefferson in the first quarter, but Max Brosmer —a n undrafted rookie making his first-ever NFL start — quickly looked elsewhere. Jordan Addison led the Vikings with ten targets and TJ Hockenson saw six looks from Brosmer, who averaged 4.2 yards per throw. It doesn’t really matter whether Brosmer or JJ McCarthy (concussion) is under center for the Vikings in Week 14 against Atlanta: Jefferson is nothing more than a top-24 fantasy option with limited upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7aa-d90e-a9da-dfafcec30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 15 times for 31 yards in the Raiders’ Week 13 loss to the Chargers, adding six receptions for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b5-d82c-a79a-f7b5898f0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty simply had nowhere to run against the Chargers’ defensive front. The unit had an excellent showing. Jeanty deserves credit for consistently getting open as a short-area route runner. His six receptions and eight targets both led the team, and his 30 receiving yards, unfortunately, trailed only TE Brock Bowers’ 63. Jeanty will have a tough time next week against the Broncos’ elite defense. Treat him as an RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7b5-d82c-a79a-f7b5898f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught all six of his targets for 59 yards in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ba-d82c-a79a-f7be38d00000</link>
      <description>It was Hockenson’s best game of the 2025 season, and it came with undrafted rookie QB Max Brosmer under center while JJ McCarthy deals with a head injury he sustained in Week 12. Hockenson was second on the team in targets and led all Minnesota pass catchers with 59 yards. He had more than 30 receiving yards just five times in 2025 headed into Week 13. Perhaps Brosmer’s check-down tendencies can make Hockenson fantasy relevant again if the rookie gets another start in Week 14 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d7ba-d82c-a79a-f7be38d00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
