<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins resumed practicing after briefly having his left ankle examined by Bengals trainers on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdde-dbe3-a9bb-fddf5a9d0000</link>
      <description>Higgins appears to be just fine. Typically, brief visits with trainers end up being afterthoughts and there is no reason to think this situation will end differently. Higgins has a lengthy lower-body injury history, particularly with regard to his hamstrings, so we’re noting this for posterity’s sake. Higgins’ third-round ADP in PPR formats is reasonable, though his WR12 ranking is perhaps a tad high. Still, he remains a reliable producer when on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdde-dbe3-a9bb-fddf5a9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn indicated Chris Rodriguez Jr. is “likely” to handle short-yardage and goal-line rushing duties.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf7-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7dce20000</link>
      <description>Beat reporter Ben Standig thankfully posed the question with fantasy managers in mind. Quinn complimented Rodriguez’s short-area tackle-breaking ability because it suits the Commanders’ “untraditional” tactic of not using a lead blocker in short-yardage situations. Jacory Croskey-Merritt is still in the hunt for lead back duties but if Rodriguez is set to assume short-yardage duties while Austin Ekeler plays on passing downs, the starter could be left with empty calorie touches between the 20s. Croskey-Merritt is a talented, young player but keep in mind, a wide range of outcomes is in play. Rodriguez makes for a worthwhile bench stash given Quinn’s comments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf7-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7dce20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh declined to address whether Najee Harris (eye) could begin the regular season on the reserve/non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</link>
      <description>When asked about Harris’ potential placement on the reserve/NFI list, Harbaugh danced his way around the answer by saying, “when Najee is ready to play, Najee will be ready to play.” He then told reporters that speculation regarding Harris’ status beyond “today” goes “over the legal limit of what-ifs.” This is not reassuring. If Harris begins the year on the reserve/NFI list, he will be required to sit out at least four games. Omarion Hampton is an RB2 with RB1 upside. Fantasy managers can treat rookie RB Raheim Sanders as a late-round bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris is expected to miss Thursday’s practice after leaving Wednesday’s practice early due to “tightness.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</link>
      <description>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh is being his typical, tight-lipped self on this one. Missing time is unideal for Harris, who has failed to secure the team’s X-receiver role. Harris will be afforded plenty more opportunities to secure a starting role, given his second-round draft capital. He should only be considered a dart throw in re-draft at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston (neck) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce3c-de13-afdc-ceffb6740000</link>
      <description>Johnston suffered the injury five days ago. His return coincides with Tre’ Harris’ (tightness) sidelining. Although Johnston has disappointed through two NFL seasons, he has yet another chance to secure a starting role in three-wide receiver sets. He will have a tough time reliably returning flex value, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce3c-de13-afdc-ceffb6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Tre’Davious White left practice early on Thursday after suffering an apparent leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdef-db7b-a5dd-edeffeb30000</link>
      <description>White reportedly hopped on one leg, over to Bills’ trainers, before being carted to the locker room. No word on the injury’s specifics yet. Fellow CB Christian Benford exited practice early as well, though he later said he is okay and “just needed some rest.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdef-db7b-a5dd-edeffeb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints announced QB Spencer Rattler will start in preseason Week 3 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce44-d332-a1fd-de76e5710000</link>
      <description>Saints quarterbacks have looked great, playing against backups through two preseason games. Last week, Rattler was the one who starred in the second half. Entering the third preseason game as the starter could suggest that Rattler has slightly pulled ahead of rookie QB Tyler Shough, though the Saints would likely prefer to have their new second-round pick win the role. Regardless, neither player is re-draft-relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce44-d332-a1fd-de76e5710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur addressed trade rumors regarding Romeo Doubs by saying, “that will not happen.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce7f-db7b-a5dd-ee7fd9460000</link>
      <description>LaFleur then explained why the organization is not open to trading Doubs, saying, “Rome is out there competing” and has done “everything that we need to see from him.” The team suspended Doubs for one game last year, after the veteran receiver complained about his target rate. It sounds like the two sides are in a good spot. Doubs is set to continue operating as a Packers starter and profiles as a matchup-based flex option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce7f-db7b-a5dd-ee7fd9460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen will not play in the Bills’ preseason Week 3 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cea4-db7b-a5dd-eea4e08e0000</link>
      <description>This is the first time in Allen’s NFL career in which he has not, and will not, play at all in the preseason. Allen said he would “appreciate” preseason reps but does not believe that he needs them. We agree. As Bills head coach Sean McDermott notes, Allen is the NFL’s reigning MVP. He finished as the overall QB2 in fantasy scoring last year and can be considered a contender for the overall QB1 spot this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cea4-db7b-a5dd-eea4e08e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones said, in his “mind,” the “term, amount, guarantees, everything” for Micah Parsons’ potential extension were established without Parsons’ agent present.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</link>
      <description>Jones’ statement effectively validates the timeline of events that Parsons outlined in a social media post. Parsons’ agent was not present for the private discussion in which Jones says the contract was negotiated, and Jones takes issue with the agent’s attempts to “improve off the mark that we’d already set.” These are bizarre circumstances. Agents are hired to represent players in contract negotiations. Jones seemingly disagrees with that practice in this specific instance. The two sides need to resolve this issue soon, ostensibly with Parsons’ agent involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
