<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons CB Billy Bowman suffered a torn Achilles last week and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6f2-d90e-a9da-bfff299b0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Raheem Morris said last week of Bowman’s injury that it was “not good.” He was right. The fourth-round rookie who has played on 300 snaps for the defense this season now sees his rookie campaign come to an end thanks to the devastating injury. Bowman played 232 of his snaps from the slot this season and earned a PFF coverage grade of 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6f2-d90e-a9da-bfff299b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (toe/shoulder) will practice all week ahead of Week 13’s game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6fe-d413-ad9f-b7ff9c4d0000</link>
      <description>Bowles said that if Irving is fine after Friday’s practice, he will be slated to play on Sunday against the Cardinals. This was the belief dating back to last Friday when Bowles said the team was eyeing a Week 13 return for Irving after ruling him out against the Rams. Irving is sitting on a 71-237-0 rushing line through four games this season and was averaging 22.5 touches per game over that span. While he’s expected to step back into his starting role, it’s hard to predict what his touch totals could look like after the string of success Sean Tucker has had in his absence. Regardless of what his role may look like, Irving still figures to lead the Bucs’ backfield by a wide margin, putting him in the RB1/RB2 mix if he’s activated this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6fe-d413-ad9f-b7ff9c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said he anticipates Joe Burrow (toe) will play against the Ravens in Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b708-d413-ad9f-b7ddcd4c0000</link>
      <description>Taylor disappointingly would not put it on the record that Burrow will play, but this seems to be a pretty strong endorsement that he will anyway. “He looks like he’s in good shape to be ready to go,” Taylor continued. Burrow will be on the QB1 line against the Ravens in Week 13 assuming he suits up, but the absence of Tee Higgins (concussion) will mean that the Bengals will be playing without their full complement of stars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b708-d413-ad9f-b7ddcd4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Tee Higgins (concussion) will not play in Week 13 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d90e-a9da-bf0f5ba40000</link>
      <description>With such a short turnaround time to clear protocol and prepare for the Ravens, Higgins has already been ruled out. The star receiver will instead set his sights on clearing concussion protocol in time to suit up for Week 14’s game against the Bills. Higgins’ absence will create another opening for Andrei Iosivas to have another impactful day after he went for 4-61-0 on seven targets against the Patriots with Ja’Marr Chase suspended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d90e-a9da-bf0f5ba40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tahj Brooks (concussion) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 13 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d413-ad9f-b7dd16330000</link>
      <description>No surprise that a player in protocol will miss a short-week game. Brooks’ absence will leave the Bengals with little behind Chase Brown unless Samaje Perine is able to return from a high-ankle sprain on Thursday. Gary Brightwell, a special teamer, is the only other back on the roster. Kendall Milton is hanging out on the practice squad. Don’t be surprised to see Bengals RB workouts ahead of Thursday’s game. Trey Hendrickson (hip) was also ruled out for Thursday, as usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d413-ad9f-b7dd16330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski has named Shedeur Sanders as the team’s starting QB.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b725-d90e-a9da-bf2f29f00000</link>
      <description>Shedeur was under center for the Browns’ third win of the season over the Raiders and helped generate a more vertical passing attack while throwing for 209-1-1 on 11-of-20 passing. Sanders’ two biggest throws of the day came on a beautifully thrown 52-yard bomb to Isaiah Bond in the first quarter, with his other coming on a 66-yard touchdown on a pass behind the line of scrimmage to Dylan Sampson. It was only going to be a matter of time before Sanders, who famously slid to the fifth-round of this year’s draft, got a chance to start. Now, the Browns will look to see if he’s their quarterback of the future over these next six weeks or another name added to a laundry list of QB1 hopefuls. Sanders shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a low-end QB2 for this week’s game against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b725-d90e-a9da-bf2f29f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Davis had three rushes for 24 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b727-d82c-a79a-b7b774020000</link>
      <description>Davis is emerging as the clear RB2 behind Javonte Williams, who had 87 scoreless yards on 20 rushes against a tough Philadelphia front seven in Week 12. Davis showed a lot of burst on two of his three carries against the Eagles, including a 21-yard run up the middle. Davis should be stashed on fantasy benches this week in case Williams gets dinged up down the stretch. Jaydon Blue was once again a healthy inactive in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b727-d82c-a79a-b7b774020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy is in the concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72d-d82c-a79a-b7bd4c070000</link>
      <description>It is the softest benching yet for McCarthy, as the team could not identify one particular hit where he picked up a concussion. McCarthy reported symptoms on the flight home. Backup quarterback and rookie UDFA Max Brosmer could be in line for a desperation start against the Seahawks in Week 13. Of course, after last week’s McCarthy performance — one where the team finished with -1 total yards as an offense after halftime — Brosmer could very well be an upgrade. O’Connell was not yet ready to rule McCarthy out and the Vikings do play on Sunday so there’s a little time for this to settle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72d-d82c-a79a-b7bd4c070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Raider will name QB coach Greg Olson as interim OC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</link>
      <description>Olson was born to be a Raider. Literally. The 62-year-old coach is in his third stint with the team since first being hired as offensive coordinator in 2013, and also spent three years as their OC from 2018-2021 under Jon Gruden. Now, instead of having to get better play out of Derek Carr, Olson will take on the task of fixing Geno Smith, who took an unprecedented 10 sacks in Week 12’s loss to the Browns. The Raiders currently ranked 31st in points scored and are 30th in yards. Running back Ashton Jeanty has had his moments, but is also underwhelming to the tune of 166-604-4 on the ground while averaging 3.6 YPC. While it’s hard to imagine the Raiders doing a complete 180 midseason, it’s also hard to imagine things will continue as they have. We’ll get our first look at the Olson-led offense in Week 13 when the Raiders face the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</link>
      <description>Officially fired on his day off, Gabriel will spend Week 13 backing up Shedeur Sanders after missing Week 12’s game due to his brain injury. Gabriel’s lack of a vertical passing game, as evidenced by a 6.4 ADOT and eight deep throw attempts over eight games, may have proven to be his downfall. Gabriel topped 200 passing yards just once in the six starts he made this season while ranking near the bottom of the league in both dropback success rate and EPA per dropback. Barring injury or a complete implosion by Sanders, there’s a good chance this is the last we have seen of Gabriel in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
