<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (calf/hand) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d005-a9bf-df74e0350000</link>
      <description>Sampson missed last week’s first two practices, dealing with the calf injury. He suited up on game day, rushing twice for four yards and catching 5-of-5 targets for 64 yards while losing one fumble. We tentatively expect him to practice tomorrow and play on Sunday. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d005-a9bf-df74e0350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars QB Trevor Lawrence (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f47-d77b-adfb-cfc7a5fe0000</link>
      <description>Wednesday’s limited session was likely just a little extra rest for the franchise signalcaller. He’ll be near the QB1/QB2 borderline in Week 15 against a Jets defense that has been waylaid by opposing passing games all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f47-d77b-adfb-cfc7a5fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints S Justin Reid (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f49-d005-a9bf-df7d0f490000</link>
      <description>It’s his first practice since injuring his knee in Week 13, and a sign that he has a chance to be active against the Panthers in Week 15. We’ll check in on Reid again tomorrow, but this is at least an encouraging sign that he could make the questionable line on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f49-d005-a9bf-df7d0f490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Cedric Tillman (concussion/rib) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f48-d8cf-affb-bf6ac4490000</link>
      <description>Tillman is on track to miss the team’s Week 15 game against the Bears, and does not need to be rostered in re-draft formats. The 25-year-old wide receiver has appeared in nine games this season. He has failed to produce even 55 receiving yards in a single one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f48-d8cf-affb-bf6ac4490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4b-d77b-adfb-cfcb33c10000</link>
      <description>So it continues. Kamara has not practiced since spraining his MCL in Week 12. He looks doubtful to play in Week 15 after two more missed practices to open the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4b-d77b-adfb-cfcb33c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (abdomen) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4c-d005-a9bf-df7c469c0000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if Neal didn’t play on Sunday after back-to-back practices, and he likely has a chance to be cleared from the injury report on Friday. Neal would make for an interesting RB3/FLEX play against the Panthers, though it’d surely help out if he caught more passes in the flow of the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4c-d005-a9bf-df7c469c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (neck) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4a-da9b-a9bf-df4fe91b0000</link>
      <description>That makes two missed practices for Taylor. Brutal. The rookie tight end led the team in targets (eight) just last week and leads the team across the full season with 64. Theoretically, his potential absence would put more work on WR Adonai Mitchell’s plate, though Mitchell flopped by catching just 1-of-6 targets for 24 yards last week and he could be stuck catching passes from QB Brady Cook in Week 15 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f4a-da9b-a9bf-df4fe91b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f53-d005-a9bf-df77de490000</link>
      <description>As long as Lamb remains symptom-free, he should be good to go for the Cowboys’ Week 15 game against the Vikings. The Cowboys last played on Thursday night, in Week 14, allowing Lamb extra time to rest before practicing this week. It seemingly paid off. He can be started as a WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f53-d005-a9bf-df77de490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder believes the Colts are “prepping” QB Philip Rivers to start in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d8cf-affb-bf6ebeeb0000</link>
      <description>Per Holder, “it isn’t difficult to tell who a team is prepping to start. That player is Rivers.” Whether this helps the pass-catching corps remains to be seen. Rivers has not played football since 2020. One hard hit from a Seahawks pass rusher could send the 44-year-old back to the sofa. Backup QB Riley Leonard suffered a PCL sprain in his knee last week, though he is currently practicing in full. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f44-d8cf-affb-bf6ebeeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks waived RB Cam Akers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d005-a9bf-df75d1cd0000</link>
      <description>Akers rushed five times for five yards and caught 0-of-1 targets in his time with the Seahawks. Griffin recorded zero pass breakups and zero interceptions on 56 coverage snaps. Both players could find spots on practice squads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f61-d005-a9bf-df75d1cd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
