<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Evan McPherson converted 2-of-2 field goal attempts in the Bengals’ Week 12 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2ca-db57-afda-f6fa2cf00000</link>
      <description>McPherson drilled a 54-yarder for the first points of the game and also added a career-long 63-yarder later in the game. It’s been a modest fantasy season for McPherson this year, with only four games of multiple made field goals. However, he has at least two field goals in four of his last five games, and Joe Burrow looks set to return on Thursday, which means McPherson could be useful for fantasy managers down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2ca-db57-afda-f6fa2cf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed two times for 10 yards in the Ravens Week 12 win over the Jets, adding one reception for nine additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2cc-db57-afda-f6fe48b30000</link>
      <description>Mitchell’s longest run of the day came on a nine-yard gain, but offensive holding on the center in the fourth quarter negated a 35-yard run that would have been the longest play of the day for any Ravens player. Mitchell was in on just 10 snaps this week after seeing 16 in Week 11 with Justice Hill out, but was the only other Ravens running back not named Derrick Henry to see a touch in this one. The volume is unlikely to ever be there for Mitchell as long as Henry and Hill are both healthy, but he could have some value as a stash in deeper leagues. Fantasy managers can avoid him in Week 13 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2cc-db57-afda-f6fe48b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Borregales converted 4-of-4 field goal attempts in the Patriots’ Week 12 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d0-d82c-a79a-b3d4c5e50000</link>
      <description>Borregales was the highest-scoring player for the Patriots on Sunday, converting on field goals from 41 yards, 45 yards, 19 yards, and 52 yards. In fact, his three second-half field goals were the only points the Patriots scored in that half, and he scored the last 12 points from the offense since the Bengals were able to stuff the Patriots inside the five-yard line on 10 separate plays on Sunday. Borregales is a good kicker on a strong offense and should be usable in most fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d0-d82c-a79a-b3d4c5e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara exited Week 12 against the Falcons with an apparent knee injury and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d3-d82c-a79a-b3d7637b0000</link>
      <description>Kamara went to the medical tent more than once in the first half of the Saints’ Week 12 game against the Falcons. He ultimately headed to the locker room and is listed as questionable to return with a knee injury. Kamara left with three carries for 11 yards and two receptions for four yards in the middle of the second quarter. Devin Neal will take over as the lead back while Kamara is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d3-d82c-a79a-b3d7637b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 30 times for 104 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 13 win over the Colts, adding three catches for 26 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2cf-d82c-a79a-b3df74f50000</link>
      <description>Hunt averaged a measly 3.5 yards per carry for Kansas City, but he had no issues grinding out the hard-fought plays for first downs and eventually a touchdown. His two-yard score in the fourth quarter was the team’s only touchdown of the day. It was also a redemption moment for Hunt after he coughed up the ball in the red zone on the previous drive. Hunt dominated the work with Isiah Pacheco sidelined once again. Pacheco should be back next week, but Hunt could lead the team in carries even with Pacheco back in the mix. Both backs will be stuck in the RB3 ranks versus Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2cf-d82c-a79a-b3df74f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 1-of-2 targets for 23 yards in the Giants’ Week 12 loss against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d1-d82c-a79a-b3d584ce0000</link>
      <description>Slayton’s 23-yard grab came on the first play of the game. He wasn’t targeted again until the fourth quarter. Slayton, returning from a hamstring injury, ran 28 routes on 43 New York drop backs, running behind Wan’Dale Robinson and Isaiah Hodgins, both of whom had a touchdown against the Lions. Slayton should be considered nothing more than a deep league flex option in the coming weeks unless he passes Hodgins in the team’s pass catching pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2d1-d82c-a79a-b3d584ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Singletary had 14 rushes for 47 yards in the Giants’ Week 12 loss against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2df-d82c-a79a-b3dfb9f80000</link>
      <description>After scoring two touchdowns last week against the Packers, Singletary had 14 touches to 23 touches for Tyrone Tracy, who was once again far more efficient. Tracy was again the clear-cut passing down back; he ran 29 routes on the day to just five for Singletary, who did not see a target. Singletary would only be fantasy relevant if Tracy were to miss time in the coming weeks. He’s a decent bench stash for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2df-d82c-a79a-b3dfb9f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 16 times for 58 yards in the Colts’ Week 12 loss to the Chiefs, adding two catches for eight yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2dc-d82c-a79a-b3dc4b190000</link>
      <description>Kansas City sold out to stop Taylor on early downs and let Daniel Jones try to beat them with his arm on third downs. That resulted in Taylor’s second-worst game of the year by rushing yards and yards per carry (3.6). Jones, in turn, posted his worst game by both passing yards (181) and YPA (5.8). Taylor’s box score today is eerily similar to his box score from the Colts’ Week 9 loss to the Steelers. Pittsburgh bullied Jones and managed to keep Taylor in check, effectively shutting down the Colts’ offense. The blueprint appears to be set for stopping the Colts. Even if the team isn’t as successful in the back half of the season, Taylor is going to get fed and remains a home run threat on every play. He will remain at the top of the running back ranks for his Week 13 date with Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2dc-d82c-a79a-b3dc4b190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy had 20 rushes for 62 yards in the Giants’ Week 12 loss against the Lions, adding three catches for 68 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2e3-db57-afda-f6f32c320000</link>
      <description>Tracy again led the Giants backfield, though Devin Singletary saw 14 carries, including some red zone work. Tracy ran 29 routes while Singletary logged five routes and did not see a target. Tracy’s biggest play of the day was a 42-yard catch and run on a wide open screen pass from Jameis Winston. Last week he had 139 total yards on 23 touches against the Packers. Some of Tracy’s fantasy luster will fade if Jaxson Dart returns in Week 13 against New England and resumes goal line rushing duties for the Giants. That role is in question after a series of head injuries for the rookie quarterback. Tracy will be a top-24 option against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2e3-db57-afda-f6f32c320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 28-of-42 attempts for 279 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Lions’ Week 12 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2eb-d413-ad9f-b7ff76590000</link>
      <description>It was a spotty outing for Goff a week after his meltdown against the Eagles. The Giants, sporting one of the worst pass rushes in the NFL, hit Goff time and again and rattled the little-hit Lions QB. He was sacked three times and hit a handful of others and appeared rattled for much of the second half. Goff missed Amon-Ra St. Brown on what would have been an easy red zone touchdown and threw a red zone interception on another target to St. Brown later in the game. That Goff couldn’t carve up the injury-marred Giants defense is a little concerning. He’ll face off against Micah Parsons and a fierce Packers pass rush on Thanksgiving Day. Goff will be a top-15 fantasy play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b2eb-d413-ad9f-b7ff76590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
