<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys acquired DT Quinnen Williams from the Jets for DT Mazi Smith, a 2026 second-round pick and a 2027 first-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5042-d713-ad9e-7c56b5d50000</link>
      <description>Williams is notably not Micah Parsons, but if for some reason you can’t have Parsons, he’s probably on the short list of defensive line stars in the league. He’s a star run defender — something we seem to recall the Cowboys needing — by virtue of splash plays. Williams has only one sack this year, but the Jets have not held many leads and Williams does have 23.5 sacks in his past seasons. The Jets star defender has 1.5 years remaining on a four-year, $96 million extension signed in 2023. So the Cowboys will make sure to have someone with an expiring contract distraction on the roster in 2026, as nature abhors a vacuum. The Jets are now a conceptual football team, the closest thing we’ve seen to one since the Sashi Brown Browns anyway. So from that standpoint, Mazi Smith, a theoretical defensive tackle, is a great addition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5042-d713-ad9e-7c56b5d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said the team would not open the 21-day practice window for Brandon Aiyuk (knee/PUP) this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5069-d45b-affe-55ff75180000</link>
      <description>We’re not surprised to see that Shanahan’s Week 10 estimate given in October was too optimistic — the 49ers have been very cavalier about feeding the optimism this year on Aiyuk. Assuming that the 49ers want him to actually have a real runway of practice before he acclimates, it is feeling more and more likely that Aiyuk is only back on the field for the final month or so of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5069-d45b-affe-55ff75180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said the timeline for Ricky Pearsall (knee) “remains fuzzy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-506e-d673-a39e-f4ffee6c0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan added that Pearsall will be “evaluated midweek to see whether he can return to practice,” which is a more optimistic point of view. Pearsall-reliant managers have gotten used to this over the last month or so, but it looks like he’s definitely questionable-at-best for a return in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-506e-d673-a39e-f4ffee6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson believes the expectation is C.J. Stroud “will not practice Wednesday, or possibly any days this week, and that Davis Mills will start.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5072-d45b-affe-55f6d5210000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly a surprising revelation to make — if Stroud were going to return, we’d probably only see movement on Thursday or Friday on the practice report — but fantasy managers should set their Week 10 waivers with the expectation that Stroud won’t play against the Jaguars in Week 10. Davis Mills will be a low-end superflex QB2 if and when he is officially named the starter for that game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5072-d45b-affe-55f6d5210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers released QB Hendon Hooker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5092-d673-a39e-f493cca60000</link>
      <description>Hooker had been on the practice squad since August, but Carolina elected to sign and elevate Mike White over him. It’s possible Hooker thinks he has a better opportunity elsewhere. Even if he does, it’s hard to imagine him finding a path to a starting role at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5092-d673-a39e-f493cca60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers acquired OL Trevor Penning from the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50aa-d45b-affe-55befe820000</link>
      <description>The former first-round pick had big tools, but has been pushed from right tackle to left guard this year after the Saints drafted Kelvin Banks. Penning’s career-best PFF pass block grade in a season is 60.8, and his 50.4 PFF grade at guard this year in 358 snaps is on pace to be a career-worst figure. He’s a stopgap for a team that just lost Joe Alt for the season, and it’s unclear if they plan to try him at tackle or if they’ll leave him inside at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50aa-d45b-affe-55befe820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports Garrett Wilson was “untouchable” in trade talks with the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50b0-d1e7-a1fa-5afa596b0000</link>
      <description>Several teams apparently tried. Wilson remains a Jet as the deadline passes, and it seems unlikely he’ll be someone the team tries to move on from after the season as well given how it was leaked that he was untouchable. Wilson injured his knee in London and has a 36/395/4 line in six games for the Jets in 2025 so far. It seems likely that he’ll return from the knee injury in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50b0-d1e7-a1fa-5afa596b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed WR Brenden Rice, formerly of the Chargers, to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50cd-d713-ad9e-7cddb2380000</link>
      <description>The son of NFL legend Jerry Rice, Brenden was drafted by the Chargers in the seventh round of the 2024 NFL Draft. He made the Chargers’ 53-man roster but only appeared in three games as a rookie and did not record any stats. Rice was then cut ahead of his second season. With Kayshon Boutte banged up, Rice gives the Chargers some extra depth at wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50cd-d713-ad9e-7cddb2380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (concussion) returned to practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50d4-d673-a39e-f4d5ceae0000</link>
      <description>It’s a big step in the right direction for the speedy wideout. Mims missed Week 9 because of the concussion and wasn’t able to practice on Monday. After looking like a safe bet to miss Week 10 as of 24 hours ago, Mims now has a shot to suit up for Denver’s Thursday date with the Raiders. Mims still has some hurdles to clear in the league’s concussion protocol, so keep an eye out for his practice status tomorrow. If he is back in the lineup for Week 10, Mims will be a boom/bust WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50d4-d673-a39e-f4d5ceae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cardinals are naming Jacoby Brissett as their starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50dc-d1e7-a1fa-5afeb6920000</link>
      <description>It’s a move that sounds shocking but felt completely inevitable after Brissett toppled the Cowboys on Monday Night Football. Brissett made three starts in place of an injured Kyler Murray. He threw for 860 yards and six touchdowns while Murray nursed his foot injury. His lowest yardage total was 261, coming against Dallas. That would have been Murray’s highest total of the year by over 40 yards. Brissett was also getting more out of both Trey McBride and Marvin Harrison Jr. McBride has four touchdowns in three Brissett starts. He has five career touchdown receptions from Murray. MHJ is coming off a career-high in receptions at seven. In the short-term, Brissett is a mid-range QB2 for fantasy purposes and both of his top pass-catchers will get a boost in the ranks for Week 10 against the Seahawks. In the long-term, the Cardinals are now headed toward an ugly breakup with Murray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-50dc-d1e7-a1fa-5afeb6920000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
