<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 04:10:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f77-d005-a9bf-df774cb40000</link>
      <description>Last week, the hamstring injury caused Adams to miss practice on Wednesday before logging a limited session on Thursday and practicing fully on Friday. He played on game day but caught just 4-of-6 targets for 29 yards. The Rams face the Lions in what should be a very high-scoring game in Week 15. The Rams are likely just managing Adams’ reps in the lead-up to the big game, though it would be great to see Adams practice on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f77-d005-a9bf-df774cb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fae-d77b-adfb-cfaf19230000</link>
      <description>Ferguson’s absence is discouraging. It is possible that yesterday’s limited session was because Ferguson suffered the injury in practice. Hopefully, today is just a planned rest day and he can resume practicing tomorrow. The Cowboys face the Vikings’ blitz-based pass defense in Week 15. Having a big-bodied target in the short-to-intermediate field depths would help out QB Dak Prescott.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fae-d77b-adfb-cfaf19230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fb8-d005-a9bf-dfbc30930000</link>
      <description>The mediocre blocker should be available to two-hand punch a few chest pads and occasionally earn a target on Sunday. Mayer is largely an afterthought in the Raiders’ passing game, though. His backup, TE Ian Thomas (calf), was limited on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fb8-d005-a9bf-dfbc30930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (collarbone) is active for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fcf-d77b-adfb-cfcf35e70000</link>
      <description>Evans takes the field on game day for the first time since Week 7. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Evans will be on “somewhat of a pitch count” in his first game back, though coaches often allow players to play without restrictions if their body responds positively to early-game work. Evans is a tad risky, but his upside remains high. He should probably be in most fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fcf-d77b-adfb-cfcf35e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Jalen McMillan (neck) is active for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd0-d77b-adfb-cfd323f60000</link>
      <description>Making his 2025 debut on the same night Mike Evans is returning from his broken collarbone, McMillan is going to be lightly targeted as the Bucs’ No. 4 wideout but can hopefully provide better routes/snaps than Tez Johnson had been of late. McMillan had an intriguing if highly inconclusive rookie year. An end-of-bench stash in dynasty leagues, McMillan is off the re-draft radar for the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd0-d77b-adfb-cfd323f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared TE Cade Otton, LB SirVocea Dennis, S Tykee Smith, CB Benjamin Morrison, G Elijah Klein, DL Elijah Simmons and QB Connor Bazelak inactive for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd1-da98-afbb-1ff9290f0000</link>
      <description>Otton is, unfortunately, sidelined by a knee injury. The pass-catching corps gets WR Mike Evans (collarbone) and WR Jalen McMillan (neck) back tonight, though, boosting QB Baker Mayfield’s fantasy-scoring potential. Mayfield will also helpfully have LT Tristan Wirfs (oblique) protecting his blindside this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd1-da98-afbb-1ff9290f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared WR Drake London, WR Jamal Agnew, ILB JD Bertrand, OL Michael Jerrell, WR Casey Washington, WR Malik Heath and DL Elijah Garcia inactive for Week 15 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd4-d005-a9bf-dff479a30000</link>
      <description>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney is, unfortunately, just a dart-throw FLEX option with London sidelined. Mooney has totaled 45-plus receiving yards just twice this season. Falcons TE Kyle Pitts will continue operating as the No. 1 pass catcher. He should be started as a high-end TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fd4-d005-a9bf-dff479a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it would not surprise him if Colts QB Philip Rivers starts in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fdd-d005-a9bf-dffd07150000</link>
      <description>Rivers is reportedly taking “some first-team reps” and is throwing the football “well.” Rivers is also, apparently, familiar with the Colts’ playbook because he runs the same offense, serving as the head coach of an Alabama high school. Perhaps unbelievably, Rivers is seemingly going to start in Week 15. He has no floor as a QB2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fdd-d005-a9bf-dffd07150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons owner Arthur Blank will evaluate the team’s football operations at the end of the year, including head coach Raheem Morris and general manager Terry Fontenot’s roles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1003-d005-a9bf-d837e9170000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport broke the news before Thursday Night Football, saying Blank had just visited the set. We suspect Rapoport’s sourcing is highly reliable here. The Falcons are currently 4-9. It is possible, both Morris and Fontenot are ousted in early 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1003-d005-a9bf-d837e9170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Hughes is questionable to return against the Buccaneers in Week 14 with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1024-d8cf-affb-bc2e34d80000</link>
      <description>Hughes is currently undergoing X-rays, and it seems more likely than not that he won’t be back for the contest. Cobee Bryant will replace Hughes at corner for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1024-d8cf-affb-bc2e34d80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
