<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Michael Wilson (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a3-def2-abdb-fde388660000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ starting quarterback and starting wide receiver trio is entirely banged up at the moment. QB Kyler Murray (foot) and WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) were both limited today, while WR Zay Jones (knee) did not practice. Wilson has been very unproductive this season and makes for an unreliable FLEX option, though he could see an increase in targets this week, pending his teammates’ availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9a3-def2-abdb-fde388660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9aa-db72-a199-fbeb7bf60000</link>
      <description>Knight’s early-week participation is promising, but it is worth noting that RB Michael Carter is the backfield’s lone healthy player. Fellow RB Emari Demercado (ankle) was sidelined on Wednesday. Knight should be expected to continue playing as the Cardinals’ preferred early-down rusher in Week 7. His practice status is worth monitoring as the week progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9aa-db72-a199-fbeb7bf60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ab-d94a-a79d-e9af454f0000</link>
      <description>Demercado’s Week 6 injury helped consolidate the backfield to a fantasy-relevant duo, including Bam Knight and Michael Carter. It is worth mentioning that Knight is nursing a knee injury, but was able to practice in a limited capacity on Wednesday. Demercado is likely to be stuck in the No. 3 role if he is active in Week 7 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ab-d94a-a79d-e9af454f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports the Giants are “big-game hunting” for a pass-catcher ahead of the trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ad-db72-a199-fbef33a30000</link>
      <description>Hughes named Jaylen Waddle, Chris Olave, and Jakobi Meyers are potential targets. At 2-4, the Giants aren’t the type of team you would expect to be buyers at the deadline, but Jaxson Dart has given them a new lease on life in a weakened NFC East this year. Even if the push proves futile for 2025, Dart will need more weapons to throw to next year, even once Malik Nabers is healthy. As Hughes notes, neither the Saints nor the Dolphins are inclined to trade their top wideout this early in the year. That, however, could change if both teams continue to lose games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ad-db72-a199-fbef33a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b8-db72-a199-fbfba2190000</link>
      <description>Ridley left the Titans’ Week 6 game against the Raiders in the second quarter and did not return. A DNP to start the week puts him on the wrong side of questionable for Week 7’s game against the Patriots. Van Jefferson led the Titans with 75 receiving yards on four catches in Ridley’s absence. Given the abysmal state of the Titans’ offense, it’s hard to recommend any of their wideouts as a FLEX option for Week 7, even with Ridley leaving plenty of targets up for grabs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b8-db72-a199-fbfba2190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9bf-d94a-a79d-e9bf45b30000</link>
      <description>Landry collided with one of his teammates in the first quarter of the Pats’ Week 6 win over the Saints and stayed on the field for a moment. He eventually walked off under his own power and managed to return to the game after a short stint with the medical staff. The former Titan already has 4.5 sacks this year, putting him on pace for a career-high in sacks. Losing Landry would be a big blow to the Patriots’ defense, though it’s hard to imagine the downtrodden Titans taking advantage of his absence, given the way they have played so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9bf-d94a-a79d-e9bf45b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ce-db72-a199-fbcfc1ee0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw suffered a torn quad in the offseason. He avoided IR or the PUP list to start the year but landed on injured reserve after Week 2. Though his recovery is clearly taking longer than expected, the fact that he was on injured reserve for the minimum of four weeks means he should be ready to go sooner rather than later. The Broncos now have three weeks to officially activate him from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9ce-db72-a199-fbcfc1ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9d1-dd4c-afb9-efd1ae510000</link>
      <description>Wilson suffered the knee injury in Week 6 against the Broncos. He played through the issue until the final whistle but immediately underwent an MRI on his knee. Though he avoided a serious injury, Wilson is reportedly expected to miss a couple of weeks. With Josh Reynolds also banged up, the Jets could be down to Arian Smith and Tyler Johnson as their top wideouts. Rookie tight end Mason Taylor should also see plenty of targets in Wilson’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9d1-dd4c-afb9-efd1ae510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel (heel) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9d5-db72-a199-fbdffd070000</link>
      <description>Samuel was held out of practice on Wednesday and Thursday last week. He was upgraded to a limited session on Friday before being listed as questionable. Samuel ultimately played through the issue but managed just 19 tards on four grabs. With Terry McLaurin potentially returning this week, Samuel’s target total could continue to fall after seeing five looks in Week 6. While we expect him to play through the heel issue once again, Samuel will move to the end of the WR2 ranks for Week 7 versus Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9d5-db72-a199-fbdffd070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9da-d94a-a79d-e9df68160000</link>
      <description>McLaurin went down with the quad injury in Week 2 and has not played since. This is his first practice in roughly a month. The Commanders could still hold him out for another week, but it’s looking more likely than not that he is out there on Sunday. Assuming he does suit up. McLaurin will return to the WR2 ranks for a phenomenal matchup versus a Dallas defense allowing the most fantasy points to opposing wideouts this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9da-d94a-a79d-e9df68160000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
