<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Roschon Johnson (foot) did not participate in the Bears’ walkthrough on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1654-d332-a1fd-967604790000</link>
      <description>Johnson has been dealing with the foot issue since early August. Rookie RB Kyle Monangai is currently limited by a hamstring injury, though he’s penciled in as the Bears’ No. 2 RB with Johnson sidelined. Hopefully, Johnson can return to practice ahead of the Bears’ Monday Night Football game against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1654-d332-a1fd-967604790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (foot) was limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1659-db7b-a5dd-b65d03990000</link>
      <description>The Packers slot wideout is dealing with a foot injury that had him in a walking boot. While this is an upgrade from Wednesday’s DNP, it doesn’t exactly paint the picture of someone who will be playing at 100 percent if he does suit up for Week 1. Reed is probably best approached as a stayaway in Week 1 slates where fantasy managers have other options, at least unless we see drastically more positive news on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1659-db7b-a5dd-b65d03990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (calf) remained limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165c-d332-a1fd-967e82450000</link>
      <description>Wicks is probably trending to the right side of questionable for Week 1 after getting in two limited sessions to start the week. His Week 1 status will probably depend a lot on what the Friday report tells us, but he could still be a fantasy factor given how dinged up Jayden Reed is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165c-d332-a1fd-967e82450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (hamstring) was limited in Thursday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165d-dbe3-a9bb-365f99750000</link>
      <description>Monangai is currently penciled in as the Bears’ No. 2 RB with Roschon Johnson still sidelined by a foot injury. Seventh-round rookies infrequently carve out roles for themselves but given the state of things, Monangai is worth stashing on fantasy benches. His early-week participation suggests he will play on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165d-dbe3-a9bb-365f99750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton (groin) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165e-db7b-a5dd-b65e652e0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from Wednesday’s limited listing. Otton appears on track to play in Week 1 after Todd Bowles said he’d “be out for a little bit” last week. He steps into a nice streaming spot against a young Falcons defense that didn’t exactly scare anybody last year, with both Chris Godwin and Jalen McMillan sidelined for Week 1. Otton could be a decent streamer TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-165e-db7b-a5dd-b65e652e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Christian Kirk (hamstring) has a strain and is expected to miss Week 1 “and possibly longer.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1662-de13-afdd-56eb7fb90000</link>
      <description>One source of Schefter’s “estimated it to be a two-week injury” for Kirk. It’s wheels up for the young Texans receiving corps, with Jaylin Noel the likely replacement for Kirk in the slot. Noel could be a surprise x-factor in fantasy leagues in Week 1 given this much workload. Jayden Higgins also likely profiles to receive more targets with Kirk removed from the equation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1662-de13-afdd-56eb7fb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) was limited in Thursday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1660-d332-a1fd-96767dda0000</link>
      <description>Johnson’s leg issue was initially reported as a hamstring injury, suffered in a “freak accident,” but it was recently reported as a groin injury instead. The calf aspect is entirely new, and we do not know when it happened. The Bears need Johnson on the field if they hope to contain Justin Jefferson in primetime on Monday night, but his status is firmly in the questionable camp despite today’s participation. Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hamstring) and DB Josh Blackwell (Groin) did not practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1660-d332-a1fd-96767dda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Brown (knee) remained limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1666-db7b-a5dd-b666f1390000</link>
      <description>Brown has essentially been dealing with this knee injury for the better part of training camp and may be on a pitch count for Week 1 if active. Fantasy managers can probably do better elsewhere, but if Brown gets a Friday upgrade he could still be startable in extremely deep leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1666-db7b-a5dd-b666f1390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill (oblique/calf) remained limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-db7b-a5dd-b66dc1d80000</link>
      <description>Hill doesn’t look to be in any real danger of missing time in Week 1, but playing through yet another set of injuries won’t be doing him any favors in fantasy football. There’s still a good chance he stumbles into plenty of value in Week 1 against a Colts cornerback room that can best be described as “veteran-laden,” but they won’t be playing Indianapolis every week. We’d like to see Hill get a full practice in on Friday to be confident that he’s got it all working, but he’ll be on the WR2/WR3 even if he is questionable on the final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-db7b-a5dd-b66dc1d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-d332-a1fd-967fc4fa0000</link>
      <description>Achane is being eased back into action and is on track to play in Week 1 against the Colts. Head coach Mike McDaniel has not been afraid to pile touches high on his stars’ plates when returning from injury. Achane is an RB1 for the occasion, though it would be nice to see him practice in full tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-d332-a1fd-967fc4fa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
