<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:29:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-dc7a-af9b-ffff68170000</link>
      <description>Odunze was a bit rusty last week, but he appears to have made it through the game without suffering a setback. The Bears face the Rams’ explosive offense in the Divisional Round on Sunday, which should result in a fantasy-friendly game script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-dc7a-af9b-ffff68170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Titans interview former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh on Thursday for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbfbc0a0000</link>
      <description>The Giants reportedly made a “massive push” to get Harbaugh to sign with them today. Of note, Harbaugh met with the Giants at their facility, toured the grounds, and even met with Jaxson Dart today. The Titans, on the other hand, are meeting him at his home. While it does seem like the Giants are in pole position to land the cycle’s hottest name, Harbaugh is still going to talk to the Titans. He will likely meet with Atlanta before making a decision as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbfbc0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears OL Braxton Jones (knee) is practicing fully for Chicago’s Divisional Round game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beac-d35e-a1bf-ffee6e910000</link>
      <description>Starting LT Ozzy Trapilo ruptured his patellar tendon in the Bears’ Wild Card win over the Packers, ending his season. Jones has not yet been officially activated from injured reserve, but his full practice participation is a good sign. If activated, he will compete with OL Theo Benedet, who manned the left tackle spot earlier this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beac-d35e-a1bf-ffee6e910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) was a full participant in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bec5-dc7a-af9b-ffff48000000</link>
      <description>Ferguson missed the Wild Card win over the Panthers with a hamstring injury, but head coach Sean McVay was optimistic the rookie would play this week. Though Wednesday’s practice report is an estimate, it is good news that Ferguson is listed as a full participant. The Rams are trending to get their full tight end room back for the Sunday Divisional matchup against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bec5-dc7a-af9b-ffff48000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-becd-d968-a19b-fefd3bfd0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall is listed as limited for the second straight day to start the week. He missed the 49ers’ Wild Card win over the Eagles and has dealt with knee issues throughout the season. Thursday’s final practice report will give a more concrete answer but Pearsall is at least practicing and trending to return in the Divisional Round against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-becd-d968-a19b-fefd3bfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring/knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bed0-d968-a19b-fef1b6170000</link>
      <description>Despite practicing fully on Tuesday coming off a hamstring injury, Cross is downgraded to limited Wednesday with a new knee issue to deal with it. Thursday’s practice will have the final report on how serious Cross’ issues are, but the new listing indicates he suffered the knee injury in practice. Seahawks fans can check back later in the week to see if the franchise left tackle will be good to go for Saturday’s Divisional matchup against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bed0-d968-a19b-fef1b6170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bee2-dc7a-af9b-ffff7eed0000</link>
      <description>Jordan suffered an ankle injury in Week 18 which caused him to miss the Wild Card win over the Steelers. The 26-year-old played well in a reserve role and was the Texans’ RB2 in Week 18 with Nick Chubb a healthy scratch. A limited practice session early in the week indicates Jordan is trending to return in the Divisional Round against the Patriots, though the Texans may keep both Jordan and Chubb active behind Woody Marks if Jordan is not fully healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bee2-dc7a-af9b-ffff7eed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Josina Anderson reports the Cowboys have requested to interview Packers defensive line coach DeMarcus Covington for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beee-d968-a19b-feff52390000</link>
      <description>Covington joined the Packers as defensive line coach prior to the 2025 season. The Packers were middle-of-the-pack in both sacks and rushing yards allowed and boasted a defensive line of Micah Parsons, Rashan Gary, and more. Green Bay was able to generate pressure under Covington, though Parsons’ late-season ACL tear stymied the pass rush. The Cowboys parted ways with Matt Eberflus after the season and are interviewing candidates for the defensive coordinator role. Covington is next up on the interview list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beee-d968-a19b-feff52390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach Post’s Hal Habib reports the Dolphins requested to interview Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bef6-d968-a19b-fef711a10000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins throw another name into the mix, adding Brady to their list of head coaching interview requests. He helmed a season that seemed underwhelming as it pertains to the Bills’ usual offensive standards. The lack of passing attack was apparent, though the run game was consistently good for Brady’s group. Brady has received a couple of interview requests this offseason and would certainly bring an interesting dimension to De’Von Achane’s usage in the Dolphins offense should he get the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bef6-d968-a19b-fef711a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions are interviewing Falcons offensive coordinator Zac Robinson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bf3f-d35e-a1bf-ffff1a110000</link>
      <description>Robinson is from the Sean McVay coaching tree and has spent the last two seasons as the Falcons’ offensive coordinator. Though the mixture of Michael Penix Jr. and Kirk Cousins at quarterback did not work out, Robinson got productive seasons out of Drake London and Kyle Pitts to go along with a dual All-Pro 2025 season from Bijan Robinson. The Lions are continuing to look for a new offensive coordinator and Robinson has some history with Jared Goff from their days with the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bf3f-d35e-a1bf-ffff1a110000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
