<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said Trey Hendrickson (back) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de8c-def2-abdb-dfeddc1c0000</link>
      <description>The MRI results apparently came back well for Hendrickson, who may have a chance to play against the Steelers on Thursday night. Hendrickson was chipped hard by Tucker Kraft on Sunday and did not return to the game. He’s likely to wind up on the questionable line for Week 7 if he gets in any (estimated) work in practice on the short week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de8c-def2-abdb-dfeddc1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid would not answer on if Josh Simmons (personal) will return for Week 7’s game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de90-d94a-a79d-df9d8dc20000</link>
      <description>Jaylon Moore started at left tackle in Simmons’ stead in Week 6 and would likely get the call in Week 7 should Simmons’ personal issue leave him out of the lineup again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de90-d94a-a79d-df9d8dc20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said he did not have an update on David Njoku’s knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de90-def2-abdb-dff1019e0000</link>
      <description>We’ll likely have more clarity on this one soon, but Stefanski didn’t have updates on any of his players who were injured in Week 6’s loss to the Steelers. Njoku twice attempted to play through the knee injury he suffered in the second quarter before officially calling it quits early in the fourth quarter, so it’s possible a few days of light practice will have him good to go for next week’s game against the Dolphins. Right tackle Jack Conklin, who exited with a concussion, will presumably be in concussion protocol and need to clear protocol if he hopes to play in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de90-def2-abdb-dff1019e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys co-owner Stephen Jones said CeeDee Lamb (ankle) could play in Week 7 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dea2-dd4c-afb9-ffe30aae0000</link>
      <description>The real tell here will be the Cowboys’ injury report, but Jones’ early optimism is a good sign for Lamb, who has missed the last three weeks after suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 3’s loss to the Bears. The Cowboys didn’t place Lamb on injured reserve in hopes he would be able to return inside of the four-game window he would be required to miss had he landed on IR, so there is a somewhat realistic chance we could see him in Week 7. His status will be one to keep an eye on when the Cowboys release their first injury report of the week on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dea2-dd4c-afb9-ffe30aae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Tutu Atwell (hamstring) “should be good to go” against the Jaguars in Week 7.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dea2-db72-a199-feebcfb40000</link>
      <description>Our Jordan Whittington shares are falling apart before we can even buy them, folks. Whittington probably belongs ahead of Atwell — he’s played more snaps than him this year — but Atwell can have a whole fantasy day on one catch and that could make him an appealing WR4 stab against the Jaguars if Puka Nacua can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dea2-db72-a199-feebcfb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys co-owner Stephen Jones said KaVontae Turpin (foot) could return in Week 7 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deab-d94a-a79d-dfafd7140000</link>
      <description>Turpin has missed the last two games with a foot injury he suffered in Week 4. If he’s able to return in Week 7, he could find himself in a more meaningful role with CeeDee Lamb (ankle) is unable to go, but Jones has also expressed optimism in Lamb’s return against the Commanders. Assuming Lamb is active next week, Turpin would have virtually no fantasy appeal in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deab-d94a-a79d-dfafd7140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said he wasn’t ready to name a starter for Week 7 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dead-def2-abdb-dfedb6580000</link>
      <description>Carson Wentz is apparently still recovering from his shoulder injury, though he will participate in practice this week. O’Connell added that J.J. McCarthy (ankle) would practice “in some capacity” this week. That’s a load-bearing “some capacity” in our opinion and we should probably have Wentz as the leader in the clubhouse for this role in Week 7. Neither player rates out as more than a QB2 against what has been a fierce Eagles defense this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dead-def2-abdb-dfedb6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Blake Corum (ankle) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb2-dd4c-afb9-fff31c460000</link>
      <description>Corum wouldn’t practice today if there were a practice, per McVay, but that’s standard for players and Corum did return and play in the second half of Week 6’s win over the Ravens. We might see the Rams hold back on Corum a bit in practice this week, but we’d be surprised if he was actually held out of Week 7’s Fourth Meal London game against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb2-dd4c-afb9-fff31c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans fired head coach Brian Callahan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb3-dd4c-afb9-fff3ca3f0000</link>
      <description>Why now? Why not 10 months ago? Frankly, it was a bit of a miracle that the Titans actually won a game this season and it took one of the most bizarre interception fumble recovery touchdowns we’ve ever seen to make it possible. Tennessee drafted Cam Ward No. 1 overall and has seen him play like one of the worst quarterbacks in the league to this point. It’s hard to say that Callahan’s offense was the main culprit as the team is entirely bereft of talent at wideout and on the offensive line, but he certainly hadn’t been elevating Ward to this point either. The Titans have not yet named an interim head coach, though we presume Bo Hardegree will continue calling offensive plays in what is officially another lost season for the franchise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb3-dd4c-afb9-fff3ca3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said “we’ll see” when asked if Rico Dowdle earned the right to be the team’s starting RB going forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb0-db72-a199-fefb925b0000</link>
      <description>Typically, when a player goes for 473 yards from scrimmage and two touchdowns in a two-week span, teams lean into that success. Dowdle’s success over these last two weeks stands out even more when you compare it to the four-game sample we have from Chuba Hubbard this season (53-217-0). Even if Dowdle doesn’t stay in the bell cow role we’ve seen sans Hubbard, it’s hard to imagine the Panthers relegating him to backup duties. Hubbard missed all of practice last week, so whether or not he returns in Week 7 is a question on its own. Sure, “we’ll see” what Canales and company decide, but there’s no doubt Dowdle has forced the Panthers’ hand a bit here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb0-db72-a199-fefb925b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
