<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed CB C.J. Gardner-Johnson, formerly of the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</link>
      <description>Gardner-Johnson will reunite with Bears defensive coordinator Dennis Allen, who coached him in New Orleans from 2019 to 2021. The mercurial cornerback will join a Chicago defense that has allowed the NFL’s fourth highest drop back success rate and the second highest completion rate over expected this season. Look for Gardner-Johnson, who has 18 interceptions over 77 NFL games, to primarily play slot corner in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) faces a 4-6 month recovery period.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</link>
      <description>The dislocated ankle Skattebo suffered in Week 8 against the Eagles came with a fibula fracture and deltoid ligament rupture, according to Rapoport. The rookie was taken to a local hospital and underwent season-ending surgery. Rapoport seems confident Skattebo will be ready for the team’s offseason program, though his recovery will be worth tracking in the coming months. Tyrone Tracy will take over as the Giants’ lead back in Skattebo’s absence. Tracy had 39 yards on ten rushes and two catches for 14 yards against the Eagles last Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB John Wolford, formerly of the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</link>
      <description>Wolford will join the team’s practice squad ahead of Minnesota’s Week 9 game against the Lions. The Vikings last week lost Carson Wentz to a season-ending shoulder injury and will be forced to start J.J. McCarthy in Week 9. McCarthy has missed nearly two months with an ankle injury. Wolford will likely serve as the team’s QB3 behind McCarthy and Max Brosmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio believes the Eagles are “shopping A.J. Brown without officially shopping” him ahead of the NFL’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</link>
      <description>Florio said he’s heard of several contending teams that are interested in acquiring Brown if the Eagles are willing to part with the star wideout. That includes, per Florio, the Patriots, whose head coach — Mike Vrabel — coached Brown in Tennessee. “This to me feels like an effort by the Eagles to shop A.J. Brown without shopping A.J. Brown, to wait for the phone to ring, to not be the one who picks up the phone” to engage in trade talks before the November 4 league deadline. “Something’s been going on there,” Florio said of Brown, who has complained for years about his lack of opportunities in the run-heavy Philadelphia offense. Brown’s fantasy prospects would see a slight bump if he were to land with a more pass-first team, and his exit from the Eagles offense would make DeVonta Smith a borderline elite fantasy option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers opened the 21-day practice window for G Chandler Zavala (knee).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</link>
      <description>Zavala has been on injured reserve with a knee injury since October 1. The Panthers, struggling to protect the passer in recent weeks, could use Zavala back in action this week against a ferocious Packers front seven. Pro Football Focus grades Carolina’s offensive line as the 12th worst pass blocking unit through Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Flacco’s (shoulder) Week 9 status is “up in the air.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</link>
      <description>Flacco is dealing with an AC joint sprain, per Rapoport. He sustained the injury late in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss against the Jets and could miss this week’s game against the Bears. That would force Jake Browning back under center for the Bengals, a huge hit to the fantasy prospects of every Cincy pass catcher, including Ja’Marr Chase. Fantasy managers should keep a close eye on Flacco’s Thursday and Friday practice status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed TE Marcedes Lewis, formerly of the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</link>
      <description>The Broncos are looking for some tight end depth with Nate Adkins potentially missing time with injury. Lewis, 41, has played 19 NFL seasons. He has six receptions over his past three years in the league. It’s safe to say he won’t have any fantasy usefulness in Denver’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed EDGE Aidan Hutchinson to a four-year contract extension worth $180 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3091-de12-a19e-36b1590d0000</link>
      <description>The mega-deal includes $141 million in guarantees, according to NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero. It’s the most guaranteed money ever for a non-quarterback in the NFL. Hutchinson, 25, who’s now signed with Detroit through 2030, has been stellar in 2025, recording six sacks and forcing four fumbles through seven games. He has 34.5 sacks in 46 NFL games since entering the league in 2022. Pro Football Focus grades Hutchinson as the league’s second best pass rusher behind Micah Parsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3091-de12-a19e-36b1590d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Michael Penix (knee) will take the “majority” of first-team practice snaps this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30a9-de12-a19e-36a9b3450000</link>
      <description>Kirk Cousins took most of the Falcons’ first-team practice snaps late last week with Penix dealing with a knee issue. Cousins started in Week 8 against the Dolphins and struggled mightily, throwing for 173 scoreless yards with an adjusted yards per attempt of 5.5. Penix’s return this week against the Patriots would be a boost for every Atlanta pass catcher, though it remains to be seen whether Drake London (hip) will be ready for Week 9. Among the most inaccurate passers in the league, Penix is only usable in deeper superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30a9-de12-a19e-36a9b3450000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
