<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 23:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe2-def2-abdb-dfe31fa60000</link>
      <description>He did, however, return to practice this week, getting in two limited sessions after being sidelined for most of the last month-and-a-half. It seems likely that Ricard will be back for Baltimore in Week 8 after their bye, and perhaps that can help get their running game back on track.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe2-def2-abdb-dfe31fa60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Devontez Walker (oblique) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe3-db72-a199-ffebe63d0000</link>
      <description>He got in a DNP on Friday after two limited sessions, perhaps signaling a setback or the Ravens understanding that they can’t push him right now. Walker heads into Baltimore’s bye as a promising player ready for a bigger role in an offense, but also someone who simply can’t do more than limited snaps on a deep Baltimore wideout depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe3-db72-a199-ffebe63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd8-dd4c-afb9-efd9b2f00000</link>
      <description>Higbee has just one finish in the TE2 ranks this season, and is largely an afterthought in the Rams’ offense. Against the Ravens’ injury-depleted defense, he is on the touchdown-dependent TE2 radar, which is hardly a ringing endorsement. He is likely available in most leagues, if need be, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd8-dd4c-afb9-efd9b2f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) is not on Las Vegas’ final injury report for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</link>
      <description>With Brock Bowers out, Mayer will serve as the clear No. 1 tight end against Tennessee. It’s not exactly a smash spot, but Mayer went 4/38 against the Patriots in the opener and has had some TE1-worthy games in the past. Mayer probably is more of a TE2 until we see a ceiling game again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe0-def2-abdb-dfe14a760000</link>
      <description>Lawrence and LB Ernest Jones (shoulder) are good to go. The Seahawks’ defense will be without LB Derick Hall (oblique). S Julian Love (hamstring), CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and CB Riq Woolen (concussion) are listed as doubtful to play in Week 6 against the Jaguars. All three defensive backs were limited on Friday. Jaguars WRs Brian Thomas Jr. and Travis Hunter have high ceilings in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe0-def2-abdb-dfe14a760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars DE Travon Walker (wrist) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cffd-d94a-a79d-cffdbab80000</link>
      <description>Walker sat out in Week 5 after undergoing surgery to correct the wrist injury he suffered in Week 5. Despite the absence, Walker ranks and/or ties for second on the team in quarterback pressures (14) and sacks (two). His return is a huge help to a Jaguars defense that is tasked with containing a Seahawks passing attack averaging an NFL-high 9.2 yards per passing attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cffd-d94a-a79d-cffdbab80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out QB Brock Purdy (toe) for Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d008-dd4c-afb9-f7c9626d0000</link>
      <description>Purdy remained sidelined all week, as did WR Ricky Pearsall, who is dealing with a PCL sprain in his knee. Just eight days ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that Purdy is considered week-to-week, so the starting quarterback’s absence is hardly surprising. Hopefully, Purdy can remain setback-free and return for the 49ers’ Week 7 game against the Falcons, though that outcome should not be viewed as guaranteed. The 49ers also ruled out WR Jordan Watkins (calf), DL Kevin Givens (pectoral) and EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (knee/hamstring).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d008-dd4c-afb9-f7c9626d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cff3-def2-abdb-dff39e360000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported last week that Pearsall “could be back” for Week 6. Unfortunately, Pearsall failed to practice even once in a limited capacity this week. Despite missing the 49ers’ Week 5 game against the Rams, Pearsall ranks 16th, positionally, with 327 receiving yards. Hopefully, he can return for next week’s game against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cff3-def2-abdb-dff39e360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee/oblique) is questionable to play in Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4e-def2-abdb-df6f7a8c0000</link>
      <description>Jones remained limited through all three practices this week and was able to participate in throwing drills on Friday. With starting QB Brock Purdy already ruled out and Jones able to practice, the 49ers’ No. 2 quarterback is in line to start, pending good health on Sunday. Jones has two QB1 finishes and one QB2 finish in three games played this season. He deserves to be treated as a borderline QB1/2 against the Buccaneers’ pass-funnel defense this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4e-def2-abdb-df6f7a8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) is questionable to play in Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d012-db72-a199-fa5b10d00000</link>
      <description>Jennings took the day off on Wednesday before practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday and Friday. Fantasy managers can expect him to play on Sunday against the Buccaneers’ pass-funnel defense, though it will be worth monitoring the news for any updates on him. If active, Jennings can be started as a borderline WR2/3, operating as the 49ers’ No. 1 wide receiver with Ricky Pearsall (knee) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d012-db72-a199-fa5b10d00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
