<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (knee) exited in the second quarter of the Bills’ Week 16 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4263-d35e-a1bf-47e3b4000000</link>
      <description>Allen took a 22-yard loss on a sack late in the second quarter and could be seen grabbing at his leg after the play. He remained in the game to handle a one-yard QB sneak on the following play, but was being evaluated on the sideline by trainers after the drive. Allen left for the locker room with less than 10 seconds to go before halftime. We should have more info on his injury in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4263-d35e-a1bf-47e3b4000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) is active for Week 16 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4264-dc7a-af9b-cffffbf50000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals reportedly plan to “ease” Harrison back into action today. Teams often cast aside snap-count plans if their recently injured star player is feeling good early in their return, but Harrison has not yet established himself as a player who regularly exceeds expectations. The prudent move is to treat WR Michael Wilson as a fantasy football WR2 and view Harrison as a WR4/FLEX. Cardinals WR Xavier Weaver (hamstring) is also active. The Cardinals declared CB Max Melton (heel), CB Elijah Jones, CB Darren Hall (concussion), S Jalen Thompson (hamstring), OL Evan Brown (personal) and LT Paris Johnson Jr. (knee) inactive for Week 16 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4264-dc7a-af9b-cffffbf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) left Dallas’ Week 16 game against the Chargers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4269-d087-addf-f3f99ab60000</link>
      <description>Flournoy caught a touchdown on Dallas’ first drive and had another negated by a questionable holding penalty on Dallas’ second. The near-instant ruleout does not bode well for his rest-of-season status, which is a shame as he was making quite a push over the last three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4269-d087-addf-f3f99ab60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (foot) has been cleared to return in Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426b-d35e-a1bf-47eb22a00000</link>
      <description>Despite previous reports of a knee injury to Allen, NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reported at halftime that Allen “had X-rays on his foot and has been cleared to return.” Allen took the field with the Bills on the opening drive of the second half and appears to be good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426b-d35e-a1bf-47eb22a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) is active for Week 16 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426f-da28-afbb-c67f71d50000</link>
      <description>We last saw London play in Week 11 against the Panthers, when he caught 7-of-9 targets for 119 yards before suffering a PCL sprain. He practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday and Thursday this week before sitting out on Friday. We really would have preferred to see him practice fully at the end of the week, though it is entirely possible that the team gave him the day off for rest and rehab. London’s target-earning ability keeps him in the WR1 tier, though his range of potential outcomes is far wider than normal. The Falcons declared CB Mike Hughes, RB Nathan Carter, LB JD Bertrand, OL Michael Jerrell, WR Casey Washington, DL Elijah Garcia and WR Malik Heath inactive for Week 16 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426f-da28-afbb-c67f71d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (right hand) left Week 16’s game against the Giants and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426f-dc7a-af9b-cfffadeb0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy suffered the hand injury while taking a punishing sack from Brian Burns at the end of the first half. He didn’t see Burns coming and was decked, losing the ball in the process. New York recovered it and took it to the house for a touchdown. McCarthy left the game right after the play and was ruled out during halftime. Max Brosmer will take his place in the lineup in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-426f-dc7a-af9b-cfffadeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared RB Bhayshul Tuten, DE Danny Striggow, OL Chuma Edoga, TE Hunter Long, DT Maason Smith inactive for Week 16 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427b-d35e-a1bf-47fb24a90000</link>
      <description>Tuten is expected to miss the rest of the season after undergoing finger surgery this week. Travis Etienne should see an increase in snaps and touches with Tuten sidelined. LeQuint Allen Jr. would presumably function as the team’s RB2 behind Etienne, and could find himself in the lead back role if Etienne were to miss time in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427b-d35e-a1bf-47fb24a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) left Week 16’s game against the Giants and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427c-d087-addf-f3fc2d7b0000</link>
      <description>Kelly previously spent time on injured reserve this year because of a concussion. He has a lengthy history of head injuries. We suspect the team will shut him down for the year after his latest concussion. Michael Jurgens is in at center for Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427c-d087-addf-f3fc2d7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Zamir White, QB Aidan O’Connell, CB Darnay Holmes, TE Ian Thomas and DT Brodric Martin inactive for Las Vegas’ Week 16 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4279-d087-addf-f3f96b560000</link>
      <description>Jordan Meredith (ankle) was questionable but is active for the Raiders. They had nobody else with a status this week, so these are all healthy scratches. White has not been active since October 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4279-d087-addf-f3f96b560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared C Graham Glasgow, OL Kayode Awosika, OL Trystan Colon, OL Tyler Lacy, WR Dominic Lovett, S Jalen Mills and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Week 16 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427e-d087-addf-f3fe53b70000</link>
      <description>The good news for Jared Goff and Lions fans is that fellow offensive linemen Taylor Decker and Christian Mahogany are active. Decker was listed as questionable with a shoulder issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-427e-d087-addf-f3fe53b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
