<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50b60000</link>
      <description>Johnson came down with a bug last Friday and was unable to play in Week 17 against the Raiders. He must be really going through it. Fortunately, Johnson was seen observing practice from the sideline. Yesterday, he was reportedly among a group of ill players sent home by the coaching staff. He has a chance to play this week. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7705-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ad6-d968-a19b-7af722460000</link>
      <description>Carter’s absence is unsurprising. The coaching staff reportedly sent him and others home yesterday. The Athletic’s Dan Duggan noted DL Dexter Lawrence was also absent on Thursday. He believes Lawrence is “also in the illness category.” Both players have a chance to face the Cowboys this week, though the team notably kept TE Theo Johnson (illness) sidelined in Week 17, and he has not yet resumed practicing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ad6-d968-a19b-7af722460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (back) practiced on Thursday and it “appears as though” he will start in Week 18 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7add-d56e-afff-fefd62b80000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter echoed Jamison Hensley’s belief that Jackson will be under center in Week 18. The Ravens (8-8) and Steelers (9-7) are competing for the AFC North crown and a ticket to the postseason. Jackson’s mobility was reportedly impeded by the back contusion he suffered in Week 16. Hopefully, that is no longer the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7add-d56e-afff-fefd62b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d968-a19b-7af7b22a0000</link>
      <description>This is the second time this week that Wirfs’ status has changed. On Tuesday, he was reportedly set to resume practicing. Instead, he was listed as a non-participant on the official injury report. Earlier today, Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles told reporters that Wirfs would be listed as questionable for Week 18. He is now good to go after practicing twice in a limited capacity. The Buccaneers (7-9) no longer control their own destiny. In order for them to make the playoffs, they must beat the Panthers (8-8) on Saturday and they need the Falcons (7-9) to lose to the Saints (6-10) on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d968-a19b-7af7b22a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder/knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d35e-a1bf-7fe6aa200000</link>
      <description>Mayfield practiced fully on Thursday and Friday while nursing injuries in his knee and throwing shoulder. The Buccaneers have a chance to make the playoffs, though they require a loss from the Falcons in order to do so. Mayfield is borderline QB1/2 for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ae6-d35e-a1bf-7fe6aa200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out CB Jamel Dean (shoulder) for Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7af2-d968-a19b-7af31f530000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will be without their No. 1 cornerback against the Panthers this week. It will be tougher for the Buccaneers to cover Panthers rookie WR Tetairoa McMillan sans Dean, which is a plus for fantasy purposes. Hopefully, Dean can resume playing this season if the Buccaneers punch a ticket to the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7af2-d968-a19b-7af31f530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions OC John Morton said he would like to stay with the team in 2026, even if he loses his current role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b02-dc7a-af9b-ffbf17da0000</link>
      <description>Morton told the Detroit Free Press’ Dave Birkett that he views the Lions’ organization as his “home.” While he would likely prefer to keep his current job, he is open to shifting duties, ostensibly to a lesser role. He served as a senior offensive assistant back in 2022. At the very least, a job like that could make sense for both Morton and the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b02-dc7a-af9b-ffbf17da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills QB Josh Allen (foot) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b0e-d35e-a1bf-7fce55e90000</link>
      <description>We expect to see Allen listed with a missed practice on the team’s official injury report shortly. Reports and observations regarding Allen’s health vary, and the Bills (11-5) cannot overtake the Patriots (13-3), though they can still jockey for playoff position in the Wild Card ranks. The team could choose to rest Allen in favor of backup QB Mitchell Trubisky against the Jets’ generally soft defense this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b0e-d35e-a1bf-7fce55e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Denver Post reports Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) is “expecting” to be healthy for the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b13-dc7a-af9b-ffbf31ee0000</link>
      <description>It goes without saying that Greenlaw will sit out this week’s game. After signing a huge free-agent deal with the Broncos, Greenlaw has played just 324 total snaps in the regular season. He did post a solid 74.8 PFF grade, and would be in line to be a difference-maker in the playoffs if he actually gets there healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b13-dc7a-af9b-ffbf31ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Chase Brown (illness) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b13-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0a7d0000</link>
      <description>Brown missed yesterday’s practice as well. Were he to sit out in Week 18 against the Browns, it would likely mean RB Samaje Perine handles a sizable, fantasy-friendly workload. Bengals rookie RB Tahj Brooks could also take on some rushing work. Players typically play through illness, but we have seen a few sickness-related game-day absences as of late. Brown still has a chance to play. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b13-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0a7d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
