<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:28:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught his only target for 10 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 12 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3ba-d90e-a9da-bfbfbb130000</link>
      <description>Brown has caught more than two passes one time over his past five games. He opened the year as an emergency WR1 for the Chiefs. He has since been relegated to rotational No. 3 duties with Xavier Worthy healthy and Rashee Rice active. Fantasy managers shouldn’t worry about Brown for Week 13, even in a good matchup versus the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3ba-d90e-a9da-bfbfbb130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku was not targeted in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3be-d82c-a79a-b3be07a40000</link>
      <description>Njoku has been playing a part-time role for over a month. He still ran a route on just over half of Shedeur Sanders’ dropbacks in this game but failed to draw even one target. He is purely a backup tight end at this point. Fantasy managers can some him to waivers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3be-d82c-a79a-b3be07a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught 4-of-6 targets for 40 yards in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3c0-db57-afda-f7f2a0370000</link>
      <description>Fannin added one carry for four yards. He was the only Browns player to catch more than two passes versus Vegas. Fannin easily led the team with a 30 percent target share. The rookie tight end has had no issues putting up floor games this year, but spike weeks have been few and far between. He will sit at the top of the TE2 ranks for Week 13 versus the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3c0-db57-afda-f7f2a0370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedric Tillman caught 1-of-3 targets for five yards in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3c5-d82c-a79a-b3d596540000</link>
      <description>Tillman led the Browns with three catches for 52 yards in Week 11. He led the receiving room with three targets, tied with Jerry Jeudy, this week but failed to hit on any big plays. The Browns are a run-first team that won’t be projected for many passing yards no matter who starts for them in Week 13. Tillman is not on the fantasy radar versus the 49ers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3c5-d82c-a79a-b3d596540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 1-of-3 targets for 39 yards in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3ca-d82c-a79a-b3de32880000</link>
      <description>Jeudy’s only catch of the day should have at least gone down as a highlight, given that is gained 39 yards. It was, instead, the worst play of his season. Looking for extra yards while sprinting down the sideline, Jeudy slowed down, high-stepped to throw a Raiders defensive back off, and promptly had the ball knocked out of his hands by a trailing Vegas defender. He was completely unaware of Jeremy Chinn chasing him down and embarrassed himself with the failed flashy move. Jeudy has one game over 50 yards since the Browns traded Joe Flacco. Even as the team’s top wideout, he is barely a WR6 heading into Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3ca-d82c-a79a-b3de32880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Bond caught both of his targets for 58 yards in the Browns’ Week 12 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3d0-d413-ad9f-b7dd16690000</link>
      <description>Bond was on the receiving end of Shedeur Sanders’ big highlight of the day. He sped past the Vegas secondary and Sanders launched a deep ball at him while on the run, resulting in a 52-yard gain. Bond came up just feet short of the end zone, but Quinshon Judkins punched in a short touchdown shortly after. Bond’s profile is too boom/bust for fantasy managers to care about in redraft leagues. He is, however, a worthwhile stash in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3d0-d413-ad9f-b7dd16690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) is doubtful to return to Week 12 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b327-db57-afda-f7371ce70000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was injured on a scramble in the second quarter as he appeared to be pinned on a tackle and unable to brace himself, with the weight of himself and two defenders landing on his non-throwing shoulder. He did not return to open the second half before the team deemed him doubtful for the remainder of the contest. The Rams held him to the third fewest passing yards in any half of his career at just 41, adding 19 yards on four carries. he threw one touchdown and two interceptions prior to departing. It’ll be veteran Teddy Bridgewater attempting a massive comeback with the team down 31-7. Fantasy managers will want to track his status ahead of a Week 13 meeting with the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b327-db57-afda-f7371ce70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 30-of-44 passes for 285 yards and a touchdown in the Raiders’ 24-10, Week 12 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3d3-db57-afda-f7f36abf0000</link>
      <description>Smith’s box score doesn’t look so bad until you see that he took 10 sacks for a total loss of 77 yards. He also lost the ball twice, one of which was scooped up by the Browns. Smith, now 35 years old and largely immobile at this point in his career, was an easy target for the Browns’ tenacious pass-rush. It got so bad at certain points that Geno simply gave himself up before taking a brutal hit multiple times. His 10 sacks are the most for a quarterback in a single game since 2018. Smith made a few nice throws but also regularly sailed passes, primarily deep shots to Tre Tucker. There isn’t much the Raiders can change heading into Week 13. Smith has very little left in the tank and Pete Carroll has no idea how to scheme around his struggling quarterback. Geno will sit at the back of the QB2 ranks for Week 13 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3d3-db57-afda-f7f36abf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 17 times for 50 yards in the Raiders’ Week 12 loss to the Browns, adding eight catches for 58 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3da-db57-afda-f7fa38ae0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty was kept in check on the ground once again this week. The last time he averaged more than 3.5 yards per carry in a game was in Week 5. The good news is that Jeanty was heavily involved through the air for the second week in a row. He led the Raiders in catches and came up four yards shy of a team-high in yards. Jeanty caught six passes on eight targets last week. He is up to four receiving touchdowns on the year. His receiving role is papering over consistently underwhelming rushing lines, keeping him in the RB2 mix. The Raiders’ struggling offense will prevent him from turning an elite role into an RB1 fantasy ranking ahead of Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3da-db57-afda-f7fa38ae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
