<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tee Higgins is back in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff95-d8cf-affb-ffbf1dbb0000</link>
      <description>Taylor told reporters that Higgins — who was checked multiple times after a couple major hits on Sunday — reported symptoms after the game. Given the quick turnaround from his last concussion, it would be surprising if Higgins managed to play this week. It looks like Andrei Iosivas and Mitchell Tinsley, as well as Mike Gesicki, will be solidly on the 12-team radar for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ff95-d8cf-affb-ffbf1dbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz suffered a torn ACL in Week 14’s game against the Vikings, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffad-da9b-a9bf-ffadd7d90000</link>
      <description>At a minimum, this is a season-ending injury for Ertz. At worst, it’s a career-ending injury for the 35-year-old tight end who has played 13 seasons and now suffered two devastating knee injuries in his career. Ertz re-upped with the Commanders on a one-year, $6.25 million deal this offseason after a bounce-back 2024 campaign in which he went for 66-654-7. Ertz continued to be a reliable safety blanket in the passing game for the 3-10 Commanders, posting a steady 5-504-4 line this season while going for 50-plus yards in three games. He’ll enter 2026 as a free agent, and may need to prove he’s fully healed in the offseason before signing a one-year contract with the Commanders or another team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffad-da9b-a9bf-ffadd7d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (elbow) is “sore” but that there’s “no long-term concerns with the elbow.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffae-d005-a9bf-ffbe12da0000</link>
      <description>Quinn then deftly declined to say if Daniels would play on Sunday. Never a good sign when the coach won’t even offer a comment on the plausibility of that happening on Monday. Marcus Mariota could be in for a smash streaming spot against a left-for-dead Giants defense in Week 15. We’re sure this is the first of many Daniels blurbs this week either way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffae-d005-a9bf-ffbe12da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers activated RB Omarion Hampton from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc1-da9b-a9bf-ffcd4c4d0000</link>
      <description>Hampton will be active for Monday night’s game against the Eagles and will likely draw the start. Hampton was seeing a bell cow workload before going down in Week 5’s game against the Commanders, and will hopefully have a healthy role in time for the fantasy playoffs. Hampton has rushed 66 times for 314 yards and two touchdowns, and has caught another 20 passes for 136 scoreless yards. His return likely deals a major blow to Kimani Vidal’s fantasy value, although Vidal could see enough work to remain in the mix as a FLEX play. We’ll have more information to go on after Monday’s game against the Eagles, but Hampton is in the RB2 mix for anybody hoping to start him on Monday night. In addition to Hampton, the Chargers have also activated RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc1-da9b-a9bf-ffcd4c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Trey Hendrickson (hip) is set to undergo core muscle surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc2-d77b-adfa-ffc3ea270000</link>
      <description>In a bit of a sourceoff, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport would only report that surgery is on the table, not that Hendrickson is “set to undergo” the surgery. Either way, undergoing the surgery would knock Hendrickson out for approximately six weeks, meaning his season would be over barring a miracle Bengals playoff appearance. It does feel like we’ve seen the last of Hendrickson for 2025, and it would appear that he’ll enter free agency unless the Bengals franchise tag him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc2-d77b-adfa-ffc3ea270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffd0-d005-a9bf-fff485620000</link>
      <description>It’s a new listing, and the first we’ve heard of a knee injury for the tight end after a 6/90 performance on Sunday. But given the fact that he was limited and not fully resting, we don’t think this is a serious concern for his Week 15 status just yet. Pitts figures to be the de facto Falcons WR1 if Drake London, as expected, remains sidelined on Thursday night. That hasn’t translated to more than TE1 PPR volume yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffd0-d005-a9bf-fff485620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (knee) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdc-d77b-adfa-ffdff03c0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimated report, but it’s a new listing for Tampa’s tight end. He’s not been particularly fantasy relevant since Tampa got Chris Godwin back, but this would seem to suggest there’s a chance he misses Week 15. Payne Durham is behind Otton in the pecking order at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdc-d77b-adfa-ffdff03c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers listed RB Bucky Irving (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdf-d8cf-affb-ffffc6640000</link>
      <description>Irving has been playing through the same shoulder injury since returning in Week 13, which may become the norm for the remainder of the season. The team listing him as a full participant on Monday’s report is a good sign for his Week 15 availability against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdf-d8cf-affb-ffffc6640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons claimed WR Malik Heath off waivers from the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old receiver has a career 31/308/3 slash line in 37 games with the Packers and can be involved on special teams. The Falcons are at a point where they’re relying on David Sills every weekend. The waiver claim makes some sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers listed QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield continues to be listed with the same left shoulder injury he has played through each of the last two weeks. We’ll assume he’s good to go for Thursday night’s game against the Falcons unless we hear otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
