<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Todd Monken said he will call plays on offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-249e-d355-a5bd-afde740d0000</link>
      <description>Monken brought former Ravens run game coordinator Travis Switzer on board as his OC. Switzer has never called plays at any level, so this news shouldn’t come as much of a surprise. Calling plays in Baltimore over the past three seasons, the Ravens finished fourth, third, and 11th in points per game. Monken has a proven trackrecord of success with an MVP-caliber quarterback. How he fares with the Browns’ messy quarterback situation will determine his fate in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-249e-d355-a5bd-afde740d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed former Broncos OC Joe Lombardi as a senior offensive assistant.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ab-d89c-a1be-afff12d70000</link>
      <description>He’ll be the steadying hand for Declan Doyle as the youngster calls plays for the Ravens. Lombardi was fired so late in the cycle that he had no real shot at an offensive coordinator job in this cycle. We suspect he’ll get interviews in 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ab-d89c-a1be-afff12d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers will interview Vikings passing game coordinator and TEs coach Brian Angelichio for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24b1-d042-afbc-7df3d73a0000</link>
      <description>As has been the norm in Mike McCarthy’s searches this offseason, Angelichio coached under McCarthy in Green Bay. He’s a long-time NFL tight ends coach who has worked with the Buccaneers, Browns, Commanders, and Panthers in addition to the Vikings and Packers. Angelichio has not called plays since he was the offensive coordinator at (wait for it) Ithaca College in the early 2000s, but he wouldn’t have that pressure with the Steelers as McCarthy is expected to call plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24b1-d042-afbc-7df3d73a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports Texans secondary coach Dino Vasso is a “name of interest” for the Cardinals defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24d4-d629-a1bc-b4dd2a8a0000</link>
      <description>Vasso also interviewed for the Titans DC job before it went to Gus Bradley. Breer adds Rams assistant head coach Aubrey Pleasant is a possibility for the job. As one of the last teams to fill their head coaching vacancy, the Cardinals are going to be left trying to find up-and-comers for their coordinator positions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24d4-d629-a1bc-b4dd2a8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills GM Brandon Beane said CB Dorian Strong (neck) is “going to have a procedure that will determine whether he can play.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ff-d355-a5bd-afff242f0000</link>
      <description>The 2025 fifth-round pick played in four games for the Bills before suffering the injury, and he’d played 39 percent of the snaps to that point so he was trending towards being a real contributor. His future in the league is in doubt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-24ff-d355-a5bd-afff242f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills GM Brandon Beane said K Tyler Bass (hip/groin) is expected to be Buffalo’s kicker in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2503-d042-afbc-7dd3980a0000</link>
      <description>Beane noted there was an outside chance that Bass could have kicked in the Super Bowl had the Bills made it, leaving us to believe that there’s little doubt he’ll be available at the start of next season. Bass missed the entire 2025 regular season with the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2503-d042-afbc-7dd3980a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Mike LaFleur said he will call plays for the Cardinals in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2507-d629-a1bc-b51f584a0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said he “missed it” during his three years as Sean McVay’s offensive coordinator and noted that “the worst playcall is a late playcall.” Stapled to an ineffective Zach Wilson early in his career, it’s hard to fully understand LaFleur’s upside as a playcaller at this point. It’s certainly possible he does better in Arizona than he did in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2507-d629-a1bc-b51f584a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapaport believes Michigan DC Wink Martindale is a “name to watch” for the Cardinals defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2533-d042-afbc-7df3268e0000</link>
      <description>Martindale appeared to be heading towards getting the Jets defensive coordinator job earlier this offseason, but after Aaron Glenn decided he wanted to call plays the two sides went separate directions. Presumably Martindale would have play-calling authority in Arizona if he were the choice, as Mike LaFleur has zero defensive coaching experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2533-d042-afbc-7df3268e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills hired former Titans quarterbacks coach Bo Hardegree as their quarterbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2563-d355-a5bd-af7794600000</link>
      <description>Hardegree was asked to call plays for the Titans for most of last season, first to supplement Brian Callahan, then to replace him after he was fired. That made it two straight seasons where Hardegree took over as a playcaller midseason, since he was on Josh McDaniels’ doomed 2024 Raiders staff. Joe Brady is hoping to not make it three times in a row.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2563-d355-a5bd-af7794600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired Indiana co-offensive coordinator Chandler Whitmer as their quarterbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-25cb-d355-a5bd-afdf8e8e0000</link>
      <description>Whitmer was co-offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach for the National Champion Indiana Hoosiers, helping shape an offense with prospective first-round pick Fernando Mendoza. The Bucs are adding to the offensive staff under new offensive coordinator Zac Robinson after Josh Grizzard was let go. Whitmer will be the quarterbacks coach for Robinson, working with Baker Mayfield as he tries to recover from a shaky second half of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-25cb-d355-a5bd-afdf8e8e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
