<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks waived RB Myles Gaskin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e157-db57-afda-f77710000000</link>
      <description>Gaskin was active on the Seahawks’ 53-man roster last week, seeing three carries for six yards against the Vikings. He is now waived as the Seahawks make room on the roster for other moves; Gaskin could be brought back on the practice squad. The Seahawks also released WR Brenden Rice and C Doug Kramer from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e157-db57-afda-f77710000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions TE Brock Wright (neck) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e195-d6c4-abfb-f79730d60000</link>
      <description>Wright was listed as a non-participant on Monday is still a DNP Tuesday after missing Week 12 due to a neck injury. Fellow tight end Shane Zylstra was listed as limited on Monday due to a knee injury, but was downgraded to DNP on Tuesday. Both tight ends are in jeopardy of missing Thursday against the Cowboys, leaving the Lions scarce at the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e195-d6c4-abfb-f79730d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e19f-d90e-a9da-ff9f56940000</link>
      <description>Sewell was not on the injury report Monday, but popped up with a shoulder injury Tuesday and did not practice. Meanwhile, LT Taylor Decker has also been listed with a DNP tag due to a shoulder issue Tuesday, after initially being listed as limited Monday. Though it is possible both tackles could play Thursday against the Cowboys without practicing, any level of practice on Wednesday would provide some relief as it pertains to Jared Goff’s blocking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e19f-d90e-a9da-ff9f56940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Bucs are expected to open the 21-day practice window for WR Jalen McMillan (neck).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e473-db57-afda-f6736e940000</link>
      <description>McMillan has been sidelined since the preseason with a neck injury, but could return for the stretch run. He could be active as early as this week against the Panthers, though it remains to be seen how the Bucs would deploy him. Mike Evans’ eventual return from injured reserve would further complicate things for McMillan’s playing time. He should remain on waiver wires for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e473-db57-afda-f6736e940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said the team will look to “reestablish physicality and a big-man presence” in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e488-db57-afda-f6ba87c70000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly news that old-school Tomlin desires a return to old-school, run-based, low-scoring football as a way to get the Steelers out of the rut they find themselves in headed into Week 14 against the Ravens. But a real commitment to a tough nosed, presumably run-heavy offensive approach should mean more touches for Jaylen Warren and perhaps Kenneth Gainwell. It might mean more involvement for Darnell Washington, who is very large and physical. The Steelers rank 18th in pass rate over expected this season, and inside the ten yard line they are the 12th pass-heaviest team. Both Warren and Gainwell should be fantasy viable if Tomlin is serious about a reestablishment of physicality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e488-db57-afda-f6ba87c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs opened the 21-day practice window for WR Mike Evans (collarbone).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4cc-db57-afda-f6fe51410000</link>
      <description>Evans gained medical clearance, per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, and could suit up as early as this Sunday against the panthers. Evans would likely take over as the team’s No. 1 receiver of struggling rookie WR Emeka Egbuka and Chris Godwin. Evans has 14 catches for 140 yards and a touchdown on 32 targets this season. His return to the Tampa offense is a fantasy boon for Baker Mayfield, whose efficiency has fallen off with Evans sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4cc-db57-afda-f6fe51410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts CB Sauce Gardner (calf) is expected to avoid injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d0-d6c4-abfb-f6d368e00000</link>
      <description>Gardner, Rapoport believes, could return to the Colts lineup within the next four weeks. That opens up the possibility that Gardner could be at full health — or something close to it — if the Colts right the ship and make it to the postseason. The Colts are expected to be careful with Gardner’s calf injury in hopes of not complicating the injury in a way that would jeopardize the corner’s entire season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d0-d6c4-abfb-f6d368e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano believes the Panthers will pick up Bryce Young’s fifth-year option in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d5-d90e-a9da-ffdfd48a0000</link>
      <description>Panthers coaches and front office officials “still believe in” Young despite his ups and downs this season, including a Week 13 meltdown against a weak Niners defense. Young finished the 2024 season on a hot streak after being benched early that season, but started 2025 with baffling decision making and poor throws both in the short areas and downfield. On the season Young ranks 21st out of 33 qualifying quarterbacks in drop back success rate and 30th out of 40 quarterbacks in yards per attempt. Graziano said he expects the Panthers to keep Young around in 2026 “because the cost will be reasonable (around $26.5 million), but then the question becomes what to do after that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4d5-d90e-a9da-ffdfd48a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said the team wants Kyren Williams fresh for the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4ea-d90e-a9da-ffefd5350000</link>
      <description>In other words, the LA backfield split between Williams and Blake Corum will continue in the final weeks of the regular season. “LaFleur told me he thinks they’ve been seeing the best version of Williams because he’s fresher and not being asked to carry as much of the load, and the Rams have their sights set on January and February games and want everyone as fresh as possible,” ESPN’s Dan Graziano said. Over the Rams’ past five games, Williams leads the backfield with 76 rushing attempts to 48 rushes for Corum. Williams has an outsized lead in running back routes, but only six targets over the past five games. Williams, dealing with an ankle injury, will be a touchdown-dependent RB2 in Week 14 against the Cardinals if he suits up. Corum should be stashed in all leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e4ea-d90e-a9da-ffefd5350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns opened the 21-day practice window for QB Deshaun Watson (Achilles).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e503-d6c4-abfb-f7032cc40000</link>
      <description>The move injects even more drama into the team’s quarterback situation after Shedeur Sanders took over as starter and is expected to remain starter for the final month of the regular season. Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said opening Watson’s practice window was a “good next step” for the veteran, though he wouldn’t commit to a timeline for Watson’s return to game action. Watson, 29, re-ruptured Achilles tendon in the offseason and has been rehabbing ever since. Watson has 19 touchdowns and 12 interceptions for the Browns over his three seasons with the team after signing perhaps the most catastrophic contract in pro sports history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e503-d6c4-abfb-f7032cc40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
