<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on Terron Armstead’s podcast ‘The Set,’ Tyreek Hill said whether or not he retires is “based upon how I feel.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1683-dab4-a3fb-9ff3e2be0000</link>
      <description>It was the first public interview given by Hill since suffering a season-ending knee injury in Week 4. The 31-year-old receiver said right now he’s happy being at home with his kids and with the career he has had before adding “I’m at the point now where I need to have a conversation [about retirement] with mom, family, everybody.” Laid up on his couch and recovering from surgery, Hill sounded more like a player who would prefer to retire than continue the NFL grind, but a lot could change between now and then. Hill will be 32 at the start of next season but remains under contract through 2026. He’ll have to undergo extensive rehab just to return to the field, and said in 2023 hewould retire after his current contract— the one he is on now — expires. Even if he does play in 2026, it’s clear Hill is on the back nine of his career, and could opt to call it quits at any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1683-dab4-a3fb-9ff3e2be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on 105.3 The Fan, Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said Trevon Diggs (concussion) and Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder) are questionable for Week 8 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16a5-d5d8-a3ff-ffe552db0000</link>
      <description>Jones’ comments come before the the Cowboys third practice of the week gets underway. We will receive a more official word on both players’ statuses later in the day, but it’s worth pointing out that Diggs and Wilson were DNPs on Wednesday and Thursday. Jones calling them questionable is a fairly optimistic take given how they are trending based on those practices. We’ll check back in once the final injury report is released but both players will probably need a limited practice on Friday if they hope to suit up this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16a5-d5d8-a3ff-ffe552db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Jones said Garrett Wilson (knee) will not play in Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16af-d245-adfb-97ffaa850000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t come as much of a surprise after Wilson was a DNP all of last week and missed the first two days of practice to open this week. Whether or not he practices on Friday clearly won’t matter after opted to rule him out before the final practice of the week, paving the way for Josh Reynolds and Allen Lazard to serve as the team’s top two receivers against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16af-d245-adfb-97ffaa850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Sauce Gardner (concussion) will not play in Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16d9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9bb4b0000</link>
      <description>Gardner suiting up for Week 8 more or less came down to whether or not he could clear concussion protocol in time. After being a DNP in back-to-back practices to open the week, Gardner was unable to clear protocol on Friday and will be ruled out as a result. It’s a tough break for a defense that has struggled through the first half of the season and now has to deal with Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins in what should be a favorable matchup for the Bengals’ top-two offensive players, in addition to Joe Flacco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16d9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9bb4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Tyrod Taylor (knee) is questionable for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa80440000</link>
      <description>Taylor has been limited in both practices to start the week after a surprise knee injury popped up on Wednesday. Speaking Friday, Glenn said Taylor, along with a number of other Jets players who are listed as questionable for the week, is trending in the right direction. This should put him in line to start Week 8 against the Bengals after rumors earlier in the week that the team was “moving toward” naming him the starter, although Glenn has still declined to do so as of the time this post was written. If Taylor does make the start in Week 8, he would have some QB2 upside in superflex leagues with six teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa80440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Mason Taylor (quad) is questionable for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16db-deb1-a39b-37df3ff70000</link>
      <description>Taylor was a surprise addition to Thursday’s injury report. The rookie tight end reportedly injured his quad during the session, but Glenn said on Friday that he was trending in the right direction entering the weekend. With six teams on bye this week, Taylor, who has seen five or more targets in four games this season, could have some streaming upside in PPR leagues against a defense that’s allowing the second-most points per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16db-deb1-a39b-37df3ff70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Breece Hall (knee) will be questionable for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16dc-dab4-a3fb-9ffcc8940000</link>
      <description>Glenn said Hall is trending in the right direction after being limited in Wednesday and Thursday’s practices. The Jets RB1 doesn’t appear to be at risk of missing Week 8’s game against the Bengals in what should be a plus matchup, but fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on inactives when they are released 90 minutes before kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16dc-dab4-a3fb-9ffcc8940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Palmer (knee/ankle) will not play in Week 8 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16e8-deb1-a39b-37ee84920000</link>
      <description>Palmer did not log a practice this week and has been ruled out ahead of Friday’s practice. The veteran receiver has logged two or fewer catches in all but one game this season and wasn’t going to be on the fantasy radar in Week 8 even with six teams on bye. His replacements, Elijah Moore and/or Curtis Samuel can also be left out of lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16e8-deb1-a39b-37ee84920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaQuan Jones (calf) will not play in Week 8 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16ec-dab4-a3fb-9ffcdfbf0000</link>
      <description>Jones suffered a calf injury while warming up for Week 6’s game against the Falcons and was unable to suit up for that game. Its been two weeks since the injury, but the veteran tackle was still unable to get on the practice field this week and has now been ruled out for Sunday’s contest against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16ec-dab4-a3fb-9ffcdfbf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
