<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels completed 24-of-42 passes for 200 yards with two touchdowns in the Commanders’ 27-18, Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd7-d86f-abdd-7fffa01d0000</link>
      <description>Daniels was unable to get much done on the ground, either, as he rushed for just 17 yards with a long of eight in the contest. The Packers’ defense swarmed the second-year signal-caller, and the box score doesn’t show how much he struggled to get the ball downfield for the overwhelming majority of the contest. Chalk this mostly up to the Green Bay defense, and expect Daniels to bounce back against the Raiders next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd7-d86f-abdd-7fffa01d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 23 times for 84 yards with a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd7-d294-a19b-fff7e5cc0000</link>
      <description>That now makes 10 straight games for Jacobs with a rushing score. The veteran tailback didn’t find a tun of room to run against the front seven of the Commanders, but did enough to keep the chains moving while adding the rushing score to make it an effective — if far from dominant — fantasy contest. Jacobs will get a chance to make it 11 straight against the Browns next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd7-d294-a19b-fff7e5cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed four times for 17 yards in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd8-d294-a19b-fff8944b0000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt was a non-factor after gashing the Giants for 82 yards in Week 2. Some of that has to do with the stout Packers defense, some of it has to do with game script, some of it just ineffectiveness. Croskey-Merritt could be looking at being considerably more involved going forward, however, as Austin Ekeler left Thursday’s game with a non-contact Achilles injury. If he can’t go, Croskey-Merritt will assuredly be RB1 for the Commanders in Week 3 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3bd8-d294-a19b-fff8944b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft caught 6-of-7 targets for 124 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d86f-abdd-7ffdba0b0000</link>
      <description>Kraft was all alone on the majority of his targets, with the two biggest connections being a 57-yard scamper from the arm of Jordan Love and an eight-yard touchdown throw from Love in the fourth quarter. The 24-year-old wasn’t nearly as involved in Week 1 against the Lions, but that’s back-to-back weeks with a receiving score for the 2023 third-round pick. He’s a TE1 for Week 3 when the Packers face off against the Browns, but don’t expect this kind of yardage total very often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d86f-abdd-7ffdba0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 3-of-5 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be2-da67-a99f-fff7d2df0000</link>
      <description>Doubs beat the middle of the Washington defense to connect with Jordan Love on a five-yard touchdown to open the scoring. The fourth-year wideout wasn’t involved often after that early touchdown, as Jordan Love was able to find a bevy of wideouts and tight ends throughout the contest. Doubs remains in the WR4 vicinity for the Week 3 tilt against the Browns, but might get a slight bump up if Jayden Reed (shoulder) can’t play in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be2-da67-a99f-fff7d2df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught 4-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d294-a19b-fff396240000</link>
      <description>Wicks ended up leading the Packers’ wideouts in targets and catches on a night where Jayden Reed left Thursday’s win in the first possession with a shoulder injury. The 24-year-old wideout remains a solid option for Jordan Love, but not solid enough to recommend him as a fantasy option even with the Reed injury potentially leading to more snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d294-a19b-fff396240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden didn’t haul in either of his targets while adding two rushes for 15 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be4-dc44-a9d9-3fe63fe20000</link>
      <description>Oh what could have been. Golden just missed a pair of touchdowns; one on a ball that was underthrown by Jordan Love on fourth down in the first possession, and another that would have been a 90-plus yard score on a ball that was just overthrown. He showed off his speed on a pair of end-arounds, but this could — and should — have been a much better fantasy day for the rookie wideout. Golden should remain part of the gameplan for Week 3 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be4-dc44-a9d9-3fe63fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 6-of-8 targets for 64 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d86f-abdd-7fffdd230000</link>
      <description>Ertz was the most reliable target for the Commanders late in the contest after Washington had to go into throw-only mode after being down two scores. He not only scored the first touchdown of the game for the Commanders, but he set up the second score by drawing a holding penalty in the corner of the end zone. That makes back-to-back games with a score, and he’ll be a high-end TE2 — if such thing exists — for Week 3 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d86f-abdd-7fffdd230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
