<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 9-of-12 targets for 67 yards in the Jets’ Week 5 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b640-d95b-addb-fe46eaff0000</link>
      <description>Taylor nearly doubled the 11 receptions he had entered Sunday’s contest with, hauling in nine targets in a game the Jets trailed the whole way. Taylor’s targets have steadily increased each week, and he’s now up to 23 targets since Week 3, boasting a line of 18-150-0 over that span. Taylor is clearly the preferred option in the offense over any wide receiver not named Garrett Wilson, and is slowly creeping into TE1 territory based on his volume alone. He gets a tough Week 6 matchup against the Broncos, but fantasy managers lacking an elite tight end should consider taking a shot on Taylor after three-straight weeks of seeing six or more targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b640-d95b-addb-fe46eaff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 10 times for 16 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 5 loss to the Panthers, adding six catches for 30 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b633-d6e9-af9d-beb3c4750000</link>
      <description>As has often been the case over the past year and change, Achane was bottled up on the ground for all four quarters. That, of course, does not matter for fantasy purposes when he simply operates as a secondary wide receiver for the Dolphins. That was the case this week and Achane looked the part of his receiving score. Achane lined up in the slot and won a toe-tapping jump ball in the end zone for his third receiving touchdown of the year. With Tyreek Hill done for the year, Achane’s role as a pass-catcher is only going to grow in the coming weeks. He is locked in as an RB1 for Week 6 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b633-d6e9-af9d-beb3c4750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 14 times for 67 yards in the Raiders’ Week 5 loss to the Colts, adding five receptions for 42 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b643-d95b-addb-fe47127f0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty qualified as a rare bright spot in a 40-6 loss, clearing 100 yards from scrimmage for the second consecutive week and posting multiple big gains while the game was still reasonably close. 84 of his 109 yards game in the first half. Things got out of hand after the break, where Jeanty was also shaken up. He was never announced with an injury and stayed in the game, but Raheem Mostert got a lot of work late. Looking more explosive and decisive, Jeanty is starting to live up to his lofty draft pedigree. The problem is everything else. The Raiders can’t block and Geno Smith is passing like one of the league’s worst quarterbacks. That keeps Jeanty’s floor low and ceiling tougher to reach ahead of Week 6 against the Titans. That’s at least an RB1 matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b643-d95b-addb-fe47127f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Dobbins rushed 20 times for 79 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 5 win over the Eagles, adding a five-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b647-dca3-a9fb-bfdfa8f10000</link>
      <description>The 20-carry effort was Dobbins’ first as a Bronco and came after he handled just seven totes in the first half. The Broncos grinded out second half drives as they came back from a 17-3 deficit, with Dobbins plunging in for a two-yard score to make it 17-10 early in the fourth. He ceded only seven change-of-pace handles to RJ Harvey, who turned his workload into a modest 30 yards. This setup doesn’t appear to be changing any time soon, keeping Dobbins locked in as a workload-based RB2 ahead of Week 6 against the Jets’ awful defense in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b647-dca3-a9fb-bfdfa8f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon rushed three times for a two-yard loss in the Dolphins’ Week 5 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b644-d95b-addb-fe4612310000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins made Jaylen Wright a healthy scratch for this game, but that didn’t mean much for Gordon’s role. Gordon had nine touches in Week 3 and hasn’t topped six in any other game. He is a distant RB2 on a struggling Dolphins team. There is no fantasy value to be had behind De’Von Achane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b644-d95b-addb-fe4612310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed four times for 12 yards in the Broncos’ Week 5 win over the Eagles, adding three receptions for 18 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b64b-deb6-a7fd-f7df62660000</link>
      <description>Harvey’s 30 yards were his third most in five games, but he got out-touched 21-7 by J.K. Dobbins. He also ceded plenty of snaps to Tyler Badie. Things change quickly in the NFL, especially in Sean Payton backfields, but there isn’t any reason to expect a meaningful adjustment here any time soon. That has summer hype all star Harvey looking like a tenuous hold with bye weeks here and injuries mounting. Perhaps he can help mop up in Week 6, where the Broncos are being flown to London to likely beat down the 0-5 Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b64b-deb6-a7fd-f7df62660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 4-of-6 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 5 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b650-d95b-addb-fe56faee0000</link>
      <description>Sitting on one catch for -3 yards at halftime, Engram rallied to reach four receptions for the second consecutive week, this time scoring his first touchdown in a Broncos uniform. He cashed in an 11-yarder for the go-ahead score in the fourth quarter, diving to reach the plane. Finally getting healthier, Engram has 13 targets over the past two weeks after seeing six combined looks in his first two contests and missing a game. Hardly world beating, of course, but at least establishing a TE2 baseline ahead of a Week 6 London road trip to face the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b650-d95b-addb-fe56faee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 4-of-5 targets for zero yards in the Dolphins’ Week 5 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b654-deb6-a7fd-f7df59430000</link>
      <description>Mike McDaniel tried to get Washington some designed touches, but the Panthers sniffed all of them out with ease. He is now averaging a dismal 2.4 yards per target this year. Washington isn’t earning downfield looks and has yet to find space to work on his screens. He is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b654-deb6-a7fd-f7df59430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 27-of-36 passes for 256 yards and three touchdowns in the Dolphins’ 27-24, Week 5 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b65b-d95b-addb-fe5f4f520000</link>
      <description>It was a tale of two games for the lowly Dolphins. They went up 17-0 early in the second quarter and immediately took their foot off the gas. The Panthers got 10 points on the board before halftime and kept their foot on the gas in the second half. The Dolphins, on the other hand, didn’t score another point until the fourth quarter when Tua found Jaylen Waddle wide open for a 46-yard score to give his team the lead. Bryce Young quickly answered and the Dolphins went three-and-out on their final drive, going out with a whimper. Tagovailoa played a solid game, but a quiet second half let the Panthers come from behind for the win. Now at 1-4, Mike McDaniel is on the hottest of seats heading into Week 6. Tagovailoa is in a similar spot as he prepares for the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b65b-d95b-addb-fe5f4f520000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
