<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jauan Jennings (shoulder) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3035-db7b-a5dd-b03548720000</link>
      <description>Schefter’s source believes Jennings has a chance to play Sunday at New Orleans, which means he’ll be in line for a big share of the team’s workload with George Kittle down. How impressive that workload is probably depends on whether or not Brock Purdy (shoulder) actually plays this week. We’ll monitor the practice reports but the drumbeat is that Jennings should be considered in making projections for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3035-db7b-a5dd-b03548720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Giants LB Micah McFadden (foot) will undergo surgery and be out “significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3070-d332-a1fd-b676dd360000</link>
      <description>McFadden injured his foot in Week 1 and is “likely to return this season.” The post sending him to injured reserve is in the drafts already. The question is just how long it will be, and based on “significant,” we’re guessing this injury will require more than the minimum required four-week stay for McFadden. Darius Muasau played the most at linebacker in McFadden’s place. It’s a small boost for the Cowboys in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3070-d332-a1fd-b676dd360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed K Eddy Pineiro.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-307d-d332-a1fd-b67fca700000</link>
      <description>The fabled two-update day on Eddy Pineiro has come to pass. At some point this year he’ll probably be fantasy-interesting, though it might not be in Week 2 given how banged up the 49ers currently are.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-307d-d332-a1fd-b67fca700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter was fined $57,222 for spitting on Cowboys QB Dak Prescott Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-308d-d93a-abbb-79df9a050000</link>
      <description>Carter will forfeit his game check for Week 1 and won’t be suspended additional games for spitting on Dak Prescott in Thursday’s season opener. The NFL considered his ejection from Week 1 sufficient enough in terms of missed time, so the $57,222 game check forfeiture will be the only additional punishment on Carter. Head coach Nick Sirianni said any punishment or conversation from the Eagles will happen “in-house.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-308d-d93a-abbb-79df9a050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed WR Christian Watson to a one-year, $13.25 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-30d9-dbe3-a9bb-30dba1970000</link>
      <description>Watson’s contract was set to expire at the end of the 2025 season, but now the Packers extend the 26-year-old to keep him for an additional year. He is currently on the physically unable to perform list with a knee injury, so the extension gives Watson more room to recover without dealing with an impending free agency. Meanwhile, the Packers keep together a crowded wide receiver room that saw five different wide receivers catch a pass in Week 1. Watson will return to this group, though he won’t be high on the pecking order given he is returning from a torn ACL. He has dealt with several leg injuries throughout his young career, totaling 98 receptions for 1,653 yards and 14 touchdowns over 38 games in three seasons. Fantasy managers should not count on Watson for fantasy-relevant play upon his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-30d9-dbe3-a9bb-30dba1970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets released WR/KR Xavier Gipson</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-338b-db7b-a5dd-b38f1db30000</link>
      <description>Gipson lost a kick return fumble in the fourth quarter of New York’s Week 1 loss to the Steelers, sealing his fate with the Jets. Head coach Aaron Glenn said after the game that the team could not afford turnovers; Gipson’s fumble was the lone turnover of the game for the Jets. Gipson, 24, is in his third NFL season. He’s operated as a kick returner and rotational wideout for New York over that stretch. Gipson could catch on with a returner-needy team in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-338b-db7b-a5dd-b38f1db30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports LB Jadeveon Clowney is visiting with the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-33ec-d93a-abbb-7bfe16040000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are looking for defensive help after being shredded by the Eagles in Week 1. Without EDGE rushers Micah Parsons, who was dealt to the Packers in August, Dallas logged a 15 percent pressure rate against the Eagles, the 16th highest rate in Week 1. Last year they led the NFL with a 31 percent pressure rate. Clowney, 32, totaled 46 tackles and 5.5 sacks in 14 games with the Panthers last season. He’s one year removed from a career-high 9.5 sack season with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-33ec-d93a-abbb-7bfe16040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said he expects OL Austin Jackson (toe) to miss Week 2 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-344d-d93a-abbb-7d5f3e400000</link>
      <description>Miami will likely be without Jackson and RG James Daniels, who was placed on injured reserve this week with a pectoral injury. It’s a major blow to the Dolphins offense, which struggled mightily in their Week 1 blowout loss to Daniel Jones and the Colts. Tua Tagovailoa in Week 1 was pressured on just 22 percent of his drop backs, the third lowest rate in the league. The team’s quick-passing offense should prevent Tagovailoa from facing much pressure this week against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-344d-d93a-abbb-7d5f3e400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers (back) was limited during Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3485-db7b-a5dd-b4851e920000</link>
      <description>As long as Nabers practices in full by week’s end, he should be OK for the Giants’ Week 2 game against the Cowboys. Nabers went for five grabs and 71 scoreless yards in Week 1 against the Commanders, leading the team in targets and air yards. Against a Dallas offense that should put up plenty of points this week, Nabers could benefit from a pass-heavy game script. He should be locked into all fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3485-db7b-a5dd-b4851e920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart will remain the QB2 in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3488-d332-a1fd-b6be92280000</link>
      <description>Daboll was once again effusive with praise for the rookie quarterback, complimenting his work ethic and understand of the team’s offense. “We’ll continue to work with him,” Daboll said. The Giants are almost assuredly prepping Dart to get under center as the team’s starter in the coming weeks following Russell Wilson’s disastrous outing in Week 1 against Washington. Only two QBs were more inaccurate than Wilson last week. Dart should be rostered in all superflex formats. He could have a shot at playing time this week against the Cowboys if things go south for Russ in a hurry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3488-d332-a1fd-b6be92280000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
