<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers waived K Jake Moody.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f6d-db7b-a5dd-af6d55780000</link>
      <description>Greg Joseph was in camp for the 49ers and is a logical solution for them if they don’t opt to hold tryouts. Moody missed two field goals against the Seahawks in Week 1 after a horrendous 2024 season. He’ll join the tryout circuit if no immediate interest materializes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f6d-db7b-a5dd-af6d55780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed George Kittle (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f72-db7b-a5dd-af76b87a0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games and be eligible to return in Week 6 against the Buccaneers. Kittle is a tough hold in shallow leagues without an injured reserve spot, but given the state of the 49ers offense he probably remains a hold. If Brock Purdy starts this week — that also seems to be in some question — it sounds like Christian McCaffrey will get all the workload he can handle against the Saints. Jauan Jennings feels like a question mark as well but would step in to a major role against the Saints if he can play, along with Ricky Pearsall. Jake Tonges will replace Kittle in the 49ers lineup and isn’t a recommended streamer at this point, though he did catch a touchdown against the Seahawks in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f72-db7b-a5dd-af76b87a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed RB Cody Schrader off the Rams practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f91-db7b-a5dd-af9567830000</link>
      <description>It’s hard to believe that Schrader could be a major part of the mix behind Travis Etienne and Bhayshul Tuten right away in the same way that Tank Bigsby hypothetically could, but it’s a great landing spot overall for the former Ram. Schrader was active in Week 1 ahead of Jarquez Hunter, though he played no offensive snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f91-db7b-a5dd-af9567830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed G Cole Strange off the Browns practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f96-db7b-a5dd-af96665b0000</link>
      <description>Strange will join the Miami interior competition in the absence of James Daniels, though it’s possible he just winds up as a pure backup. There’s got to be someone out there with a #RevengeGame narrative for Strange playing against the Patriots — who drafted him in the first round in 2022 — in Week 2, but we’d be surprised if he got many snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f96-db7b-a5dd-af96665b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala believes the Commanders may push the ball downfield more often to Deebo Samuel this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f9c-dbe3-a9bb-3fdf6e560000</link>
      <description>“With the 49ers, Samuel was a deep target roughly eight times a season, per TruMedia,” Jhabvala writes. She notes that the Commanders targeted Samuel on deeper routes “regularly” during training camp, and that Samuel had two deep targets in Week 1 against the Giants. It’s probably not a major step for Samuel’s fantasy value, which has always been more about PPR and explosive plays, but mixing in more deep routes could keep the 29-year-old receiver’s fantasy floor more stable. He handily out-targeted Terry McLaurin in Week 1 and has the look of a draft day bargain at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f9c-dbe3-a9bb-3fdf6e560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Birds’ Derrick Gunn reports Will Shipley (ribs) is dealing with a fracture.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fa2-d93a-abbb-7ffa71310000</link>
      <description>It helps explain the Tank Bigsby trade a little more. Eagles beat reporters denied that Shipley’s health was related to the trade yesterday, but now Bigsby can help step into fill the void Shipley may be leaving. If it’s serious, Shipley could be an injured reserve candidate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fa2-d93a-abbb-7ffa71310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed RB Deuce Vaughn to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fc4-db7b-a5dd-afc4a8cc0000</link>
      <description>He’ll prepare to be the next Tyler Badie. The 23-year-old Vaughn has good pass-catching chops and has performed well in small samples when given a chance, but his lack of size makes it hard to believe he’ll ever be more than a complementary NFL back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fc4-db7b-a5dd-afc4a8cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Schottenheimer said the Cowboys need to see more consistency from Jaydon Blue to make him active.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fdf-d93a-abbb-7fdffff60000</link>
      <description>In other words, don’t expect Blue to get into the Dallas running game rotation at any time in the near future. He probably doesn’t need to be held in 12-team leagues at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fdf-d93a-abbb-7fdffff60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent K Eddy Pineiro is visiting with the 49ers Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fe3-db7b-a5dd-afe783190000</link>
      <description>He’s one plausible replacement for the recently-waived Jake Moody. The 49ers kicker job generally comes with a lot of fantasy appeal, but they’re banged up enough to this point that whoever kicks for San Francisco this weekend against the Saints may not see many attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2fe3-db7b-a5dd-afe783190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed P Cameron Johnston.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-300c-d332-a1fd-b63e57550000</link>
      <description>They waived Brad Robbins. Not sure why the Bills figured they’d need a punter after what we saw on Sunday night, but if they attempt any in Week 2, Johnston will be taking them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-300c-d332-a1fd-b63e57550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
