<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) did not participate in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a7c-d673-a39e-fefd10b70000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed Week 10 with back/hip issues and is trending to miss Week 11 as well. Also not practicing on the defense were LB Baron Browning (concussion), LB Mack Wilson (ribs), or S Dadrion Taylor-Demerson (ankle). The Cardinals defense is hurting heading into a Week 11 matchup against the 49ers and each of these players will need to log a practice to have a chance to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a7c-d673-a39e-fefd10b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden (quad) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a83-d45b-affe-7f97d37a0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden gets the best possible start to the week as the Chargers list him as a full participant for Wednesday’s practice. Despite not returning in Week 10 against the Steelers, Gadsden’s MRI did not show any major issues and is now participating fully in practice. He is now on track to play Week 11 against the Jaguars, where he should be in the low-end TE1 range for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a83-d45b-affe-7f97d37a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (shin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a86-d45b-affe-7f96d0df0000</link>
      <description>Johnston popped up on Wednesday’s injury report with a shin issue. There is little cause of concern as of now, given it is the first practice of the week and the 24-year-old was at least a limited participant. Rookie Tre Harris could see a boost in perimeter snaps should he miss time, but Johnston is still in the WR3 range for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a86-d45b-affe-7f96d0df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (ankle) was a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a8b-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb19820000</link>
      <description>McConkey had dealt with a calf issue last month, but now pops up with an ankle issue to open the week. It is still early, so a limited practice participation indicates McConkey is on track to play in Week 11 against the Jaguars. If he does miss time, Keenan Allen should see a boost in targets. Stay tuned to McConkey’s practice participation the rest of the week, but expect him to be in the fantasy WR2 range this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a8b-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb19820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Parker Washington (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a8e-d713-ad9e-7ede81680000</link>
      <description>Washington made an impact with a punt return touchdown and a receiving touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 10 loss to the Texans. With Travis Hunter confirmed to be out for the season, Washington is in line to be the Jags’ slot receiver and a fantasy WR3/4 the rest of the way. However, a hamstring injury kept the 23-year-old out of practice to start the week. It is still early, so fantasy managers should stay tuned to practice reports later in the week for Washington’s Week 11 status. Should Washington miss time, the newly acquired Jakobi Meyers is next man up while Brian Thomas Jr. should return to WR1 status in the Jags offense if he returns from his ankle injury this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a8e-d713-ad9e-7ede81680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a92-d45b-affe-7f96ad9a0000</link>
      <description>Thomas starts out this week limited after not participating the first two practices of last week. His participation indicates Thomas is trending to return to the field Week 11 against the Chargers. Fantasy managers should stay posted for his practice status the rest of the week as a full practice gives us more confidence that Thomas will play. If he does suit up, Thomas is a fantasy WR2 with Travis Hunter out for the season and Parker Washington now dealing with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a92-d45b-affe-7f96ad9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) was a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa3-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb83bf0000</link>
      <description>Horton was dealing with a groin injury last week before also injuring his shin in practice. He missed Week 10, but is on track to return with a limited practice participation to start the week. The addition of Rashid Shaheed nullifies some of Horton’s deep ball fantasy value, but the rookie is still a boom-or-bust play in deep leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa3-d1e7-a1fa-7aeb83bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa8-d713-ad9e-7efc2e3b0000</link>
      <description>Bond missed Week 10 with a foot injury but returns in a limited fashion to open Week 11. A full practice later in the week boosts Bonds’s chances of playing against the Ravens, but he does not have much fantasy relevance in the Dillon Gabriel offense. Cedric Tillman (glute) was also limited a week after coming off injured reserve. Tillman is ahead of Bond is the pass-catching order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7aa8-d713-ad9e-7efc2e3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a98-d713-ad9e-7edc45dc0000</link>
      <description>Strange had his 21-day practice window opened this week and was a limited participant in his first practice back. With Travis Hunter out for the season, Parker Washington dealing with a new hamstring injury, and Brian Thomas working back from an ankle injury, Strange may be in line for major usage upon his return. He tallied 23 targets from Weeks 1-4 and should be in the low-end TE1 range upon his return, whether that is Week 11 against the Chargers or Week 12 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a98-d713-ad9e-7edc45dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said RB Trey Benson (knee) is “taking it day by day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7abb-d45b-affe-7fbfef920000</link>
      <description>At this point, Benson has been out four games and is slated to miss his fifth this week. There is still no confirmation on severity of his injury or a timetable other than Gannon vaguely saying he is “doing better” last week and he is “taking it day by day” this week. It sounds like Benson’s practice window won’t be opened until next week at the earliest, so fantasy managers can expect him back on the field Week 12 at best, but more likely Week 13 against the Buccaneers, barring setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7abb-d45b-affe-7fbfef920000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
