<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars placed WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ac0-d1e7-a1fa-7aea245a0000</link>
      <description>Less than 24 hours after learning that Hunter suffered a knee injury in Thursday’s practice, the two-way player will now miss a minimum of four games because of said injury. According to Coen, the Jaguars are “currently assessing” the knee injury, which was of the non-contact variety, and the team still hasn’t determined how long Hunter’s absence could be. The rookie won’t be eligible to return until Week 13 at the earliest and now leaves the Jaguars short on both sides of the ball. The rookie has played on 323 offensive snaps per PFF compared to just 162 defensive snaps, and has seen 209 of his offensive snaps come from the slot. His absence should result in an expanded role for Parker Washington, who enters Week 9 averaging 4.7 targets per game, but could also be supplemented by Dyami Brown (shoulder) who was a full participant in Thursday’s practice. Both players make for interesting stashes heading into a generous Week 9 matchup against the Raiders but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than WR4/WR5s in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ac0-d1e7-a1fa-7aea245a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins fired GM Chris Grier.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ada-d673-a39e-bedb10f00000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter was the first to report the “mutual” split between Grier and the Dolphins. A long-time employee of the Fins, Grier got his start with the team in 2000 as a scout and worked his way up to general manager in 2016. The firing of Grier is the first major move the Dolphins have made following their dreadful 2-7 start to the season, and potentially buys head coach Mike McDaniel a little bit of time. Grier notably traded CB Jalen Ramsey and TE Jonnu Smith to the Steelers this past offseason in exchange for S Minkah Fitzpatrick, and then brought Darren Waller out of retirement to fill the void left by Smith. During his 10 years as the team’s primary roster builder, Grier failed to lead the team to a division title or playoff win. Once the Dolphins hit nine losses this season, they will have had five losing seasons under Grier. Senior personnel executive Champ Kelly is expected to take over as the team’s interim GM, and could have some big decisions to make ahead of next week’s trade deadline with the Dolphins looking like obvious sellers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ada-d673-a39e-bedb10f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel is expected to remain with the team through this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ae7-d673-a39e-bef7a55c0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins made the decision to part ways with GM Chris Grier on Friday as their first move toward a front office rebuild following a 2-7 start to the season. McDaniel seems unlikely to retain his job past this season, but owner Stephen Ross will decide on his future once the season has concluded. McDaniel’s team has struggled in ways that once felt unimaginable after going 20-14 during his first two seasons while leading a top-10 scoring offense in his first three. Despite the early success, the Dolphins offense has imploded this season, ranking near the bottom of the league in points per game, yards per game, and EPA per play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ae7-d673-a39e-bef7a55c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolf reports “multiple teams” have called the Dolphins about trading for Bradley Chubb and Jaelan Phillips.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3af4-d673-a39e-bef5c34c0000</link>
      <description>Interim GM Champ Kelly has five days to orchestrate some moves before Tuesday’s trade deadline. The Dolphins are sitting on a 2-7 record and have several players who could be of interest to contenders, with Chubb and Phillips likely topping the list in a league that covets pass rushers. Chubb, who has totaled four sacks this season, is still under contract through the 2027 season, while Phillips’ contract is set to expire at the end of this season. Phillips has managed three sacks in the nine games he has appeared in. After hesitating to pull the trigger on any trade requests before Week 9’s loss to the Ravens, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Dolphins looked to deal some players in hopes of recouping draft picks entering the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3af4-d673-a39e-bef5c34c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills ruled out Josh Palmer (ankle/knee) for Week 9 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3afb-d45b-affe-7fff0f770000</link>
      <description>Palmer continues to work his way back from an injury he suffered in Week 6. Palmer hasn’t contributed much this season when healthy, and is currently sitting on a 14-234-0 line through six games. His absence shouldn’t have much of an impact on a Bills offense that has relied on Khalil Shakir, Keon Coleman, and Dalton Kincaid as its top three pass catchers. In addition to Palmer, the Bills also ruled out DT DaQuan Jones and LB Shaq Thompson for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3afb-d45b-affe-7fff0f770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (hamstring) will start in Week 9 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b05-d45b-affe-7f97ed720000</link>
      <description>Daniels has been trending toward a return all week. The Commanders’ QB1 was a full participant in both Wednesday and Thursday’s practices and will presumably log another full practice on Friday before entering the weekend. The Commanders are 3-5 on the season and need to pull out a win over a tough Seahawks team in Week 9 to avoid a fourth-straight loss. While Terry McLaurin (quad) has already been ruled out, Daniels’ rushing upside should keep him in the mix as a QB1 this week for fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b05-d45b-affe-7f97ed720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) said he is feeling good ahead of Week 9’s matchup against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b15-d713-ad9e-7f554a160000</link>
      <description>Flacco didn’t say if he expected to play in Sunday’s game, but that was clearly the vibe the veteran signal-caller was giving off on Friday when speaking with the media. Flacco and the Bengals plan to test his shoulder before ultimately deciding on his availability, but it sounds like he should be good to go in a plus matchup against the Bears barring any setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b15-d713-ad9e-7f554a160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b1e-d713-ad9e-7f5ea5540000</link>
      <description>Young was a full participant in practice all week and was removed from the injury report on Friday. Despite initial concerns that he could miss multiple games with the ankle injury he picked up in Week 7, Young was only sidelined for one game and will be back under center against a stout Packers defense. Young will be hard to trust outside of 2QB/Superflex leagues even with a few good quarterbacks on byes this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b1e-d713-ad9e-7f5ea5540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette will play in Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b24-d45b-affe-7fb6cbcb0000</link>
      <description>Legette was never really at risk of missing Week 9’s game against the Packers after popping up with an illness on Thursday’s injury report. Legette has been an unreliable producer all season and saw one less target than Jalen Coker in last week’s blowout loss to the Bills. Legette can be left off Week 9 fantasy rosters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b24-d45b-affe-7fb6cbcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers listed OG Chandler Zavala (knee) as questionable for Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b29-d673-a39e-bfb9afe80000</link>
      <description>The Panthers didn’t open Zavala’s 21-day return window until this week, but the third-year guard was listed as a full participant in all three practices. Players who log a full week of practice tend to suit up come game day, so it’s possible this questionable designation is more cautious optimism than anything else. In addition to Zavala the Panthers also listed OG Damien Lewis (oblique), OT Taylor Moton (knee), S Nick Scott (groin), and LB Trevin Wallace (shoulder) as questionable for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b29-d673-a39e-bfb9afe80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
