<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley (ribs) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a15-da68-ad9d-ff5fd57f0000</link>
      <description>He was present at practice but did not participate. Even if he is questionable and practices on Friday, it feels likely that the Eagles will shift some workload off his plate with the addition of Tank Bigsby. Shipley is not the miracle desperation FLEX you’re looking for in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a15-da68-ad9d-ff5fd57f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed RB Ty Chandler (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a17-d8e3-affd-7bb7a5330000</link>
      <description>Blake Cashman (hamstring) joins him in missing at least the next four weeks. Zavier Scott will elevate to the team’s No. 3 back in Chandler’s absence. Cam Akers is undoubtedly leaving calls on Kevin O’Connell’s phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a17-d8e3-affd-7bb7a5330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio said the Chiefs and Steelers’ interest in trading for Tyreek Hill has been “complicated” by Hill’s most recent domestic violence allegations.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-d214-a3b9-3e7d1cc30000</link>
      <description>Florio opines that Hill will not be on the Dolphins’ roster next year, and with the Dolphins’ season already “off the rails,” jettisoning Hill sooner rather than later makes sense. The accusations made public from Hill’s current divorce case could result in a suspension, and Florio notes that “any team that would be interested in trading for Tyreek Hill wants to be sure that they’re not trading for a guy who’s going to be suspended before the end of the season.” If the Chiefs or Steelers are willing to bring him aboard, it stands to reason that they might choose to wait until after the NFL’s investigation concludes before making an offer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-d214-a3b9-3e7d1cc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a1b-da68-ad9d-ff5b0a3d0000</link>
      <description>At this point it would be surprising if Likely played in Week 2, which should keep Mark Andrews’ usage boosted — for all the good that did on Sunday — and condense the target tree in Baltimore. Likely still hasn’t practiced since undergoing surgery towards the end of July after getting hurt in a training camp practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a1b-da68-ad9d-ff5b0a3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Goedeke (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a21-da68-ad9d-ff7b97ff0000</link>
      <description>Nine days after getting an extension, Tampa’s stalwart right tackle pops up on the injury report with a new injury. Coach Todd Bowles said he is “hopeful” Goedeke can play, and Goedeke did play all 58 snaps on Sunday. His absence would be huge for a line already missing Tristan Wirfs against a fearsome Texans front on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a21-da68-ad9d-ff7b97ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio believes the Dolphins could fire head coach Mike McDaniel “if the losses continue.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a22-d8e3-affd-7bb2091b0000</link>
      <description>Florio described the Dolphins’ season as being “off the rails” following their Week 1, 33-8 loss to the Colts, and compared this season to the Dolphins’ 2015 season, in which then-head coach Joe Philbin was fired after a 1-3 start. Florio also astutely notes that McDaniel’s “refreshing” authenticity plays well when the team is winning. The Dolphins face the Patriots, Bills, Jets and Panthers over the next four weeks. If McDaniel can get his team to win at least two games during that stretch, it’s possible he buys himself more time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a22-d8e3-affd-7bb2091b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Kalel Mullings (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39fe-d214-a3b9-3ffea6df0000</link>
      <description>That makes two absences for Mullings this week. If the sixth-round rookie cannot suit up for Week 2, that would leave the Titans with just Tony Pollard and Julius Chestnut as the available running backs on the active roster. Pollard totaled 19 touches against the Broncos last week, with Tyjae Spears (ankle) on injured reserve. He is likely to do so again against a slightly softer Rams defense. Titans OT JC Latham (hip) and DT T’Vondre Sweat (ankle) were also not seen practicing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39fe-d214-a3b9-3ffea6df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee) said he is “optimistic” he’ll play in Week 2 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a4e-d214-a3b9-3e7e820b0000</link>
      <description>Fuaga said he’s dealing with an inflamed patellar tendon that he aggravated in the second quarter against the Cardinals in Week 1. “I’m going to be good this week,” Fuaga said. “Just making sure I’m good, making sure … nothing’s inflamed or anything. Just making sure it’s calmed down.” The pain was so sharp that Fuaga left the game in the fourth quarter despite playing through the injury in the third. It sounds like Fuaga may need to be managed quite a bit this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a4e-d214-a3b9-3e7e820b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) said he is confident he will resume playing in less than three weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a51-d214-a3b9-3e7dfdde0000</link>
      <description>Smith declined to go into detail about the injury other than to say it was “physical” as opposed to a mental health matter. “We’re kind of fluid with if I’m ready to go or not, and if I am going to help the team or not,” Smith told reporters. The veteran safety seems unlikely to play in Week 2, but could be a consideration for Week 3 or Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a51-d214-a3b9-3e7dfdde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Goodson (elbow) remained limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a57-d214-a3b9-3e7fae1f0000</link>
      <description>He was inactive for Week 1 and there’s a chance he’ll reclaim the No. 2 job from DJ Giddens if healthy, but certainly there’s no reason to roster him in shallow leagues while Jonathan Taylor is healthy and has the lion’s share of the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a57-d214-a3b9-3e7fae1f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
