<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Steelers are finalizing a deal to hire Vikings pass game coordinator Brian Angelichio as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a0d-d629-a1bc-ba1da0490000</link>
      <description>Angelichio served as the tight ends coach under Mike McCarthy in Green Bay for three years. He has been in the NFL for nearly two decades and has held the role of tight ends coach for almost his entire pro coaching career, spanning six teams. He also coached college football at Pitt, making this a homecoming of sorts. He now returns to Pittsburgh for the first offensive coordinator gig of his career. It’s safe to assume that McCarthy will serve as the team’s play-caller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a0d-d629-a1bc-ba1da0490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Ravens will not retain quarterbacks coach Tee Martin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a28-d042-afbc-7ffa58cb0000</link>
      <description>Martin joined the Ravens in 2021 as a wide receivers coach. He was eventually promoted to quarterbacks coach and, as Schultz notes, was one of the people closest to Lamar Jackson in the organization. With Jesse Minter replacing John Harbaugh as the head coach and Declan Doyle taking over as OC, Martin will be replaced by a hire from the new braintrust. Martin received several head coaching interviews over the year, including meetings with the Commanders and Lions a month ago, so there should be plenty of interest in him this offseason. It would not be surprising to see Martin follow John Harbaugh to New York, potentially in the same role, for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a28-d042-afbc-7ffa58cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired former Jets offensive coordinator Nathaniel Hackett as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a32-d629-a1bc-ba3f6ecf0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins tabbed Hackett as their quarterbacks coach earlier in the offseason. With the Cardinals offering him a better position, Hackett will instead join Mike LaFleur in Arizona. The two have never worked together directly, but Hackett spent three years under Matt LaFleur as Green Bay’s offensive coordinator. He also rejoined the Packers as a defensive analyst in 2025. Hackett has largely flamed out since his first stint in Green Bay. His offenses never finished better than 24th in scoring across two seasons as the Jets’ OC and one as the Broncos’ head coach. As long as LaFleur is the one calling plays, this hire shouldn’t be viewed too negatively, even if it’s clearly based on his familiarity with the system as opposed to his recent track record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a32-d629-a1bc-ba3f6ecf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers hired former Commanders defensive coordinator Joe Whitt Jr. as their assistant head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a3f-d629-a1bc-ba3f8c990000</link>
      <description>Whitt will also hold the title of secondary coach. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero was first on the news. He notes that Whitt coached under new Steelers head coach Mike McCarthy for 11 seasons in Green Bay. White also spent another three years with McCarthy in Dallas. As expected, McCarthy is getting the band back together in Pittsburgh. Whitt spent the past two years as the Commanders’ defensive coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a3f-d629-a1bc-ba3f8c990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested an interview with Giants OLB coach Charlie Bullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a49-d629-a1bc-ba5d69860000</link>
      <description>Bullen took on the role of interim defensive coordinator for the Giants this year after they fired Shane Bowen. The team interviewed him for the permanent DC job after John Harbaugh signed on as head coach. While they ultimately went in a different direction, Bullen was retained by the new staff. Bullen previously served as a position coach for the Cardinals under Kliff Kingsbury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a49-d629-a1bc-ba5d69860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye (shoulder/illness) said he expects to practice in full ahead of Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a6f-d629-a1bc-ba7f32860000</link>
      <description>Maye was listed as questionable on the Pats’ initial injury report last week. He was limited for the first two practices of the week. The team then held him out of Friday’s session because of the illness, not the shoulder issue. There was never any risk of him missing this game and his comments today confirm that. A full practice today means the shoulder injury shouldn’t affect Maye in any capacity on the biggest stage in football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a6f-d629-a1bc-ba7f32860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed WR Terrace Marshall to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a79-d042-afbc-7ffb48120000</link>
      <description>The former second-round pick was cut by the Panthers after three seasons. He caught three passes for the Raiders in 2024 and most recently spent time on the Eagles’ practice squad. His R/F deal with the Dolphins will give him a chance to make a good impression early in the offseason program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a79-d042-afbc-7ffb48120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested an interview with Texans defensive backs coach Dino Vasso for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a81-d355-a5bd-afd5afcc0000</link>
      <description>Vasso interviewed with Tennessee for their DC opening in January but didn’t get the job. Ariona also requested an interview with Giants OLBs coach Charlie Bullen for their DC job. Expect them to bring in a few more names over the next week. Vasso has been a position coach for the Texans since 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a81-d355-a5bd-afd5afcc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NFL’s Jay Glazer believes Maxx Crosby’s time with the Raiders is done.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2aae-d629-a1bc-babf29b20000</link>
      <description>Speaking with Yahoo Sports, Glazer speculated that the Raiders could get more in return for Crosby than the Cowboys did when they traded Micah Parsons. For reference, Dallas netted defensive tackle Kenny Clark and a pair of first-round picks. Glazer also noted that the two sides are at a crossroads as a result of Crosby’s desire to not see another rebuild. It’s possible that the new regime, likely led by Klint Kubaik, can sell him on this not being a lengthy rebuild. However, it’s safe to say Crosby has also heard that pitch before. Crosby has 44.5 sacks over the past four seasons and won’t turn 29 until the end of training camp. He is under contract for three more seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2aae-d629-a1bc-babf29b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
