<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired Ken Zampese as their new senior offensive assistant and pass game specialist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers also hired T.J. Yates as pass game coordinator, Andrew Mitchell as assistant offensive line coach and Todd Bowles Jr. as a defensive assistant. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport previously reported both Zampese and Yates’s expected hirings. Bowles joins his father’s coaching staff after playing most recently at Long Island University in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Patriots ILB coach Zak Kuhr could replace former DC Terrell Williams, who now occupies a “high-ranking role on the staff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ca-d629-a1bc-f3dfe9480000</link>
      <description>Kuhr took over defensive play-calling duties while Williams underwent treatment for prostate cancer this season. Williams is reportedly cancer-free, and will occupy a new role next season. Rapoport labels Kuhr “a top candidate” for the Patriots’ new defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ca-d629-a1bc-f3dfe9480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals completed an interview with Seahawks DB coach and pass game coordinator Karl Scott for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53cd-d629-a1bc-f3dd72070000</link>
      <description>Scott has served in his current roles with the Seahawks for the past four seasons. He coached Vikings defensive backs in 2021 after working his way up the college coaching ranks with six different schools from 2007-2020. He served as a defensive coordinator once before, at Southeastern Louisiana in 2014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53cd-d629-a1bc-f3dd72070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Dave Borgonzi as their new linebackers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5436-d355-a5bd-df761dc30000</link>
      <description>Titans general manager Mike Borgonzi is Dave’s brother. The latter Borgonzi previously coached linebackers with the Cowboys (2025), Bears (2022-2024) and Colts (2018-2021). He held offensive and defensive assistant roles with the Cowboys and served as a defensive quality control coach with the Buccaneers before that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5436-d355-a5bd-df761dc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derek Carr said he is willing to unretire if given the opportunity to join a team that has a “chance to win a Super Bowl.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5448-d042-afbc-7ddaf4500000</link>
      <description>Carr’s comments, made during a podcast with his older brother, David, confirm a recent report from NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. David notably stated that Derek is currently healthy, and suggested a team whose colors are “purple and gold,” like the Vikings, would make for an ideal fit. The younger Carr declined to respond, but he certainly seems interested in returning to the NFL in the right situation. The Saints currently retain his contract rights. Whether they would ask for significant trade compensation to acquire him is unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5448-d042-afbc-7ddaf4500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said that the Seahawks could use the franchise tag or the transition tag to keep RB Kenneth Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54a0-d042-afbc-7df2b49b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that “it does sound like Seattle would like to keep him.” In a three-player segment, Rapoport only mentioned the transition tag in relation to Walker. The transition tag is worth less than the franchise tag, but it allows the player to go “shop” his contract offer from the his current team to see if another team will beat it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54a0-d042-afbc-7df2b49b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said the Cowboys “are going to” franchise tag WR George Pickens and could be willing to trade him away for a second-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54aa-d355-a5bd-dffef7f90000</link>
      <description>Rapoport previously suggested a tag-and-trade scenario is possible. This time, he notes that the Cowboys acquired him for a third-round pick, so sending him away for a second would be a nice value increase. NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo also believes the Cowboys will franchise tag Pickens, but made it a point to express consternation over the idea of then trading him away if the Cowboys’ goal is to one day win a Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-54aa-d355-a5bd-dffef7f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Cardinals are expected to hire former Falcons and Texans QB Matt Schaub as QBs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5597-d89c-a1be-ffdf10c60000</link>
      <description>44-year-old Schaub, who retired in 2021, spent 2023 as an offensive analyst for the Falcons but otherwise has zero coaching experience. Arizona would represent a reunion of sorts, as new Cardinals coach Mike LaFleur was on the Falcons’ staff in 2015-16 when Schaub was backing up Matt Ryan. It’s always a bit risky to make a zero-experience coaching hire, but Schaub should know a thing or two about coaching up quarterbacks. This seems like a good get for first-time head man LaFleur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5597-d89c-a1be-ffdf10c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Cardinals will retain DC Nick Rallis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-559c-d629-a1bc-f59dde5a0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ defensive coordinator each of the past three seasons, 32-year-old Rallis was the youngest DC in the league when he was first hired three years ago. He’s had a rollercoaster ride in Arizona thus far, finishing bottom four in scoring defense two of the past three years. Discouraging, though former head coach Jonathan Gannon was largely responsible for his own defense. Rallis evidently impressed enough people inside the building to hang around under new head coach Mike LaFleur. It’s a gamble for a Cardinals team that arguably needed wholesale change, but also an olive branch to players who will at least now have one familiar face sticking around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-559c-d629-a1bc-f59dde5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Giants OLB coach Charlie Bullen will remain with the team in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-571f-d355-a5bd-df5fe2eb0000</link>
      <description>Bullen will have the title of run-game coordinator added to his title for the upcoming season. The 41-year-old coach received interviews for defensive coordinator openings from the Browns, Cowboys, and Cardinals after being passed on for the Giants’ DC role, but opted to remove his name from consideration for the remaining openings. Bullen joined the Giants in 2024 and briefly served as the team’s interim defensive coordinator in 2025 after Shane Bowen was fired in late-November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-571f-d355-a5bd-df5fe2eb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
