<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:05:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Zay Flowers (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d66c-dd4c-afb9-f7edab290000</link>
      <description>Flowers was limited in all three practices this week before being listed as questionable. He will not be joined on the field by Lamar Jackson. Jackson remains out with a hamstring injury, meaning Flowers will be catching passes from Cooper Rush on Sunday. Flowers survived Rush’s first start with five grabs for 72 yards, but the Ravens’ offense imploded and Flowers was targeted just five times. Even as the team’s clear No. 1 receiver, Flowers is barely a WR2 until Jackson returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d66c-dd4c-afb9-f7edab290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronos declared RB Tyler Badie, QB Sam Ehlinger, LB Jonah Elliss, OL Frank Crum, DL Jordan Jackson, and DL Sai’Vion Jones inactive for Week 6 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d855-def2-abdb-dd751dae0000</link>
      <description>Badie is being replaced by Jaleel McLaughlin in the lineup for the first time this year. Badie was dealing with a shoulder injury earlier this week but was cleared on Friday, meaning this is a healthy scratch. It could mean more work for rookie running back RJ Harvey. Given Sean Payton’s mercurial backfield usage this year, we aren’t holding our breath.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d855-def2-abdb-dd751dae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared CB Michael Carter, WR Allen Lazard, RB Khalil Herbert, OT Esa Pole, TE Jelani Woods, DL Tyler Baron, and DL Leonard Taylor inactive for Week 6 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d859-dd4c-afb9-ffd90cf10000</link>
      <description>Carter remains out with a concussion. He did not practice at all this week and was ruled out on Friday. Per usual, the Jets are a great matchup for opposing passers. Bo Nix will look to take advantage this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d859-dd4c-afb9-ffd90cf10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jauan Jennings (rib/ankle) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d85c-dd4c-afb9-ffdd7b2e0000</link>
      <description>Jennings missed Wednesday’s practice but returned for a pair of limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. He was officially listed as questionable for Week 6. With Ricky Pearsall out again, Jennings will operate as the team’s clear No. 1 receiver if he plays a full complement of snaps. There is some re-injury risk with the veteran receiver, but fantasy managers can at least treat him as a WR3 versus the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d85c-dd4c-afb9-ffdd7b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mac Jones (knee/oblique) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d862-db72-a199-fa6b50890000</link>
      <description>Jones was limited in practice throughout the week. 49ers GM John Lynch said on Thursday that Jones should be ok for Week 6’s game, but a questionable tag on Friday cast some doubt on that. Jones now appears to be good to go, though the injuries are piling up for him at an alarming rate. As Schefter notes, it’s possible Brock Purdy is back for Week 7, though we suspect it could be at least one more week before San Francisco’s starter is back on the field. Jones is a high-end QB2 in a potential shootout with the Bucs this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d862-db72-a199-fa6b50890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there is a chance” Brock Purdy (toe) can return for Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d867-dd4c-afb9-ffe713010000</link>
      <description>It’s barely even a report from Schefter. What’s more revealing is the fact that the 49ers aren’t even laundering much optimism to Schefter ahead of their Sunday Night Football date with the Falcons in Week 7. It looks like Mac Jones will get today’s game versus the Bucs and a matchup with Atlanta to create a quarterback controversy in San Francisco. We don’t expect Kyle Shanahan to stick with Jones once Purdy is healthy, but Jones is averaging over 300 yards with two scores as a starter. He is 3-0 this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d867-dd4c-afb9-ffe713010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) is not expected to play in Week 6 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d86c-dd4c-afb9-ffed74840000</link>
      <description>Sanders is still working his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. He got in a full practice on Thursday but returned to a limited status on Friday before being listed as questionable. The Panthers are being cautious with his return, but he should be available in Week 7. Tommy Tremble and Mitchell Evans will split the tight end snaps versus Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d86c-dd4c-afb9-ffed74840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers activated S Malik Mustapha (knee) from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d870-d94a-a79d-d97d6a2e0000</link>
      <description>Mustapha aggrevated a previously torn ACL late last year and opened the 2025 season on the PUP list while recovering. He practiced in full three times this week before being cleared for action. Mustapha appeared in 16 games with a rookie and was credited with 12 starts. He broke up five passes and stole one interception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d870-d94a-a79d-d97d6a2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Brock Bowers (knee) is “unlikely” to play in Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d877-def2-abdb-dd77c18f0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders get their bye in Week 8. Bowers is dealing with a PCL injury and a bone bruise in his knee. He tried to play through them for a few weeks but eventually needed to be sat down. Assuming he misses Week 7, Bowers will get a month to recover from the knee issues. That is likely what should have happened in the first place. Michael Mayer will start in his place until Bowers returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d877-def2-abdb-dd77c18f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports “there have been no serious discussions about benching” Geno Smith.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d87c-dd4c-afb9-fffd7f320000</link>
      <description>Pete Carroll’s “I am not benching Geno Smith” shirt is raising a lot of questions already answered by the shirt. Geno has nine interceptions and 16 sacks this year. He leads the league in picks and isn’t far off in sacks. The Raiders, in turn, are riding a four-game losing streak. Smith will get benched if this level of play continues, but turning to Kenny Pickett isn’t going to turn the Raiders’ season around. Carroll will give Smith every opportunity to right the ship before pulling the plug in favor of Pickett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d87c-dd4c-afb9-fffd7f320000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
