<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MarShawn Lloyd rushed six times for 15 yards and caught 1-for-4 targets for 33 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b455-d05a-adda-bed7575f0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd wasn’t able to find a ton of room as a runner, but did show off his athleticism on the 33-yard reception. The 24-year-old played ahead of Emmanuel Wilson, and while Wilson outrush Lloyd with 33 yards, Wilson did lose a fumble. Right now, there doesn’t seem to be a clear backup answer to Josh Jacobs in Green Bay, and fantasy managers who roster Jacobs may need to look elsewhere for a safety valve behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b455-d05a-adda-bed7575f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Etienne rushed seven times for 18 yards in the Panthers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b469-d05a-adda-beeb9b6f0000</link>
      <description>Etienne also caught one pass for seven yards on his only target. The 21-year-old is attempting to work his way into a role with the Panthers after being selected in the fourth round, but he hasn’t looked the part in these first two preseason games. Chuba Hubbard was always there starter, but Rico Dowdle will be the backup to open the year with Etienne unlikely to see many touches to begin the campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b469-d05a-adda-beeb9b6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed 7 times for 40 yards while catching his lone target for no gain in the Texans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b46f-d05a-adda-beefeab30000</link>
      <description>Marks had a long gain of 12, and looked solid after Nick Chubb exited the game along with the other starters. The former USC tailback has some potential dynasty upside, but isn’t likely to be a helper in redraft leagues this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b46f-d05a-adda-beefeab30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said EDGE Nic Scourton suffered a collapsed lung in Thursday’s practice and will miss some time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b48e-df63-a199-fdaf5aad0000</link>
      <description>According to Canales, Scourton’s injury was worse than initially feared, and the rookie pass rusher is expected to miss some time. We don’t yet know the exact duration, but it sounds like Scourton could be at risk of missing the Week 1 opener against the Jaguars. We should have more insight on his injury and recovery timeline soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b48e-df63-a199-fdaf5aad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 5-of-7 passes for 66 yards in the 49ers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Raiders, adding one yard on his lone carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b445-d90d-a5bd-b65fd8490000</link>
      <description>Purdy started off the series hot, completing his first five pass attempts before the drive stalled in the red zone. He directed his first three passes towards second-year wide receiver Ricky Pearsall, connecting on all three for 42 yards. Both Jauan Jennings and Christian McCaffrey sat this one out but it was good to see a pure connection with Pearsall play out on the field. Kittle was not targeted before the trio departed the game. It is still uncertain whether or not the 49ers will play their starters in the final tuneup game next weekend against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b445-d90d-a5bd-b65fd8490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle was not targeted in the 49ers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b498-d45c-a7fc-b69aaa2e0000</link>
      <description>Kittle started and played with Purdy through the end of the first possession but was not targeted. Purdy connected with second-year wide receiver Ricky Pearsall on his first three pass attempts while both Christian McCaffrey and Jauan Jennings were held out. The fantasy upside for all primary contributors on this offense is considerate as the 49ers look to return to the top five in scoring in 2025 after ranking 14th a season ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b498-d45c-a7fc-b69aaa2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said he hopes to have all four QBs for the team’s preseason finale against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b498-d05a-adda-be9aa20f0000</link>
      <description>Both Shedeur Sanders (oblique) and Kenny Pickett (hamstring) missed Saturday’s preseason game against the Eagles, but Stefanski is already on record saying he is “cautiously optimistic” that Sanders will be back next week. The Browns still have a lot to figure out at quarterback with just 11 days to go until roster cutdown day. It’s not often we see teams roster four quarterbacks, but with so much uncertainty behind Joe Flacco, the Raiders may benefit from rostering a handful of signal-callers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b498-d05a-adda-be9aa20f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Taylor (shoulder) is questionable to return to the 49ers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49b-df63-a199-fdbb92cf0000</link>
      <description>Taylor drew the start in the backfield in the absence of Christian McCaffrey, Isaac Guerendo, and Jordan James, losing six yards on four carries prior to departing with a shoulder injury. While listed questionable to return, it would stand to reason that his day is done. Corey Kiner was the next back up Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49b-df63-a199-fdbb92cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers OL Dominick Puni (knee) was ruled out for preseason Week 2 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-df63-a199-fdbfefaa0000</link>
      <description>Puni is in line to start at right guard for a team looking to return to the top five in scoring after a down 2024 regular season. He was immediately ruled out for the remainder of the contest, making his situation worth monitoring during the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-df63-a199-fdbfefaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Corey Kiner was carted from the field in Saturday’s preseason game due to an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-d45c-a7fc-b69fa3090000</link>
      <description>Kiner is a UDFA from Cincinnati who has been impressing in Niners camp. The rookie broke off a 19-yard run in the second quarter and remained down after the play, only to later be carted from the field. While he’d typically be considered a long shot to make the roster, Kiner may have had an opening given the current state of the 49ers’ backfield. We’ll hopefully know more on his injury soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b49f-d45c-a7fc-b69fa3090000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
