<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussions) is contemplating retirement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f63-dc7a-af9b-cfff7da60000</link>
      <description>Ward is quoted as saying that even a small bump on his head in normal day-to-day activity recently left him with a debilitating migraine, and adds: “I do know going into next season, if I do come back and play again, if I get one more (concussion), I’ll for sure probably retire.” A big-name free agent addition by the Colts this past offseason, Ward was only able to play seven games while dealing with brain injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f63-dc7a-af9b-cfff7da60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB DaRon Bland (foot) said he expects to be fully healthy for Dallas’ offseason program.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f69-d35e-a1bf-cfeb0b490000</link>
      <description>Bland will undergo foot surgery later this week after missing the final three weeks of the season with the foot ailment. Signed to an extension during training camp, Bland had a career-worst (though still fairly solid) 64.5 PFF coverage grade in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f69-d35e-a1bf-cfeb0b490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said the team would like to have Daniel Jones come back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f6e-d35e-a1bf-cfeeaf5a0000</link>
      <description>For his part, Jones also told reporters in a locker room availability that he’d like to be back. Finding the right contract for a quarterback coming off a late-season Achilles tear could be a little difficult, but it sure sounds like Indianapolis’ initial plan is to run back the first part of the 2025 season and hope that the last seven games don’t happen again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f6e-d35e-a1bf-cfeeaf5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco told reporters he isn’t considering retirement and wants to play in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f73-d56e-afff-effb06c60000</link>
      <description>Flacco finished out the season as Cincinnati’s backup quarterback after Joe Burrow returned from injury in Week 13. The soon-to-be 41-year-old told reporters he’s open to staying on as Burrow’s backup, but also open to fielding calls from a team that needed a quarterback next season. It sounds like Flacco has yet another One Last Job season loading for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f73-d56e-afff-effb06c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins QB Tua Tagovailoa said he is open to a “fresh start” elsewhere in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f8b-d56e-afff-efeb2f870000</link>
      <description>“That would be dope. I would be good with it,” Tagovailoa continued, and even confirmed to reporters that he understood that meant a fresh start with a different team. Tagovailoa’s contract appears all but unmovable, and the best-case scenario for him to escape would probably be a post-June 1 release ala Russell Wilson’s exit with the Broncos. This probably isn’t something that will resolve in a hurry, but you rarely hear quarterbacks so eager to leave their current organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f8b-d56e-afff-efeb2f870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested permission to interview Chiefs OC Matt Nagy for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f95-d56e-afff-effdaab20000</link>
      <description>Nagy has obvious connections to the job as Titans GM Mike Borgonzi had been with Nagy in Kansas City before taking over in the Titans’ GM role. It’s hard for us to find good things to say about Nagy given how the Chiefs offense appeared to meaningfully regress as soon as he took over for Eric Bieniemy as offensive coordinator — that doesn’t necessarily mean it’s Nagy’s fault, as Tyreek Hill also left around the same time, but it’s also hard to point to Nagy’s work the last two years as something that should guarantee him interviews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f95-d56e-afff-effdaab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested to interview Broncos DC Vance Joseph for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f99-d56e-afff-eff9d8a30000</link>
      <description>Joseph interviewed with the Jets and was also requested by the Bears last offseason. Denver’s defense slipped a bit in 2025, though it also missed Pat Surtain for several games and dealt with other normal attrition issues. He appears to be one of the hottest candidates of the 2025 offseason and we expect him to get plenty of interviews this cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f99-d56e-afff-eff9d8a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f9c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd6590000</link>
      <description>Expected to draw plenty of interest this cycle after a breakout 2025 season while leading Seattle’s offense to a 10th place finish in DVOA with Sam Darnold at quarterback, Kubiak gets his first interview request from the Falcons. Kubiak, the son of former NFL head coach Gary Kubiak, had previously worked as Saints OC in 2024 and 49ers passing game coordinator in 2023. He’d establish a return to the Shanaclan ways in Atlanta if he were to accept this job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f9c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd6590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested to interview Chiefs DC Steve Spagnuolo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fb7-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe32a0000</link>
      <description>The former Rams head coach went a ghastly 10-38 in his three years at the helm from 2009-2011, but is one of the most-respected defensive coordinators in the league. It’s certainly possible that he could draw multiple interviews this cycle as he was connected to the Giants gig — the place that launched his original HC gig — in November. Spagnuolo’s defense suffered a down year as they just couldn’t muster enough pass rush in 2025, but the Chiefs have finished in the top 10 in points allowed in six of the last seven seasons. He also has an easy link to Titans GM Mike Borgonzi, who used to work in the Chiefs front office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fb7-dc7a-af9b-cfbfe32a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested permission to interview Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fbc-d968-a19b-dffd80b40000</link>
      <description>One of four requests on the day for the Titans, Anarumo was a finalist for the Cardinals job in 2023 when it went to Jonathan Gannon, but saw only defensive coordinator requests last offseason after he was fired. The Colts defense was more scrappy than terrific in 2025 — though they dealt with plenty of injuries at the cornerback position that helps explain some of that — but NFL decision-makers continue to be enamored with Anarumo anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8fbc-d968-a19b-dffd80b40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
