<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts opened the 21-day practice window for CB Charvarius Ward (concussion).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9cf7-d673-a39e-bcf7a0a70000</link>
      <description>Ward sustained a concussion during pre-game warmups ahead of the Colts’ Week 6 game against Arizona and was placed on injured reserve. He could suit up as soon as this week against the Chiefs if he clears the NFL’s concussion protocol and gets the green light from Colts trainers. Ward will be a welcome addition to a Colts secondary that has struggled of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9cf7-d673-a39e-bcf7a0a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s James Palmer reports Falcons QB Michael Penix sustained a partial ACL tear and is out for the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9cfd-d45b-affe-ddfff27b0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons’ season is all but over after injuries to Penix and Drake London (knee) in Week 11’s loss to the Panthers. Kirk Cousins will take over at quarterback and play out the rest of the season unless the Falcons bring in competition for starting snaps. Cousins, who ranks 45th out of 46 qualifying QBs in accuracy this season, is a big downgrade for all Atlanta pass catchers. A dormant passing attack isn’t good new for Bijan Robinson either as Falcons opponents are likely to stack the box with Cousins at the helm. Fantasy managers should downgrade all Falcons players for the final month and change of the fantasy season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9cfd-d45b-affe-ddfff27b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Marvin Harrison, Jr. (appendicitis) has been ruled out for Week 12 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d02-d1e7-a1fa-dfea9cf50000</link>
      <description>That Harrison was ruled out so early in the week could mean he’s iffy for Week 13 as well. He missed Arizona’s Week 11 game against the 49ers after undergoing surgery for appendicitis. In stepped Michael Wilson, who had 15 receptions for 185 yards against the Niners — more catches and yards than MHJ has ever had in an NFL game. Wilson is a must-start fantasy play for as long as Harrison is sidelined. Harrison’s absence doesn’t mean much for Jacoby Brissett, who remains an interesting fantasy play in the pass-heavy Cardinals offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d02-d1e7-a1fa-dfea9cf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals opened the 21-day practice window for RB Trey Benson (knee).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d06-d45b-affe-dd9617600000</link>
      <description>Benson has been sidelined for five Cardinals games after sustaining a serious knee injury in early October, shortly after the team lost James Conner for the season. It’s hard to say what role Benson will return to if he’s able to suit up in Week 12 against the Jaguars, but he’ll likely split the backfield workload with some combination of Bam Knight and Michael Carter. Emari Demercado has been ruled out for Week 12 with an ankle injury he sustained last week. Benson shapes up as a decent flex option if he plays against Jacksonville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d06-d45b-affe-dd9617600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals ruled out RB Emari Demercado (ankle) for Week 12 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d0a-d713-ad9e-fd5e8a0f0000</link>
      <description>Demercado suffered the ankle injury last week against the 49ers and did not return to the game. Bam Knight and Michael Carter proceeded to split the backfield workload. That will be complicated in Week 12 if Trey Benson (knee) is able to return to action. Benson’s 21-day practice window was opened on Wednesday after five weeks on the sideline. Arizona’s backfield will be tough to decipher ahead of Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d0a-d713-ad9e-fd5e8a0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said he hopes Drake London (knee) can play in Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d11-d1e7-a1fa-dffb0afc0000</link>
      <description>Morris confirmed London will miss the Falcons’ Week 12 game against the Saints. The head coach’s comments don’t inspire a lot of confidence that London will be able to suit up in Week 13. With Michael Penix (knee) done for the season and the team’s postseason hopes dwindling, the Falcons will likely be cautious with their superstar wideout. With London sidelined, Darnell Mooney becomes the team’s WR1. Kyle Pitts should see an increase in targets as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d11-d1e7-a1fa-dffb0afc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said QB Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d27-d1e7-a1fa-dfef1b600000</link>
      <description>Glenn confirmed that Justin Fields would once again be benched after his abysmal Week 11 outing against New England. Taylor will take over the Jets offense for now, starting with a tough matchup against a now-healthy Baltimore defense. Taylor’s insertion into the starting lineup likely means more drop back volume for Jets pass catchers. It could make Mason Taylor and perhaps AD Mitchell interesting in deeper formats, along with John Metchie, who last week against the Patriots had three catches for 45 yards and a touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d27-d1e7-a1fa-dfef1b600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Giants QB Jaxson Dart (concussion) is “trending” toward playing in Week 12 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d2b-d45b-affe-ddbfc2430000</link>
      <description>“Barring any setbacks,” Dart should be back for Week 12, Raanan added. Dart remains in the league’s concussion protocol following his Week 10 head injury against the Bears. His rushing role in the New York offense will be under scrutiny in the coming weeks after he took a series of massive hits as a runner in the weeks leading up to his Week 10 brain injury. More than half of Dart’s fantasy production this season has come on the ground. He’ll be a fringe starting option in 12-team formats if he suits up against Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d2b-d45b-affe-ddbfc2430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d40-d713-ad9e-fd5425a20000</link>
      <description>Thibodeaux missed the Giants’ Week 11 game against the Packers with a shoulder injury, and unless he can log a late-week practice this week, he’s likely out for Week 12 against the Lions. New York’s defense remains one of the league’s worst, with or without Thibodeaux. The Lions offense should make quick work out of the Giants this Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d40-d713-ad9e-fd5425a20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
