<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Damarri Mathis (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ada-dbe3-a9bb-3adbc0b10000</link>
      <description>Mathis had been claimed off waivers by the Panthers at last cuts, but unfortunately tore his ACL on his first day of practice with his new club. He’ll enter free agency this offseason and should compete for a roster spot somewhere as long as this is a relatively clean ACL tear. He was a depth piece for the Panthers so his loss shouldn’t change much about their cornerback rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ada-dbe3-a9bb-3adbc0b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Myles Garrett (hip) will play against the Bengals in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1adf-de13-afdd-5edfa2650000</link>
      <description>The Browns will need Garrett to hunt against the Bengals to have any chance of an upset win. Ultimately, he’s not on the final injury report. Garrett’s missed practice Thursday was surprising, but ultimately didn’t put his status in any real jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1adf-de13-afdd-5edfa2650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) will not play in Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ace-d332-a1fd-9efec8340000</link>
      <description>Things have been trending in this direction for a while. Gonzalez has been sidelined with a hamstring injury since late July and missed the first two days of practice to start the week. The Patriots have been holding off on predicting a return date for their star corner, but the fact that he avoided the injured reserve list to start the season suggested the team thinks he can return sometime during the first four weeks of the season. The team will now set its sights on a Week 2 return against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ace-d332-a1fd-9efec8340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L’Jarius Sneed (knee) is questionable for the Titans’ Week 1 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ae2-dbe3-a9bb-3af3f4670000</link>
      <description>Sneed was again out there on Friday, so he’s likely on the optimistic side of questionable. We’re not sure how much the Titans should expect from Sneed after all his time off, but they have to be hoping he can at least help contain Courtland Sutton and company on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ae2-dbe3-a9bb-3af3f4670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is questionable for Week 1 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1afc-d332-a1fd-9efe997d0000</link>
      <description>Mooney logged three limited practices this week, which is a good sign for his Week 1 availability despite the questionable designation. Fantasy managers in deeper leagues will still want to keep an eye out for his name popping up on the inactive list when they’re announced 90 minutes before kickoff, but Mooney has been practicing in some capacity for the last two weeks. If he’s unable to go against the Buccaneers, backup Casey Washington is listed as next in line on the team’s depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1afc-d332-a1fd-9efe997d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Heyward (business) told reporters he’s preparing to play in Week 1 against the Jets but “we’ll see.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b0b-db7b-a5dd-bb0f22c20000</link>
      <description>It sounds like this is still uncertain, as Heyward looks for a contract adjustment. What is clear is that Heyward is healthy as he practiced in full yesterday and Thursday’s absence was a veteran’s day off per the injury report. If Heyward doesn’t play on Sunday, it would be good news for the Jets run-heavy attack in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b0b-db7b-a5dd-bb0f22c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed CB Zyon McCollum to a three-year, $48 million extension with $35.4 million in guarantees.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b26-d332-a1fd-9f36207a0000</link>
      <description>McCollum is an ascending player after posting a 66.1 PFF coverage grade in 2024 during 757 coverage snaps. He was entering the final year of his deal and looks likely to be a short-term fixture for the Buccaneers outside. McCollum had asked for an extension in training camp and cashes in just before the start of Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b26-d332-a1fd-9f36207a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints ruled out EDGE Chase Young (calf) for Week 1 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b0d-de13-afdd-5fcf4f740000</link>
      <description>Young’s absence is a tough loss to stomach for a transitioning Saints’ defense. Veteran EDGE Cameron Jordan will start in Young’s stead. CB Alontae Taylor was cleared to play after successfully rehabbing a groin injury suffered on August 8th. Saints OG Trevor Penning (toe) will also miss the game, weakening the left side of New Orleans’ offensive line. Although the Saints’ first-round rookie LT Kelvin Banks Jr. can be expected to hold his own, the coaching staff would undoubtedly prefer to have a proven veteran on the field next to him. Penning is backed up by former Titans starter, OG Dillon Radunz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b0d-de13-afdd-5fcf4f740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) is doubtful to play in Week 1 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b1e-dbe3-a9bb-3b5f14300000</link>
      <description>Brutal. Thomas started the week off with limited participation, which put him on track to play. He was downgraded on Thursday, but head coach Brian Daboll indicated Thomas would practice in some capacity on Friday. Apparently, it wasn’t enough. Thomas will continue rehabbing last season’s Lisfranc injury, with the goal of suiting up in Week 2 against the Cowboys. Former Browns OT James Hudson III is Thomas’ backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b1e-dbe3-a9bb-3b5f14300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Harmon (knee) is out for the Steelers’ Week 1 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b3b-db7b-a5dd-bb3f37df0000</link>
      <description>As expected. Though Harmon didn’t head to injured reserve, he doesn’t look close to playing at the moment after missing all three practices this week. Harmon’s Week 2 status is likely also in some question at this point. Yahya Black, Isaiahh Loudermilk, and Daniel Ekuale will take on bigger roles in Week 1 with the rookie defensive tackle out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b3b-db7b-a5dd-bb3f37df0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
