<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave (back) is active for Week 17 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65ca-dc7a-af9b-efff789f0000</link>
      <description>Olave was a surprise addition to the injury report on Friday. The team listed him as a limited participant and gave him a questionable designation. It was quickly reported that he was expected to play. Coming off a career day with 148 yards and two scores versus the Jets, Olave is inching closer to the WR1 ranks as the season nears its end. Inactive for the Saints are S Ugo Amadi, DT Bryan Bresee, WR Mason Tipton, CB Rejzohn Wright, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, RB Alvin Kamara, and OG Cesar Ruiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65ca-dc7a-af9b-efff789f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared OL Aaron Brewer, S Minkah Fitzpatrick, OT Kendall Lamm, LB Derrick McLendon, QB Tua Tagovailoa, and WR Nick Westbrook-Ikhine inactive for Week 17 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65ca-dc7a-af9b-efffc0760000</link>
      <description>Brewer is Dolphins’ starting center and entered Sunday questionable with a neck injury. He is officially out for Week 17 against the Bucs. Tagovailoa will be the team’s emergency third quarterback again, while Fitzpatrick was ruled out with a calf injury on Friday and Westbrook-Ikhine is a notable healthy scratch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65ca-dc7a-af9b-efffc0760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) is active for Week 17 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d1-d35e-a1bf-65d386fd0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter has reported MHJ will be on a snap count, making him a volatile WR3 for what fantasy managers are hoping will be a shootout in Cincinnati. Inactive for the Cardinals are K Joshua Karty, S Budda Baker, CB Kei’Trel Clark, CB Kalen King, TE Pharaoh Brown, OL Evan Brown and DL P.J. Mustipher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d1-d35e-a1bf-65d386fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin is active for Week 17 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d56e-afff-e7fa2d680000</link>
      <description>It was reported earlier that Fannin was expected to play after he was added to Friday’s injury report due to a groin injury. The rookie tight end has been a focal point of the Browns’ passing game for much of the season and has averaged 8.4 targets per game in during Shedeur Sanders’ time as a starter. Fantasy managers can lock him in as their TE1 for championship week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d56e-afff-e7fa2d680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (illness) is active for Carolina’s Week 17 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d968-a19b-7df3091a0000</link>
      <description>Those with the luxury of playing a similar receiver will likely want to do so as McMillan was added to the injury report with an illness on Sunday and the Seahawks defense wasn’t exactly an enticing matchup anyway, but most fantasy managers will probably be sticking with a sick McMillan. Hopefully he winds up being sick (complimentary) against Seattle today. Inactive for the Panthers are: DT Tershawn Wharton (hamstring), WR Hunter Renfrow, S Demani Richardson, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte and TE James Mitchell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d968-a19b-7df3091a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared S Jerrick Reed II, OL Brandon Crenshaw-Dickson, OL Garrett Dellinger, OL Drew Moss, and DL Cam Horsley inactive for Week 17 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d968-a19b-7df393070000</link>
      <description>The Titans only had two players listed as questionable heading into the weekend: outside linebacker Ali Gaye and cornerback Micah Robinson. Both players are active for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-d968-a19b-7df393070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared T Tristan Wirfs, OLB Anthony Nelson, WR Sterling Shepard, S Rashad Wisdom, LB John Bullock, and QB Connor Bazelak inactive for Week 17 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-dc7a-af9b-efff2d0c0000</link>
      <description>The Bucs declared Wirfs out with a toe injury; they will likely lean on Graham Barton to shift over to left tackle in Wirfs’ absence. Also out is Anthony Nelson (knee), who did not practice this week. Sterling Shepard is a healthy scratch with the Bucs’ receiving group now fully healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d2-dc7a-af9b-efff2d0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LT Charles Cross, S Coby Bryant, QB Jalen Milroe, OL Bryce Cabeldue, OL Mason Richman, EDGE Jared Ivey and NT Brandon Pili.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-d35e-a1bf-65d75df00000</link>
      <description>Cross has not played since Week 15 as the Seahawks look to get his hamstring injury right ahead of the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-d35e-a1bf-65d75df00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared QB Will Howard, WR Calvin Austin, RB Kaleb Johnson, CB Brandin Echols, CB James Pierre, OG Isaac Seumalo, and LB T.J. Watt inactive for Week 17 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-dc7a-af9b-efff71b40000</link>
      <description>With DK Metcalf also suspended for this one, the Steelers will need to lean heavily on their tight ends in the pass-catching game, while Adam Thielen and Marquez Valdes-Scantling could also see an uptick in targets. Watt was ruled out before the weekend but was able to practice in a limited capacity this week. Watt should have a good shot at returning in Week 18 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-dc7a-af9b-efff71b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said T.J. Watt (lung) is expected to play in the Steelers’ next meaningful game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-d56e-afff-e7fd6a0b0000</link>
      <description>The Steelers can win the AFC North today with a victory over the Browns. That would lock them in as the No. 4 seed in the AFC. It would also make their Week 18 date with the Ravens meaningless, and the Steelers would obviously choose to hold him out for that contest. If they lose today, Watt would seemingly be on the field for an AFC North title match versus Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-65d5-d56e-afff-e7fd6a0b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
