<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 22:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt (lung) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b6c-dc7a-af9b-ffff33cc0000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin previously said Watt needs to get in a week of full practices before being cleared. His limited participation is encouraging, but he is not yet guaranteed to suit up on game day, which means Watt may have played his last snap of the season already. The Steelers (9-7) and Ravens (8-8) are playing for a trip to the postseason on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b6c-dc7a-af9b-ffff33cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (knee/ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b6f-d968-a19b-7bff714c0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from a Wednesday DNP. St. Brown will have some re-injury/blowout risk on Sunday if he just isn’t able to gut it out in a meaningless game against the Bears, but he appears to be trending towards playing. He likely belongs on the WR1 line if he is able to play, though perhaps as more of a mid-range option given the potential of a mid-game shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b6f-d968-a19b-7bff714c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (hand) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b71-dc7a-af9b-ffff1beb0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy’s rehab continues to progress. He is on track to start one final time this season. McCarthy’s accuracy and decision-making have left something to be desired this season, but he can sometimes scramble his way to fantasy success, keeping him on the QB1/2 borderline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b71-dc7a-af9b-ffff1beb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b72-d35e-a1bf-7ff2ebe00000</link>
      <description>Fannin was unsure of his potential availability when asked about it following Sunday’s win and doesn’t appear likely to play. David Njoku (knee/NIR-personal), as well, remained out. It looks to be wheels up for Blake Whiteheart and Sal Cannella szn in Week 18, though we will check in on Friday to be sure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b72-d35e-a1bf-7ff2ebe00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b71-d35e-a1bf-7ff3243e0000</link>
      <description>Jones has played through myriad injuries this season, so even with two absences, he still has a chance to play. That said, it would make sense for the Vikings to shut him down. Jones is 31 years old and remains under contract in 2026. His backup, RB Jordan Mason (ankle), upgraded to full participation today. He would start in Jones’ stead if the veteran player cannot go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b71-d35e-a1bf-7ff3243e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Jordan Mason (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b58-d968-a19b-7bf93cb30000</link>
      <description>With RB Aaron Jones (hip) sidelined by a hip injury, Mason has a chance to start. Vikings No. 3 RB Zavier Scott would likely play in passing situations, if this is indeed, the case. Mason would be on the RB3/FLEX radar. The Vikings face the playoff-bound Packers in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b58-d968-a19b-7bf93cb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE T.J. Hockenson (shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b72-d968-a19b-7bf3242f0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson sat out in Week 17 against the Lions and he appears likely to sit out this week as well. Hockenson’s backup, TE Josh Oliver, should not be in re-draft lineups against the Packers even if Hockenson cannot play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b72-d968-a19b-7bf3242f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b88-d56e-afff-ffe8cab20000</link>
      <description>Wicks seems highly unlikely to be available for his team’s Week 18 game against the Vikings. The team could choose to declare him inactive even if he clears the NFL’s concussion protocol. The Packers are already locked into the NFC’s No. 7 playoff seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b88-d56e-afff-ffe8cab20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b85-d35e-a1bf-7fc78bd90000</link>
      <description>The Packers have already shut down Nos. 1 and 2 QBs, Jordan Love, who cleared the NFL’s concussion protocol, and Malik Willis (right shoulder/hamstring), for Week 18. We expect them to do the same with their key skill position players. Packers No. 2 RB Emanuel Wilson has been a meaningful contributor this season. If the Packers choose to keep Jacobs and Wilson out this week, No. 3 RB Chris Brooks could be the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b85-d35e-a1bf-7fc78bd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b8b-d968-a19b-7bfbaa6a0000</link>
      <description>Adams sat out yesterday, and head coach Sean McVay has already said he does not expect Adams to play this week. The Rams are currently in the NFC’s No. 6 playoff seed. If they beat the Cardinals and the Seahawks beat the 49ers, the Rams can jump up to the No. 5 seed. The improvement could be helpful, but may not be worth risking Adams’ playoff availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b8b-d968-a19b-7bfbaa6a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
