<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine rushed 14 times for 39 yards in the Bengals’ Week 13 win over the Ravens, adding two catches for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8e0-d6c4-abfb-dee365e40000</link>
      <description>Perine missed the previous two games with an ankle injury but was cleared to play early this week. The Bengals immediately split their backfield in two, giving Perine just one fewer carry than Chase Brown. The latter, of course, was far more efficient, running for 5.2 yards per carry compared to 2.8 for Perine. Perine also coughed up a red zone fumble late in the game. He still saw carries on the next drive, meaning his coaches weren’t deterred by the mistake. Perine doesn’t hold much fantasy value heading into Week 14, but he will be a thorn in the side of fantasy managers hoping for a better workload from Brown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8e0-d6c4-abfb-dee365e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrei Iosivas caught 1-of-2 targets for 29 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 13 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8e6-d90e-a9da-dfef23af0000</link>
      <description>Tee Higgins was out this week, freeing up some work for the Bengals’ depth receivers. Despite Mitchell Tinsley seeing nine targets to Iosivas’s two, Iosivas ultimately went for more yards and scored the only receiving touchdown for a Cincinnati wide receiver today. Higgins missed five games in 2024. Iosivas only caught eight passes in those games, but he found the end zone three times. Higgins missed this game with a concussion, meaning he could be back for Week 14. Iosivas won’t be on the fantasy radar if that happens. He will be a touchdown-or-bust WR6 if Higgins is out again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8e6-d90e-a9da-dfef23af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitchell Tinsley caught 2-of-9 targets for 22 yards in the Bengals’ Week 13 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8ea-db57-afda-defaee790000</link>
      <description>With Tee Higgins out because of a concussion this week, Tinsley ultimately operated as the team’s No. 2 receiver, just like he did in Week 12. He earned plenty of targets, but the young wideout failed to come up with any of his difficult targets, only bringing in the layups Joe Burrow threw his way. Higgins could be back next week. Even if he isn’t, the Bengals will likely try to get Andrei Iosivas more involved after this inefficient performance from Tinsley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8ea-db57-afda-defaee790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Gesicki caught 2-of-4 targets for 19 yards in the Bengals’ Week 13 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8ef-d82c-a79a-fbff2c3a0000</link>
      <description>Gesicki was the leader of a tight-end-by-committee in Week 13. Tanner Hudson, Drew Sample, and Noah Fant all caught one pass on two targets. Hudson’s only grab was a toe-tapping touchdown from 14 yards out. Tee Higgins was out with a concussion this week, but Geiscki did little to earn more work if Higgins misses another game. He will barely be on the TE2 radar even if Higgins remains out for Week 14 versus the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8ef-d82c-a79a-fbff2c3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 10 times for 60 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals, adding one catch for 44 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8f3-d82c-a79a-fbf755d20000</link>
      <description>For fantasy managers, it’s a shame the Ravens couldn’t keep this game close, because The Big Dog was ready to feast on Thanksgiving. He got things going early with a 28-yard score on Baltimore’s opening drive. That was about it for his night. The Ravens quickly spiraled out of control on the back of five turnovers, making it impossible for the Ravens to establish a ground game as they played from behind. Henry still made his presence known by turning a routine check-down into a 44-yard catch at the end of the third quarter, but the game script turned a potential blow-up spot into a usable floor week from the stud back. The good news is that the Ravens get the Steelers at home next week. Henry will keep his spot in the RB1 ranks as the Ravens look to course-correct in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8f3-d82c-a79a-fbf755d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed two times for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals, adding two catches for 12 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8f8-db57-afda-defa8a0f0000</link>
      <description>Mitchell rewarded fantasy managers bold enough to start him with an 18-yard touchdown sprint late in the third quarter. Those fantasy managers should likely take their chips off the table after this game. Even with Justice Hill out this week, Mitchell split the backup duties with Rasheen Ali. Ali easily out-snapped Mitchell and saw four carries, though three of them came on the team’s final drive. Despite scoring in Week 13, Mitchell isn’t really on the FLEX radar heading into a Week 14 matchup with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8f8-db57-afda-defa8a0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely caught 5-of-6 targets for 95 yards in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8fc-db57-afda-defe87780000</link>
      <description>Likely led the Ravens in all receiving categories. He set a season-high in receiving yards and put 38 yards between himself and the team’s No. 2 pass-catcher, Mark Andrews. Likely broke chunk plays seemingly at will, gashing the Bengals for gains of 43 and 30 yards in this game. All of his hard work, however, was undone by one costly mistake. On his 43-yard catch and run, Likely fought his way toward the end zone, only to cough up the ball inches short of the goal line. The ball went out of bounds in the end zone, resulting in a turnover. The Ravens didn’t go away from Likely after this, but it’s still a frustrating play from a player who hasn’t found his stride this year. Still splitting work with Mark Andrews, Likely will be stuck in the TE2 ranks for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c8fc-db57-afda-defe87780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 4-of-6 targets for 47 yards in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c901-d82c-a79a-fb95bd750000</link>
      <description>Andrew tied Isaiah Likely for second on the team in targets. The two tight ends each earned 19 percent target shares. Andrews ran more routes and was used as a check-down option, while Likely saw more downfield work, resulting in a team-high 95 yards from the explosive tight end. Neither player can be declared the team’s clear TE1 and the Ravens are struggling on offense as Lamar Jackson nurses various injuries. Andrews will hold the edge in the fantasy rankings next week, though both tight ends will sit outside the top 12 options versus Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c901-d82c-a79a-fb95bd750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman failed to catch his only target in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c906-d82c-a79a-fb9687d10000</link>
      <description>Bateman made his return from the high-ankle sprain that cost him two games. He ran plenty of routes, but Lamar Jackson barely noticed him, throwing just one pass his way. He should get more involved next week as he continues to put distance between himself and the ankle issue, but fantasy managers cannot trust him until they see some production. He will sit somewhere in the WR5/6 ranks for Week 14 versus the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c906-d82c-a79a-fb9687d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 2-of-7 targets for six yards in the Ravens’ Week 13 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c909-d90e-a9da-df0f3d2c0000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Flowers’ seven targets led the team. He logged a 22 percent target share. The bad news? Everything else. The Ravens tried to get Flowers going downfield, but he and Lamar Jackson were seemingly never on the same page. The two-time MVP regularly sailed passes to Flowers and was visibly frustrated with the situation late in the game. To top things off, Flowers coughed up a fumble late in the fourth quarter, putting to rest any hope of a Baltimore comeback. Better days should be ahead for the young wideout, but he was looking like a potential WR1 a month into the season. Now he is fighting for a spot in the WR2 ranks heading into Week 14 versus Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c909-d90e-a9da-df0f3d2c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
