<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3ef-d968-a19b-fbffcfef0000</link>
      <description>Shula led the Rams defense to a top-5 defensive DVOA rating despite being the lowest-paid defense in the NFL. It was always inevitable he’d emerge as an interview candidate this cycle. The Titans figure to be the first of many teams talking to Shula despite his team currently being in the playoffs. The Rams head to Charlotte for their Wild Card round game on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3ef-d968-a19b-fbffcfef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f1-d35e-a1bf-e7f3f13b0000</link>
      <description>We had Kubiak down with interviews requests from the Falcons, Giants, Cardinals, and Raiders before today. He scores one with Baltimore on the heels of turning his Sam Darnold-led offense into a top-10 DVOA offense this past season. It would not seem that Kubiak’s system would be the best use of Lamar Jackson’s ability to scramble and buy time to make plays, but the Shanaclan has roots everywhere and it wouldn’t necessarily limit Jackson from a fantasy perspective if Kubiak was the play here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f1-d35e-a1bf-e7f3f13b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers G Ben Bredeson (knee) is expected to be fully recovered for the team’s offseason program.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f4-d968-a19b-fbf5ea0a0000</link>
      <description>The guard, entering his age-28 season in 2026, was placed on season-ending IR in early December. This is good news for the Bucs as they try to retool from their end-of-season disaster, as Bredeson is a bit of a stalwart for them on the interior line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f4-d968-a19b-fbf5ea0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OC Todd Monken said “it was a great three-year run” and “I wish them nothing but the best” when asked about his time in Baltimore.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f6-d35e-a1bf-e7f6e6f30000</link>
      <description>Not that this is unexpected news, but Monken does appear to be very publicly saying that he won’t return to his post as Ravens OC after the firing of John Harbaugh. Monken has a history of coordinating good NFL offenses and would be an interesting pickup for a number of teams in need of a good play caller on that side of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f6-d35e-a1bf-e7f6e6f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested to interview Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f9-d968-a19b-fbf97acb0000</link>
      <description>It sure doesn’t feel like Brady has had his best season as Bills fans have watched the team struggle to put together any kind of passing attack beyond Josh Allen Hero Ball, but he apparently remains top of mind for Baltimore. To his credit, the Bills did generate top-of-league rushing yardage for James Cook this year. As a fantasy football website, we’d love to see that kind of commitment to Derrick Henry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3f9-d968-a19b-fbf97acb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots DT Khyiris Tonga (foot) won’t play in New England’s Wild Card game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3fd-d35e-a1bf-e7ff7c420000</link>
      <description>The good news for the Patriots is that Robert Spillane (ankle) practiced in full and appears likely to play on Sunday, giving them one of their two big run stuffers back against the Chargers. Mike Vrabel also said that OLB/DE Harold Landry (knee) was questionable for the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3fd-d35e-a1bf-e7ff7c420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) is questionable for New England’s Wild Card game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3ff-dc7a-af9b-effff4130000</link>
      <description>Boutte was added to the injury report with a limited session on Thursday and is now in some question for this week’s game. Kyle Williams is probably who the Patriots would turn to alongside Stefon Diggs and Pop Douglas if Boutte couldn’t go. New England’s outside receiver room has taken a beating of late with Mack Hollins already on injured reserve and Boutte struggling to play for most of the last four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3ff-dc7a-af9b-effff4130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) is practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a402-d56e-afff-e6eaa82b0000</link>
      <description>He is spotted wearing a “big brace” on his right ankle. It seems like Hampton is going to make the questionable line despite not practicing in either of the first two sessions of the week, but beyond that we couldn’t speculate much on his chances at playing time at this moment. We’ll get a second update later today when the injury report comes down, but Hampton is officially on shaky ground as a Playoff Best Ball/DFS play this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a402-d56e-afff-e6eaa82b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders interviewed Cardinals WR coach and passing-game coordinator Drew Terrell for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3fb-d35e-a1bf-e7fbb7590000</link>
      <description>Terrell, then Commanders receivers coach, got a request for the Cardinals OC job before coming over to join Jonathan Gannon’s staff when Ron Rivera was fired. It sounds like with the Cardinals in the midst of a regime change of their own, Terrell has a chance to be considered for their OC role or perhaps reprise his passing-game coordinator role for the Commanders. They also interviewed in-house candidates, some of which are speculated to be David Blough, Brian Johnson, and Anthony Lynn, for the vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a3fb-d35e-a1bf-e7fbb7590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports John Harbaugh is “likely” to interview with the Giants next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a409-dc7a-af9b-efbf989d0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh is probably awaiting to see if any other openings hit before he figures out his full plan of attack, but with nine teams already interested it seems safe to say that Harbaugh will be the one candidate this cycle who can name his own terms about who he’d like to work with, and seems likely to land an eight-figure contract when it is all said and done. Raanan adds that the Giants “want Harbaugh badly.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a409-dc7a-af9b-efbf989d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
