<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:18:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 3-of-3 targets for 37 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40c8-d355-a5bd-cfdc14930000</link>
      <description>It was a Super Bowl night to forget for Diggs, with the only silver lining being the same was true for every other Patriot. Officially in the mercenary stage of his career, 32-year-old Diggs signed a three-year deal with the Pats as he completed his recovery from a torn ACL. In reality playing on more of a one-year contract — Diggs can be cut loose with relatively little pain for the Pats — he was the No. 1 wideout in an offense where that didn’t mean as much as it might elsewhere. Diggs was just 71st in Pro Football Focus’ “route percentage,” with Mack Hollins and Kayshon Boutte both playing more snaps when healthy. Diggs did squeak by 1,000 yards, but he contributed only four touchdowns. He did manage a strong 2.42 yards per route run. Nevertheless, Diggs is getting up in age and becoming an increasing off-the-field distraction. It’s quite possible the Pats decide to make his Boston tenure one-and-done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40c8-d355-a5bd-cfdc14930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught 1-of-5 targets for 21 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40ca-d042-afbc-7dda9de20000</link>
      <description>The down-field opportunities just weren’t there for a Patriots offense that got dominated whistle to whistle. Boutte’s 33/551/6 statline mostly repeated his 2024 marks, though he doubled his touchdowns and added three yards to his YPC (16.7). Boutte was a legit role-playing weapon down the field for the Pats’ rotational receiver corps. That’s despite Mack Hollins serving much the same role. Hollins is signed for 2026 but is going on 33 and is more known for his blocking than pass catching. There should be an opportunity for 24-year-old (in May) Boutte to take another step forward in the final year of his rookie deal, though he seems to be maxing out as a situational deep threat. He should be rostered in dynasty, but is not the highest-upside option despite his relative youth and elite quarterback play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40ca-d042-afbc-7dda9de20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught 4-of-8 targets for 78 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40cc-d89c-a1be-efdfbc180000</link>
      <description>Hollins was the only Pat to post an above-average box score in a title tilt where their offensive line got utterly dominated. Battling with Kayshon Boutte for the Patriots’ primary down-field role, 32-year-old Hollins posted the second highest yardage total of his career (550) despite missing two games with injury. Playing on his fifth time in five years, his 46 receptions were also his second most. Excellent stuff, though Hollins’ most notable contribution remains his blocking. Signed for $2.9 million in 2026, Hollins should be back with the Pats, though his salary is not guaranteed. Although the Patriots had success with this year’s motley receiving crew, upgrading the corps figures to be an offseason priority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40cc-d89c-a1be-efdfbc180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 5-of-7 targets for 45 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d1-d89c-a1be-efdfb4200000</link>
      <description>A third-year sixth-rounder, Douglas’ production fell off even as the Patriots’ offense ascended. His 31 grabs were a new career low by 18. This, as the “target competition” was Stefon Diggs, Hunter Henry, etc. MVP runner-up Drake Maye likes to throw deep, and Douglas’ game is middle-of-the-field chess play. The pint-sized slot man has managed to stay healthy in back-to-back seasons, no small feat as he enters the final year of his rookie deal. However, a career that once looked like it could turn into a “Wan’Dale Robinson situation” is now little more than a small guy playing a smaller role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d1-d89c-a1be-efdfb4200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams caught 1-of-2 targets for seven yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d3-d629-a1bc-f0df535f0000</link>
      <description>A third-round rookie hype merchant in an offense many were expecting to be better, Williams ended up struggling to get on the field, catching just two passes across his first nine games. He was more involved down the stretch, but still finished the regular campaign with all of 10 grabs. He turned that limited work into more than 20 yards per catch and three touchdowns, but Williams was a strict role player in an offense that has fellow field-stretchers Mack Hollins and Kayshon Boutte. With both those wideouts likely back for 2026, Williams could have a difficult time commanding a bigger role. He turns 24 in November, making him a lower-upside hold in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d3-d629-a1bc-f0df535f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 4-of-4 targets for 54 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Super Bowl LX win over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d4-d629-a1bc-f0dda9590000</link>
      <description>The No. 121 overall pick of the 2024 Draft, Barner had a solid rookie season but upgraded as a sophomore, turning his initial 30/245/4 line into 52/519/6. The 23-year-old was a consistent big-play threat down the stretch, and finished third on his Super Bowl squad in yards. Quietly, he was also the TE14 by total PPR points. Considering his youth and steady early-career trajectory, Barner could easily ascend to TE1 status in 2026. He is an exciting dynasty league asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d4-d629-a1bc-f0dda9590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo was held without a catch in the Seahawks’ Super Bowl LX victory over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d6-d629-a1bc-f0df11130000</link>
      <description>Arroyo was not targeted as he made his postseason debut after battling a knee injury. The No. 50 overall pick of the draft, Arroyo ended up languishing behind second-year fourth-rounder AJ Barner. Arroyo caught more than two passes one time all year, and was a non-factor for the season’s stretch run. Arroyo is young (23 in April) at a complex position, but so is Barner. Arroyo’s draft pedigree means he should maintain some long-term benefit of the doubt in dynasty leagues, but 2026 seems unlikely to be the year he breaks out in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d6-d629-a1bc-f0df11130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 3-of-5 targets for 31 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d7-d629-a1bc-f0dfde8a0000</link>
      <description>Flying under the radar as always, 31-year-old Henry finished with a career-high 768 yards. His 60 receptions tied for his second most, while his seven scores were his most since 2021. Only Stefon Diggs had more receiving yards on the Pats. Although this is a skill corps that needs to be upgraded, Henry should remain an integral part of it for 2026. He is headed into the final year of his contract, and could be a candidate for a short offseason extension. The TE9 by total PPR points this season, Henry will remain in the TE9-12 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d7-d629-a1bc-f0dfde8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Hooper caught 2-of-3 targets for 10 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d9-d042-afbc-7ddb33c30000</link>
      <description>Hooper’s second season in New England produced the second fewest yards (263) of his 10-year career. The lowest total came in 2023 in Las Vegas. Hooper has a reliable pair of hands for a backup, but has never been a reliable scorer. He still possesses some down-field juice up the seam, but Hooper’s returns will continue to diminish. He is set for free agency in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d9-d042-afbc-7ddb33c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak confirmed he will be taking the Raiders’ head coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-429b-d042-afbc-7fdb772e0000</link>
      <description>Shortly after leading the Seahawks to their second Super Bowl title in franchise history, Kubiak confirmed his decision to join the Raiders with NFL Network’s Stacey Dales. Kubiak joined the Seahawks as their offensive coordinator last offseason and immediately propelled them to the top of the league. Seattle’s offense ranked third in points score and eight in total yards, and was buoyed by an efficient passing game that ranked second in net yards per pass attempt (7.6) this season. He’ll take on a tough challenge with the Raiders, but will hopefully benefit from having the No. 1 overall pick, which is expected to be used on Indiana QB Fernando Mendoza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-429b-d042-afbc-7fdb772e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
