<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 4-of-6 targets for 73 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6e-db57-afda-df7ef14e0000</link>
      <description>Henry led the team in receiving on a night quarterback Drake Maye attempted only 31 passes due to positive game script throughout, aided by a 94-yard punt return touchdown from Marcus Jones. His fantasy day could have been much bigger had a 30-yard touchdown grab in the fourth quarter not been called back by offsetting penalties. That pass would have also pushed Maye over 300 yards through the air for the first time in his career. Henry remains a back end TE1 but will head to his bye in Week 14 before a rematch with the division rival Bills in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6e-db57-afda-df7ef14e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught 4-of-5 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd71-d82c-a79a-fff5de6e0000</link>
      <description>Boutte showcased the preseason work he put in with quarterback Drake Maye with his three-yard touchdown in the first quarter, a beautifully placed fade against man coverage to the back corner of the end zone. He would not see his number called frequently from there on out considering the low total pass volume from the Patriots, highlighting his status as a true touchdown-or-bust fantasy option while the other skill position players remain healthy. His next chance to return usable counting stats comes in Week 15 against the Bills following the team’s Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd71-d82c-a79a-fff5de6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams caught his only target for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd75-d82c-a79a-fff502a50000</link>
      <description>The electric rookie made the most of his lone target, reeling in a 33-yard dime from Drake Maye on an over-the-shoulder catch down the sideline in the end zone to extend the team’s lead to 24-7. It was not the first time the downfield threat made a big play, but also highlights his status as a boom-or-bust fantasy asset unless there is an injury ahead of him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd75-d82c-a79a-fff502a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught all three targets for 33 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd77-d90e-a9da-df7f8d630000</link>
      <description>The diminutive receiver made the most of the opportunities he received but remains unlikely to see significant weekly volume, keeping him from legitimate consideration in fantasy circles for the time being. That said, he could be busier against the nickel-heavy Bills defense in Week 15 following the team’s Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd77-d90e-a9da-df7f8d630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd79-d82c-a79a-fffd8c700000</link>
      <description>The modest target total was primarily a product of extremely positive game script following a 94-yard punt return touchdown by Marcus Jones in the first quarter, which the team would add to before the first frame was complete. They would eventually take a 30-7 lead into the break, muting the offensive production from all skill position players in the second half. Diggs continues to operate as one of many primary contributors in an offense built around packaged mismatches, meaning he is unlikely to return elite fantasy ceiling without an injury to another skill position player. Up next for Diggs is a matchup against one of his former teams when the Patriots take on the Bills following their Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd79-d82c-a79a-fffd8c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert underwent successful surgery on his left hand.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dcda-d90e-a9da-dfdf6ead0000</link>
      <description>It will come down to pain tolerance for Herbert as the Chargers prepare for a Week 14 matchup with the Eagles. Herbert said Sunday that he plans on suiting up one week after having his hand surgically repaired. It’s his non-throwing hand, so it might be possible for Herbert to play against the Eagles. If he’s sidelined, Trey Lance will likely start for LA in Week 14. It would be a huge downgrade for all Chargers pass catchers, though Lance would have some appeal in superflex formats thanks to his rushing upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dcda-d90e-a9da-dfdf6ead0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df49-d6c4-abfb-df4b38d80000</link>
      <description>Arnold re-injured his shoulder in the Lions’ Thanksgiving game against the Packers and will undergo season-ending surgery in the coming days, per Pelissero. He had tried to play through the injury after hurting his shoulder in Week 5. The Lions secondary will take a hit with Arnold sidelined. Detroit has allowed the NFL’s seventh lowest drop backs success rate in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df49-d6c4-abfb-df4b38d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts are trying out K Blake Grupe, formerly of the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df97-d6c4-abfb-df97c4930000</link>
      <description>Michael Badgley missed a critical extra point in the Colts’ Week 13 loss to the Texans and head coach Shane Steichen was noncommittal on Badgley keeping the starting job for Week 14. Grupe, who was released by the Saints last week, had missed eight of his 26 field goal tries this season. An 85 percent field goal kicker during his NFL career, Grupe would have some fantasy upside in the Colts offense if he lands the starting job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-df97-d6c4-abfb-df97c4930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed WR Elijah Moore, formerly of the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfea-d90e-a9da-dfef61770000</link>
      <description>Moore will start with Denver’s practice squad ahead of the team’s Week 14 game against the Raiders. Moore appeared in nine games for the Bills this season and had nine catches for 112 yards. If he’s active for the Broncos in the coming weeks, Moore would likely be a rotational player who sees limited snaps and routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfea-d90e-a9da-dfef61770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said he’s “hopeful” WR Brandon Aiyuk will play for the team this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfed-d82c-a79a-fffd6aa00000</link>
      <description>Lynch wouldn’t call it realistic for Aiyuk to suit up for the Niners late in the regular season or the postseason, but said he remained hopeful the wideout would play at some point in 2025. Aiyuk, coming back from a brutal knee injury, has not had his 21-day practice window opened and is unhappy with the team after the Niners reportedly voided his 2026 contract guarantees. The Athletic reported in November that Aiyuk had likely played his final game for the 49ers. It would be shocking if Aiyuk returned in the final weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dfed-d82c-a79a-fffd6aa00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
