<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 04:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Diontae Johnson visited the Giants on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</link>
      <description>Desperation will drive one to that. Darius Slayton was active again in Week 8 and Wan’Dale Robinson has been performing up to par, but sans Malik Nabers the Giants have had trouble finding another wideout they can count on. Johnson makes some sense given that idea — the baggage is there, but he can certainly earn some targets in a way that Jalin Hyatt has not yet proven he can.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed WR Tyler Scott to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ce9-deb1-a39b-2def2b920000</link>
      <description>Scott is a former fourth-round draft pick by the Bears, tallying 18 receptions for 173 yards in two seasons with the team. He was the odd man out in the Chicago pass-catching group heading into the season and was released in August. Scott has bounced around the Colts and Seahawks since then and now joins the Rams practice squad with Tutu Atwell hitting injured reserve. CB Tre Brown was cut in a corresponding move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ce9-deb1-a39b-2def2b920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Julian Hill (ankle) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf1-deb1-a39b-2dff6f940000</link>
      <description>Hill was listed as a non-participant for the second straight day due to an ankle issue. S Ashtyn Davis (quad) also has back-to-back DNPs to start the week. It will be difficult for either player to come back on a short week for a Thursday showdown against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf1-deb1-a39b-2dff6f940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf8-dab4-a3fb-bff8e7c90000</link>
      <description>Jackson said himself that he is ready to go for Week 9 against the Dolphins. Back-to-back full practice participant listings support his statement as he returns to fantasy QB1 status for the rest of the season. Fantasy managers can safely fire Jackson up against a middling Dolphins defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf8-dab4-a3fb-bff8e7c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Radio 810’s Jason Anderson reports Chiefs are signing DT Mike Pennel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</link>
      <description>Pennel was briefly on the Bengals to begin this season, but was released on Tuesday. The Chiefs waste no time bringing the veteran back, after spending each of the last two seasons in Kansas City. Pennel will play a depth role again for the Chiefs’ defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers acquired EDGE Keion White and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Patriots in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d14-d245-adfb-bd5fd6690000</link>
      <description>White was inactive in Week 8 as the Patriots found a suitor for the former second-round pick. He tallied five sacks last season but fell out of favor on the defensive line this season. The 49ers had been looking for pass rush help with Nick Bosa (ACL) out for the season and now add White for the price of a late-round pick swap. White ranks last in PFF pass rush grade this season but will get a fresh start to make an impact in San Francisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d14-d245-adfb-bd5fd6690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers acquired S Kyle Dugger and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Patriots in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d27-dab4-a3fb-bf77e5c00000</link>
      <description>The Patriots continue to deal defensive players that have fallen out of favor in their current scheme, sending Dugger to the Steelers just minutes after sending Keion White to the 49ers. Both deals were structured the same, with the Pats swapping late-round picks in exchange for giving up the defensive player. Dugger had started all 45 games played for the Patriots from 2022-2024, but started four out of seven games played this season. The veteran has nine career interceptions, 24 passes defended, and 25 tackles for loss over a six-year career. The Steelers had a need at safety with DeShon Elliott week-to-week due to a knee injury suffered in Week 8. Dugger will mix into a Steelers secondary that needs improvement if they are to make a playoff push.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d27-dab4-a3fb-bf77e5c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers placed S DeShon Elliott (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</link>
      <description>Elliott was considered week-to-week with a knee injury he suffered in Week 8 against the Packers. However, with the Steelers acquiring Kyle Dugger from the Patriots, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Elliott will be placed on injured reserve. He will miss a minimum of four games and could return later in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed EDGE Clelin Ferrell to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers continue to add to their pass rush, signing Ferrell to the practice squad after trading for Keion White. Ferrell began his career with the Raiders and has bounced around the last three years, appearing in one game for the Chargers this season. He brings 17.0 career sacks over six seasons to the 49ers practice squad, including 3.5 sacks during a 2023 stint with the 49ers. San Francisco continues to add pass rush depth with Nick Bosa (ACL) out for the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jets S Andre Cisco suffered a pectoral tear in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</link>
      <description>Cisco reportedly tore his pectoral muscle in the Jets’ Week 8 win over the Bengals. The 25-year-old signed with the Jets in the offseason and started all eight games, tallying 41 combined tackles on the season. Cisco’s pectoral tear needs repair and he will be sidelined for some period of time, leaving the Jets to turn to Isaiah Oliver and Tony Adams for help at the safety spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
