<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills claimed CB Darius Slay off waivers from the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e644-d90e-a9da-ff4f74020000</link>
      <description>Slay was released by Pittsburgh earlier this week. The move was described as a mutual parting of ways. Slay opened the year as a starter for the Steelers but was eventually relegated to backup duties. He was even made a healthy scratch late in his Steelers tenure. Slay doesn’t have much left in the tank, but he is at least a useful depth option for Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e644-d90e-a9da-ff4f74020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e648-db57-afda-f67a5d4c0000</link>
      <description>At this point, anything other than a DNP to open the week is a good sign for Jackson. The beleaguered quarterback has been listed with four different injuries throughout the year. He hasn’t missed a game in over a month, but the maladies have taken their toll on his numbers. Jackson hasn’t run for more than 50 yards in a game since Week 1. His passing stats have also fallen compared to 2024. The rushing decline, in particular, has Jackson barely on the QB1 radar for Week 14 versus the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e648-db57-afda-f67a5d4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e64d-db57-afda-f67fab410000</link>
      <description>Bateman returned from his high-ankle sprain last week but failed to secure his only target of the night on Thanksgiving. With Lamar Jackson’s otherworldly efficiency taking a major step back this year, Bateman’s boom/bust fantasy profile has resulted in almost exclusively busts this year. Bateman is buried in the WR6 ranks for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e64d-db57-afda-f67fab410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Anderson (shoulder/chest) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e650-d6c4-abfb-f653ca160000</link>
      <description>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans told reporters earlier today that Anderson will be fine. The DNP is likely just a rest day for the cornerstone of the Texans’ defense. Anderson has 10.5 sacks and three forced fumbles this year. He should return to practice later this week. We fully expect to see him on the field, giving Patrick Mahomes trouble on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e650-d6c4-abfb-f653ca160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMeco Ryans said Woody Marks (foot) will be fine for Week 14 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e656-db57-afda-f676bb010000</link>
      <description>Ryans specifically included Marks among a group of DNPs on Wednesday who he said will be fine. Texans fans can breathe a sigh of relief knowing that Will Anderson was also in the group of players who will be fine. Marks briefly left Week 13’s game with the foot issue but retook the field after a brief stint on the sidelines. He ran for 64 yards on 19 carries in total. Assuming no setbacks, Marks will be in the RB2 mix for his Week 14 date with Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e656-db57-afda-f676bb010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Gray (concussion/shoulder) practiced in full on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e65b-d316-abff-f6dbe4860000</link>
      <description>Gray missed last week’s game with the concussion. The shoulder issue is a new addition to his practice report, though a full practice means it won’t stop him from suiting up this week. Gray isn’t on the fantasy radar for Week 14 but does bring plenty to the table as an extra blocker and a backup tight end for the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e65b-d316-abff-f6dbe4860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RT Jawaan Taylor (tricep/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e65d-d6c4-abfb-f65fc5c80000</link>
      <description>The tricep injury, suffered in Week 13 against the Cowboys, is what will prevent Taylor from playing this week if he is ruled out. A DNP today puts him on the wrong side of questionable for now. Right guard Trey Smith missed Wednesday’s practice with an ankle injury. Left tackle Josh Simmons underwent wrist surgery and was placed on injured reserve. That’s three starting linemen unlikely to play or explicitly ruled out for a must-win game versus Houston. Expect Patrick Mahomes to get the ball out quickly as often as possible on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e65d-d6c4-abfb-f65fc5c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes (knee) is practicing in full for Week 14 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e663-db57-afda-f67389190000</link>
      <description>It’s never great to see a star quarterback on the injury report, but a full practice means the knee injury should be a non-issue by Sunday. That better be the case for Mahomes as he is set to take on the Texans’ vaunted pass-rush with as many as three of his starting linemen on the sidelines because of injuries. Expect a lot of quick passing and an uptick in scrmalbing for Mahomes this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e663-db57-afda-f67389190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed Mark Andrews to a three-year, $39.3 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e666-d90e-a9da-ff6fb94b0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens tend to keep their best players in-house when possible, but it’s still a bit of an odd move from GM Eric DeCosta. Andrews is 30 years old and is currently on pace for the worst year of his career by yards per game (27.7) and yards per route run (1.3). On the other hand, Lamar Jackson has missed time this year and hasn’t played up to his MVP-caliber standards when healthy, so it’s hard to pin Andrews’ statistical delcine solely on himself. John Harbaugh has also found a niche use for Andrews as the team’s tush push specialst. He has nine carries for six first downs and one touchdown, which came on a tush push fake that went for 35 yards. Andrews is now under contract through 2028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e666-d90e-a9da-ff6fb94b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 14 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e66e-d90e-a9da-ff6f38d40000</link>
      <description>McCarthy missed Week 13 with the brain injury. Despite being one of the least efficient quarterbacks in recent memory, McCarthy still proved to be a better option than Max Brosmer once the latter took the field. Brosmer was intercepted four times versus Seattle, including one pick-six. McCarthy isn’t on the fantasy radar, even if a great matchup versus the Commanders. He might, however, be able to keep the light on for Justin Jefferson as a WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e66e-d90e-a9da-ff6f38d40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
