<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:26:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Enquirer’s Kelsey Conway reports the Bengals will gather information from other teams about Trey Hendrickson’s market at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</link>
      <description>The Bengals have left open the option to trade Hendrickson through the franchise tag, but that seems like a really unrealistic scenario on paper. Hendrickson would, after being tagged back-to-back years, be guaranteed a $30.2 million salary in 2026. He could simply sign the tag and likely do better for himself than he would on the free market. This feels a lot like the Vikings trying to drum up a market for Sam Darnold in a tag-and-trade last year — if a team can’t afford to tag the player and simply keep him, it’s hard to believe that a trade will come to fruition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec believes Tyler Linderbaum “appears primed” to eclipse Creed Humphrey as the league’s highest-paid center in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d89c-a1be-efffca0a0000</link>
      <description>Linderbaum is expected to have a strong market, in other words. The two natural landing spots will be a return to Baltimore and a reunion with coach John Harbaugh in New York, though neither are exactly flush with cap space. Linderbaum has posted PFF grades above 74.6 in all four of his seasons and is a strong run blocker despite being undersized. He’ll turn 26 in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d89c-a1be-efffca0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec reports the Ravens have made “no progress” in their efforts to extend Isaiah Likely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d3e-d990-a1de-6d7e88ff0000</link>
      <description>When the Ravens surprisingly re-upped Mark Andrews in-season, it seemed to point to the idea that Likely could leave in free agency. This report only accentuates that. Turning 26 in April, Likely would seem to be one of the few free agent tight ends (perhaps alongside Chig Okonkwo) with any real starter upside. Zrebiec believes “he should do quite well” in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d3e-d990-a1de-6d7e88ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall believes it’s “hard to imagine” the Falcons will be able to bring back Tyler Allgeier.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d42-d042-afbc-7dd2635d0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier will probably be one of the highest-regarded backs on the market, and Kendall notes that the Falcons can’t afford to give him starting running back money behind Bijan Robinson. Allgeier could wind up in a terrific fantasy situation this year — the Chiefs and Texans (our speculation) are two rooms he could step into as the lead back easily with real upside — and could find himself in the RB2 tier in the right landing spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d42-d042-afbc-7dd2635d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt believes the Jets could release Justin Fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d4e-d89c-a1be-efdf54210000</link>
      <description>Fields would incur a $22 million dead cap hit and save the Jets only $1 million against the cap if released, and yet Rosenblatt still believes that is a likely scenario because the Jets are not lacking for cap space. Fields would likely find backup work somewhere if released, but the Jets runout appears likely to have been his final chance to cut it as a starter in the NFL. Rosenblatt also notes that it’s unlikely any team would trade for Fields at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d4e-d89c-a1be-efdf54210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kimberley A. Martin reports Buccaneers WR Mike Evans will play in 2026 and will explore his free agency options.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d8a-d042-afbc-7ddaf8b80000</link>
      <description>It was sort of assumed that Evans would just run it back in Tampa as a career Buccaneer, but perhaps he’s actually interested in seeing what is out there for him. That’s about how it played out the last time Evans hit free agency, when he wound up with a two-year, $41 million contract with $29 million in guarantees. The Buccaneers have a much better wideout room now than they did in 2024, at least on paper, with Emeka Egbuka, Chris Godwin, and Jalen McMillan under contract. Evans is also entering his age-33 season and coming off a year where he missed time with a broken collarbone, so his market may also be reduced. Still, he played well while healthy. This will be one to watch over the next few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d8a-d042-afbc-7ddaf8b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns and G Joel Bitonio agreed to push the void date on his contract to the end of the league year in March.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6db0-d990-a1de-6dfe633a0000</link>
      <description>Bitonio, who has been contemplating retirement openly, asked the Browns for a few more weeks to do so. The club agreed. If Bitonio plays in 2026, he’ll be entering his age-35 season. Bitonio last carried a PFF grade above 80 in the 2022 season, though he’s remained solid and reliable for the Browns over the last three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6db0-d990-a1de-6dfe633a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Woods retired from the NFL after 12 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6dc1-d629-a1bc-fdddce070000</link>
      <description>He signed a one-day contract to retire as a Ram. Woods peaked with the Jared Goff Era early Sean McVay Rams, where he signed as a free agent after a four-year rookie deal in Buffalo. Woods managed 3,289 yards and 14 touchdowns over a three-year stretch from 2018-2020. His last real action was with the Texans in 2023 and 2024, though he bounced around the Steelers in the 2025 offseason and did a few practice squad stints. Woods retires with 683 receptions for 8233 yards and 38 scores.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6dc1-d629-a1bc-fdddce070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots promoted linebackers coach Zak Kuhr to defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e0e-d89c-a1be-efdfd3740000</link>
      <description>Kuhr was the team’s interim defensive coordinator after former defensive coordinator Terrell Williams underwent treatment for prostate cancer. He first started as a coach in the NFL under Mike Vrabel with the Titans and called a Pats defense that forced eight turnovers in the playoffs en route to a Super Bowl LX appearance. Vrabel now makes Kuhr the permanent defensive coordinator as Williams takes a high-ranking role on the staff, looking to build upon a strong unit for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e0e-d89c-a1be-efdfd3740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers assistant head coach and special teams coordinator Rich Bisaccia is stepping down.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e20-d042-afbc-7ff221b10000</link>
      <description>Bisaccia had been the Packers’ special teams coordinator for the past four seasons under Matt LaFleur, but is now stepping down from his role. The 65-year-old is pausing his coaching career, which includes a stint as the Raiders’ interim head coach in 2021. Meanwhile, the Packers will have to look externally for his replacement, with former assistant special teams coach Byron Storer now the Browns’ special teams coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6e20-d042-afbc-7ff221b10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
