<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-369e-d713-ad9e-7edeab940000</link>
      <description>It looks like Jaret Patterson (11/30 against the Vikings in Week 8) will saunter into a desperation FLEX role behind Kimani Vidal against the Titans in Week 9. Haskins has dealt with chest and hamstring injuries since Vidal took the lead role from him against the Dolphins in Week 6 and doesn’t look particularly close to returning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-369e-d713-ad9e-7edeab940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Josh Palmer (knee/ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a3-d713-ad9e-7ef793900000</link>
      <description>It’s the first time he’s practiced since suffering the injury against the Falcons in Week 6’s Monday game. Palmer may be able to get up off the mat to steal some targets from Khalil Shakir and Keon Coleman in what projects as a pass-heavy game script against the Chiefs. We’d be surprised if he did enough to be fantasy-viable on his own coming off the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a3-d713-ad9e-7ef793900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ray Davis (illness) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a5-d713-ad9e-7ef56f770000</link>
      <description>Sounds like a 24-hour bug. Davis won’t hold a standalone-worthy role in Week 9 against the Chiefs, but has some fantasy upside in the event that James Cook misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a5-d713-ad9e-7ef56f770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a0-d673-a39e-b6b171f90000</link>
      <description>Ridley is headed toward another missed game, while the Titans’ youngsters, WRs Elic Ayomanor and Chimere Dike, attempt to carve out roles. The latter player is making a case for weekly WR4 treatment. The Titans are on bye in Week 10, so a logical plan of action is for Ridley to rest up until the team’s Week 11 game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a0-d673-a39e-b6b171f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Daniel Bellinger (neck) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a9-d673-a39e-b6b922b80000</link>
      <description>Bellinger looks unlikely to play in Week 9 following back-to-back DNPs. He re-aggravated his neck injury in Week 8’s game against the Eagles. Theo Johnson is the tight end you’re looking for from the Giants this week in fantasy circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a9-d673-a39e-b6b922b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a8-d673-a39e-b6b936c50000</link>
      <description>This will likely go down as a DNP. Okonkwo was limited on Wednesday, so one wonders if he suffered the injury during practice that day. Okonkwo’s Friday participation should clarify his Week 9 availability, but for now, it appears as though rookie TE Gunnar Helm has a chance to operate as the team’s clear-cut No. 1 tight end against the Chargers. He would warrant TE1 streaming consideration, if so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36a8-d673-a39e-b6b936c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ab-d673-a39e-b6bbfe3d0000</link>
      <description>Simmons is now on the wrong side of questionable, which is a tough loss for the Titans’ defense. The unit could also be without OLB Arden Key (quadricep) and backup OLB Jihad Ward (undisclosed) who were also absent during the portion of practice open to the media. The Titans are tasked with containing the Chargers’ offense in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ab-d673-a39e-b6bbfe3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ab-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb9d480000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the Panthers are still managing Young to some extent — they were eager to see how he’d perform on their hardest practice of the week — but he looks like a good bet to start on Sunday from here. Andy Dalton (thumb) got in a limited session after not practicing on Wednesday. Mike White was signed to the active roster today and most reporters mentioned Dalton, not Young, as the likely scratch in the scenario that White is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ab-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb9d480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Xavier Legette (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36af-d1e7-a1fa-7eefefb70000</link>
      <description>Well, it’s a relief for Legette that it’s only an illness instead of another soft-tissue injury. We’d still tentatively expect him to play, but that’s adding in some belief that he does something on Friday. His absence would free up a lot of targets for the Panthers in Week 9 against the Packers, but the Panthers haven’t exactly had a fantasy-reliable second option this year regardless of who is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36af-d1e7-a1fa-7eefefb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36b0-d713-ad9e-7ef4663d0000</link>
      <description>Joseph has dealt with this knee injury for weeks now. His continued absence following the Lions’ Week 8 bye is unfortunate. Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) continues to practice in full while CB Avonte Maddox (hamstring) remains limited. The unit should at least get Arnold back for their Week game against the Vikings, though Joseph and Maddox are up in the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36b0-d713-ad9e-7ef4663d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
