<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) was limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ab-deb6-a7fd-d7fff7340000</link>
      <description>All indications continue to be that he’ll make his debut against the Jets on Monday night. Without proof of concept that he can be anything in this offense, we’d avoid him even in MNF slates due to the likelihood he’ll be on a snap count in his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ab-deb6-a7fd-d7fff7340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ae-deb6-a7fd-d7ff08250000</link>
      <description>There was never a reason to be concerned about Waddle’s Week 4 status. He’ll be a WR3 against the Jets on Monday night and the state of the Jets secondary leaves us open to the idea that he should be ranked even higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ae-deb6-a7fd-d7ff08250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is not on Cleveland’s final injury report for Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87af-deb6-a7fd-d7ff6c700000</link>
      <description>He got in two full sessions after a limited Wednesday and should be considered a low-end TE1 against the Lions on reputation. The Browns haven’t exactly gotten their pass offense on track through three weeks, and Njoku’s actual lines of 5/40, 4/40, and 3/37 read like a Dalton Schultz game log.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87af-deb6-a7fd-d7ff6c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Noah Fant (concussion) did not practice Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b2-dca3-a9fb-bfbbe00e0000</link>
      <description>It seems pretty unlikely that he’ll play on Monday night given the two DNPs and lack of known advancement through the protocol. Fant’s (expected) absence could make Mike Gesiciki a reasonable what-the-heck TE1 play or Monday Slate play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b2-dca3-a9fb-bfbbe00e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8794-dca3-a9fb-bf9d6f0e0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs should handle another high-end RB1 workload against the Cowboys this week. The Packers will be without both RT Zach Tom (oblique) and his direct backup, RT Anthony Belton, who is on the injury report with an ankle injury. Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said Tom injured his knee on Wednesday. It is worth noting that high-ankle sprains and MCL sprains often share the same injury mechanism. Packers LG Aaron Banks (groin) is doubtful to play. On the plus side, TE Tucker Kraft (knee/elbow) will play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8794-dca3-a9fb-bf9d6f0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers TE Tucker Kraft (knee/elbow) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87aa-d6e9-af9d-8fbad44c0000</link>
      <description>Kraft was limited in the Packers’ first two practices this week. He was upgraded to full on Friday. Kraft played on 91.4 percent of offensive snaps in Weeks 1 and 2, and was promisingly on the field for 86.4 percent of snaps in Week 3 despite entering the game with a knee injury and picking up an elbow injury along the way. He is a TE1 against the Cowboys this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87aa-d6e9-af9d-8fbad44c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes believes the Jets could trade Breece Hall at the deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b5-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf2a60000</link>
      <description>In the assumption that the team is not competitive this year, Hughes believes the head of the Jets’ RB committee could be a trade candidate in the final year of his rookie deal. Hall put up an amazing Week 1 but has just 90 total yards in two games since. Hall would be an upgrade for several teams at running back, and would probably not carry a high cost given how much the Jets seem to like Braelon Allen. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b5-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf2a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 4 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c2-d95b-addb-efc69f920000</link>
      <description>Despite the listing, we’d say it sounds more dire than that. Higbee appears to have suffered a hip injury in practice on Thursday, and did not practice at all on Friday. Colby Parkinson (shoulder) joins Higbee on the questionable line. Is it Terrance Ferguson time in LA? Or will Davis Allen catch a touchdown for the third time this season? We live in interesting Rams tight end depth chart times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c2-d95b-addb-efc69f920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (back) said he is “good to go” for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c9-d6e9-af9d-8fd9020a0000</link>
      <description>Engram began the week as a full practice participant. His back injury is evidently behind him. The Broncos’ matchup against the Bengals’ pushover defense theoretically puts Engram on the streaming radar, though his play in 2025 leaves a lot to be desired. He does not need to be started this week, but he is a viable option, based on the matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c9-d6e9-af9d-8fd9020a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) won’t play in Las Vegas’ Week 4 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-deb6-a7fd-d7df74010000</link>
      <description>Mayer’s absence may open up things for Brock Bowers to be used more as a traditional tight end instead of as a wideout — which is where he spent a lot of the first three weeks of the season. Maybe that can get Bowers going after a slow start. Mayer did not practice at any point this week and will enter Week 5 on the questionable line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-deb6-a7fd-d7df74010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
