<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers S Antoine Winfield (toe) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1789-d5d8-a3ff-ffe956910000</link>
      <description>He and Lavonte David (knee/rib) both upgraded to full practices on Friday and were removed from the report. The Buccaneers will have their back-seven leaders ready for a divisional matchup against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1789-d5d8-a3ff-ffe956910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-177c-d5d8-a3ff-ff7d12c80000</link>
      <description>Slayton remained limited in all three practices this week, so his game-day workload is difficult to predict, though teams tend to let players log the typical snap allotment once they retake the field. Slayton has not played since straining his hamstring in Week 5 against the Saints. He is a boom-bust FLEX option against the Eagles this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-177c-d5d8-a3ff-ff7d12c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Roschon Johnson (back) will not play in Chicago’s Week 8 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178b-deb1-a39b-378f99e00000</link>
      <description>He did not practice at any point this week and looks to be questionable for Week 9 as well. His absence further helps Kyle Monangai, as it keeps the RB2 carries from getting divvied up. Johnson has barely played all season while dealing with a foot injury for the entirety of the preseason — he’s been active for just five games and has only two carries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178b-deb1-a39b-378f99e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (back) will not play in Chicago’s Week 8 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178d-d5d8-a3ff-ffeda9cf0000</link>
      <description>Full steam ahead for Colston Loveland, who is a borderline TE1 play this week with Kmet indisposed. Kmet did not practice at any point this week and was given the “week to week” designation by head coach Ben Johnson in a presser earlier today. He sounds extremely iffy for Week 9 at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178d-d5d8-a3ff-ffeda9cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 8 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178f-d5d8-a3ff-ffef012f0000</link>
      <description>It’s a repeat of last week, where Swift didn’t do more than limited practices and was listed questionable before detonating the Saints for 124 yards on the ground and a score. We expect more of the same this week, and would label Swift as on the optimistic side of questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178f-d5d8-a3ff-ffef012f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants K Graham Gano (groin) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1783-d5d8-a3ff-ffe37d830000</link>
      <description>Gano was designated to return from injured reserve earlier this week, and he promisingly practiced in full three times since then. Giants fill-in K Jude McAtamney converted just 2-of-4 extra point attempts last week. Getting Gano back would be a plus for the G-Men. The Giants will be getting back starting C John Michael Schmitz, who has been sidelined since the Giants faced the Eagles in Week 6. Giants S Jevon Holland (neck) is doubtful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1783-d5d8-a3ff-ffe37d830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears K Cairo Santos (thigh) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 8 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1791-d5d8-a3ff-fff1865a0000</link>
      <description>He did get in full practices each of the last two days, which would seem to be an indication that the veteran kicker will be back against Baltimore. If not, Jake Moody will get another practice squad elevation and kick for the Bears in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1791-d5d8-a3ff-fff1865a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip) is not on Chicago’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1793-dab4-a3fb-9ff300ce0000</link>
      <description>Moore has games of 38, 42, 43, 46, and 68 yards this year — it’s been a remarkably consistent run of games that won’t do anything in fantasy football without a touchdown. Moore has one touchdown. He’s a FLEX play at best against the Ravens in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1793-dab4-a3fb-9ff300ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Brian Burns (hip) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178b-d245-adfb-97dfb9c20000</link>
      <description>Burns told reporters that he expects to play on Sunday, which is good news because he managed just one limited practice session this week. Giants rotational EDGE Chauncey Golston has been ruled out with a neck injury of his own. Burns ranks second on the team in quarterback pressures (26) and first in sacks (eight).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-178b-d245-adfb-97dfb9c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Tyrique Stevenson (shoulder) won’t play in Chicago’s Week 8 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1794-dab4-a3fb-9ff4b6200000</link>
      <description>Ditto Kyler Gordon, who popped up on the injury report late this week with a groin/calf designation and didn’t practice on Friday. Stevenson didn’t practice at any point this week and enters Week 9 as a question mark. If Lamar Jackson is healthy enough to go in Week 8, this would sure seem to set up as a big game for the MVP candidate against a Bears defense missing it’s top-three cornerbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1794-dab4-a3fb-9ff4b6200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
