<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared WR Jermaine Burton, CB Marco Wilson, C Matt Lee, TE Cam Grandy, DT McKinnley Jackson, and DT Howard Cross III inactive for Week 1 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d0-de13-afdd-66dbe9f70000</link>
      <description>Burton reportedly made progress this offseason after a rookie campaign plagued by off-field issues. The fact that he made the roster shows the Bengals still have some hope for him, but it’s not going to happen early in the year. Andrei Iosivas remains the team’s No. 3 receiver versus Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d0-de13-afdd-66dbe9f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared WR Allen Lazard inactive for New York’s Week 1 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-d332-a1fd-b6feac260000</link>
      <description>He lost a few weeks of training camp to a shoulder injury, but we’re still a bit surprised he went straight to the healthy scratch line. As has been rumored all offseason, Josh Reynolds is likely to be New York’s No. 2 receiver. Chukwuma Okorafor (hand) is playing on a questionable tag. Also inactive for the Jets are: EDGE Braiden McGregor, T Esa Pole, TE Jelani Woods, and DT Leonard Taylor III.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-d332-a1fd-b6feac260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) is inactive for Week 1 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d3-dbe3-a9bb-34d35dbf0000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear why Ekwonu wasn’t just formally ruled out on Friday. NFL teams and the games they play. Yosh Nijman is filling in on Bryce Young’s blindside. Hardly ideal for the opener, especially with Young’s receiver corps looking thin. Also inactive for the Panthers are WR Jimmy Horn, WR Dalevon Campbell, TE James Mitchell and DT Cam Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d3-dbe3-a9bb-34d35dbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) is inactive for Week 1 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d4-db7b-a5dd-a4d48b5a0000</link>
      <description>Recovering from shoulder surgery, Mooney was listed as questionable after logging limited practices ahead of the Falcons’ season opener against Tampa. He’ll miss at least one week while continuing his rehab. That should mean more targets for Drake London and Kyle Pitts, who had 174 receiving yards in two games against the Bucs last season. Ray-Ray McCloud should slot in as the team’s WR2 with Monney out. Also inactive for the Falcons are CB Clark Phillips III, S DeMarcco Hellams, RB Nathan Carter, ILB Josh Woods, OL Jack Nelson, and DL Sam Roberts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d4-db7b-a5dd-a4d48b5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared RB Tyler Goodson, CB Jonathan Edwards, QB Riley Leonard, TE Will Mallory, LB Chad Muma, OT Luke Tenuta, and DE JT Tuimoloau inactive for Week 1 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d66d290000</link>
      <description>Goodson is battling an elbow injury, but he has also likely been passed by rookie DJ Giddens on the depth chart, which makes Goodson just the third running back in Indianapolis. Leonard might earn his way onto the field later in the season, but he’s just the emergency quarterback right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d66d290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared Nick Herbig (hamstring) inactive for Pittsburgh’s Week 1 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-dbe3-a9bb-34db9d5c0000</link>
      <description>Herbig was on the questionable tag and should be considered questionable for Week 2 at this point. Also inactive for the Steelers are: DT Derrick Harmon (knee), QB Skylar Thompson (third quarterback/hamstring), G Max Scharping, G Andrus Peat, and DT Esezi Otomewo. The latter three are all healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-dbe3-a9bb-34db9d5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals OG Will Hernandez (knee) is inactive for Week 1 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d670950000</link>
      <description>Hernandez tore his ACL in Week 5 of last season and has been working his way back. He is not ready yet, now set to miss Week 1 still rehabbing his knee. Isaiah Adams is the team’s starting right guard for now. Also inactive for the Cardinals are RB Bam Knight, CB Kei’Trel Clark, CB Elijah Jones, and LB Xavier Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d670950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Efton Chism (knee) is inactive for Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d6-db7b-a5dd-a4d66cf00000</link>
      <description>It’s technically a healthy scratch since Chism was removed from the injury report on Friday, but he had been listed with a knee issue. The UDFA drew some summer hype — evidently justified since he made the team — but isn’t a part of the receiver rotation to begin the year. He’s an end-of-bench stash in deeper Dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d6-db7b-a5dd-a4d66cf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Nick Chubb will be the “bell cow” running back for the Texans in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24da-db7b-a5dd-a4deb5880000</link>
      <description>We’re expecting to see Chubb take a majority of the early-down snaps and Dare Ogunbowale to be the third-down back for the Texans. The fact that Chubb will have the majority of the snaps makes him a worthwhile RB2/FLEX starter, and it makes Dameon Pierce and Woody Marks hard to play at this point. If Chubb is available in your league — he was a late riser due to Joe Mixon’s injury — he’s a worthwhile pickup ahead of the rosters locking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24da-db7b-a5dd-a4deb5880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Texans WR Xavier Hutchinson is expected to get “starter snaps” in Week 1 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d9-de13-afdd-66db9dc10000</link>
      <description>Christian Kirk has already been ruled out for Week 1, leaving a vacant slot role up for grabs. Hutchinson and third-round rookie Jaylin Noel are vying for the job and it sounds like the veteran has the upper hand. Noel was an interesting Week 1 sleeper for the Rapoport report, but fantasy managers should now find another DFS dart throw for their lineups. Both he and Hutchinson should only be rostered in deep formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d9-de13-afdd-66db9dc10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
