<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) is questionable for Dallas’ Week 15 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1479-d005-a9bf-dc7d19e90000</link>
      <description>Brian Schottenheimer said that he was “relieved” that Ferguson will be able to “answer the bell” in a press availability earlier, which strongly points at him playing. No longer at the point of the season where he’s spiking six touchdowns in the span of a month, Ferguson is now more of a low/mid-range TE1 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1479-d005-a9bf-dc7d19e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys T Tyler Guyton (ankle) won’t play in Dallas’ Week 15 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-147d-d1bc-a3fb-957dfa1e0000</link>
      <description>Nate Thomas got the tackle work the last two weeks and should be set for another start against the Vikings defense in Week 15. Guyton has not played or practiced since suffering the dreaded high-ankle sprain in Dallas’ Week 12 win over the Eagles. The second-year tackle should be considered questionable for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-147d-d1bc-a3fb-957dfa1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jordan Addison (Achilles) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1474-d8cf-affb-bc7eb4ad0000</link>
      <description>Addison’s injury is a bit concerning, as is QB J.J. McCarthy’s erratic play. McCarthy had a decent last week though, and the Cowboys’ pass defense is relatively fantasy-friendly. Addison is a low-end WR3 in what could be a high-scoring game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1474-d8cf-affb-bc7eb4ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Cameron Heyward (knee) did not practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1483-d77b-adfb-de8310c50000</link>
      <description>It’s a new listing, and one that puts Heyward’s status for Week 15 in some doubt ahead of Monday night. The veteran likely doesn’t actually need the practice at this point, but mid-week downgrades are always a bit scary. Sunday’s report should add some clarity to the proceedings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1483-d77b-adfb-de8310c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-147e-d1bc-a3fb-957ecc640000</link>
      <description>Jones will continue to play through the pain in his age-31 season. Over the last four weeks, Jones’ best showing earned him the overall RB26 spot in half-PPR scoring. The Vikings’ game against the Cowboys profiles as a fantasy-friendly one, though, warranting low-end RB2 treatment for Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-147e-d1bc-a3fb-957ecc640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (calf) was limited in Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1484-d1bc-a3fb-95a4b1c60000</link>
      <description>It was a mid-week downgrade, never a great sign. Austin played a season-low 16 offensive snaps on Sunday with new additions Marquez Valdes-Scantling and Adam Thielen taking bigger roles, so he’s droppable in most leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1484-d1bc-a3fb-95a4b1c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE T.J. Hockenson (shin) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-146d-d005-a9bf-dc7dd66f0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson is good to go for the Vikings’ intriguing game against the Cowboys this weekend, though he can only be viewed as a low-end TE1, at best. The veteran tight end finished as the overall TE14 in half-PPR scoring in consecutive weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-146d-d005-a9bf-dc7dd66f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos OL Mike McGlinchey (shoulder) is questionable for Denver’s Week 15 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1487-d005-a9bf-dcb735790000</link>
      <description>McGlinchey popped up on the injury report as a Friday DNP after being healthy earlier in the week. Not auspicious. Geron Christian and Frank Crum are the backup tackles on the roster for Denver, and one of them could be pressed into service on Sunday if McGlinchey can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1487-d005-a9bf-dcb735790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns DT Mason Graham (rib) is questionable for Cleveland’s Week 15 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148d-d77b-adfb-de8ffd560000</link>
      <description>Graham was limited on Friday, but didn’t practice on either Wednesday or Thursday. He did play through the injury in Week 14 against the Titans. The rookie No. 5 overall pick has a 68.8 PFF defensive grade in 572 snaps this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148d-d77b-adfb-de8ffd560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) is questionable to play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148e-d77b-adfb-de8fcb150000</link>
      <description>Add backup RB Emanuel Wilson wherever available. Jacobs is seemingly on track to play on Sunday, but it cannot hurt to be safe. Wilson operated as the team’s featured running back with Jacobs sidelined against the Vikings a few weeks ago, rushing 28 times for 107 yards and two touchdowns. The Broncos’ elite defense will put up a fight, but Wilson would be a volume-based RB2 if Jacobs cannot play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-148e-d77b-adfb-de8fcb150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
