<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 5 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abe0-deb6-a7fd-fbffd5580000</link>
      <description>Joining Hamilton on the shelf off the questionable line is star tackle Ronnie Stanley, who will be replaced by Joe Noteboom. The rest of Baltimore’s inactive list was decided on Friday: QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring), FB Patrick Ricard (calf), MLB Roquan Smith (hamstring), CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) and CB Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring). The Ravens and 49ers are jostling for most-banged-up team in the NFL and Baltimore looks to have pulled ahead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-abe0-deb6-a7fd-fbffd5580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders (knee/ankle) is inactive for Week 5 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b500-d95b-addb-fd46b3cb0000</link>
      <description>Rookie Jaydon Blue will back up Javonte Williams in Sunday’s game against the Jets. Blue makes for an interesting fantasy stash heading into Week 5, but fantasy managers should resist any urges to slot him into their fantasy lineups. In addition to Sanders, the Cowboys also declared OT Tyler Guyton (concussion), WR CeeDee Lamb (ankle), OG Tyler Booker (ankle), WR KaVontae Turpin (foot), DE Marshawn Kneeland (ankle), and DT Jay Toia inactive for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b500-d95b-addb-fd46b3cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Sam Howell, WR Xavier Gipson, C Drew Kendall and CB Mac McWilliams inactive for Week 5 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd466ba80000</link>
      <description>The Eagles’ main Week 5 injury questions resolved themselves earlier in the week. They are healthy, relatively speaking, as they try to remain unbeaten against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd466ba80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared RB Jaylen Wright, CB Storm Duck, QB Quinn Ewers, DT Zeek Biggers, and WR Cedrick Wilson Jr. inactive for Week 5 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf920d930000</link>
      <description>Wright looks like a healthy scratch for Week 5. Ollie Gordon has run away with the No. 2 job in Miami behind De’Von Achane. Gordon is a touchdown-or-bust RB4 for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf920d930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Braxton Berrios, CB Zion Childress, QB Graham Mertz, LB Christian Harris, OL Jarrett Kingston, and OL Trent Brown inactive for Houston’s Week 5 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf9248320000</link>
      <description>All of these players are healthy scratches. The only players ruled out for Houston on Friday were placed on IR before the game or are designated to return players still in their 21-day window. Notably, Dameon Pierce is active as Houston’s third running back. Berrios missed the first two weeks with a hamstring injury and has not been active yet this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d6e9-af9d-bf9248320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juwan Johnson (ankle) is active in Week 5 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd461bbd0000</link>
      <description>With Foster, Mauro and Tyson Hill also both active, the Saints will have their top three tight ends all active for the same game for the first time this season. What that means for all of their usage remains to be seen, but it’s hard to start any of them with confidence this week until we see how the Saints deploy them. The Saints declared OG Cesar Ruiz, CB Isaac Yiadom, DE Chase Young, DT Khristian Boyd, OT Xavier Truss, and RB Devin Neal inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b502-d95b-addb-fd461bbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared TE Ja’Tavion Sanders, CB Chau Smith-Wade, RB Chuba Hubbard, LB Claudin Cherelus, DT Jaden Crumedy, and DT Tershawn Wharton inactive for Week 5 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdea60000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as both Sanders and Hubbard were ruled out earlier in the week. Sanders is dealing with a high-ankle sprain and is expected to miss multiple weeks. Tommy Tremble will start in his place, putting him on the TE2 periphery for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-deb6-a7fd-f7dfdea60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) is inactive for Week 5 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-dca3-a9fb-bd9d0d2a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson was questionable entering the weekend but will now miss his third-straight game due to the ankle injury he suffered in Week 2. Johnson was the only questionable player the Jets had heading into Sunday. In addition to him, the Jets also declared CB Michael Carter (concussion), RB/KR Kene Nwangwu (hamstring), TE Stone Smartt, TE Jelani Woods, DT Leonard Taylor, and OT Esa Pole inactive for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b504-dca3-a9fb-bd9d0d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Adonai Mitchell is inactive for Week 5 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b507-d6e9-af9d-bf9772d20000</link>
      <description>Mitchell will supposedly be limited after his mistake-plagued Week 5, but with Alec Pierce (concussion) on the shelf, consider us skeptical. Mitchell probably won’t be out there for the first series, but all bets are off after that. Joining Pierce on the shelf are QB Riley Leonard, CB Kenny Moore II, RB Tyler Goodson, LB Buddy Johnson, OT Luke Tenuta and DT Eric Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b507-d6e9-af9d-bf9772d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants ruled RB Tyrone Tracy Jr., ILB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles, OL Evan Neal, DL Elijah Garcia, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 5 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b506-d6e9-af9d-bf9662510000</link>
      <description>Tracy is nursing a shoulder injury and had been listed as doubtful, but he was always a longshot to play this weekend. He’s getting closer and could make his return next week, but it will be Cam Skattebo dominating the snaps and touches for another week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b506-d6e9-af9d-bf9662510000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
