<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c30-d968-a19b-7cf1a3300000</link>
      <description>Bryant is progressing through the NFL’s concussion protocol and should be able to play in Week 18 against the Chargers, though the Chargers are expected to rest some starters, which could result in an easy run-heavy win for the Broncos. The Broncos (13-3) currently hold the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. They can retain it with a win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c30-d968-a19b-7cf1a3300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports there is mutual interest between Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile and the Titans regarding Tennessee’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c48-d56e-afff-fee87a2b0000</link>
      <description>Per Wolfe, Campanile has become a player favorite with the Jaguars, and LB Devin Lloyd credits Campanile with his development. Campanile has had quite the year. The Jaguars hired him as their defensive coordinator roughly 11 months ago. In early October, ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler put Campanile on his shortlist of “young defensive coaches” who could be head coaching candidates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c48-d56e-afff-fee87a2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that Patriots pass game coordinator and TE coach Thomas Brown is going to get “a bunch” of a head coaching interviews.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c36-d35e-a1bf-7df625260000</link>
      <description>The Bears gave Brown two in-season promotions after hiring him as their pass game coordinator in 2024. He was first elevated to offensive coordinator before eventually taking over as the team’s interim head coach. He served as the Panthers’ offensive coordinator in 2023 after coaching in multiple roles under head coach Sean McVay with the Rams from 2020-2022. Per Wolfe, Brown has helped the Patriots incorporate pre-snap motion and tight end-usage concepts learned under McVay. Per Wolfe, “he is ready to run his own ship.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c36-d35e-a1bf-7df625260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports the Giants are expected to interview a bevy of candidates for their open head coaching position that includes former coaches Mike McCarthy, Antonio Pierce and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f60-d968-a19b-7ff132b80000</link>
      <description>McCarthy didn’t coach in 2025 after a five-year stint with the Cowboys. He has the most experience of anyone on the Giants’ list, which also includes Packers defensive coordinator Jeff Hafley, Colts defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo, former Raiders coach and Giants player Antonio Pierce and Rams defensive coordinator Chris Shula. Raanan passes along that GM Joe Schoen is leading the coaching search and multiple sources believe he’s coming back next year, so the Giants have that going for them after a Schoen oversaw a 6-27 record in the last two years. Norte Dame’s Marcus Freeman removed his name from consideration for the Giants job earlier this week. New York’s coaching search seems to be centered around quantity rather than quality at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f60-d968-a19b-7ff132b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (neck) has been ruled out for Week 18 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f69-d56e-afff-ffe99a9e0000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as Taylor hasn’t played since Week 14 due to a neck injury. The 21-year-old tight end finished his rookie season with 44 receptions, 369 yards and a touchdown. With improved health and quarterback play, things should be looking up for Taylor in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f69-d56e-afff-ffe99a9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott told reporters QB Josh Allen (foot) is “good to go” for Week 18’s game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f8e-d56e-afff-ffeea5510000</link>
      <description>Allen hasn’t practiced yet this week, but McDermott said he’ll be limited in practice Friday and good to go for the game on Sunday. McDermott said earlier in the week that Allen was trending in the right direction. The Bills are locked into a Wild Card spot, which could make Allen a tricky start in Week 18. McDermott didn’t indicate how much of the game Allen might play as the Bills could turn to Mitchell Trubisky in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f8e-d56e-afff-ffeea5510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (ribs) is questionable for Week 18 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f99-dc7a-af9b-ffbf5a7e0000</link>
      <description>Waddle left Week 17’s game against the Buccaneers with a rib injury and didn’t return. The 27-year-old receiver returned to practice Thursday, which is a good sign for his availability despite his questionable designation. Waddle certainly has a chance to play, though with the Dolphins already out of playoff contention, the organization could opt to err on the side of caution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f99-dc7a-af9b-ffbf5a7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane (shoulder) didn’t practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f9a-d56e-afff-fffaacbd0000</link>
      <description>Achane hasn’t practiced all week. With the Dolphins already eliminated from playoff contention, it seems highly unlikely that the 24-year-old running back will try to tough it out against the Patriots in Week 18. We expect him to be ruled out later today and Jaylen Wright would be the expected starter against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7f9a-d56e-afff-fffaacbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed TE Darren Waller (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fa0-d968-a19b-7ff16e650000</link>
      <description>Waller had seen his role in the offense diminish since Quinn Ewers took over as quarterback. The 33-year-old tight end had 66 yards and two touchdowns in his last game with Tua Tagovailoa, but had just 40 yards in a dream matchup against the Bengals in Ewers’ first start. Last week, Greg Dulcich usurped Waller completely. With Waller’s season now over, Dulcich has the role all to himself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fa0-d968-a19b-7ff16e650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) was limited in practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fa4-d56e-afff-ffec8c840000</link>
      <description>Kincaid missed Week 17’s loss to the Eagles with a knee injury, but the 26-year-old tight end has practiced in a limited fashion all week this week. We expect him to suit up against the Jets in Week 18, though he could see fewer snaps given his condition and the Bills already being locked into a Wild Card spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7fa4-d56e-afff-ffec8c840000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
