<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb2-d651-a9df-efb7b64d0000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be fine, but Ertz missed Wednesday’s practice with the ailment. Given how things are trending for the Commanders main passing weapons, Ertz could be in for a throwback game against a weak Cowboys pass defense in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb2-d651-a9df-efb7b64d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (hip) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeaa-df81-ab9b-feef98d70000</link>
      <description>Outstanding news. Olave appeared on Wednesday’s injury report as a limited participant but he is now firmly on track to play in Week 7 against the Bears. The two struggling defenses should facilitate a fantasy-friendly environment for both teams’ offensive stars. Olave’s 61 targets are second only to Puka Nacua’s 64. Olave is a locked-in WR2 with upside this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeaa-df81-ab9b-feef98d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb5-d651-a9df-efb5f2760000</link>
      <description>We expect Pearsall to officially be listed as a non-participant once again when the 49ers’ injury report comes out later today. The 49ers’ wide receiver has neither practiced nor played since spraining his PCL in Week 4, and appears to be heading toward another missed game this weekend. Kendrick Bourne could again operate as the 49ers’ No. 1 wide receiver when they face the Falcons on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb5-d651-a9df-efb5f2760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (ankle) said he will play in Week 7 against the Commanders “without limitations.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eecb-d651-a9df-efdf38400000</link>
      <description>Lamb told reporters that he could have played in Week 6 against the Panthers, but sat out an extra week so he could be “fully healthy” upon his return. Lamb remains sidelined through two Week 7 practices, but we assume this is simply a precautionary measure as the star wide receiver eases back into action following a high-ankle sprain suffered in Week 3. He can immediately be started as a high-end WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eecb-d651-a9df-efdf38400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eebc-d99b-a1dd-febc711e0000</link>
      <description>Cowboys RG Tyler Booker (ankle) also remained limited on Thursday. Both players are on track to play, though it would be nice to see them graduate to full participation on Friday. Turpin is unlikely to be fantasy relevant, earning targets behind WRs CeeDee Lamb (ankle) and George Pickens, plus TE Jake Ferguson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eebc-d99b-a1dd-febc711e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eead-df81-ab9b-feeff3690000</link>
      <description>Murray’s limited participation reportedly included throwing passes to practice squad players. At this point, it seems likely that backup QB Jacoby Brissett starts for the Cardinals in Week 7 against the Packers. Murray’s mobility is a key aspect of his game. If he is at all compromised in that regard, the Cardinals are likely better off going with Brissett, who remains a somewhat capable pocket passer at 32 years old.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eead-df81-ab9b-feeff3690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) was limited in practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeda-da18-a39b-fedbcc010000</link>
      <description>Harrison was limited yesterday as well. Today, Harrison sported a yellow non-contact jersey while participating in team drills, as is standard for players in phase four (club-based, non-contact drills) of the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol. Harrison is close to returning, but he must remain setback-free and graduate to full football activity before he can retake the field. He should be considered questionable at this time, though today’s limited, yellow-jersey session is encouraging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeda-da18-a39b-fedbcc010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Michael Wilson (foot) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eed7-d651-a9df-efd731210000</link>
      <description>Wilson is now in position to handle No. 2 wide receiver duties in Week 7 against the Packers. Fellow WR Zay Jones (knee) has not yet practiced this week and No. 1 WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) is making his way through the NFL’s concussion protocol. Wilson’s target-earning ability is unreliable, though, rendering him just a dart-throw FLEX in the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eed7-d651-a9df-efd731210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eee7-df81-ab9b-fee71ed30000</link>
      <description>Knight is now on track to handle lead-back duties for the Cardinals in Week 7 against the Packers. The Packers’ defensive front has dealt with a number of injuries this season, though the defense remains strong as a whole. Knight’s role warrants RB3/FLEX consideration, though a ceiling game may be difficult to come by.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eee7-df81-ab9b-fee71ed30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB JJ McCarthy (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eedb-df81-ab9b-fedfa2b30000</link>
      <description>That makes two straight limited sessions for McCarthy while QB Carson Wentz (shoulder) continues to practice in full. It sure looks like Wentz will be the Vikings’ Week 7 starter against his former team, the Eagles. Wentz can be viewed as a QB2 this week while McCarthy remains a worthwhile bench stash in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eedb-df81-ab9b-fedfa2b30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
