<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Broncos are “optimistic” that Patrick Surtain (pectoral) can return after their Week 12 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b2-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa10830000</link>
      <description>Ditto Alex Singleton (illness), who had surgery aimed to remove testicular cancer that feels a little bigger than the (illness) tag implies. These would be two major defensive pieces back for the stretch run. It’s possible each of them return for Week 13 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b2-d1e7-a1fa-dbfa10830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said K Eddy Pineiro (hamstring) has a strain and is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b5-d45b-affe-d7b7b81a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers will have a kicker workout on Tuesday or Wednesday. Given the 49ers’ offensive firepower and how often Shanahan is willing to settle for field goals, whoever the 49ers sign could be worthy of fantasy consideration in Week 12 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b5-d45b-affe-d7b7b81a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said LB Tatum Bethune (ankle) has a high-ankle sprain and will miss “a few” weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b7-d673-a39e-b7b78ba00000</link>
      <description>Curtis Robinson was the main replacement for Bethune, who left Week 11’s game against the Cardinals after 24 snaps. Bethune, who took the middle linebacker mantle for the injured Fred Warner, played some pretty decent run defense as a fill-in. He’s expected to avoid injured reserve at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93b7-d673-a39e-b7b78ba00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Ja’Marr Chase has been suspended for one game for spitting on Steelers DB Jalen Ramsey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93bd-d713-ad9e-fffd14a00000</link>
      <description>Tape don’t lie. Shortly after he denied spitting on Ramsey in Week 11’s loss to the Steelers, videos emerged that clearly showed Chase spitting on Ramsey during a scuffle between the two in the fourth quarter. Ramsey was ejected for punching Chase following the incident, but the league appears to have sided with him in this matter. Chase can and will appeal the league’s decision to suspend him if he chooses to do so, but the evidence is pretty convincing. Chase will miss Week 12’s game against the Patriots if the suspension is upheld.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93bd-d713-ad9e-fffd14a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams S Quentin Lake (elbow) will be “sidelined for an undetermined amount of time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93c0-d673-a39e-b7d1f7820000</link>
      <description>The Rams are having testing done on Lake’s elbow and have said it’s possible that he’ll be placed on injured reserve. Sean McVay said he was “bummed out for him,” which seems to forecast a significant injury. Lake played 32 snaps in Week 11’s win over the Seahawks, with Jaylen McCollough and Josh Wallace getting extra work after he left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93c0-d673-a39e-b7d1f7820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendrickson (hip) is doubtful for Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93e2-d45b-affe-d7f6521f0000</link>
      <description>Taylor said the same of Hendrickson at the start of last week before the star pass rusher was eventually ruled out. It sounds as if Hendrickson is a near lock to miss his third-straight game with this injury, which will have sidelined him for nearly a month by the time Sunday’s game against the Patriots comes around. The decision not to place Hendrickson on IR would suggest he could have a shot at returning in Week 13 against the Ravens, although we’ll wait to see how practice unfolds before drawing any conclusions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93e2-d45b-affe-d7f6521f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed K Jake Moody, formerly of the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93eb-d673-a39e-b7fbb3720000</link>
      <description>A former third-round pick of the Niners back in 2023, Moody was waived by the 49ers for missing two kicks in Week 1’s win over the 49ers. The third-year kicker missed a whopping 10 kicks last season, but has gone 8-for-9 on his attempts in two games with the Bears, although he notably hasn’t attempted a field goal from 50-plus yards this season. Moody replaces Matt Gay, whose struggles primarily came from distances of 50-plus yards. If the goal is to find a kicker with more range, it seems unlikely that Moody will prove to be the difference-maker the Commanders are looking for. For his career, Moody is 6-for-12 on attempts from 50-plus yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-93eb-d673-a39e-b7fbb3720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (ankle) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9417-d673-a39e-b49713a50000</link>
      <description>Although there don’t appear to be any reasons for concern regarding Collins’ status ahead of a Thursday Night Football showdown with the Bills, the same cannot be said of quarterback C.J. Stroud, who continued to be listed as a non-participant on Monday’s estimated practice report as he pushes to clear the league’s concussion protocol. Stroud has yet to see the practice field in any capacity, something he will need to rectify if he wants to make it back in time for Thursday. He will only have two chances to do so. Tight end Dalton Schultz was also listed as limited Monday but, like Collins, appears to be trending towards suiting up against the Bills. Fantasy managers will want to track the coming practice reports diligently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9417-d673-a39e-b49713a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared DT Solomon Thomas, RB Jaydon Blue, WR Jonathan Mingo, LB Damone Clark, CB Trikweze Bridges, and OL Hakeem Adeniji inactive for Week 11 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-941c-d1e7-a1fa-defe751e0000</link>
      <description>Malik Davis was elevated ahead of Monday Night Football, likely to serve as the direct backup to Javonte Williams. The Cowboys enjoy relative health as they take on the Raiders in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-941c-d1e7-a1fa-defe751e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Zamir White, S Chris Smith II, G Calbe Rogers, WR Alex Bachman, DT JJ Pegues, and DL Leki Fotu inactive for Week 11 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9437-d673-a39e-b4b709920000</link>
      <description>The Raiders enter their showdown with the Cowboys as one of the healthier teams in the league. Raheem Mostert should serve as the primary change of pace option in the backfield behind starter Ashton Jeanty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9437-d673-a39e-b4b709920000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
