<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 21:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylin Noel caught 5-of-6 targets for 63 yards in the Texans’ Week 8 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2248-deb1-a39b-234e89fd0000</link>
      <description>The overall stat line is good, but Noel simply isn’t seeing the usage that Jayden Higgins is. A 44-yard play-action catch made up the bulk of Noel’s stat line in what was mostly a dink-and-dunk attack. The fact that Noel played just 31 of 80 snaps is frustrating — he looks the part of a fantasy football league winner, but the Texans simply haven’t unleashed him yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2248-deb1-a39b-234e89fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed 14 times for 34 yards in the Patriots’ Week 8 win over the Browns, adding one catch for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-223b-d5d8-a3ff-fb7bf4ed0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson once again started in the Pats’ backfield and had three carries for zero yards and one reception for 15 yards on the first possession of the game. He showed less burst than TreVeyon Henderson against the Browns, tallying 2.4 yards per carry. Stevenson still vastly out-snapped Henderson 47-to-14, indicating it is still the veteran’s backfield. He is a low-end RB2 based on his usage for Week 9 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-223b-d5d8-a3ff-fb7bf4ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 3-of-4 passes for 30 yards in a Week 8 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2244-deb1-a39b-234ef9510000</link>
      <description>The Bills didn’t need much from the passing game with James Cook rushing for over 200 yards. Still, it’s a little concerning from a fantasy perspective that Coleman has been unable to connect with Josh Allen on any big plays since Week 1. Some of that is on Coleman, but a decent amount of blame is on Josh Allen’s inconsistent performance and the Bills’ offensive scheme. He can be left on benches in deeper fantasy formats in case the Bills can figure out their passing game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2244-deb1-a39b-234ef9510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 7-of-9 targets for 63 yards in the Ravens’ Week 8 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2247-dab4-a3fb-bb7711410000</link>
      <description>Flowers was leaned on early by Tyler Huntley in his return to Baltimore. The Ravens’ WR1 ripped off a 20-yard gain on the Ravens’ second possession that helped set up an eventual Derrick Henry touchdown, and was instrumental in moving the ball downfield on the team’s third possession, catching three passes for another 26 yards to help position them for a field goal. Most of Flowers’ production came in the first half, and his day could have been much bigger had Huntley not missed him on a deep throw down the middle of the field in the third quarter. Still, fantasy managers won’t be disappointed with the effort or the volume. Flowers will have high-end WR2 upside in Week 9’s tilt with the Dolphins, which should feature the return of Lamar Jackson (hamstring).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2247-dab4-a3fb-bb7711410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 1-of-3 targets for 23 yards in a Week 8 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-d245-adfb-b75fd66f0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid returned to action after missing Week 7 with an oblique injury, but the Bills didn’t need him with James Cook rushing for 216 yards in a blowout win. Kincaid should play a much bigger role next week against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-d245-adfb-b75fd66f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 2-of-5 targets for 26 yards in the Giants’ Week 8 loss against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-dab4-a3fb-bb7be16f0000</link>
      <description>Slayton’s box score could have been much bigger if his long second half touchdown hadn’t been called back on a suspect offensive pass interference call. Slayton, back from a hamstring injury, led the Giants with five targets in this one. As Jaxson Dart’s primary downfield option, Slayton will enter Week 9 against the Niners with some upside, though he’ll remain a volatile fantasy option who should only be rostered in deep leagues. He has just 14 receptions on the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-dab4-a3fb-bb7be16f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers DT Jordan Elliott (ankle) left San Francisco’s Week 8 game against the Texans and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224d-deb1-a39b-234f96f50000</link>
      <description>The 49ers continue to rack up injuries on defense. Elliott played 18 snaps before being ruled out, and Alfred Collins will assume a bigger role going forward with Elliott out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224d-deb1-a39b-234f96f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 10 times for 77 yards and a fumble in the Patriots’ Week 8 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bc1290000</link>
      <description>Henderson finally ripped off some explosive plays in Week 8 against the Browns, including a career-long 27-yard rush for his first carry over 20 yards this season. The good news is he seemed to get nothing but first downs when he was in the game, converting his four of his first five carries into first downs. The bad news is that he only saw 14 snaps, no targets, and fumbled for the first time since before his college days in the red zone in the fourth quarter. Henderson got more usage on outside runs in space and will continue to find success as that type of players. He has some FLEX upside for Week 9 against the Falcons, but just doesn’t have the usage to be anything more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bc1290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 2-of-4 targets for 51 yards in the Ravens’ Week 8 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224c-d5d8-a3ff-fb6d53950000</link>
      <description>On one hand, Bateman saw more targets than the 2.8 per game he was averaging entering the day. On the other hand, it was a typical low-production day for the veteran receiver, who would’ve had a completely forgettable outing were it not for a 36-yard reception on the opening play of the second half. Even with Lamar Jackson set to return in Week 9 against the Dolphins, Bateman can be left off the fantasy radar now and for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-224c-d5d8-a3ff-fb6d53950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
