<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 19-of-30 passes for 174 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ 13-11, Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d950-db72-a199-fb5b08dc0000</link>
      <description>Denver put up 10 points in the first quarter and promptly took the next three quarters off. Nix threw for 135 yards and a touchdown in the first half. He managed just 39 yards in the second half. Denver went three-and-out on four of their six second-half drives, excluding a pair of kneel-downs to end the game. They also took a safety on a holding penalty in the end zone in the third quarter. The Broncos are now 4-2, but Nix has thrown for more than 206 yards just twice and has two multi-score games. Even if they continue to grind out ugly wins, Nix has played himself out of the QB1 ranks heading into his Week 7 matchup with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d950-db72-a199-fb5b08dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson caught 3-of-8 targets for 13 yards in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d957-def2-abdb-dd7773320000</link>
      <description>It was a nightmare performance for the entire Jets offense, but no player was more impacted by the team’s struggles than Wilson. Week 6 will go down as his season-low in catches and a season-low in yards by 37. Justin Fields routinely missed throws to Wilson or was late to make the throw, allowing a defender to break up the pass. Things reached a boiling point at the end of the first half when the Jets let the clock run out in the middle of what appeared to be their most successful drive of the day. Wilson gave his coaches an earful on the way to the locker room at halftime. Wilson then got banged up in the second half. He got up slowly multiple times and even missed a handful of plays in the third and fourth quarters while on the bench or being looked at by trainers. Head coach Aaron Glenn called it a hip injury after the game. The Jets have struggled on offense this year, but this was a new low. Wilson should be able to rebound as a high-end WR2 versus the Panthers next week, but his WR1 days may have come to an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d957-def2-abdb-dd7773320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Dobbins rushed 14 times for 40 yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d964-dd4c-afb9-ffe509250000</link>
      <description>Dobbins dropped his only target of the day. It was the worst week of the year for the veteran back by most stats, including yards and yards per carry. It was also his first game without a reception and just his second without a touchdown. Denver’s passing game didn’t pose much of a threat in this contest and Dobbins was bottled up on the majority of his attempts. His longest gain was an eight-yard tote. The good news is that he ceded just three carries to his backups. Things should turn around for Dobbins and the offense in Week 7 when they face the Giants. Dobbins will stay in the RB2 ranks despite the quiet showing in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d964-dd4c-afb9-ffe509250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) is inactive for Week 6 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d966-d94a-a79d-d96f19b80000</link>
      <description>Ward suffered a concussion in pre-game warmups and is out against the Cardinals. Rookie UDFA Johnathan Edwards is starting in his place for an already banged-up Colts secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d966-d94a-a79d-d96f19b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed two times for four yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets, adding four catches for 21 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d969-def2-abdb-dd698a840000</link>
      <description>The Broncos made Tyler Badie inactive for this game, but it didn’t make much of a difference for Harvey’s role. Jaleel McLaughlin pitched in for some work on passing downs and Harvey was again relegated to distant No. 2 duties. He did, however, tie his season-high in receptions. Harvey isn’t closing the gap on J.K. Dobbins and doesn’t have a weekly floor of designed touches. He is barely on the fantasy radar as FLEX play heading into Week 7 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d969-def2-abdb-dd698a840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals TE Travis Vokolek was carted off in Week 6 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d96e-db72-a199-fb6f97be0000</link>
      <description>Vokolek was hurt on a kickoff return in the first quarter against the Cardinals. He was unable to get up and was placed on a medical stretcher and carted off. It looks to be a serious injury for Vokolek that will keep him out beyond Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d96e-db72-a199-fb6f97be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 5-of-6 targets for 42 yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d96e-def2-abdb-dd6f24a20000</link>
      <description>Engram got going early in the game with four catches in the first half. The Broncos’ offense all but disappeared after halftime and Engram caught one pass for 12 yards over the final 30 minutes of action. He also lost a touchdown to backup tight end Nate Adkins in the first half. Engram is still a part-time player, which greatly reduces his weekly fantasy ceiling. His role on underneath work, however, gives him a solid floor in PPR leagues. He will remain at the top of the ET2 ranks for Week 7 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d96e-def2-abdb-dd6f24a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nate Atkins caught both of his targets for 23 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d975-def2-abdb-dd75c6fc0000</link>
      <description>Atkins typically plays a blocking role, but he broke free for a 16-yard score in the first quarter, giving him his first touchdown of the season. He is still splitting reps with Evan Engram, though the latter operates as the team’s primary pass-catching tight end. It should go without saying, but Atkins is not on the fantasy radar for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d975-def2-abdb-dd75c6fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 1-of-3 targets for 17 yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d977-dd4c-afb9-fff753e50000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ offense struggled to get much going outside of check-downs versus the Jets. Sutton, in turn, was scarcely involved. He finished fourth on the team in targets and logged a measly 10 percent target share. It goes down as his second one-catch game of the season. He had one such game all of last year. Denver’s offense has yet to find its footing this year, and Sutton’s box scores have taken a hit as a result. He should, however, get a good shot at a rebound game versus the Giants’ defense next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d977-dd4c-afb9-fff753e50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
