<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:29:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills completed an interview with OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ab-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2a90000</link>
      <description>Hiring Brady would certainly make for a smooth transition. The Bills’ offensive coordinator has served in his current role for the past two seasons. He was the Bills’ quarterbacks coach in 2022 and 2023, and was promoted to interim offensive coordinator in the latter year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ab-dc7a-af9b-efbfa2a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed an interview with former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2b1-dc7a-af9b-efbff3b10000</link>
      <description>McCarthy took the year after being relieved of his duties with the Cowboys following the 2024 season. McCarthy also interviewed with the Giants and Titans, though both organizations chose to go with other candidates. McCarthy’s 2024 Cowboys squad averaged just 5.0 yards per play during the regular season, ranking 27th among NFL offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2b1-dc7a-af9b-efbff3b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed TE Jaheim Bell to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e279-d56e-afff-e6f912390000</link>
      <description>Bell was drafted by the Patriots in 2024. He did not make the roster this year and joined the Eagles’ practice squad. That didn’t last long and he spent the end of the year on the Steelers’ practice squad. Back in Philly, Bell could crack the team’s roster if Dallas Goedert walks in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e279-d56e-afff-e6f912390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills scheduled an interview with Commanders run game coordinator and RB coach Anthony Lynn for their head-coaching vacancy on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2c2-d968-a19b-faf3dffd0000</link>
      <description>Lynn, 57, has served in his current roles over the last two seasons. In the two seasons before that, he served as the 49ers’ assistant head coach and running backs coach. He spent the 2021 season as the Lions’ offensive coordinator following a four-year run as the Chargers’ head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2c2-d968-a19b-faf3dffd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2e8-d968-a19b-faf92ffb0000</link>
      <description>Landry has been dealing with the knee issue for a few weeks now but played through it the first two playoff games for the Patriots. Also not practicing was LB Marte Mapu (hip). Mapu has not played in the playoffs yet, so he is more of a question mark. Given he has played through the knee injury already, Landry has a better chance of playing in the AFC Championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2e8-d968-a19b-faf92ffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ee-d968-a19b-faffc06f0000</link>
      <description>Darnold was dealing with an oblique injury last week and he reportedly did not throw a football between suffering the injury Thursday and the Divisional Round on Saturday. However, he did not look hindered in the Seahawks’ win over the 49ers, tossing for 124 yards and a touchdown on 17 passing attempts. Darnold starts off the week limited in practice and is in line to play in the NFC Championship against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2ee-d968-a19b-faffc06f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e30e-d968-a19b-fbffa5db0000</link>
      <description>Cross left in the Divisional Round against the 49ers with a foot injury. He was previously dealing with hamstring/knee injuries as well, with the Divisional Round being his only game played since Week 15. Head coach Mike Macdonald said on Monday that Cross is day-to-day, indicating the left tackle will play in the Championship game against the Rams. With backup left tackles Josh Jones (knee/ankle) and Amari Knight (knee) also dealing with injuries and not practicing, the Seahawks have slim options at the position if Cross cannot go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e30e-d968-a19b-fbffa5db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams EDGE Byron Young (knee) did not practice in Wednesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e315-d56e-afff-e7fd95b50000</link>
      <description>Young tallied five combined tackles in the Rams’ Divisional Round win over the Bears. He starts out this week not practicing due to a knee injury he has been managing for a good chunk of this season. Also not practicing was DB Quentin Lake (illness). Practice reports later in the week will provide more clarity, but both Young and Lake look to be playing in the Championship game against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e315-d56e-afff-e7fd95b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed defensive coordinator Brian Flores to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e319-d35e-a1bf-e7db57b80000</link>
      <description>The Vikings made the announcement Wednesday that they signed Flores to an extension. The 44-year-old led the Vikings defense to back-to-back top-10 finishes by points allowed. He was interviewing for both defensive coordinator and head coaching jobs this offseason, but now guarantees a return to Minnesota if he cannot land a head coaching role. Flores is still in the running for the Steelers and Ravens head coaching vacancies, though he will get more time to build the Vikings’ defense if he does not get hired this coaching cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e319-d35e-a1bf-e7db57b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Packers are interviewing Bears defensive backs coach Al Harris for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e31e-d968-a19b-fbff7e250000</link>
      <description>Harris is the Bears’ defensive pass game coordinator and defensive backs coach. He played a prominent role in building the Bears’ defense this season and is an established leader around the league. With 13 years of coaching under his belt, Harris has spent the last six season with the Cowboys and Bears. A former player for the Packers, Harris is now interviewing for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e31e-d968-a19b-fbff7e250000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
