<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared RB Rhamondre Stevenson, S John Saunders, EDGE Caleb Murphy, DT Eric Gregory, OT Caedan Wallace, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 9 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456d-d673-a39e-e5fd6beb0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson was declared out earlier this week due to a toe issue, leaving TreVeyon Henderson, Terrell Jennings and D’Ernest Johnson as the Pats’ three backs. DeVito will serve as the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456d-d673-a39e-e5fd6beb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared DE Samson Ebukam, RB DJ Giddens, WR Anthony Gould, DE Tyquan Lewis, S Reuben Lowery III, TE Will Mallory, and OT Luke Tenuta inactive for Week 9 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4568-d713-ad9e-6d7cb0290000</link>
      <description>Lewis is a bit of a surprise scratch after logging full practices in back-to-back days to close out the week and drawing a questionable tag, but everything else is as we expected. The Colts are operating at near full strength ahead of Sunday’s AFC showdown with the 4-3 Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4568-d713-ad9e-6d7cb0290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LB Quay Walker (calf) is active for Week 9 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456e-d713-ad9e-6d7eef810000</link>
      <description>Walker was a surprise DNP in the middle of the week because of the calf injury. He returned for a limited session on Friday before being listed as questionable. Brandon McManus was also questionable and is active. Inactive for the Packers are WR Dontayvion Wicks, K Lucas Havrisik, OG Jacob Monk, OT Donovan Jennings, DL Lukas Van Ness, and DL Warren Brinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456e-d713-ad9e-6d7eef810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions T Taylor Decker (shoulder) is active for Detroit’s Week 9 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456e-d1e7-a1fa-5feee2a30000</link>
      <description>He’ll play off a questionable tag, as he’s done for most of this season. Inactive for the Lions are: S Erick Hallett II, S Kerby Joseph, DL Mekhi Wingo, DL Quinton Jefferson, RB Craig Reynolds, S Jammie Robinson. Every questionable player for the Lions is playing (Avonte Maddox, Sione Vaki) while Joseph (knee) and Reynolds (hamstring) were ruled out on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-456e-d1e7-a1fa-5feee2a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) is active for Week 9 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbded00000</link>
      <description>Flacco had been listed as questionable to face the Bears after sustaining a shoulder injury last week against the Jets. He’ll play through the injury against a soft Chicago defense, but presents a very real in-game injury risk. The fantasy prospects of every Bengals player rely on Flacco being under center for the pass-heavy Cincinnati offense. Bengals declared CB Marco Wilson, LB Logan Wilson, OL Dalton Risner, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, and DE Trey Hendrickson (hip) inactive against Chicago. With Hendrickson out, the Bengals defense presents an even better matchup for Caleb Williams and the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbded00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared S Jevon Holland, CB Paulson Adebo, CB Cor’Dale Flott, DL Chauncey Golston, OT Jermaine Eleumunor, and TE Daniel Bellinger inactive for Week 9 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d673-a39e-e5f159ed0000</link>
      <description>Holland tested his knee out in pre-game warmups but wasn’t cleared to play. He will look to return in Week 10 against the Bears. The Giants are down multiple starters this week, making them a strong matchup for Mac Jones, who is a solid QB2 option in Superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d673-a39e-e5f159ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Scotty Miller, S Chuck Clark, S Jabrill Peppers, LB Cole Holcomb, OG Andrus Peat, and DT Logan Lee inactive for Week 9 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4570-d45b-affe-55f695a00000</link>
      <description>Both Clark and Holcomb were ruled out before the weekend, so there are no notable surprises here. The Steelers, who have dropped their last two games are hoping a home matchup against the Colts can break in their favor as they look to distance themselves from the resurgent Ravens in the AFC North.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4570-d45b-affe-55f695a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared RB D’Andre Swift, WR Luther Burden III, RB Roschon Johnson, DE Dominique Robinson, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 9 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4575-d45b-affe-55f7abb70000</link>
      <description>The Bears will be without their lead back for the first time in 2025. That leaves rookie RB Kyle Monangai as the team’s default RB1 against one of the worst rush defenses in the NFL. Monangai, who has 20 carries over his past two outings, should be in every 12-team league fantasy lineup today, facing a Bengals defense allowing 133 rushing yards per game this season. Burden’s absence should mean more routes and targets for Olamide Zaccheaus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4575-d45b-affe-55f7abb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Terry McLaurin (quad) is expected to miss Week 10 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4573-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbf31b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport also mentioned that McLaurin could miss Week 11. The Commanders then get a Week 12 bye, giving McLaurin a month to recover from his lingering quad injury. The Commanders didn’t put him on injured reserve, which would have forced him to sit for at least four games. That means they expect him to be back with fewer than four games missed, though things have yet to go as expected for McLaurin this year. Luke McCaffrey and Chris Moore will round out the team’s starting wide receiver trio until McLaurin returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4573-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbf31b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaguars LB Devin Lloyd (calf) is not expected to play in Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-457c-d45b-affe-55fee18a0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd had a chance to return to action this week after being listed as questionable on Friday. He was limited in practice throughout the week. Holding him out for one more game should ensure Lloyd doesn’t re-aggravate the issue. He will eye a Week 10 return against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-457c-d45b-affe-55fee18a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
