<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury said he was “still confident” in Jacory Croskey-Merritt despite his fumbles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee53-d651-a9df-ef57d4a00000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt put the ball on the turf in each of the last two games, while Jayden Daniels bobbled a handoff on a snap to “Bill” in the fourth quarter that also wound up as a Commanders turnover. It’s never a good sign when the offensive coordinator is being asked about the fumbles as a frequent problem, but it doesn’t sound like the Commanders have wavered from “Bill” despite this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee53-d651-a9df-ef57d4a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee55-d651-a9df-ef558e3b0000</link>
      <description>Demercado is heading toward a Week 7 absence. Assuming this is the case, and Bam Knight is able to play through his knee injury, the Cardinals will again employ a two-player backfield featuring Knight and RB Michael Carter. Knight handled primary rushing duties while Carter operated as the passing game specialist in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee55-d651-a9df-ef558e3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee56-d651-a9df-ef5703c70000</link>
      <description>Njoku is enough of a veteran to possibly get a Friday practice going, ride a questionable tag, and play on Sunday. We haven’t quite ruled him out yet, but odds are certainly dwindling that he’ll be active. If he were to be inactive, Harold Fannin would have a great matchup against the Dolphins and, along with Quinshon Judkins, would seem likely to take advantage of it on the surface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee56-d651-a9df-ef5703c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee59-d99b-a1dd-fe5d2b1f0000</link>
      <description>It does not look like Ridley is going to make it to active status after former head coach Brian Callahan said following Week 6’s injury exit that he couldn’t run. His absence will likely open up Elic Ayomanor and Van Jefferson as potential low-end-to-desperate FLEX options against the Patriots in what projects as another trailing game script for Cam Ward and the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee59-d99b-a1dd-fe5d2b1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee74-d651-a9df-ef75b9400000</link>
      <description>Hubbard’s continued participation puts him on track to play, though he should not yet be considered a lock to do so. If Hubbard can upgrade to full participation on Friday, he should be good to go for Week 7 against the Jets, but the team could opt to rest him if he remains limited once again. Panthers head coach Dave Canales has indicated that Hubbard will split backfield touches with RB Rico Dowdle upon his return, but the exact touch count distribution remains ambiguous. Given Hubbard’s current limitations, the team could let Dowdle handle starting duties this week, even if Hubbard is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee74-d651-a9df-ef75b9400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee64-df81-ab9b-fee738300000</link>
      <description>Sanders is seemingly on track to play in his first game since the Panthers’ Week 3 win over the Falcons. Unfortunately, slot WR Jalen Coker (quad) is also on track to play, which pushes Sanders further down the target pecking order than when he last took the field. Sanders is a boom-bust TE2 if active this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee64-df81-ab9b-fee738300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers placed S Miles Killebrew (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee8f-df81-ab9b-fecf0f7e0000</link>
      <description>Killebrew’s season is over. The safety is mainly a key special teams cog and has played just 141 defensive snaps over the past four years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee8f-df81-ab9b-fecf0f7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee95-d651-a9df-ef95edc50000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Wednesday will be a rest day going forward for Kamara as he is dealing with this ankle injury, Kamara will likely be limited and possibly questionable for Sunday. But since he already did this last week, he figures again to be part of a platoon against the Bears at running back. Kendre Miller and Taysom Hill have each cordoned off their own roles in this backfield, sapping a little juice from Kamara’s role, though the extra receptions last week certainly helped his RB2 case for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee95-d651-a9df-ef95edc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers S DeShon Elliott (personal) “will be upgraded to not have a game status designation” and is expected to play in Week 7 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee57-df81-ab9b-fed779a50000</link>
      <description>The news comes directly from the Steelers’ senior director of communications, Burt Lauten, so we read the “expected to play” line as a formality. Elliott missed practice on Tuesday and Wednesday due to a personal issue, but he has now arrived in Cincinnati and is evidently good to go. The Steelers defense is tasked with containing the Joe Flacco-led Bengals on Thursday Night Football this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee57-df81-ab9b-fed779a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee99-d651-a9df-ef9d81d20000</link>
      <description>He hasn’t practiced since injuring his hamstring in Week 5’s loss to the Saints. With no real timeline for him to be active that is public, shallow league managers can probably move on from Slayton for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee99-d651-a9df-ef9d81d20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
