<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed 12 times for 65 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4805-d1e7-a1fa-5aef216f0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez saw increased work after the team fell behind 31-7 entering the half, cashing in on his second garbage time touchdown in a three-game span. The Commanders lost quarterback Jayden Daniels to what appeared to be a broken left arm in the fourth quarter, potentially setting up another game with negative script for the Commanders when they host the Lions in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4805-d1e7-a1fa-5aef216f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught all four targets for 46 yards in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4807-d673-a39e-ec97bc3e0000</link>
      <description>Another week, another blowout loss for a Commanders team that is now going to be without starting quarterback Jayden Daniels for the foreseeable future following a fourth quarter broken arm. Ertz has notched no more than four receptions in the three games started by Marcus Mariota this season, spelling trouble for his fantasy expectations for the rest of the season. That starts with a Week 10 matchup with the 5-3 Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4807-d673-a39e-ec97bc3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 5-of-6 targets for 41 yards in the Commanders’ Week 9 loss to the Seahawks, adding three yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-480a-d1e7-a1fa-5aea2b8a0000</link>
      <description>Samuel and the rest of the Washington receiving cadre will be without quarterback Jayden Daniels for the foreseeable future after the second-year starter injured his left arm in the fourth quarter of the blowout loss. The five receptions were a season low in games started by Daniels, but Samuel has caught only 11 balls in three Marcus Mariota starts this season. Fantasy managers are likely best looking elsewhere for wide receiver production, starting in Week 10 when the Commanders host the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-480a-d1e7-a1fa-5aea2b8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports X-rays on Jayden Daniels’ elbow were negative.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d0-d713-ad9e-6dd42a700000</link>
      <description>These negative X-rays confirm that Daniels did not suffer any kind of fracture when he went down in Sunday night’s game against the Seahawks. The MRI, however, will determine what, if any, ligament damage occurred and how severe it is. There’s still a lot to learn here, but this news, coupled with an earlier report from Rapoport that said “there is a chance this is not a season-ending injury” for Daniels, is a very encouraging sign. We’ll likely know more before the day is over, but it goes without saying that Daniels is out for the foreseeable future, putting Marcus Mariota back in the starting role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d0-d713-ad9e-6dd42a700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles acquired LB Jaelan Phillips from the Dolphins in exchange for a 2026 third-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d6-d1e7-a1fa-5bfee6a50000</link>
      <description>The Eagles continue to bolster their defense via the trade market ahead of Tuesday’s deadline. Phillips, who is on an expiring contract, becomes the third defensive player to be acquired by the Eagles in the last week and should provide an immediate boost to a pass rush that ranks 23rd in the league with 16 sacks. According to NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo,the Eagles are trading their own third-round pick to the Finsas opposed to the one they acquired from the Jets in the Haason Reddick deal, and Phillips will also count toward the Eagles’ compensatory formula should he leave next offseason via free agency. Phillips has totaled 15 tackles and three sacks for the Dolphins this season, and has often looked like a player on the verge of a breakout season before a devastating injury cuts things short. He’ll have a chance to breakout with the Eagles defense over the final nine weeks of the season in hopes of bolstering their defense while also building his case as a top free agent next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-49d6-d1e7-a1fa-5bfee6a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Luke McCaffrey suffered a broken collarbone in Week 9’s loss to the Seahawks, likely ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a06-d1e7-a1fa-5aee79c70000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey fielded the opening kickoff to start the game and immediately left the field after being tackled. The second-year receiver, who has caught 11 passes for 203 yards and three touchdowns this season, will likely miss the remainder of the year, in what has become a season to forget for the now 3-6 Commanders. Assuming his recovery goes as expected, McCaffrey should be back in time for training camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a06-d1e7-a1fa-5aee79c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Commanders believe Marshon Lattimore suffered a torn ACL in Week 9’s loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a20-d673-a39e-eeb116820000</link>
      <description>The hits keep coming. After possibly losing Jayden Daniels (elbow) and Luke McCaffrey (collarbone) for the season, the Commanders may now be looking at another season-ending injury. Lattimore will undergo an MRI to confirm, but it sounds like the veteran corner is shaping up to miss the remainder of the season with his injury. Lattimore has struggled since arriving in Washington, consistently getting beaten in coverage while also being among the most penalized cornerbacks in the league. The Commanders traded a third-round pick to the Saints last season to acquire him ahead of the deadline. He remains under contract through 2026 butcan be cut for a cap savings of $18.5 million, per OverTheCap.com.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a20-d673-a39e-eeb116820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Bengals are still seeking a first-round pick for Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a93-d1e7-a1fa-5afbd5360000</link>
      <description>The asking price remains high for Hendrickson, who did not play in Week 9 due to a hip injury and has managed just four sacks in the seven games he has appeared in this season. Hendrickson is still on an expiring contract and has reportedly generated interest from multiple teams, per a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter over the weekend. With the trade deadline set for Tuesday, there is still time for the Bengals to lower the asking price if they hope to move Hendrickson for some assets, but for now, the price remains high for one of the league’s premiere pass rushers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a93-d1e7-a1fa-5afbd5360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns designated WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a95-d45b-affe-5f9760190000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin Stefanski said last week that the team hopes to have Tillman back after their Week 9 bye, so it’s possible we see Tillman as early as Week 10 against the Jets. Given the release of S Damontae Kazee, it sounds like the team is already clearing room for a return. Tillman enjoyed a five-game stretch last season where he totaled 26 receptions for 330 yards and three touchdowns before a concussion ended his season. In four games this season — all with Joe Flacco, he went for 11-106-2 while averaging five targets per game. While he’s shown an ability to make plays down field, Tillman is now playing with one of the most conservative passers in the league in Dillon Gabriel. It’s hard to imagine him having anything more than WR4 upside in a passing offense that has lived primarily in the short areas of the field since Gabriel took the reins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a95-d45b-affe-5f9760190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
