<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Jacory Croskey-Merritt will not play in the Commanders’ preseason finale against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d796-dbe3-a9bb-f7d746df0000</link>
      <description>Both Croskey-Merritt and Austin Ekeler will sit this one out as the Commanders plan to rest nearly all of their starters. For fantasy managers trying to figure out the Commanders’ running back depth chart ahead of Week 1, Croskey-Merritt and Ekeler sitting out the preseason finale could suggest they’re the top two backs on the depth chart, while Chris Rodriguez and Jeremy McNichols both appear set to play. Croskey-Merritt has been picking up steam all offseason and performed well enough for the Commanders to trade Brian Robinson to the 49ers on Friday. While his touch distribution remains a question mark, it goes without saying that he’s worth adding in fantasy drafts in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d796-dbe3-a9bb-f7d746df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers beat writer Gerry Dulac reports the Steelers don’t plan to place Derrick Harmon (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7b0-de13-afdc-d7fbca450000</link>
      <description>Dulac reported earlier that the Steelers believe Dulac could be out 4-6 weeks. Now, Dulac is reporting that the rookie defensive tackle will likely avoid IR and that the team thinks “it’s possible he will miss only one game.” Harmon was diagnosed with an MCL sprain after exiting the Steelers’ preseason finale against the Panthers on Thursday. When asked about Harmon’s injury, head coach Mike Tomlin classified him as “week-to-week” anddeclined to commenton whether or not the rookie would start the year on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7b0-de13-afdc-d7fbca450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught both targets for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ preseason Week 3 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7e3-dbe3-a9bb-f7f345df0000</link>
      <description>The rookie tight end got the Browns on the board in the first quarter with a 15-yard catch up the seam, holding on through contact as he entered the end zone. Fannin has generated significant buzz throughout the offseason and continues to prove that he’ll be heavily involved in the offense from the jump, indicating a high likelihood we see the Browns deploying elevated rates of 12-personnel alongside veteran David Njoku. The two tight ends combined to see four targets on 10 Joe Flacco pass attempts with the starters on the field against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7e3-dbe3-a9bb-f7f345df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught 2-of-2 targets for 41 yards and one touchdown in the Lions’ preseason game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7fd-dbe3-a9bb-f7ff3a810000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa made a highlight reel touchdown catch in the first quarter when he hauled in a long contested catch down the sideline for a 33-yard score. The rookie third-rounder found the end zone in three of the four preseason games he appeared in this preseason and finishes with a line of 10-154-3 on 14 targets. He’ll face stiff competition for targets from Amon-Ra St. Brown, Jameson Williams, and Sam LaPorta, but TeSlaa is making his case to have an early role in the office after yet another strong showing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d7fd-dbe3-a9bb-f7ff3a810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 10-of-14 passes for 110 yards and one touchdown in the Broncos’ preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d823-db7b-a5dd-f827c4cf0000</link>
      <description>Nix targeted Courtland Sutton on seven of his 14 attempts. He connected with the veteran receiver for gains of 43 and 19 yards on the Broncos’ third drive of the game. The 19-yard pass to Sutton resulted in Nix’s lone touchdown pass of the day, as the second-rounder appeared to be in midseason form in his final preseason game before Week 1 kicks off on September 7th. Nix was impressive in his rookie campaign, throwing for 3,775-29-12 while adding another 430 yards and four touchdowns on the ground. He’ll profile as a fringe QB1/QB2 in fantasy and could be poised for plenty of spike weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d823-db7b-a5dd-f827c4cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 5-of-8 passes for 43 yards in the Saints’ preseason game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d831-db7b-a5dd-f835795d0000</link>
      <description>Rattler drew the start to close out one of the more underwhelming quarterback battles in recent memory. Rattler was in on three drives for the Saints, leading the offense to 53 yards and three points thanks to a 49-yard field goal by Blake Grupe. He also took one sack. Rattler played it safe for most of his outing, finishing with a 6.9 ADOT with his longest pass of the day coming on a 12-yarder to Chris Olave. It wasn’t a bad performance, but there wasn’t anything memorable here. Who wins the Saints’ QB battle is anybody’s guess at this point, but we would expect to see both Rattler and rookier Tyler Shough under center this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d831-db7b-a5dd-f835795d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed five times for 34 yards in the Commanders’ preseason game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d842-dbe3-a9bb-f853f96a0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez figures to be a part of the Commanders’ backfield rotation, but the fact that he drew the start while Austin Ekeler and Jacory Croskey-Merritt will certainly raise questions about where he sits on the depth chart. Rodriguez’s long run of the day came on a 12-yard scamper, as his preseason comes to an end with an impressive 17-118-0 (6.9 YPC) line on the ground. Rodriguez reportedly added some speed to his game this offseason and has the body to be a goal-line vulture for the Commanders should they call on him. There’s a lot to be sorted out here, but it’s possible C-Rod opens the season as the Commanders’ RB3, given the team’s decision to play him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d842-dbe3-a9bb-f853f96a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said QB Lamar Jackson is expected to practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d817-de13-afdc-dedf23ea0000</link>
      <description>Jackson had his foot stepped on during Wednesday’s practice last week. He appears to be on track to practice Monday following clean x-rays, with coach Harbaugh adding a clear out to the media in the form of, “unless he doesn’t want to.” Fans and fantasy managers alike can breath a sigh of relief for the perennial MVP candidate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d817-de13-afdc-dedf23ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dameon Pierce rushed seven times for 17 yards in the Texans’ preseason game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d84b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bb2060000</link>
      <description>With Nick Chubb sidelined for this one, Pierce got the start and did little with the opportunities he received. The fourth-year back was playing mostly with backups but could see work with the starters when the regular season rolls around as Joe Mixon continues to be sidelined with a foot injury. Pierce has struggled mightily since 2022, when he rushed for 220-939-4 as a rookie and could eventually lose playing time to rookie Woody Marks, who was drafted in the fourth round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d84b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bb2060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Shough completed 12-of-20 passes for 102 yards in the Saints’ preseason game against the Broncos, adding two carries for 20 yards and a touchdown on the ground.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85d-dbe3-a9bb-f85f3d3f0000</link>
      <description>Shough played on five drives in this one. The rookie outperformed Spencer Rattler in the box score, but also lost a fumble on a strip sack in the third quarter. Shough would rebound to lead arguably his best drive of the season, driving the Saints 77 yards downfield on 6-of-8 passing for 57 yards and found pay dirt on an 11-yard quarterback keeper to cap the drive. Shough is hoping to beat Rattler for the rights to be named the Saints’ QB1 for Week 1 when they take on the Cardinals. Head coach Kellen Moore has some time before preparing for the first week of the season, but this will be the last test until then. We would expect to get a final word on the starter soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d85d-dbe3-a9bb-f85f3d3f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
