<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Broncos and Cardinals will sit most of their starters, when the two teams play their preseason Week 2 game this weekend.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab17-d90d-a5bd-ab5ff19a0000</link>
      <description>Broncos head coach Sean Payton adds that five or six starters who currently “have a lack of reps” will play on an “eight-play pitch count.” Those five or six players will be worth watching, namely to determine if the group includes players like RJ Harvey, Marvin Mims, Troy Franklin and/or Pat Bryant. Should any of those players take the field, it would be nice to see them get the start and leave quickly thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab17-d90d-a5bd-ab5ff19a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that the Dolphins “never showed any genuine interest in moving [Tyreek] Hill during the offseason.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab27-d45c-a7fc-ab3fc6d00000</link>
      <description>Howe cites “several high-ranking league sources” in the report. Recent buzz around Hill has not been great and he is now nursing an oblique injury. Still, the Dolphins do not appear to be interested in allowing the 31-year-old wide receiver to play elsewhere and Howe thinks that “there’s reason to believe [the distractions have] been left in the past.” If Hill really is turning a corner in his commitment to football, and the Dolphins can get him back to performing at an elite level, it would be a boon to the offense as a whole.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab27-d45c-a7fc-ab3fc6d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said, after reviewing the tape of today’s practice, he has decided to sit Baker Mayfield for the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab2b-d90d-a5bd-ab7b497c0000</link>
      <description>Bowles initially told reporters that all starters, aside from Mike Evans and Lavonte David, would play on Saturday. Per The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Mayfield “played so well today in the joint workout with the Steelers” that Bowles changed his mind. It’s unfortunate for fantasy managers who were hoping to catch a glimpse of Mayfield’s connection with WR Emeka Egbuka but the game should still give us a look at the Buccaneers’ running back rotation with Rachaad White sidelined by a groin injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab2b-d90d-a5bd-ab7b497c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said A.J. Brown (hamstring) is “working through some things” when asked if Brown suffered a setback after missing practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab52-d45c-a7fc-ab5a7f8d0000</link>
      <description>Brown was sidelined by a hamstring strain in early August. He briefly resumed practicing before being sidelined once again. Team reporters are listing Brown as being sidelined by a hamstring injury, though Sirianni’s comments on the matter are vague. For what it’s worth, NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo said, “it feels like the hope is” that Brown resumes practicing “sometime in the near future,” adding that he doesn’t “sense any great concern” from the team, regarding the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ab52-d45c-a7fc-ab5a7f8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said “sooner rather than later would be nice” when asked about when he would like to name the QB1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-adfa-d90d-a5bd-affbec7a0000</link>
      <description>Speaking Thursday, Steichen said he doesn’t “have an exact timetable” on when he will name the Colts’ QB1, but with the Colts’ second preseason set to take place on Saturday against the Packers, it wouldn’t be surprising if Steichen came to a decision on his QB1 before the preseason finale in order to avoid starting him in a meaningless game. Anthony Richardson played only seven snaps last week against the Ravens before exiting the game with a dislocated pinky finger. Steichen will undoubtedly want to get a longer look at him this weekend as he looks to cement his decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-adfa-d90d-a5bd-affbec7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Akron Beacon Journal’s Chris Easterling reports Browns LB Devin Bush’s trial for his domestic violence case has been scheduled for December 2nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae18-d05a-adda-ae9a571a0000</link>
      <description>Bush was arrested in May and faces charges of assault and harassment. The late trial likely means Bush will be available for the Browns for much of the season, as their regular-season schedule concludes on January 4th when they face the Bengals in Week 18, but a late-season suspension, or one to kick off the 2026 campaign, could be on the table should the league pursue one after the trial has concluded. Bush signed a one-year contract with the Browns this offseason after totaling 76 tackles, one sack, and eight TFLs for them last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae18-d05a-adda-ae9a571a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Stone (soft tissue) returned to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae5f-df63-a199-ff7fa59c0000</link>
      <description>Stone was listed as week-to-week last weekend after dealing with an unspecified soft tissue injury. Instead, the veteran safety missed less than a full week of practice and was spotted on the field Friday with the rest of the team. Stone totaled 81 tackles and four interceptions for the Bengals last season and signed a restructured deal this offseason. Barring any setbacks, it sounds like he’ll be good to go for Week 1 when the Bengals take on the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae5f-df63-a199-ff7fa59c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans OC Nick Caley praised Dameon Pierce for being a “physical, violent runner” in camp.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae90-d05a-adda-ae92a9a90000</link>
      <description>It’s the time of year when coaches and front office members alike praise several players on the team, but with Joe Mixon’s (foot) health still a mystery, and Nick Chubb coming off a disappointing 2024 (102-332-3) following his return from a devastating knee injury, it’s fair to assume a role could be had by Pierce if things break right. Pierce rushed for 220-939-4 as a rookie, and averaged an impressive 7.3 YPC on a small sample size (40-293-2) last season. He’s already split first-team reps with Chubb since returning to camp, and Caley added that he’s “had an appreciation for (Pierce) since he came out of college.” At just 25 years old, Pierce may be the most explosive back in an offense that has two 29-year-old backs on the roster. While his rookie year success wasn’t followed with similar success in 2023 or 2024, he could make for an intriguing late-round dart throw in fantasy drafts while this backfield situation attempts to sort itself out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae90-d05a-adda-ae92a9a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott has not decided if he will let Josh Allen play in the Bills’ second preseason game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae9e-d90d-a5bd-aedfee8e0000</link>
      <description>McDermott beat around the bush regarding his MVP quarterback and whether or not we would see him on Sunday night against the Bears. Speaking Friday, McDermott said his team is using the joint practice against the Bears “to see where (Allen is) at and how he feels” and will decide later in the weekend if Allen will suit up. If Allen doesn’t play, we would expect Mitch Trubisky to draw the start and see plenty of work. Last week, Trubisky started against the Giants, throwing for 138 yards and a touchdown on 9-of-13 passing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae9e-d90d-a5bd-aedfee8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars HC Liam Coen said Travis Hunter (upper body) may miss the team’s second preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aeb9-d45c-a7fc-aebba9ff0000</link>
      <description>Coen said the decision to sit Hunter would be out of precaution, seemingly downplaying whatever upper-body injury the two-way star is dealing with. Hunter played on 11-of-12 offensive snaps with the starters last week, and was expected to see a little more work in his second tune-up as he prepares for his rookie season. The Jaguars don’t play until Sunday, which could give Coen some extra time to consider Hunter’s status for the weekend, but it wouldn’t be too surprising if the team opted not to push things with the season just weeks away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aeb9-d45c-a7fc-aebba9ff0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
