<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Josh Jacobs (knee) will go through individual drills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a258-d413-ad9f-b7ddeb910000</link>
      <description>Jacobs did not participate in practice on Wednesday. It’s encouraging to see him get in any amount of work today, but his status for Week 12 remains up in the air. Jacobs suffered a knee contusion in Week 11 against the Giants. It is not expected to be a long-term issue. If Jacobs can’t suit up this week, Emanuel Wilson will make his first NFL start. Wilson should be rostered in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a258-d413-ad9f-b7ddeb910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants QB Jaxson Dart (concussion) will practice again today and is “heading in the right direction.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a272-db57-afda-f672a3080000</link>
      <description>We suspect Dart was in the NFL concussion protocol’s third phase yesterday. If he passed through to the fourth phase, things could progress quickly, as long as he remains setback-free. Dart’s fantasy-friendly rushing propensity helped him rack up five straight QB1 finishes, including three in the top four. This aspect of his game could be subject to change once he retakes the field on game day. The team is reportedly set on reducing the number of hits Dart takes, and interim head coach Mike Kafka will ostensibly attempt to design plays that provide Dart with checkdown options more often. We do not expect the Giants to fully restrict Dart’s dual-threat talents, but it is possible his per-game fantasy-scoring output ticks down a tad. He will still warrant QB1 treatment initially, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a272-db57-afda-f672a3080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e20-d45b-affe-dfb680350000</link>
      <description>Jackson sat out on Wednesday last week, dealing with knee soreness, before practicing in full on Thursday and Friday. After Jackson sat out yesterday, Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters that Jackson would likely practice in a similar capacity this week. We do not yet know if Jackson will practice fully today, but he is on track to play in Week 12 against the Jets. Jackson can be treated as a QB1 and is always a candidate to finish as the highest-scoring player at his position, though the nagging lower-body issues may be impacting his play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e20-d45b-affe-dfb680350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Travis Etienne (shoulder) was a non-contact participant at practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2ac-d82c-a79a-b3bce0ac0000</link>
      <description>We expect Etienne to be listed as a limited participant on the official injury report. The Jaguars regularly wrapped rookie RB Bhayshul Tuten in a non-contact jersey before allowing him to suit up on game day, while dealing with a shoulder injury earlier this year. He also handled far smaller workloads than the healthy Etienne did. Etienne’s continued participation puts him on track to play, though it is currently difficult to project touch counts between him, Tuten and fellow rookie RB LeQuint Allen. Hopefully, Etienne practices fully on Friday and can be trusted to at least handle double-digit touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2ac-d82c-a79a-b3bce0ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Burrow took snaps with the starting offense again on Thursday, “preparing him for the possibility that he could play” in Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2b3-d90e-a9da-bfbfbd530000</link>
      <description>At this point, Burrow seems capable of suiting up on game day. Whether the team plans to keep him sidelined for one more week, out of an abundance of caution, remains unknown. If active, Burrow would of course possess some re-injury risk, and may need to shake off rust. This offense has been a notoriously slow starter in each of the last three seasons, with Burrow bizarrely failing to clear 170 passing yards in Week 1, from 2023-2025. He broke his touchdown-less curse by tossing one in Week 1 this season. He would also be without No. 1 WR Ja’Marr Chase (suspension) this weekend. That said, Burrow’s talent is not in question and his ceiling sits firmly in the QB1 tier. Hopefully, Bengals beat reporters provide us with actionable intel tomorrow. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2b3-d90e-a9da-bfbfbd530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OC Josh Grizzard said Sean Tucker’s workload has been going up each week as he continues to do well, and he “expects that to continue.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2c1-d413-ad9f-b7dd0b790000</link>
      <description>We don’t yet know the status of Bucky Irving (shoulder) for Week 12’s game against the Rams, but it stands to reason that Tucker could easily be the head of a committee even if Irving comes back given the long layoff. Tucker should be considered on the RB2 line this week even in a rough matchup against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2c1-d413-ad9f-b7dd0b790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Bryce Young (ankle) is practicing in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2c3-d82c-a79a-b3d7d0870000</link>
      <description>That should clear up any confusion over whether Young will be starting against the 49ers on Monday night. Young left Week 11’s game against the Falcons with the injury, but played through it on the way to an out-of-nowhere 448-yard performance. He’ll be on the QB2 line against the 49ers injury-ravaged defense, but probably pretty high on it between what could be a sneaky shootout and what feels like a real dearth of good quarterbacks available in Week 12 with four teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2c3-d82c-a79a-b3d7d0870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (ankle) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2b8-d82c-a79a-b3bc8f290000</link>
      <description>Warren was seen going through ball security and footwork drills on Thursday, which is a good sign for his Week 12 availability. Although Warren’s ankle sprain is unideal, we have only received positive commentary from Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin, who first said Warren could have returned to the game on Sunday, if need be, and on Tuesday, told reporters that he is optimistic about Warren’s odds of playing this weekend. He is on track to face the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2b8-d82c-a79a-b3bc8f290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2cb-d90e-a9da-bfcf1ef10000</link>
      <description>Njoku is enough of a veteran to come off back-to-back DNPs and hit the questionable line on Friday, but this puts him in actual doubt of missing Week 12’s game against the Raiders. If Njoku missed the game, Harold Fannin could consolidate the TE targets for Cleveland and, in theory, have a volume TE1 case. It’s a flimsy case with Shedeur Sanders back there, but it exists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2cb-d90e-a9da-bfcf1ef10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Xavier Legette (hip) is practicing in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2d1-d90e-a9da-bfdf42f70000</link>
      <description>Legette has a little more helium than usual this week as a FLEX play considering Canales told reporters on Monday that there’s a “focused effort” to get him more targets. Playing against an injury-ravaged 49ers defense doesn’t hurt, either. It’s worth considering in 14-team leagues, certainly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a2d1-d90e-a9da-bfdf42f70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
