<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports Garrett Wilson (knee) will be a DNP on Friday and miss Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</link>
      <description>This is according to a source who spoke with Zenitz, but we assume the team’s official injury report, which will come later Friday, will have Wilson ruled out. The star receiver was expected to miss multiple weeks with the knee injury he picked up in Week 6, so the idea of him missing Week 7 doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Jets will hope the duo of Josh Reynolds and Allen Lazard can step up in Wilson’s absence as they look to pick up their first win of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said there is “real uncertainty” about Terry McLaurin (quad) playing in Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</link>
      <description>Pelissero also said the same of Deebo Samuel (heel). It sounds a bit redundant given that Pelissero said on Thursday night there was “real concern” about both receivers’ Week 7 availability, but the fact the tone hasn’t changed over the last 12-plus hours suggests both receivers are trending in the wrong direction for a pivotal NFC East matchup. The Commanders will take the practice field in a few hours, so we should know more about both receivers’ availability soon. That said, a DNP for either player likely means them being ruled out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Garrett Wilson (knee) will be doubtful for Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2b6-df81-ab9b-fef747fa0000</link>
      <description>It’s a slight contradiction from an earlier report that said Garrett Wilson will miss Week 7’s game against the Panthers, but players listed as doubtful are often near locks to be ruled out come game day — if not sooner. Fantasy managers will still want to watch for any surprise announcements regarding Wilson, but it’s safe to assume he will miss Sunday’s game against the Panthers. Fantasy managers should plan accordingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2b6-df81-ab9b-fef747fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua (ankle) will not play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c2-d651-a9df-fbd7a8a80000</link>
      <description>With Nacua officially ruled out, Tutu Atwell and Jordan Whittington will be the favorites to handle receiving duties opposite Davante Adams. The Rams have a Week 8 bye before returning in Week 9 to face the Saints. Hopefully two weeks of rest will be enough for Nacua to return in a timely manner for the Rams and his fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c2-d651-a9df-fbd7a8a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) will not play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c7-df81-ab9b-fec7c6130000</link>
      <description>Sunday will mark the third-straight missed game for Havenstein, who will hopefully have a chance to return after the Rams’ Week 8 bye. Backup tackle Warren McClendon has started the last two games for the Rams in Havenstein’s absence and will again draw the start over seas against the Jaguars in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c7-df81-ab9b-fec7c6130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutu Atwell (hamstring) will play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2cb-d651-a9df-fbdff8340000</link>
      <description>Atwell is dealing with a hamstring injury, but was upgraded to a full participant for Thursday’s practice. The mid-week upgrade was a good sign that he was trending in the right direction, and could come at a good time for the Rams and fantasy managers who will be without Puka Nacua (ankle) this week. Since 2023, Atwell has averaged seven targets per game in games Nacua missed, which could signal a decent floor for his fantasy outlook. While the potential for a big week is there, we’ll conservatively project Atwell as a WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2cb-d651-a9df-fbdff8340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniels said any trade rumors about his players “are baseless.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2d1-d651-a9df-fbd519490000</link>
      <description>McDaniel is doing his due diligence to not let trade deadline talks get the best of his team. As has been the case for years in the NFL, most trade rumors are often rumors until they become reality and a player is on the move. The 1-5 Dolphins certainly have the look of a team that could be sellers at the deadline, which will be on Tuesday, November 4th, and have a handful of players on contracts that contenders would be willing to take on for the remainder of the season. We’ll see if anything comes of these rumors in the following weeks, but we wouldn’t expect McDaniel to acknowledge the team is looking to move any player before a deal is done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2d1-d651-a9df-fbd519490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) will not play in Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2f8-da18-a39b-fafb294f0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin returned to the practice field on Wednesday, but after being kept out of Thursday’s practice, there was fear that things were trending in this direction. We don’t yet know the official practice status for McLaurin as far as Friday is concerned but we did see him warming up with the other receivers, although he notably did not have his helmet. Sunday’s absence will mark the fourth-straight missed game for McLaurin, who will now shift his focus to being ready for Week 8’s game against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2f8-da18-a39b-fafb294f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer said Trevon Diggs suffered a concussion and will not play in Week 7 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2fd-da18-a39b-faffa59b0001</link>
      <description>We don’t know the specifics of this, but according to Schottenheimer, Diggs’ concussion is the result of an at home accident. The veteran corner has totaled 18 tackles and one TFL in six games this season while earning a PFF coverage grade of 62.5 Opposing QBs have targeted him just 15 times on the year, but could find a little more room to throw C.J. Godwin expected to step up in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2fd-da18-a39b-faffa59b0001</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) will play in Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f30e-df81-ab9b-ffcf5f620000</link>
      <description>The return of Hubbard likely spells the end of Rico Dowdle in a bell cow role, although that doesn’t mean we should expect Hubbard to see the 29 percent opportunity share he enjoyed through the first five weeks of the season. Dowdle totaled 473 yards from scrimmage and two touchdowns in the two games Hubbard missed, touching the ball an absurd 60 times over that span. They get a decent Week 7 matchup against the Jets, but until we see how the touches are distributed, neither back should be viewed as much more than a fringe RB2/RB3 play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f30e-df81-ab9b-ffcf5f620000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
