<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed CB J.T. Gray, formerly of the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7e8-db57-afda-f7fa8ccb0000</link>
      <description>Gray has spent time with both the Ravens and Broncos this season. He earned first-team All-Pro honors once, and second-team All-Pro honors twice, with the Saints in 2021, 2019, and 2024, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7e8-db57-afda-f7fa8ccb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills QB Josh Allen said his left shoulder “went a little numb on me” after a hit in Week 12’s loss to the Texans but said “we’re good.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a80d-d82c-a79a-bb9df1bd0000</link>
      <description>The quarterback flexed his hand multiple times on the field and apparently was continuing to do so in the postgame locker room. Allen is probably not a risk to miss time moving forward at this point, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he popped up on the injury report this week given the eight-sack beating he took against the Texans on Thursday night. Luckily he’ll get a little extra time to recover ahead of Week 13’s matchup with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a80d-d82c-a79a-bb9df1bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Flacco (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will be active for Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a821-d413-ad9f-bdfda5ad0000</link>
      <description>Flacco upgraded to full participation on Friday. Whether his services will be needed come Sunday is currently unknown. Joe Burrow (toe) is questionable to play after practicing fully all week and the Bengals now have until 4 PM EST on Saturday to decide whether to activate him from injured reserve. Flacco is a borderline QB1/2 if the team opts to give him another start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a821-d413-ad9f-bdfda5ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 12 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a82d-d82c-a79a-bbbd011e0000</link>
      <description>An Athletic article from Matt Schneidman described the Packers trying to get Josh Jacobs to sit this one out as a “prize fight” between Jacobs and the training staff. This was another limited session for Jacobs, as expected. We’ll probably see this one go all the way up to inactives on Sunday. Jacobs would be an easy RB1 if he plays, while Emanuel Wilson is more of an RB2 as the lead of a committee if he winds up starting on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a82d-d82c-a79a-bbbd011e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Isaac TeSlaa (oblique) is questionable to play in Week 12 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a82d-d82c-a79a-bbbd5e990000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa was limited in practice all week, putting him firmly in the questionable camp. The springy rookie is not fantasy-relevant on his own, but were he to sit out on Sunday, he would cede snaps and a tiny target share to the remaining, healthy players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a82d-d82c-a79a-bbbd5e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (collarbone) won’t play in Green Bay’s Week 12 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a830-db57-afda-fe325b530000</link>
      <description>He did literally just rejoin practice today, so yeah, that’s not a huge surprise. Given Green Bay’s Thanksgiving Day game next week, Week 14 is probably a more reasonable estimate for Reed to rejoin the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a830-db57-afda-fe325b530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder/wrist) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 12 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a831-d413-ad9f-bdfd8eec0000</link>
      <description>He, Dontyavion Wicks (calf), and Savion Williams (foot) are the three Packers main receivers who find themselves on the questionable line. Golden is barely hanging on to FLEX relevancy as is and would not seem particularly trustworthy for fantasy purposes playing through multiple injuries in Week 12. Neither Wicks nor Williams have done enough to even be on the fantasy radar at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a831-d413-ad9f-bdfd8eec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Brian Branch (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 12 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a819-d82c-a79a-bb9de6cf0000</link>
      <description>The Lions’ difference-making defensive back will be on the field when his team takes on the Jameis Winston-led Giants. Lions CB Terrion Arnold (concussion) will not play. The unit is a decent bet to record one or more interceptions for D/ST purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a819-d82c-a79a-bb9de6cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) is off Green Bay’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a834-d413-ad9f-bdfd08560000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a playable FLEX option against the Vikings after coming up with two touchdowns against the Giants in Week 11. Watson’s yardage ceiling has not been high enough to justify him as a WR3 just yet, but the touchdown upside is there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a834-d413-ad9f-bdfd08560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Romeo Doubs (wrist) is not on Green Bay’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a836-d90e-a9da-bf3f35390000</link>
      <description>Doubs has played through a chest injury in recent weeks and will now do the same with the wrist. Nobody is generating more targets than Doubs in this passing game, with an average of 7.6 over his last seven games, but it’s only yielded 378/3 as Green Bay’s passing game has hit plenty of bumps along the way. He’s a credible WR3/FLEX this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a836-d90e-a9da-bf3f35390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
