<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe believes Seahawks S “Nick Emmanwori should be considered a dark-horse candidate to win NFL Defensive Rookie of the Year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f861-db7b-a5dd-f865fa790000</link>
      <description>Emmanwori “has been a playmaking force in practice,” and will “eventually” take on a similar role as the one Ravens S Kyle Hamilton played in head coach Mike Macdonald’s scheme when he served as the defensive coordinator in Baltimore. Howe believes “Macdonald’s defense should be even better in his second season.” It’s squarely on the D/ST1 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f861-db7b-a5dd-f865fa790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that the Seahawks’ offense “seems to be quickly coming together with a more unified vision” under new OC Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f86a-d332-a1fd-fe7eca850000</link>
      <description>Kubiak is expected to feature a zone rushing attack while confusing defenses with motion and attacking downfield via play-action. No. 2 RB Zach Charbonnet had a great training camp while starting RB Kenneth Walker III nursed a sore foot, though Walker is now back in action. Should Charbonnet force a timeshare, or even take over the starting job, both he and Walker should produce fruitful weeks regularly. Jaxon Smith-Njigba is in line for a large workload, operating as Seattle’s inside-outside No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f86a-d332-a1fd-fe7eca850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bengals believe Joe Burrow “enjoyed the best training camp of his career,” according to The Athletic’s Jeff Howe.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f877-de13-afdc-feff40d90000</link>
      <description>Burrow is fully healthy and the Bengals believe “he might have actually improved his accuracy and decision-making” this summer. Though Burrow lacks the rushing upside that the other elite QB1s possess, his exceptional passing talents and top-tier receiving weapons keep him firmly in the top-five conversation. The Bengals also reportedly believe Ja’Marr Chase looks “like he could still be ascending after leading the NFL with 127 catches, 1,708 yards and 17 touchdowns.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f877-de13-afdc-feff40d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed WR Jalen Coker (quad) on injured reserve with a designation to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbae-de13-afdc-ffef1bc40000</link>
      <description>According to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter, Coker will miss at least the first four games of the season with a quad injury. He was looking like a great late-round receiver option with the Panthers trading Adam Thielen and recent reports that Coker would primarily work out of the slot. While the Panthers have signed Hunter Renfrow to the active roster, Xavier Legette is the most likely to benefit from Coker’s absence as the Panthers’ WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbae-de13-afdc-ffef1bc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed WR Hunter Renfrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is back with the Panthers mere days after being cut, according to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter. The Panthers can better use Renfrow’s services now after they traded Adam Thielen to the Vikings and Jalen Coker (quad) went down with an injury. Renfrow could see a good amount of work from the slot in at least the first four games of the season as that’s where the team planned on using Coker. Can a Hunter Renfrow PPR scam work in 2025? I guess we’re going to find out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL fined former Buccaneers S Shilo Sanders $4,669 for unnecessary roughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</link>
      <description>Sanders threw a punch towards Bills tight end Zach Davidson in the team’s third preseason contest and was eventually waived by the franchise. Coming after his release, the fine represents more than three times Sanders’ guaranteed money this season. Sanders remained unsigned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez spent the offseason improving his speed, losing weight and working on his receiving skills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-00ea-db7b-a5dd-a0eed1400000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez spent 2024 floating between the practice squad and active roster, and was told by ST coach Larry Izzo to refine himself physically. He had swelled to 235 pounds following a high-ankle sprain in his 2023 rookie season. Rodriguez, now tipping the scales at 222, said he was clocked at 20-plus MPH “more times in training camp than I have in almost my whole life.” His improved speed was evident on a 40-yard preseason scamper, during which he hit 20.37 MPH. Rodriguez also hired private receiving coach Drew Lieberman, whose résumé includes Brandon Aiyuk and Chase Brown, but unfortunately dropped his lone preseason target. He has just three career catches. Rodriguez is a worthwhile dart throw given his position group’s shifting state and head coach Dan Quinn’s positive comments regarding his short-yardage rushing abilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-00ea-db7b-a5dd-a0eed1400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed CB DaRon Bland to a four-year, $92 million extension through 2029.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-011b-dbe3-a9bb-315bcffb0000</link>
      <description>This extension has been in the works since July, but it was likely held up by the Micah Parsons fiasco. It includes $50 million in guarantees. The fourth-year pro is expected to return to the slot-coverage role that he excelled in during his first two NFL seasons, where he racked up eight pass breakups and 14 interceptions. He primarily played on the outside last year, breaking up just three passes and recording zero interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-011b-dbe3-a9bb-315bcffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee tendinitis) did not practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0119-de13-afdd-47dba3d30000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Andy Reid, Royals is the only player on the active roster who was unable to practice today. A 22-year-old player already dealing with tendinitis is less than ideal, but overall, this is great news. The Chiefs’ wide receiver corps was feeling a little thin, following Rashee Rice’s six-game suspension. Hollywood Brown (ankle) returned to practice on August 18th. Reports on his rehab have been sparse, but we take Reid’s comments on Royals as an indirect positive on Brown’s rehab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0119-de13-afdd-47dba3d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vikings are “optimistic” about WR Jalen Nailor’s (hand) availability for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings recently brought back Adam Thielen via trade, with Jordan Addison set to serve a three-game suspension, and immediately listed Thielen as the fill-in No. 2 wide receiver. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that “Minnesota envisions a key role for Nailor, especially with Jordan Addison out via suspension,” but that’s tough to trust given his injury and the recent personnel development. Nailor is best-suited to single-game DFS lineups and should really only be considered for flex duties in 14-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
