<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley Jr. (oblique) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ce7-dca3-a9fb-7dff50fd0000</link>
      <description>Stingley left Week 3 with the injury and was quickly ruled out. Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans called him day-to-day on Monday. A DNP to open the week is an ominous sign for the shutdown corner. The Texans have been leaning on their stout defense to start the season while their offense attempts to get on track. Losing Stingley would be a notable blow to their secondary. Stingley has three pass breakups and eight tackles this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ce7-dca3-a9fb-7dff50fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf7-deb6-a7fd-7fffaa4b0000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t come as a surprise. Lamb suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 3 and could miss upwards of four weeks. ESPN’s Adam Schefter called him “unlikely” to play in Week 4. Though he hasn’t been ruled out by the Cowboys yet, we fully expect that to happen on the final injury report of the week. Jake Ferguson caught 13 passes in Week 3 and is in line for a monstrous workload sans Lamb. George Pickens should also see an uptick in intermediate looks, rounding out his fantasy profile and making him a more reliable WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf7-deb6-a7fd-7fffaa4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin met with core muscle specialist, Dr. William Meyers, to discuss what has been reported as a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d05-d95b-addb-7d4768f70000</link>
      <description>We already knew that McLaurin was seeking a second opinion after suffering a leg injury against the Raiders in Week 3, but meeting with a core muscle specialist is a bit surprising. Groin injuries often fall into the core muscle category, and Meyers recently performed surgery on Bears CB Jaylon Johnson, who suffered a groin injury in Week 2 that has sidelined him indefinitely. McLaurin’s injury has been reported as a quad issue. The two muscle groups obviously neighbor each other, so this could just be precautionary. It’s worth noting that the injury could be more complex than initial reports indicated, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d05-d95b-addb-7d4768f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson said he won’t ask for a release or trade after being benched for Jaxson Dart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d15-d95b-addb-7d57e5860000</link>
      <description>Wilson told reporters he’s focused on helping the Giants win and helping Dart. He’s taking the benching in stride despite making it just three games as the team’s starting quarterback. Even if he doesn’t ask to be moved, the Giants could find a trade partner for their new backup if quarterback injuries keep piling up across the league. Head coach Brian Daboll has already committed to Dart as the team’s starter for the remainder of the season, so there isn’t much value to be had in hanging on to Wilson. The team also has Jameis Winston on the roster, giving them another viable QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d15-d95b-addb-7d57e5860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson was the first player to take reps in a “tackling/ball-carrier drill” on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d09-d6e9-af9d-ff99c9de0000</link>
      <description>Backup RB Antonio Gibson went second and incumbent starter RB Rhamondre Stevenson went last. Both Gibson (one) and Stevenson (two) fumbled in the Patriots’ Week 3 loss to the Steelers. Henderson, meanwhile, avoided fumbling and led the backfield in offensive snaps, early-down snaps and two-minute drill snaps, per PFF’sNathan Jahnke. Three-player backfields are difficult to trust in fantasy. It will be worth following head coach Mike Vrabel’s comments on the matter in the lead-up to the Patriots’ Week 4 game against the Panthers. This could be a breakout game for Henderson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d09-d6e9-af9d-ff99c9de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said injuries to other players won’t change Travis Hunter’s role on offense or defense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d25-d95b-addb-7d67e9b80000</link>
      <description>Hunter is currently stuck in the F receiver role on offense, putting him in the slot for 63 percent of his routes this year. For reference, Hunter ran six percent of his routes from the slot in his final season of college ball. He played more out of the slot in previous seasons, but it was never his primary position. The note on injuries is especially relevant right now. Dyami Brown went down with a shoulder injury on Sunday and is not practicing as of Wednesday. Parker Washington took over his role in Week 3 and Coen mentioned him as the next man up when talking about Hunter’s fixed role. Hunter has 10 catches for 76 yards through three games. Between his limited role and the tax of playing both ways, he appears to be stuck in the WR4 fantasy ranks for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d25-d95b-addb-7d67e9b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said TE Oronde Gadsden is “going to be in there more,” because “he earned that.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d1b-deb6-a7fd-7fdfb5750000</link>
      <description>Gadsden caught 5 passes for 46 yards against the Broncos last week. It was his first time taking snaps in a game. The fifth-round rookie took snaps in the slot (10), in-line (nine) and out wide (three). Gadsden is worth adding to fantasy benches at this point, to see how things shake out in Week 4. Chargers TE Will Dissly is battling a knee injury and TE Tyler Conklin failed to catch either of his two targets last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d1b-deb6-a7fd-7fdfb5750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d3d-d95b-addb-7d7f70f20000</link>
      <description>Head coach Dave Canales called McMillan day to day with the calf issue. This is McMillan’s first appearance on the injury report, meaning he sustained the injury sometime during Carolina’s week 3 destruction of the Falcons. A DNP to open the week is worrying, but Canales didn’t sound overly concerned when talking about McMillan. As long as he returns to practice at some point this week, we expect the first-round rookie to suit up on Sunday. With at least eight targets in every game this year, McMillan should be treated as a WR2 for his Week 4 date with the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d3d-d95b-addb-7d7f70f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers head coach Dave Canales said Jalen Coker (quad) “is progressing, but remains week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d3b-d6e9-af9d-ffbb39fc0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Coker will be eligible to return from injured reserve in Week 5, but it sounds like his return to play timeline extends past his earliest activation date. For fantasy managers with an injured reserve spot or ample bench space, he can be speculatively stashed at this time. He cannot be counted on to return value in Week 5, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d3b-d6e9-af9d-ffbb39fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d45-d6e9-af9d-ffd5b3740000</link>
      <description>Leggete was limited in all three practices last week before being ruled out 90 minutes before kickoff. Head coach Dave Canales called him day to day on Wednesday, but being downgraded to a DNP after practicing in some capacity for all three sessions last week is a red flag. Legette is highly questionable for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d45-d6e9-af9d-ffd5b3740000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
