<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 21:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (quad) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5954-dfde-a1bd-5fdd43e00000</link>
      <description>This is the first we’re hearing of a quad injury for Swift, though a limited practice to start the week is usually not a cause for concern. Even if Swift doesn’t miss any time because of the injury, it could give head coach Ben Johnson a reason to increase the workload for rookie running back Kyle Monangai. Swift coughed up a fumble in Week 2 and is averaging a pedestrian 4.0 yards per carry despite the Bears’ line looking vastly improved compared to 2024. Swift is still the top option in the Chicago backfield, but fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on this quad issue going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5954-dfde-a1bd-5fdd43e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts TE Tyler Warren (toe) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5957-d1b3-a5dd-597796280000</link>
      <description>No word from the beat reporters regarding the severity of Warren’s injury. It’s unclear when and how it happened, but the rookie tight end certainly did not appear to be impacted by the injury against the Broncos last week. Fantasy managers must monitor his practice participation closely this week. Ideally, he will graduate to full participation on or by Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5957-d1b3-a5dd-597796280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5957-dfde-a1bd-5fdf62970000</link>
      <description>Downs may have picked up the ankle injury in-game last week, when he earned a team-high eight targets against the Broncos. Downs’ practice participation on Thursday and Friday will give us an idea of how he is doing, if the beat reporters are unable to dig up helpful info by the end of the week. Downs dealt with two ankle injuries last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5957-dfde-a1bd-5fdf62970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5959-d6a5-adff-ffddad580000</link>
      <description>Egbuka has been one of the early rookie breakouts of the 2025 class. He has three touchdowns and 96 receiving yards through two weeks. His absence from practice could be just a precaution, but it’s officially one of the biggest storylines of the week as the Bucs prepare to take on the Jets. Egbuka was flirting with a WR2 ranking before suffering the injury. He would be a slightly riskier bet if he attempts to play through it on Sunday. Sterling Shepard would take over as the Bucs’ No. 2 receiver if Egbuka can’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5959-d6a5-adff-ffddad580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LT Tristan Wirfs (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-595f-d6a5-adff-ffdf86730000</link>
      <description>Wirfs was limited for the first two practices of Week 2 before being downgraded to a DNP on Saturday. He was then ruled out. The late-week DNP was part of their plan for his rehab from the knee injury, but it also means a limited practice on Wednesday doesn’t necessarily put him on track to suit up. Right tackle Luke Goedeke also missed Wednesday’s practice with a foot issue that knocked him out of Week 2’s win over the Texans. Right guard Cody Mauch missed today’s practice as well. It’s a nightmare runout for this offensive line. The cluster of injuries makes Baker Mayfield and the rest of the Bucs’ fantasy options slightly worse bets for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-595f-d6a5-adff-ffdf86730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (foot/toe) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5964-d93f-ad9d-5be7af580000</link>
      <description>Mayfield had his leg tangled up in a tackle from Texans safety C. J. Gardner-Johnson on Monday. He appeared to be in serious pain, though that didn’t stop him from popping up to trash-talk the veteran defender. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported this morning that Mayfield did not undergo any testing after the game despite getting banged up. Mayfield should be good to go for his Week 3 date with the Jets. Even after a slow start for fantasy purposes, Mayfield will sit on the QB1/2 border for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5964-d93f-ad9d-5be7af580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596a-d93f-ad9d-5befb7770000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was on the injury report plenty of times last year and the Packers never made an effort to scale his workload back. A limited practice to start the week is likely maintenance for the veteran runner and shouldn’t cause fantasy managers any concern. Jacobs remains an RB1 for his Week 3 date with the lowly Browns. Chris Brooks and Emanuel Wilson will continue to share the backup duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596a-d93f-ad9d-5befb7770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed DL Elijah Simmons, formerly of the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596c-d1b3-a5dd-597d6e970000</link>
      <description>Simmons will serve as interior defensive line depth with DT Calijah Kancey landing on injured reserve with a season-ending pectoral tear. Simmons, a 2025 undrafted free agent, spent the first two weeks of the season on the Cardinals’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596c-d1b3-a5dd-597d6e970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LG Joel Bitonio (back) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596f-d93f-ad9d-5bef6b610000</link>
      <description>Bitonio is a 12-year veteran and no stranger to playing through injuries. Thursday’s injury report will be a bit more telling. Joe Flacco has done a good job avoiding sacks this year, taking just two in each of his first two games back in Cleveland. Losing Bitonio would likely force him to get the ball out quicker, resulting in more check-downs, but that’s something to think about only if Bitonio is unable to suit up later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-596f-d93f-ad9d-5bef6b610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes (wrist) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5975-d93f-ad9d-5bf7424b0000</link>
      <description>A full practice means the wrist issue will be a non-story by Sunday, but it’s always worth noting when a star quarterback makes a surprise appearance on the injury report. Mahomes has been running more this year and currently leads the league with 13 scrambles. He has 50 rushing yards and a rushing score in both games this year, marking the first time in his career he has hit those marks in consecutive weeks. The wrist issue could cause him to be more conservative with his legs, though he and the Chiefs are desperate to get the offense going and his legs are getting the job done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5975-d93f-ad9d-5bf7424b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
