<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (concussion) will “have an opportunity to play next week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1b-d6c4-abfb-df1b2ded0000</link>
      <description>He can be cleared from concussion protocol as soon as Monday. The Commanders would represent a step down in competition for McCarthy (or Max Brosmer) after two rounds in the Packers-Seahawks torture chamber, but neither of these players can be reliably started in superflex leagues given how poor they and the Vikings offense have been of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1b-d6c4-abfb-df1b2ded0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones is believed to be day-to-day after suffering a shoulder injury in Week 13’s loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1d-d6c4-abfb-df1fea540000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, Jones “is likely to be considered day-to-day” with his injury. Jones exited in the third quarter of Sunday’s shutout loss to the Seahawks and didn’t return to the field. The phrasing in Schefter’s report suggests the Vikings are still waiting to get a final word on Jones’ injury, but it sounds like he avoided the worst. If he is day-to-day, Jones will have a chance to suit up in Week 14 when the Vikings face the Commanders this week, but if he’s unable to go, we can expect Jordan Mason to step into a lead role with Zavier Scott likely working in on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1d-d6c4-abfb-df1fea540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db54-d82c-a79a-fbd43ef70000</link>
      <description>Most reporting has this as a 1-2 week injury, so it would be surprising if St. Brown were able to get active for Thursday night’s game against the Cowboys but not exactly unprecedented. A Monday DNP definitely puts him on the wrong side of active, though. If St. Brown misses the game, Jameson Williams will be in a smash role as the only volume pass-catcher the Lions have available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db54-d82c-a79a-fbd43ef70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Drake London (knee) “has a chance to play” in Week 14 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db60-d82c-a79a-fbf4e1740000</link>
      <description>London has missed the last two games for the Falcons after suffering a sprained PCL in Week 11. The Falcons’ WR1 avoided a stint on injured reserve, meaning he can come back whenever the team thinks he’s healthy enough to do so. London did not log a practice last week, so a return to the practice field on Wednesday would be a step in the right direction. His status will be one to monitor throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db60-d82c-a79a-fbf4e1740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Justice Hill (neck) could return in “3-4 weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db77-d90e-a9da-df7f0aba0000</link>
      <description>Rasheen Ali will continue as the Ravens third-down back in the meantime, per Harbaugh. Keaton Mitchell is probably a better second Ravens back to roster at this point for most fantasy leagues than Ali. Hill can be dropped in all shallow formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db77-d90e-a9da-df7f0aba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tee Higgins (concussion) remains in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db90-d90e-a9da-df9f3cc40000</link>
      <description>It’s not the best news, but it’s possible that Higgins clears by the end of the week given he suffered the concussion in Week 12’s loss to the Patriots. This will be one we’re tracking closely ahead of Week 14’s (in most cases) final regular season game for most leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db90-d90e-a9da-df9f3cc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said DL Devonte Wyatt (ankle) is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db91-d6c4-abfb-df9350b70000</link>
      <description>Wyatt finishes his fourth season with his best PFF tackling grade (76.8) of his career and continued to be a solid contributing pass rusher. He’ll enter his fifth-year option season in 2026 after he recovers from this ankle fracture, and will likely be available for training camp at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db91-d6c4-abfb-df9350b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendrickson (hip) is still considered “week-to-week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db91-d90e-a9da-df9fd7a50000</link>
      <description>Taylor said Hendrickson was doubtful entering the week before saying the star pass rusher is still considered “week-to-week” when asked about his future availability. Hendrickson has missed three straight games due to his injury and is primarily working with trainers, per Taylor. We’ll see if Hendrickson can get back on the field come Week 15 when the Bengals face the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db91-d90e-a9da-df9fd7a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles HC Nick Sirianni said OC Kevin Patullo will continue to call plays in Week 14 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dba6-d82c-a79a-fbb64bc60000</link>
      <description>When asked if Patullo would remain as the team’s play-caller, Sirianni endorsed his long-time friend and first-time offensive coordinator with a resounding, “yeah.” The Eagles’ offensive struggles have been a story throughout most of the season, but things have felt particularly bleak as of late. The Eagles have topped 20 points just once in their last four games, and lost 24-15 at home to the Bears on Black Friday. Patullo will remain as play-caller for Week 14’s game against the Chargers, but at this time, he feels far from a lock to finish out the season in his current role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dba6-d82c-a79a-fbb64bc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (elbow) has not yet been cleared for contact.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbaf-d82c-a79a-fbbff6860000</link>
      <description>Quinn said Daniels was “ripping” throws today and that the team will take it to “later in the week” before deciding if Daniels will play in Week 14. The Commanders coach mentioned it as “functional contact” the ability to stiff arm and make football moves. It sounds like Marcus Mariota has a real chance at getting a Week 14 start if the Commanders have not yet made a decision on Daniels playing on Monday. Mariota would be a worthwhile superflex start against the Vikings, while Daniels would obviously make the QB1 line if he were ready to go. We’ll probably get another update on this Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbaf-d82c-a79a-fbbff6860000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
