<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE Alex Highsmith (pectoral) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1b-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbcd570000</link>
      <description>He’s missed back-to-back practices, but told reporters he was optimistic about Friday. Highsmith always seems to be fighting through something, but he has played each of the last five weeks and should be considered questionable for this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1b-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbcd570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers T Broderick Jones (groin) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe71950000</link>
      <description>Generally offensive linemen will play off murkier statuses than most positions, so we’d be surprised if Jones wasn’t at least questionable now that he has made an appearance following Wednesday’s DNP. Calvin Anderson would be the next man up if Jones isn’t able to get right for Week 11’s game against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f1e-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe71950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Flacco (right shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0c-d45b-affe-7f9e79110000</link>
      <description>The Bengals are simply managing Flacco’s reps as he rehabs an AC joint sprain in his throwing shoulder. Ideally, the team needs him for two more games, before QB Joe Burrow’s (toe) hopeful return. Expect Flacco to continue producing as a QB1 against the Steelers’ defense this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f0c-d45b-affe-7f9e79110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f24-d713-ad9e-7f7484720000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is highly unlikely to play after injuring his foot during a hip-drop tackle in Week 10. Broncos head coach Sean Payton has employed a fantasy-unfriendly running back rotation with his backups at times, but rookie RB RJ Harvey is currently in a position to handle an RB2-worthy workload in Week 11 against the Chiefs. Fellow backup RB Tyler Badie can be added in deep PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f24-d713-ad9e-7f7484720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2d-d45b-affe-7fbf99290000</link>
      <description>Fellow backup RB Justice Hill (toe) remains sidelined, setting up Mitchell for No. 2 running back duties against the Browns. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters earlier this week that he hopes to further incorporate Mitchell on game day. That should not be an issue with Hill heading toward a Week 11 absence. Mitchell should be stashed at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2d-d45b-affe-7fbf99290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (hip) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2c-d1e7-a1fa-7fee28af0000</link>
      <description>Likely should have no issue suiting up on game day, though he can only be started as a touchdown-dependent TE2, operating as TE Mark Andrews’ sidekick. Andrews is barely a better option than Likely, though Andrews has QB Lamar Jackson’s trust in the red zone, leading to three touchdowns scored over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f2c-d1e7-a1fa-7fee28af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f39-d45b-affe-7fbfe8a40000</link>
      <description>The fleet-of-foot rookie remains sidelined, putting him firmly in the questionable camp after missing Week 10 with the same issue. Veteran WR Cedric Tillman returned from a multi-week hamstring injury last week, only to pick up a glute injury. Neither player is fantasy-relevant in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f39-d45b-affe-7fbfe8a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f36-d713-ad9e-7f76414b0000</link>
      <description>Fannin played through the injury, catching 4-of-7 targets for 44 yards in Week 10. The talented rookie tight end sits on the TE1/2 borderline, tethered to erratic quarterback play in the Browns’ uninspiring offense. It would be great to see Fanning upgrade to full participation to close the practice week tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f36-d713-ad9e-7f76414b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f49-d45b-affe-7fdfb98d0000</link>
      <description>Ridley looks like he may need another week off before returning, though he still has Friday to upgrade his participation level. If active, Ridley is difficult to trust. He is no longer a difference-making wide receiver at age 30 and the Titans face the Texans’ top-tier pass defense. Consider him a classic boom-bust FLEX if he is cleared to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f49-d45b-affe-7fdfb98d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f4e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee8dad0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo is clearly still impacted by the foot injury, coming off the Titans’ Week 10 bye. The Titans face the Texans this weekend, lowering Okonkwo’s already limited ceiling, assuming he is active. The veteran tight end is just a TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f4e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee8dad0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
