<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce (ribs) is practicing in full for Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a25-d77b-adfb-caa704ac0000</link>
      <description>Pierce left Week 14’s game for a concussion evaluation in the fourth quarter. He was never given an injury designation and did not enter the league’s concussion protocol after the game. A full practice today with a different injury listed on the report means he should be good to go for Week 15. With either Riley Leonard or Phillip Rivers now starting in place of an injured Daniel Jones, our hopes aren’t high for Pierce as a fantasy option versus Seattle’s elite defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a25-d77b-adfb-caa704ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (abdomen) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a20-da9b-a9bf-de2d898e0000</link>
      <description>While Neal’s new injury listing might feel like a gut punch, his early-week participation puts him on track to play in Week 15 against the Panthers. Neal handled a career-high 20 touches last week, so being a little banged up the following week is unsurprising. The rookie running back warrants RB3/FLEX treatment thanks to his three-down skillset and workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a20-da9b-a9bf-de2d898e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a28-d8cf-affb-be2a82a90000</link>
      <description>The ankle issue is new for Downs, but he has been playing through various injuries all year. A full practice puts him on track to play in Week 15. With Daniel Jones out and one of Riley Leonard or Phillip Rivers drawing the start, Downs will be stuck in the WR5 ranks for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a28-d8cf-affb-be2a82a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a2c-da9b-a9bf-de2d84900000</link>
      <description>It took an MCL sprain in Week 12 to sideline Kamara, who had played through an ankle injury for much of the year. He remains sidelined and appears to be highly unlikely to suit up for the Saints’ Week 15 game against the Panthers. Rookie RB Devin Neal (abdomen) will continue starting in his stead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a2c-da9b-a9bf-de2d84900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a2d-d8cf-affb-be2f064a0000</link>
      <description>This is Lawrence’s first appearance on the injury report this year, which is longer than most players make it before dealing with some. A limited practice puts him on track to play this week, though the ankle issue could limit his mobility. Lawrence has 251 rushing yards and five scores on the ground this year. Some of his best fantasy outings have been fueled by his nose for the end zone as a runner. Lawrence will stick in the QB2 ranks for his Week 15 date with the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a2d-d8cf-affb-be2f064a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars EDGE Travon Walker (knee) is practicing in full for Week 15 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a35-d005-a9bf-da3518100000</link>
      <description>Walker has been out since Week 11 with the knee issue. He returned to practice for two limited sessions last week but didn’t play through his questionable tag on Sunday. Potentially facing the Brady Cook-led Jets, Walker should be able to return with a sack or two in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a35-d005-a9bf-da3518100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos designated LG Ben Powers (biceps) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a32-da9b-a9bf-de3fd5770000</link>
      <description>The team now has 21 days to observe Powers in practice before officially activating him. Today, he promisingly “stretched with the team during the viewing period.” Powers is a proficient run blocker and pass protector. His return would be a boon to QB Bo Nix and the Broncos’ running backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a32-da9b-a9bf-de3fd5770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a38-d8cf-affb-be3a14530000</link>
      <description>Washington missed last week’s game with the hip issue after getting in two limited practices. He appears to be on the right side of questionable as of today, but the Jags may want to see him practice in full before clearing him for Week 15. Tim Patrick spiked for 78 yards and a touchdown with Washington out last week. He would be a WR5 if Washington is out once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a38-d8cf-affb-be3a14530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed QB Adrian Martinez, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a3c-d005-a9bf-da3c9ef80000</link>
      <description>Martinez already spent time on both the Jets and 49ers’ rosters this year. Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (groin) and QB Justin Fields (knee) were unable to practice on Wednesday. Martinez’s return provides the team with a backup option behind QB Brady Cook for the Jets’ Week 15 game against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a3c-d005-a9bf-da3c9ef80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions claimed S Jalen Mills off waivers from the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a43-d77b-adfb-cac334d70000</link>
      <description>Mills was released by Houston earlier this week. He appeared in four games for the Texans this year, logging four tackles while playing a mix of special teams and defense. With the Lions seemingly losing a new defensive back to injury every week, Mills will give the team some extra depth on defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a43-d77b-adfb-cac334d70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
