<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 2 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ae7-d294-a19b-fef7c0920000</link>
      <description>Decker underwent offseason shoulder surgery and missed time in training camp as a result. He played all 67 offensive snaps in Week 1 but “a problem with his shoulder caused” him to miss practice on both Wednesday and Thursday this week. Lions OC John Morton commented on the matter succinctly, saying, “we’re totally expecting Decker to play.” Decker’s availability does not appear to be jeopardized, but Detroit’s blindside protector is ailing. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ae7-d294-a19b-fef7c0920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) is active for Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdd7bb0000</link>
      <description>The Packers’ vaunted defense will have its new star pass rusher on the field. Unfortunately, the Packers declared CB Bo Melton, S Zayne Anderson, RT Zach Tom (oblique), LG Aaron Banks (ankle/groin), TE Ben Sims and DL Warren Brinson inactive. Losing both Tom and Banks hurts Jordan Love’s protection. It would be unsurprising to see the Packers dial up quick-hitting pass plays to help reduce pressure from Washington’s pass rush. On the plus side, Packers CB Nate Hobbs (knee) is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdd7bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez is inactive for Week 2 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aff-dc44-a9d9-3ffffa740000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez’s absence once again clears the way for rookie Jacory Croskey-Merritt to lead the Commanders’ rushing attack. Austin Ekeler led the backfield with 33 offensive snaps last week, though, and is the favorite to do so again, operating in his typical receiving-heavy role. The Commanders also declared P Mitch Wishnowsky, QB Josh Johnson, LB Ale Kaho, LB Kain Medrano, T Trent Scott and T George Fant inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aff-dc44-a9d9-3ffffa740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Roschon Johnson (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdcae30000</link>
      <description>Johnson is being eased into action following a lengthy rehab program. Initially, his limited session on Wednesday seemed to indicate that he was on track to debut in Week 2. His continued limitations put him firmly in the questionable camp. Earlier this week, Bears head coach Ben Johnson said he wanted to get RB Kyle Monangai more involved as a rusher. Johnson could find himself in the No. 3 role, if Johnson’s plan comes to fruition and Monangai seizes the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3aed-d86f-abdd-7ffdcae30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b0f-d86f-abdd-7fbf5e670000</link>
      <description>Bears slot CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring), unfortunately, remains sidelined. Johnson should be good to go for Week 2 against the Lions at this point. We should find out soon if Johnson is truly back to full health when he is asked to cover Detroit speedster Jameson Williams. Gordon’s likely absence is significant for Lions slot receiver Amon-Ra St. Brown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b0f-d86f-abdd-7fbf5e670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b23-d86f-abdd-7fbf80600000</link>
      <description>Seahawks S Julian Love (groin) was also downgraded to a non-participant after practicing in a limited capacity on Wednesday. Fellow Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) was recently placed on injured reserve. With the secondary in such rough shape, the Seahawks signed CB Shaquill Griffin from the practice squad. The team correspondingly released WR Cody White before immediately signing him to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b23-d86f-abdd-7fbf80600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams OL Rob Havenstein (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b29-d86f-abdd-7fbd948b0000</link>
      <description>Havenstein sat out Wednesday’s practice, so his return is a great sign. The Rams also got back OL Kevin Dotson (ankle), who likewise practiced in a limited capacity. Fellow OL Steve Avila (ankle) remained sidelined. The Rams’ offensive line is banged up, but the unit is at least on the upswing, which bodes positively for Matthew Stafford’s ability to stay upright against the Titans in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b29-d86f-abdd-7fbd948b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan James (finger) is expected to be ready to play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b4a-dc44-a9d9-3f6e61800000</link>
      <description>James was a limited participant during Thursday’s practice, but 49ers executive John Lynch told reporters that the fifth-round pick is “ready to go.” Obviously Christian McCaffrey is the bellbow in the offense, but James should see some involvement; particularly for a team that is expected to run the football an awful lot of Mac Jones under center against a not-so-good New Orleans football team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b4a-dc44-a9d9-3f6e61800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b58-d294-a19b-fff88b0f0000</link>
      <description>Reed injured the shoulder while coming down with a touchdown that ended up being negated by a holding penalty. The 25-year-old is also nursing a foot injury, but it’s the upper-body ailment that makes him questionable to return Week 2 against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b58-d294-a19b-fff88b0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deatrich Wise was carted off the field with a lower-body injury in Thursday’s Week 2 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b59-d294-a19b-fff994f10000</link>
      <description>Wise was rolled up while attempting to block an extra point in the second quarter. The 31-year-old defender will assuredly miss the rest of this game, and there should be an update on his status for the upcoming contests in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b59-d294-a19b-fff994f10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
