<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 22 times for 69 yards in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks, catching 9-of-10 targets for 73 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2687-d332-a1fd-b6b77f6c0000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey entered Week 1 just three days removed from an in-practice calf tweak. His five first-quarter touches were reasonable, though admittedly a team-high. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan threw caution to the wind as the game progressed, loading up McCaffrey with 8-9 touches in each of the next three quarters. Both George Kittle (hamstring) and Jauan Jennings (shoulder) were forced from play, helping McCaffrey earn a team-high seven targets in the second half. The veteran running back looked good as a receiver, but was unable to get things going on the ground. He gets a far softer defensive front next week, against the Saints, keeping him firmly locked into the elite RB1 tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2687-d332-a1fd-b6b77f6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said George Kittle (hamstring) would undergo an MRI on his hamstring on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-268e-de13-afdd-66cfb3400000</link>
      <description>Kittle exited in the second quarter of Sunday’s win over the Seahawks and did not return to the field. The veteran tight end dealt with two hamstring injuries last season and will now attempt to work his way back from another to start this season. Kittle caught four passes for 25 yards and a score before his injury. Backup tight end Jake Tonges stepped up to catch 3-of-3 targets for 15 yards and a touchdown, but shouldn’t be counted on as a streaming option in Week 2 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-268e-de13-afdd-66cfb3400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 19 times for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions, adding one catch for four yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2692-d332-a1fd-b6b647b90000</link>
      <description>The Lions kept Jacobs in check for nearly all of this game, but the body blows wore down Detroit’s defense and Jacobs started getting the better of them in the fourth quarter. Jacobs ran nine times for 38 yards in the final frame and punched in a short touchdown from three yards out to ice the game. No other Packers back saw more than one carry. Per usual, Jacobs is a workhorse runner on an offense willing to establish a ground game. He will sit at the top end of the RB1 ranks for his Week 2 matchup with the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2692-d332-a1fd-b6b647b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed one time for two yards in the Rams’ Week 1 win over the Texans, adding a catch for 14 yards on his only target.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2694-de13-afdd-66df0bc80000</link>
      <description>He played ten of Los Angeles’ 60 snaps. Corum would stumble into a worthwhile fantasy role if the Rams lost Kyren Williams for any reason — especially with Jarquez Hunter becoming a healthy scratch this week — but he’s unplayable as things stand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2694-de13-afdd-66df0bc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Ward completed 12-of-28 attempts for 112 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2695-de13-afdd-66df5aa10000</link>
      <description>Ward played much better than his stat line would indicate. Titans pass catchers dropped five well-thrown passes from the rookie in his NFL debut, including two late-game drops that spoiled the team’s chance of a last-minute comeback win over the heavily-favored Broncos. Ward threw from a variety of arm angles, and almost connected with downfield threat Elic Ayomanor on a few deep shots in the first half. Ward had plenty of time to operate in the pocket; only five quarterbacks in Week 1 had a higher average time to throw, according to PFF. Ward did not record a rushing attempt. That’s something of a concern for his fantasy prospects. The rookie isn’t a fantasy option for Week 2 against the Rams. Not yet, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2695-de13-afdd-66df5aa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson rushed nine times for 33 yards in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks, adding one reception for four yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2674-d332-a1fd-b67666120000</link>
      <description>Robinson earned two targets on the day. Robinson’s touch count was likely inflated by the 49ers’ in-game injuries. Both George Kittle (hamstring) and Jauan Jennings (shoulder) were forced from play. Robinson failed to stand out against the Seahawks’ talented defensive front but the usage did confirm that he is the clear-cut backup to Christian McCaffrey. He should be stashed on benches for the 49ers’ Week 2 game against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2674-d332-a1fd-b67666120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins caught 3-of-5 targets for 25 yards in the Texans’ Week 1 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2697-de13-afdd-66df2ce70000</link>
      <description>The fact that he dominated snaps (53 of 63, by far the most among Texans receivers) and did that little with them tells you something about this new Texans offense. And not something good. This would have been Collins’ lowest target total all year in 2024 if we didn’t count games he was hurt in or left early. It’s usage that we haven’t seen since the middle of 2023. Fantasy managers have little choice but to trust this can get better next week against the Buccaneers, but it’s an ominous beginning for someone who was already stuck being the bright spot in a bad offense last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2697-de13-afdd-66df2ce70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Hutchinson caught 2-of-2 targets for 30 yards in the Texans’ Week 1 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-269b-dbe3-a9bb-36db63030000</link>
      <description>The Texans backed up an Ian Rapoport report that Hutchinson would receive starter snaps by seeing 43 of the 63 snaps, second-most on the team. It did little. Without better statistical lines, we’d expect Hutchinson to eventually lose playing time to Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-269b-dbe3-a9bb-36db63030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 31-of-39 passes for 225 yards, a touchdown, and an interception in the Lions’ 27-13, Week 1 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2697-de13-afdd-66df763f0000</link>
      <description>Goff’s completion percentage of 79 percent is impressive, but it was the only redeeming quality of the Lions’ offense. Goff was constantly under pressure, forcing him to either take a check-down or wait for someone to get open. Waiting was often untenable as Goff took four sacks. He was also pressured by Micah Parsons on his interception, a quick throw he tried to force to Amon-Ra St. Brown. Detroit lost multiple starters along their offensive line during the offseason and offensive mastermind Ben Johnson left for Chicago. The losses loomed large in this contest and could foreshadow more disastrous days if the issues aren’t fixed in short order. Goff will likely fall just outside of the QB1 fantasy ranks for his Week 2 matchup versus Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2697-de13-afdd-66df763f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
