<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-319e-d321-a5bf-b3df59100000</link>
      <description>Jackson was a full participant in practice throughout the week and told reporters on Tuesday that he was ready to go. It looked like Jackson would be back in Week 8 after the team listed him as a full participant on Friday, but that charade was quickly unmasked when it was reported that he worked with the scout team for the final practice of the week. The team then ruled him out and even retroactively changed his practice status, a move that could result in a fine. A final week of rest may have been for the best as Jackson appears to be fully healthy, putting him back at the top of the QB ranks for Week 9. His return will also push Zay Flowers up in the WR2 range while keeping Mark Andrews at the back of the TE1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-319e-d321-a5bf-b3df59100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-319e-d48c-ad9f-fddf30d20000</link>
      <description>Watson played very well in his first game back last week, catching 4-of-4 targets for 85 yards against the Steelers. Today’s limited session is nothing to worry about. The Packers are just managing his reps. Watson is a WR4/FLEX against the Panthers this week, though it could be some time before the coaching staff allows him to operate as a full-time player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-319e-d48c-ad9f-fddf30d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Julian Hill (ankle) will not play in Week 9 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a4-d321-a5bf-b3f79eb10000</link>
      <description>With Darren Waller on injured reserve and Hill ruled out, Tanner Conner will draw the start for Miami this week. Greg Dulcich will also see some run. Neither player is on the redraft radar, but DFS players can take shots on both tight ends in large tournaments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a4-d321-a5bf-b3f79eb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a8-d321-a5bf-b3fff55f0000</link>
      <description>It looks like we’re getting another week of three-down duties for Kimani Vidal. The second-year back gashed the Vikings for 117 yards and a touchdown on 23 carries last week. It was his second game with more than 100 yards and a touchdown in the past three weeks. In a great matchup versus the Titans, Vidal will flirt with an RB1 rank for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a8-d321-a5bf-b3fff55f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a8-de12-a19e-37a8ede60000</link>
      <description>This may partially explain why ESPN’s Mike Reiss reported earlier that the Patriots are likely targeting a running back ahead of the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline. The injury’s severity has not yet been reported on, but Stevenson has been an offensive focal point for them this season, with rookie RB TreVeyon Henderson failing to meaningfully challenge Stevenson for the starting role. Practice reports over the next two days should clarify Stevenson’s Week 9 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a8-de12-a19e-37a8ede60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Evan Hull, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a4-d48c-ad9f-fdedd2250000</link>
      <description>Hull joins the Saints’ practice squad a little more than a week after RB Kendre Miller was lost for the season to a torn ACL. Hull is unlikely to become fantasy-relevant this season, but the speedy youngster gives the Saints an extra player to work with in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31a4-d48c-ad9f-fdedd2250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31b4-d48c-ad9f-fdfdee480000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson aggravated his hip injury in Week 8, putting his availability back in the “day-to-day” category. It is an unfortunate development for the veteran EDGE and the Bengals’ front office, which is reportedly fielding trade inquiries for him. His status for Week 9 is currently up in the air. The Bengals face the Bears this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31b4-d48c-ad9f-fdfdee480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31b5-d321-a5bf-b3f755890000</link>
      <description>Joseph played through the knee issue early in the year but was eventually put on ice. He missed Week 7 with the knee issue and got Detroit’s Week 8 bye to rest. It seemingly wasn’t enough time off and he appears to be headed for another week on the bench. On the bright side, cornerback Terrion Arnold was a full participant in practice. He should be good to go after missing a few weeks with a shoulder injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31b5-d321-a5bf-b3f755890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill reports that Saints head coach Kellen Moore “further clarified that his intent is to have QB Tyler Shough start the rest of the year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31af-d48c-ad9f-fdef8e360000</link>
      <description>Specifically, Moore said, “Tyler’s starting. We’re not looking back on that.” We won’t hold him to it if Shough’s play drops below his expectedly low bar, but letting the 26-year-old rookie audition for the starting role from here on out makes sense. Shough does not belong in single-quarterback lineups at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31af-d48c-ad9f-fdef8e360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31bc-d48c-ad9f-fdfdcf9d0000</link>
      <description>Backup running back Devin Neal was also limited with an ankle injury. Kamara has been dealing with the ankle issue for weeks. It has yet to cost him any playing time. He appeared to exacerbate the issue on Sunday when his leg got rolled up during a tackle in the second quarter. While it looked serious at the time, a limited practice to start the week says otherwise. Kamara will suit up on Sunday versus the Rams. His dwindling role and poor efficiency will have him well outside of the RB2 ranks for Week 9. Neal is barely on the radar as a FLEX play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31bc-d48c-ad9f-fdfdcf9d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
