<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 4-of-6 targets for 27 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills, adding a six-yard rush.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6028-d93f-ad9d-7aef828d0000</link>
      <description>A hyped 2024 Day 3 pick who ended up doing very little as a rookie, 24-year-old Washington has come out much stronger this season, quickly establishing himself as the Dolphins’ No. 3 receiver and No. 4 passing-game weapon. It’s just hard for that to mean much in a hard-capped offense with compilers Tyreek Hill, De’Von Achane and Jaylen Waddle all ahead of Washington in the pecking order. He’s an intriguing end-of-bench stash in Dynasty leagues, but would need injury ahead of him to make 2025 re-draft noise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6028-d93f-ad9d-7aef828d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Johnson rushed three times for 13 yards in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins, adding an eight-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-602a-d93f-ad9d-7aefba4d0000</link>
      <description>With Ray Davis off to a poor start, Johnson was the Bills’ No. 2 running back this evening, out-touching Davis 4-0. Pro Football Focus charted Johnson with a 15-4 snaps advantage. Noteworthy for the Bills in “real life,” but still inconsequential in fantasy. Neither back is going to carve out standalone fantasy value behind James Cook, while a committee would form were Cook to go down with injury. This could also just be a one-week aberration. For now, Cook’s insurance backs can be ignored in re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-602a-d93f-ad9d-7aefba4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans S Jimmie Ward had his domestic violence case dismissed by a Montgomery County grand jury on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-61e9-d6a5-adff-f7ed755d0000</link>
      <description>KPRC 2’s Aaron Wilson writes that Ward’s case “was no-billed, meaning the grand jury didn’t find probable cause that a criminal offense occurred.” Ward still remains on the commissioner-exempt list and is not eligible to play, as he still faces a $20 million civil lawsuit based on domestic violence allegations from his former fiancée. While his domestic violence case has been dismissed, the league could opt to delay Ward’s return until the lawsuit he’s facing is resolved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-61e9-d6a5-adff-f7ed755d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mohamed Sanu retired from the NFL after 10 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6238-d93f-ad9d-7aff15030000</link>
      <description>This one probably could’ve gone without an announcement. Sanu, 36, who last played a regular-season snap in 2021, was drafted in the third round by the Bengals back in 2012, and walks away with a career receiving line of 435-4,871-27. While he never topped the 1,000-yard mark, Sanu eclipsed 700 yards in a season three times, with his best year coming in 2018 when he went for 66-838-4 with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6238-d93f-ad9d-7aff15030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) was seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6240-d1b3-a5dd-6371dd840000</link>
      <description>We’ll await official word from the team before drawing any conclusions on Egbuka’s Week 3 status, but the fact that he was able to get on the field Friday is a good sign. The team will release its injury report later in the day, which will give us a better sense of where things stand, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he was listed as questionable heading into the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6240-d1b3-a5dd-6371dd840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) was not spotted at the media portion of Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6288-d1b3-a5dd-63f9fdcd0000</link>
      <description>As head coach Dan Quinn pointed out earlier in the week,Daniels would need to practiceif he hopes to play in Week 3 against the Raiders. Barring an unexpected turn of events, the second-year quarterback is looking like a DNP for the third-straight day, further putting his availability in doubt. We’ll see where things stand when the Commanders release their final injury report later in the day, but it’s growing increasingly more likely that Marcus Mariota will be under center against his former team on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6288-d1b3-a5dd-63f9fdcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said CB Jason Marshall is likely week-to-week with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6291-d1b3-a5dd-63f1c5200000</link>
      <description>The rookie fifth-rounder played on 60 defensive snaps through the first two weeks of the season, but exited early in Thursday night’s contest against the Bills and did not return to the field. Playing almost exclusively as a slot corner, Marshall has allowed seven receptions on seven targets for 88 yards and a touchdown, with most of that coming in Week 3’s loss to the Bills. We’ll likely know more about his Week 4 availability later next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6291-d1b3-a5dd-63f1c5200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Glenn declined to answer whether Justin Fields (concussion) could lose his QB1 role while injured.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629b-d1b3-a5dd-63fbdeac0000</link>
      <description>Jets beat writer Rich Cimini wrote on social media that Glenn declined to answer “when asked his philosophy on whether a player can lose his job while injured — a reference to Justin Fields, of course.” The Jets are 0-2, and Fields’ Week 2 performance against the Bills through nearly four full quarters of football was bad enough to warrant questions about his job security if Tyrod Taylor plays well and leads the Jets to a victory in Week 3 against the Buccaneers. Glenn’s refusal to answer could just be the result of a frustrated coach not wanting to play into the media’s hands three weeks into the season, but it goes without saying that Taylor turning out a strong performance could lead to calls for a change at the position from a base that’s desperate for competent quarterback play from anybody who can provide it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629b-d1b3-a5dd-63fbdeac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets ruled out LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) for Week 3 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629a-d6a5-adff-f6df796f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson suffered an ankle injury in Week 2’s loss to the Bills and was a DNP all week. His absence shouldn’t come as a surprise, given his inactivity on Wednesday and Thursday. Now, the fourth-year pass rusher will hope to return in Week 4 for a Monday night matchup against the Dolphins. In addition to Johnson, the Jets also ruled out Josh Reynolds (hamstring), Kene Nwangwu (hamstring), and Jay Tufele (illness) for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629a-d6a5-adff-f6df796f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
