<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 03:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Giddens caught 0-of-1 targets in the Colts’ Week 2 win over the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4af3-d86f-abdd-4fff28880000</link>
      <description>This game remained close from start to finish, so the Colts never had a clear opportunity to get their backup rookie running back a few touches. Giddens did not rush the ball even once. On the plus side, fellow backup Tyler Goodson (elbow) was inactive for this one, suggesting Giddens is ahead of him on the depth chart at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4af3-d86f-abdd-4fff28880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Benson had three rushes for 14 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 2 win against the Panthers, adding four catches for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b0c-d86f-abdd-4fbd7e290000</link>
      <description>Benson continues to eat into James Conner’s workload in the Arizona backfield. Benson, who had 69 yards on eight rushes last week against the Saints, ran more routes than Conner and saw six targets, the second most among Cardinals pass catchers on the day. A far more explosive option than Conner, Benson should continue seeing a small but reliable weekly workload in a run-first Arizona offense. Benson would be something close to a top-12 option if Conner were to miss time in 2025. He needs to be rostered in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b0c-d86f-abdd-4fbd7e290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 6-of-10 targets for 100 yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b1e-dc44-a9d9-4f7e92570000</link>
      <description>The rookie once again operated as Bryce Young’s clearcut No. 1 target. He saw 30 percent of Carolina’s air yards and led the Panthers in target for a second straight week. McMillan’s highlight came on a 40-yard catch and run where he showed off his vision and speed after the catch. He now has 19 targets through two games. If the Panthers continue struggling on defense, Young and McMillan could be forced into frequent pass-heavy game scripts that would inflate drop back and target volume. McMillan should be locked into all fantasy lineups for Week 3 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b1e-dc44-a9d9-4f7e92570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Renfrow caught 7-of-9 targets for 49 yards and two touchdowns in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b26-da67-a99f-cff7f12e0000</link>
      <description>Renfrow ran as the Panthers’ primary slot receiver — as he did in Week 1 — and caught two of Bryce Young’s three touchdowns in Carolina’s furious second half comeback attempt. Hunter, as he did in his Raiders days, creates space in the short areas and is sure handed. He could function as a solid outlet for Young all season as the team’s No. 2 receiver (Xavier Legette turned eight targets into -2 yards on Sunday). Renfrow could benefit from pass-heavy game scripts this season if the Carolina defense remains one of the NFL’s worst. He’s a passable option in PPR formats for Week 3 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b26-da67-a99f-cff7f12e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette caught 1-of-8 targets for -2 yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b2f-d294-a19b-efff530a0000</link>
      <description>Legette had one of the most stunningly inefficient games in NFL history. In fact, he’s the only player in the modern era to post negative receiving yards on eight targets. Yet he continues to run nearly all the routes in the Carolina offense. Tetairoa McMillan, meanwhile, turned ten targets into 100 yards against the Cardinals, and Hunter Renfrow saw nine targets and caught two touchdowns from Bryce Young. It wouldn’t be surprising if Legette is phased out of the Carolina offense sooner rather than later. He can remain on waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b2f-d294-a19b-efff530a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle had six rushes for nine yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals, adding one catch for ten yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b37-d294-a19b-eff738f10000</link>
      <description>Dowdle saw just four fewer carries than lead back Chuba Hubbard while splitting pass-catching duties with him. Hubbard caught five balls against Arizona, one that went for a short touchdown. Dowdle last week had five touches for 16 total yards. He should be rostered in most 12-team leagues in case Hubbard misses time in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b37-d294-a19b-eff738f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders caught 7-of-11 for 54 yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b3c-d86f-abdd-4fbdb5d00000</link>
      <description>Jake Ferguson was the only tight end on Sunday who had more targets than Sanders, who ran a pass route on 42 of 63 Bryce Young drop backs. Sanders worked primarily as a short-area check down option for Young, who completed 35 passes against Arizona in a pass-heavy game script. Fellow TE Tommy Tremble caught all three of his targets for 20 yards. Sanders profiles as a somewhat interesting deep league option for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b3c-d86f-abdd-4fbdb5d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) questionable to return to Week 2 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b43-d294-a19b-eff307aa0000</link>
      <description>It is unclear when Jones departed from the game but he was spotted on the sideline without his helmet in the fourth quarter. Sideline reporters later confirmed that the veteran back was questionable to return. Jones managed 23 yards on five carriers and failed to catch his only target before departing. Fantasy managers will want to track his practice status ahead of the team’s Week 3 meeting with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b43-d294-a19b-eff307aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brycen Tremayne caught 3-of-5 targets for 48 yards in the Panthers’ Week 2 loss against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b44-dc44-a9d9-4f666fb40000</link>
      <description>Tremayne drew five targets on just 14 pass routes. His receptions included a 26-yard gain on a strong throw from Bryce Young in the second half. Tremayne, who spent time on the Commanders practice squad a couple seasons ago, was far more efficient and productive than Xavier Legette, who had -2 yards on eight targets against Arizona. Tremayne could be on his way to unseating Legette as Carolina’s WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b44-dc44-a9d9-4f666fb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleb Johnson had one rush for one yard in the Steelers’ Week 2 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b4b-d86f-abdd-4fff708e0000</link>
      <description>It was on special teams where Johnson committed a catastrophic error by touching a kickoff and letting the ball roll into the end zone, where Seahawks players fell on the football for a touchdown that essentially sealed the game for Seattle. Already in the dog house for pass protection issues in the summer, Johnson’s kickoff return error could banish him to special teams for his entire rookie campaign. Kenneth Gainwell would be the Steelers’ No. 1 back if Jaylen Warren were to miss time in 2025. There are exceedingly few scenarios in which Johnson gets a crack at weekly usage in the Pittsburgh rushing attack. The rookie has a lot of trust to earn in the coming weeks and months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4b4b-d86f-abdd-4fff708e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
