<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>JuJu Smith-Schuster caught all five of his targets for 55 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d52-d332-a1fd-9f76242e0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs lost Xavier Worthy to a shoulder injury early in this game and Rashee Rice is serving a six-week suspension, elevating Smith-Schuster to a starting role. He was open for the occasional check-down from Patrick Mahomes but wasn’t overly involved in the game plan. Hollywood Brown led the team with a staggering 16 targets. JuJu’s five looks were second-most on the squad. Smith-Schuster will have WR6 fantasy value if Worthy is sidelined for Week 2 versus the Eagles, though most fantasy managers won’t need to dig that deep this early in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d52-d332-a1fd-9f76242e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 2-of-4 targets for 41 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d55-de13-afdd-5fdfa0db0000</link>
      <description>A strong training camp showing earned Thornton a roster spot in Kansas City and he may be needed even more than expected over the next few weeks. Rashee Rice is suspended for five more games and Xavier Worthy left this game with a shoulder injury. He took a hard hit from Travis Kelce on a crossing route and was quickly ruled out after a trip to the locker room. Patrick Mahomes overthrew Thornton on a deep shot early in the game but got on the same page as his deep threat late in the second quarter. That was his final catch of the game. Thornton has taken over the Justin Watson/Marquez Valdes Scantling role in the offense, but that’s not one worth chasing for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d55-de13-afdd-5fdfa0db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 2-of-4 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d5b-de13-afdd-5fdb59640000</link>
      <description>Kelce’s night got off to a rocky start when he collided with Xavier Worthy on a shallow route, knocking the diminutive wide receiver out of the game with a shoulder injury. With Worthy out and Rashee Rice on the sidelines for the first week of his six-game suspension, the Chiefs desperately needed someone to step up. Despite this, Kelce was nowhere to be found, catching one pass for 10 yards through three quarters. He did, however, redeem himself by slipping behind the LA defense for a 37-yard touchdown early in the fourth quarter. It was his final catch of the night. The touchdown saved his outing for fantasy managers, but being out-targeted 16-4 by Hollywood Brown is a stunning indictment of his ability to earn opportunities at the age of 35. Kelce may hang around the TE1 ranks out of sheer necessity for a few weeks, but one of Worthy or Rice could send him to the TE2 range later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d5b-de13-afdd-5fdb59640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed RB Quinshon Judkins to fully guaranteed deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f33-de13-afdd-5ffb7de50000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Judkins received a fully guaranteed deal. Now all draft picks are under contract for the season. Rapoport also adds that Judkins isn’t expected to play for the Browns in Week 1 against the Bengals, but could play in Week 2 against the Ravens. Expect Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford to handle the running back duties for the Browns until Judkins hits the field. While no charges remain in Judkins’ legal situation, the NFL investigation is ongoing. In the meantime, the Browns will receive a roster exemption that can last up to two weeks for Judkins and won’t have to make an additional roster move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f33-de13-afdd-5ffb7de50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans agreed with S Amani Hooker on three-year, $48.6 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f87-dbe3-a9bb-3fd749e60000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the deal includes $29 million in guaranteed money. While more details about the contract are unknown, this is already Hooker’s third contract just months after turning 27 in June. He’s started at least nine games for the Titans in four consecutive seasons, but is arguably coming off his best season with 71 tackles and a career-high five interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f87-dbe3-a9bb-3fd749e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL will interview Browns RB Quinshon Judkins this week in relation to his domestic battery case.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ffb-dbe3-a9bb-3ffb6d7c0000</link>
      <description>The criminal charges against Judkins were dropped relating to a domestic battery case in July, which allowed him to sign with the Browns earlier Saturday. That said, he still faces potential league discipline per the personal conduct policy, the proceedings of which are set to begin this week. The findings of the league investigation will be presented to Judge Sue L. Robinson, after which a recommended punishment will be handed down. Judkins can appeal any ruling but it certainly seems likely he will miss more time in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ffb-dbe3-a9bb-3ffb6d7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins elevated K Riley Patterson and RB Jeff Wilson ahead of their Week 1 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2014-dbe3-a9bb-305716630000</link>
      <description>Wilson gets the game day elevation in the wake of Jaylen Wright’s injury while the Dolphins entered Week 1 preparations without a kicker on the active roster. De’Von Achane remains the unquestioned top back while rookie Ollie Gordon appears set to step into the primary change of pace role, leaving Wilson as a likely emergency back. The team also did not elevate a tight end, meaning they will take on the Colts with only Julian Hill and Tanner Conner with Darren Waller set to miss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2014-dbe3-a9bb-305716630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans elevated WR Jared Wayne ahead of Week 1 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202a-dbe3-a9bb-307ba87f0000</link>
      <description>Wayne’s standard elevation was expected following injuries to fellow wide receiver Christian Kirk and Braxton Berrios, leaving the team thin at the position. he could find himself active in the coming weeks as well pending the length of recovery for Kirk and Berrios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202a-dbe3-a9bb-307ba87f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams elevated RB Cody Schrader from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202d-d332-a1fd-b63f21450000</link>
      <description>It’s an interesting development considering we rarely see Sean McVay teams hold four active backs on game day, a potential hint that the team could be primed to make rookie Jarquez Hunter a healthy inactive for the team’s Week 1 contest against the Texans. Schrader enters his second year in the league and was active on two occasions late last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202d-d332-a1fd-b63f21450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai is off the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2050-db7b-a5dd-a054fe330000</link>
      <description>Fellow running back Roschon Johnon is listed as questionable after getting in a limited session Saturday, potentially paving the way for Monangai to serve as the primary change of pace option in his first professional appearance for the Bears. Joining Johnson as questionable for Monday Night Football are DB Jaylon Johnson and DB Josh Blackwell, while LB T.J. Edwards is listed as doubtful with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2050-db7b-a5dd-a054fe330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
