<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn would not announce a starting quarterback for Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cac-da09-adde-bdfe1bc50000</link>
      <description>Glenn apparently wants to launch a last-minute sneak attack against the Bengals. The Jets are reportedly leaning toward starting Tyrod Taylor after Justin Fields’ abysmal play over the past few weeks, but Glenn isn’t ready to make the move official. Taylor, who is now dealing with a knee injury, would be an upgrade for the team’s pass catchers and should be rostered in all superflex formats against a soft Bengals defense. The potential for an in-game Fields benching makes him a risky fantasy play if he gets the Week 8 nod.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cac-da09-adde-bdfe1bc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) is day to day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0caf-deb1-a39b-2dafed580000</link>
      <description>With the Jets reportedly leaning toward starting Taylor in Week 8 against the Bengals, he might be unavailable and leave the team with no choice but to stick with Justin Fields. Fields has been horrific through Week 7. He ranks 25th out of 33 qualifying QBs in accuracy and 24th in drop back success rate. Fields has taken a sack on a league-high 14 percent of his drop backs this year. Taylor would be a significant upgrade for the New York pass catchers if he’s able to play through his knee issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0caf-deb1-a39b-2dafed580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed TE Darren Waller (pec) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cc7-deb1-a39b-2dcf3e180000</link>
      <description>The injury isn’t expected to require surgery, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, but Waller will miss at least the next four weeks while recovering from the pec injury he sustained in Week 7 against the Browns. Waller had become an important part of the Miami passing offense, recording ten receptions and four touchdowns over three games while running most of the routes in the Dolphins offense. With Waller out, look for De’Von Achane to see even more targets than usual. Malik Washington could also see a slight target bump over the next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cc7-deb1-a39b-2dcf3e180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Post’s Nicki Jhabvala reports Jayden Daniels (hamstring) won’t play in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd0-d245-adfb-9ddf9c960000</link>
      <description>Jhabvala said Daniels will sit and Marcus Mariota will get his third start of the season against Kansas City on Monday night. Mariota has proven an adept game manager with some fantasy appeal in his two 2025 starts, throwing three touchdowns and two interceptions while rushing for 94 yards and a touchdown. Daniels’ absence will be a downgrade for all Washington pass catchers and the general scoring environment of this Washington-KC matchup. Mariota should be started in all superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd0-d245-adfb-9ddf9c960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) is out for Week 8 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</link>
      <description>Irving hasn’t played since Week 4 as he struggles with injuries to his foot and shoulder. Rachaad White will continue as the Bucs’ lead back this week against the Saints, a middle rush defense. White’s involvement in the pass game has kept him afloat as a top-20 option with Irving sidelined. He should remain in lineups this week against a New Orleans defense allowing 104 rushing yards per game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Chris Godwin (fibula) won’t play in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9f0400000</link>
      <description>Godwin will miss yet another game with his fibula injury. The veteran, coming off a season-ending 2024 ankle injury, has suited up for just two games this season. The hope is that Godwin is able to return to action after Tampa’s Week 9 bye, though that’s far from certain. For now. Emeka Egbuka is the team’s clear-cut WR1, with Tez Johnson and Sterling Shepard mixing in as well. Cade Otton has seen a target bump with Godwin sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9f0400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Mike Evans underwent surgery to repair his broken collarbone and is expected to return in “eight weeks or fewer.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce3-d5d8-a3ff-fde345b40000</link>
      <description>That timeline still keeps Evans off the field for the bulk of the regular season, but it’s more optimistic than the initial reporting. Evans could even be back for the fantasy playoffs and will almost certainly be ready by the time the Bucs are in the NFL’s playoffs. With Chris Godwin out for Week 8 and Evans sidelined for roughly two months, rookie sensation Emeka Egbuka should stay hot and dominate the Bucs’ targets for the foreseeable future. Despite a quiet Week 7, Egbuka is near the top of the WR2 ranks going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce3-d5d8-a3ff-fde345b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce8-deb1-a39b-2dee8c400000</link>
      <description>Wilson could return for a limited session later today, but all signs point to a DNP for the young wideout. With a Week 9 bye on the horizon, the winless Jets shouldn’t be in a hurry to rush Wilson back to the lineup. Fantasy managers should move forward under the assumption Wilson is out for Week 8. Josh Reynolds, Tyler Johnson, and Mason Taylor each caught three passes last week. Reynolds gets a slight edge over Johnson in the fantasy ranks with Wilson out, but Taylor’s tight end eligibility makes him the best start of the trio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce8-deb1-a39b-2dee8c400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans interim head coach Mike McCoy said DT Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) is considered week to week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cf5-deb1-a39b-2dffa3230000</link>
      <description>Cornerback L’Jarius Sneed is expected to miss some time with a quad injury. McCoy didn’t rule out Simmons for Week 8, but it doesn’t sound like he is expected to play this week. Simmons has been one of the few bright spots for the Titans this year with 4.5 sacks and a forced fumble through eight games. The Titans’ defense will continue to struggle in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cf5-deb1-a39b-2dffa3230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d04-d245-adfb-9d5f9c410000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Dan Graziano, there is still a chance that Jackson misses Week 8, but things are at least trending in the right direction as of the first practice of the week. We will assume it’s a limited session until the Ravens drop their full injury report. Jackson has been out since Week 4 with the hamstring issue and is coming off a bye week, giving him plenty of rest ahead of a must-win game versus Chicago. Bears coach Ben Johnson has already said he is preparing as if Jackson is playing. Assuming things go to plan and Jackson is available by Sunday, he will, of course, jump right to the top of the fantasy ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d04-d245-adfb-9d5f9c410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
