<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released QB Tommy DeVito.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e64c-dbe3-a9bb-f65fef8c0000</link>
      <description>While DeVito was competing for the backup quarterback job in camp, he had little chance of making the Giants roster after New York brought in Russell Wilson, Jameis Winston and Jaxon Dart this offseason. The 27-year-old started six games with the Giants in 2023, throwing for eight touchdowns and three interceptions. DeVito is unlikely to be claimed by another team on waivers, meaning he’s destined for a practice squad. While carrying a fourth quarterback on the practice squad may be a little excessive, Wilson and Winston aren’t exactly spring chickens either and DeVito’s best path forward for his career may be to remain in the Giants organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e64c-dbe3-a9bb-f65fef8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports CB Rasul Douglas is signing a one-year deal with the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e658-d332-a1fd-f67e68700000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins had been in contact with Douglas over the offseason. The signing comes just in time for the season and it addresses a crucial need as it was already readily apparent the Dolphins needed help in the secondary. Douglas started 30 games mostly for the Bills over the last two seasons. The 30-year-old cornerback isn’t what he was earlier in his career, but with less than two weeks before the start of the regular season and the Dolphins desperate for secondary help he’s a good fit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e658-d332-a1fd-f67e68700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Browns have acquired G KT Leveston from the Rams in exchange for a 2028 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e66d-de13-afdc-e6ef1db90000</link>
      <description>Leveston was drafted in the seventh-round of the 2024 NFL Draft by the Rams out of Kansas State. While the Rams seem content to get whatever they can for Leveston, this could be a worthwhile gamble for a Browns team looking for offensive line depth. If not, well, the investment they’ve made in Leveston is minimal as the 2028 NFL Draft is still years away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e66d-de13-afdc-e6ef1db90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived CB Dane Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e67d-db7b-a5dd-e67da9490000</link>
      <description>The Bills signed Jackson this offseason to compete for depth in the secondary but the veteran was unable to secure a roster spot. He spent the first four years of his carer with the Bills before spending one season in Carolina. It is likely he gets another crack at an NFL roster in short order, either through waivers or once he clears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e67d-db7b-a5dd-e67da9490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released WR/KR Laviska Shenault.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e683-de13-afdc-e6cb1dd00000</link>
      <description>Shenault appeared to be the preferred kick returner for the Bills, the duties of which could now fall to Brandon Codrington. The five-year NFL veteran offers an intriguing upside profile stemming from his evasive abilities but has yet to fully transfer those talents onto the field while playing for the Jaguars, Panthers, Seahawks, and Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e683-de13-afdc-e6cb1dd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers have waived WR Trey Palmer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e692-de13-afdc-e6db13c40000</link>
      <description>A sixth-round pick by the Buccaneers in 2023, Palmer started eight games that year and had 385 yards on 39 catches and three touchdowns. Palmer finished the 2024 season with just 172 yards on 12 catches and one touchdown. He wasn’t able to make the 53-man roster given the Buccaneers’ crowded receiver room. Palmer’s ability to return kicks and punts could help him catch on with another organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e692-de13-afdc-e6db13c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons released K Lenny Krieg.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e691-dbe3-a9bb-f6d38b830000</link>
      <description>Krieg’s release means veteran Younghoe Koo has won the kicking battle for the Falcons. The undrafted free agent was signed to compete with Koo early in the offseason but ultimately came short in his push to unthrone Koo, the latter of whom has kicked for the Falcons for the previous six seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e691-dbe3-a9bb-f6d38b830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released WR Diontae Johnson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69d-db7b-a5dd-e69dea8d0000</link>
      <description>Johnson totaled 4,363 yards and 25 touchdowns over the first five years of his career with the Steelers, but his career came off the rails last year. After flaming out with the Panthers, Ravens and Texans in 2024, Johnson signed a $1.2 million contract containing no guaranteed money with the Browns. Now that the Browns are also moving on without Johnson, it’s unclear what the next step is for the 29-year-old receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69d-db7b-a5dd-e69dea8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars released LB Chad Muma.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69a-d332-a1fd-f6be87970000</link>
      <description>Quite the surprise for the former No. 70 overall pick in the 2022 NFL Draft. Muma started just seven games across 50 appearances for the Jaguars since being drafted but shouldn’t wait long to resurface on a professional roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69a-d332-a1fd-f6be87970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers released LB/S Isaiah Simmons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6a4-d332-a1fd-f6b6a22a0000</link>
      <description>Simmons signed with the Packers in April after the Giants let him walk in free agency but was unable to crack the final 53 in Green Bay. His unique athletic profile allows him to play multiple positions in the middle of the field, something that could help him catch on with another team via waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6a4-d332-a1fd-f6b6a22a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
