<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 19:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) is out for Week 8 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</link>
      <description>Irving hasn’t played since Week 4 as he struggles with injuries to his foot and shoulder. Rachaad White will continue as the Bucs’ lead back this week against the Saints, a middle rush defense. White’s involvement in the pass game has kept him afloat as a top-20 option with Irving sidelined. He should remain in lineups this week against a New Orleans defense allowing 104 rushing yards per game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd6-dab4-a3fb-9ff61de30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said Chris Godwin (fibula) won’t play in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9f0400000</link>
      <description>Godwin will miss yet another game with his fibula injury. The veteran, coming off a season-ending 2024 ankle injury, has suited up for just two games this season. The hope is that Godwin is able to return to action after Tampa’s Week 9 bye, though that’s far from certain. For now. Emeka Egbuka is the team’s clear-cut WR1, with Tez Johnson and Sterling Shepard mixing in as well. Cade Otton has seen a target bump with Godwin sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cd9-dab4-a3fb-9ff9f0400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Mike Evans underwent surgery to repair his broken collarbone and is expected to return in “eight weeks or fewer.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce3-d5d8-a3ff-fde345b40000</link>
      <description>That timeline still keeps Evans off the field for the bulk of the regular season, but it’s more optimistic than the initial reporting. Evans could even be back for the fantasy playoffs and will almost certainly be ready by the time the Bucs are in the NFL’s playoffs. With Chris Godwin out for Week 8 and Evans sidelined for roughly two months, rookie sensation Emeka Egbuka should stay hot and dominate the Bucs’ targets for the foreseeable future. Despite a quiet Week 7, Egbuka is near the top of the WR2 ranks going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce3-d5d8-a3ff-fde345b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce8-deb1-a39b-2dee8c400000</link>
      <description>Wilson could return for a limited session later today, but all signs point to a DNP for the young wideout. With a Week 9 bye on the horizon, the winless Jets shouldn’t be in a hurry to rush Wilson back to the lineup. Fantasy managers should move forward under the assumption Wilson is out for Week 8. Josh Reynolds, Tyler Johnson, and Mason Taylor each caught three passes last week. Reynolds gets a slight edge over Johnson in the fantasy ranks with Wilson out, but Taylor’s tight end eligibility makes him the best start of the trio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ce8-deb1-a39b-2dee8c400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans interim head coach Mike McCoy said DT Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) is considered week to week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cf5-deb1-a39b-2dffa3230000</link>
      <description>Cornerback L’Jarius Sneed is expected to miss some time with a quad injury. McCoy didn’t rule out Simmons for Week 8, but it doesn’t sound like he is expected to play this week. Simmons has been one of the few bright spots for the Titans this year with 4.5 sacks and a forced fumble through eight games. The Titans’ defense will continue to struggle in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0cf5-deb1-a39b-2dffa3230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d04-d245-adfb-9d5f9c410000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Dan Graziano, there is still a chance that Jackson misses Week 8, but things are at least trending in the right direction as of the first practice of the week. We will assume it’s a limited session until the Ravens drop their full injury report. Jackson has been out since Week 4 with the hamstring issue and is coming off a bye week, giving him plenty of rest ahead of a must-win game versus Chicago. Bears coach Ben Johnson has already said he is preparing as if Jackson is playing. Assuming things go to plan and Jackson is available by Sunday, he will, of course, jump right to the top of the fantasy ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d04-d245-adfb-9d5f9c410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d0c-deb1-a39b-2d0ee4dd0000</link>
      <description>Collins suffered the concussion on Monday night versus Seattle. He went down in the fourth quarter and did not return. A significantly short week will make it even harder for him to clear the league’s concussion protocol by Sunday. With Christian Kirk also sidelined, Xavier Hutchinson appears to be the team’s top wideout heading into Week 8. Rookie Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins should both see more work as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d0c-deb1-a39b-2d0ee4dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1c-deb1-a39b-2d1efb850000</link>
      <description>Kirk suffered a hamstring injury in practice last week and was downgraded to a DNP on Friday. The team ruled him out before the weekend. A DNP to start the week suggests Kirk will also miss Week 8’s game against the 49ers. Kirk also missed time to start the year because of a hamstring issue. Fantasy managers can cut ties with him once he is officially ruled out later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1c-deb1-a39b-2d1efb850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed WR Ray-Ray McCloud, formerly of the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d21-d245-adfb-9d7f906b0000</link>
      <description>McCloud has been signed to the Giants’ practice squad. The move reunites McCloud with Giants head coach Brian Daboll. The two spent McCloud’s 2018 rookie season with the Bills, where Daboll served as the offensive coordinator. McCloud barely played that year, catching 5-of-6 targets for 36 yards, but the 29-year-old wide receiver has become a capable returner and can fill in as a rotational receiver as needed. Injuries have thinned out the Giants’ perimeter wide receiver corps, so a Week 8 call-up from the practice squad is in the cards for McCloud. He is not on the FLEX radar in 12-team re-draft leagues, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d21-d245-adfb-9d7f906b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) was seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1a-dab4-a3fb-9f7aeeff0000</link>
      <description>Austin could end up being officially listed as limited today, but his return to practice is a good sign overall. The Steelers’ diminutive wide receiver was taken to the hospital after injuring his shoulder in Week 4 against the Vikings and has not practiced since then. The Steelers (4-2) sit atop the AFC North, and face a talented Packers (4-1-1) team with playoff aspirations. Austin would enter the FLEX conversation if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0d1a-dab4-a3fb-9f7aeeff0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
