<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:29:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 4-of-5 targets for 17 yards in the Titans’ Week 15 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7b-d8cf-affb-bf7bacd30000</link>
      <description>Dike had the most targets of any Titans wide receiver, but that’s not much to write home about. The Titans love to run screen passes, and Dike is really shifty after the catch, so you figure he’d be a good option on those plays, but they don’t seem to agree. However, the rookie also had a brutal drop in the fourth quarter on a play where Cam Ward evaded three rushers and escaped to the sideline before throwing a dart that hit Dike in the chest. He needs to make those catches, and the drop is a good example of why he’s hard to trust in fantasy leagues right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7b-d8cf-affb-bf7bacd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the “initial belief” is that Packers EDGE Micah Parsons “suffered a torn ACL” in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7b-d005-a9bf-df7fa3360000</link>
      <description>Parsons’ season would be over if that is indeed the case. He will undergo further testing soon. Per PFF’s initial statistical Week 15, post-game tally, Parsons totaled 19 tackles, 79 quarterback pressures and 14 sacks in his first season as a Packer. He is under contract through 2029, having signed a four-year, $186 million contract extension this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7b-d005-a9bf-df7fa3360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught his only target for 17 yards in the Titans’ Week 15 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7c-d8cf-affb-bf7eab290000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor had only one target on the day, but he hauled it in, so that’s something. The Titans don’t seem to want Cam Ward to throw the ball downfield much, which means it’s really hard for anybody to roster Ayomanor in re-draft leagues for the remainder of this season. However, Ayomanor and Ward also had a miscommunication on a fourth-quarter pass that almost led to an interception, so maybe that hesitancy makes some sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7c-d8cf-affb-bf7eab290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Jefferson caught 1-of-5 targets for 43 yards in the Titans’ Week 15 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7e-d8cf-affb-bf7e66040000</link>
      <description>Jefferson was second on the Titans in receiving yards and did it all on one catch. He was also second on the team with five targets and would have had a 40-yard touchdown catch in the second quarter if Cam Ward, who was pressured on the play, hadn’t sailed the pass over his head. The Titans have talked about getting Jefferson more involved, and he’s the clear depth threat in this offense, so perhaps he will luck into some garbage time production over the final weeks. However, he did leave the game in the fourth quarter with a lower back injury after making an impressive leaping catch and landing directly on his back. Keep an eye on his practice reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f7e-d8cf-affb-bf7e66040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 25-of-41 passes for 338 yards and three touchdowns in the Lions’ 41-34, Week 15 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f75-d005-a9bf-df7560f90000</link>
      <description>There wasn’t really much Goff did wrong in this one — he only took one sack and managed two red zone strikes to Amon-Ra St. Brown. The Lions converted their two fourth-down gos. The running game was bad and put Goff in big spots that he usually delivered on, and the game turned when Detroit fell apart in the third quarter, as between the sack and a couple rough plays they punted three straight times. Goff corrected course, but couldn’t keep pace with the Rams, who averaged 7.5 yards per play to Detroit’s 6.4. A Week 16 date with the Steelers should keep Goff on the QB1 line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f75-d005-a9bf-df7560f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 23-of-34 passes for 304 yards and four touchdowns in the Broncos’ 34-26, Week 15 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f73-d8cf-affb-bf7b317a0000</link>
      <description>Nix was methodical all afternoon, working his way downfield time and time again against a vaunted Packers defense. The Broncos’ signal-caller played turnover-free football and didn’t take a sack while leading his offense to five separate scoring drives on the day. Nix got the Broncos on the board in the second quarter when he connected with practice squad vet Michael Bandy for a 20-yard score on a catch-and-run, and added another five-yard touchdown pass to Lil’Jordan Humphrey before halftime. He would add two more touchdown passes in the third quarter — one to Courtland Sutton and another to Troy Franklin, to given the Broncos the lead heading into the fourth. They would hold onto that lead the remainder of the and now enter Week 16 with a 12-2 record. Nix’s four touchdown passes tie a career-high. He’ll be a fringe QB1/QB2 in Week 16 against the Jaguars next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f73-d8cf-affb-bf7b317a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters that Davante Adams’ (hamstring) availability is in doubt for Week 16 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f86-d1bc-a3fb-9fa607020000</link>
      <description>Adams pulled up lame while running a route downfield in Week 15 against the Lions, evidently aggravating the hamstring strain that he played through last week. Adams still leads the NFL with 14 receiving touchdowns despite being held out of the end zone since Week 13. Backup plans should be made at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f86-d1bc-a3fb-9fa607020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 24-of-40 passes for 276 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Packers’ 34-26, Week 15 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f85-d77b-adfb-df87cd050000</link>
      <description>Love led the Packers to points on every possession in the first half. Three of those drives ended with field goals; their lone touchdown came on a beautifully thrown ball to Josh Jacobs in the end zone, who hauled in a contested catch to give the Packers a 13-7 lead. The Packers found the end zone again on the opening drive of the third quarter, thanks in part to a DPI call on Riley Moss on third-and-four to keep the drive alive. Josh Jacobs would run in a 40-yard touchdown on the following play, but the wheels fell off for Love and the Packers after that. On the Packers’ next possession, Love was picked off by Patrick Surtain II on a deep pass to Christian Watson, and threw his second pick of the day to Moss two drives later on a pass that bounced off Dontayvion Wicks’ hands. Love and the Packers now head to Chicago for a Week 16 matchup against the Bears. Fantasy managers shouldn’t view him as anything more than a high-end QB2 next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f85-d77b-adfb-df87cd050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 12 times for 73 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 15 loss to the Broncos, adding two receptions for 19 additional yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f92-d1bc-a3fb-9fb6e1a50000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was reportedly on a “pitch count” entering Sunday, but the Packers’ RB1 ended up handling 12 of the Packers’ 16 running back carries. Jacobs put the Packers on the board with a highlight reel catch in the second quarter when he hauled in a contested target over LB Dre Greenlaw in the end zone for the 14-yard score. Then, following a 25-yard DPI penalty by Riley Moss in the third quarter on third-and-four, Jacobs broke free for a 40-yard rushing score to give the Packers a 23-14 lead. He remained involved throughout the day, but with two drives cut short by turnovers and another ending after six plays, there was little opportunity for Jacobs to do much in the second half. Assuming he doesn’t suffer any setbacks this week, Jacobs will be on the RB1 radar in Week 16 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f92-d1bc-a3fb-9fb6e1a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 24-of-38 passes for 368 yards, two touchdowns and one interception in the Rams’ 41-34, Week 15 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f96-d8cf-affb-bfbea1860000</link>
      <description>Stafford was nearly pick-sixed on his first drive when Aidan Hutchinson read a screen and took a target for Colby Parkinson back 58 yards into the Rams’ red zone. But the MVP leader in the clubhouse led the Rams to scores on three of his other four first-half drives, then quickly pushed the Rams to a 10-point lead with a 39-yard toss to Puka Nacua that led to a Blake Corum sideline scamper to put the Rams up 34-24. It probably wasn’t one of Stafford’s best games of the season, and he did leave a few throws out there, but that just meant he *merely* threw for 368 yards. Stafford will be in one of his toughest spots of the season on a short-week road trip to Seattle, but his red zone excellence has made his floor pretty sound in the QB1 tiers all year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f96-d8cf-affb-bfbea1860000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
