<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:57:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes “it’s reasonable” to think George Kittle (Achilles) could return in Week 5 “or so.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85fe-d629-a1bc-b5ffa7d80000</link>
      <description>Wagoner’s long piece on Kittle’s injury is rooted in the idea that Kittle’s Achilles tear was “clean” and “happened high up by his soleus,” meaning the blood flow wasn’t as poor as it could be during the recovery. Kittle did not entirely rule out the idea of being ready for Week 1. We’d be surprised if a tight end entering his age-33 season was ready for Week 1, but we’ve learned not to count out any wild physical feats from Kittle. This timeline makes him a little more interesting in 2026 best ball, at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85fe-d629-a1bc-b5ffa7d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nick Kosmider expects the Broncos to “explore multiple other options” before attempting to re-sign J.K. Dobbins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8612-d629-a1bc-b61f0c5b0000</link>
      <description>As well as Dobbins played, this makes plenty of sense. The Broncos stumbled into him in post-draft free agency — he was no primary target — and he (as usual) missed a huge chunk of last season with an injury. With the Russell Wilson cap hold gone, the Broncos could be a sneaky threat for the bigger-name running backs in free agency in 2026. Kosmider does say it would not be “shocking” if Dobbins eventually comes back, but he’s not a priority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8612-d629-a1bc-b61f0c5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos hired John Morton as their new pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-86fe-d629-a1bc-b6ff8e2d0000</link>
      <description>Morton served as the Broncos’ pass game coordinator in 2023 and 2024 before accepting the Lions’ offensive coordinator role in 2025. He was relieved of play-calling duties in-season last year and fired in early January. The Broncos then brought him aboard as an offensive consultant for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-86fe-d629-a1bc-b6ff8e2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Mario Jeberaeel as their new run game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8709-d042-afbc-ffdb55c90000</link>
      <description>Jeberaeel has coached in the NFL for five seasons, spending the last two seasons with the Jaguars and the three before that with the Falcons. He got started with the latter team as a diversity coaching intern and offensive line coach in 2021. He served as the assistant offensive line coach in 2022 before becoming a special projects coach on defense. The Jaguars hired him as an assistant outside linebackers coach in 2024. He spent 2025 working as a defensive assistant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8709-d042-afbc-ffdb55c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio reports there is a “belief in league circles” that the Jets will apply the transition tag to RB Breece Hall.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-873e-d990-a1de-ef7ee07c0000</link>
      <description>The 2026 transition tag for running backs is expected to fall between $11.5 million and $11.9 million. Applying this tag would allow Hall to shop the contract around the NFL. If another team ups the offer, the Jets will have the chance to match the new offer. Florio notes, however, if the Jets decline to match the new offer, Hall’s departure would not count toward the “next year’s slate of compensatory draft picks” because he is not leaving the team via the typical free agency fashion. If the Jets “catch wind” of a potentially serious suitor, they can rescind the transition tag before an official counteroffer is made, rendering Hall a free agent and restoring his compensatory pick viability. Perhaps the seemingly disgruntled running back will be playing elsewhere in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-873e-d990-a1de-ef7ee07c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Post’s Vincent Bonsignore believes the Rams could draft a developmental quarterback prospect in the 2026 NFL Draft’s first round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-877a-d042-afbc-fffa71800000</link>
      <description>Matthew Stafford, 38, is entrenched as the 2026 starter. Bonsignore writes that “the Rams are already planning for that inevitable transition” that will occur whenever Stafford chooses to retire. Indiana QB Fernando Mendoza is unlikely to be available when the Rams are on the clock with the 13th and 29th first-round picks. Bonsignore singles out Alabama QB Ty Simpson as an option for the Rams, while noting that they will likely take a look at Penn State QB Drew Allar, Miami QB Carson Beck, Arkansas QB Taylen Green, Georgia Tech QB Haynes King, Clemson QB Cade Klubnik and LSU QB Garrett Nussmeier at the upcoming NFL Scouting Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-877a-d042-afbc-fffa71800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL competition committee co-chairman Rich McKay said the committee has received zero requests to ban the Tush Push thus far this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87a2-d89c-a1be-afff08a90000</link>
      <description>Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts fumbled on a Tush Push attempt in Philadelphia’s 24-15, Week 13 loss to the Bears. He told reporters after the game that it is “becoming tougher and tougher” to run the play. Teams are having more success against it, defensively, than they did previously, while others have begun successfully running it themselves. Seahawks TE AJ Barner moonlighted as a Tush Push quarterback this season. Per PFF, Barner picked up one touchdown and nine first downs on 11 rushing attempts across the full NFL season. It is still possible for teams to submit a ban proposal, but at this point, McKay does not “envision it” happening this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87a2-d89c-a1be-afff08a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports that “the Cowboys are “in talks” with K Brandon Aubrey about a long-term contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87cb-d990-a1de-efcfed280000</link>
      <description>Aubrey’s agent, Todd France, and the Cowboys have been in talks “for some time,” and Cowboys owner Jerry Jones confirmed that the two sides have been exchanging contract offers. Jones is seemingly intent on keeping Aubrey, saying the Cowboys will “tender him before the deadline” if they have to. Aubrey has earned Pro Bowl honors in each of the last three seasons. He was a first-team All-Pro in 2023 and was a second-team All-Pro in 2024 and 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87cb-d990-a1de-efcfed280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Seahawks plan to sign WR Jaxon Smith-Njigba and CB Devon Witherspoon to contract extensions this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8788-d89c-a1be-afdf244f0000</link>
      <description>Smith-Njigba led the NFL with 1,793 receiving yards en route to Offensive Player of the Year, first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors this season. He turned 24 years old earlier this month and believes he deserves to be the highest-paid wide receiver in the NFL. Smith-Njigba’s teammate, and fellow 2023 first-round draftee, Witherspoon also took home Pro Bowl and second-team All-Pro honors this year. Witherspoon should end up being handsomely paid as well, though it is unclear whether he is a candidate to reset the positional market. ESPN’s Brady Henderson notes that the Seahawks can exercise a fifth-year option on both contracts by May 1, giving all involved extra time to negotiate long-term deals if need be. Were the Seahawks to make Smith-Njigba the NFL’s highest-paid wide receiver, the contract would average more than $40 million per year in new money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8788-d89c-a1be-afdf244f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins believes that if the Cowboys use the franchise tag on WR George Pickens, there is a “strong possibility he will not report to the offseason programs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8806-d89c-a1be-afdf60c30000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are currently expected to use the franchise tag on Pickens. While a tag-and-trade scenario is possible, Watkins adds that “both sides have mutual interest in the star receiver returning.” Star players have had contentious negotiations with the Cowboys’ front office in recent seasons, including QB Dak Prescott, WR CeeDee Lamb and EDGE Micah Parsons, who was ultimately traded to the Packers. A speedy resolution would allow Pickens to join his teammates for offseason training without injury-related contract concerns looming overhead. This outcome is likely best for all involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8806-d89c-a1be-afdf60c30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
