<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tahj Brooks (concussion) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 13 game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d413-ad9f-b7dd16330000</link>
      <description>No surprise that a player in protocol will miss a short-week game. Brooks’ absence will leave the Bengals with little behind Chase Brown unless Samaje Perine is able to return from a high-ankle sprain on Thursday. Gary Brightwell, a special teamer, is the only other back on the roster. Kendall Milton is hanging out on the practice squad. Don’t be surprised to see Bengals RB workouts ahead of Thursday’s game. Trey Hendrickson (hip) was also ruled out for Thursday, as usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b70c-d413-ad9f-b7dd16330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski has named Shedeur Sanders as the team’s starting QB.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b725-d90e-a9da-bf2f29f00000</link>
      <description>Shedeur was under center for the Browns’ third win of the season over the Raiders and helped generate a more vertical passing attack while throwing for 209-1-1 on 11-of-20 passing. Sanders’ two biggest throws of the day came on a beautifully thrown 52-yard bomb to Isaiah Bond in the first quarter, with his other coming on a 66-yard touchdown on a pass behind the line of scrimmage to Dylan Sampson. It was only going to be a matter of time before Sanders, who famously slid to the fifth-round of this year’s draft, got a chance to start. Now, the Browns will look to see if he’s their quarterback of the future over these next six weeks or another name added to a laundry list of QB1 hopefuls. Sanders shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a low-end QB2 for this week’s game against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b725-d90e-a9da-bf2f29f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Davis had three rushes for 24 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 12 win against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b727-d82c-a79a-b7b774020000</link>
      <description>Davis is emerging as the clear RB2 behind Javonte Williams, who had 87 scoreless yards on 20 rushes against a tough Philadelphia front seven in Week 12. Davis showed a lot of burst on two of his three carries against the Eagles, including a 21-yard run up the middle. Davis should be stashed on fantasy benches this week in case Williams gets dinged up down the stretch. Jaydon Blue was once again a healthy inactive in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b727-d82c-a79a-b7b774020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy is in the concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72d-d82c-a79a-b7bd4c070000</link>
      <description>It is the softest benching yet for McCarthy, as the team could not identify one particular hit where he picked up a concussion. McCarthy reported symptoms on the flight home. Backup quarterback and rookie UDFA Max Brosmer could be in line for a desperation start against the Seahawks in Week 13. Of course, after last week’s McCarthy performance — one where the team finished with -1 total yards as an offense after halftime — Brosmer could very well be an upgrade. O’Connell was not yet ready to rule McCarthy out and the Vikings do play on Sunday so there’s a little time for this to settle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72d-d82c-a79a-b7bd4c070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Raider will name QB coach Greg Olson as interim OC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</link>
      <description>Olson was born to be a Raider. Literally. The 62-year-old coach is in his third stint with the team since first being hired as offensive coordinator in 2013, and also spent three years as their OC from 2018-2021 under Jon Gruden. Now, instead of having to get better play out of Derek Carr, Olson will take on the task of fixing Geno Smith, who took an unprecedented 10 sacks in Week 12’s loss to the Browns. The Raiders currently ranked 31st in points scored and are 30th in yards. Running back Ashton Jeanty has had his moments, but is also underwhelming to the tune of 166-604-4 on the ground while averaging 3.6 YPC. While it’s hard to imagine the Raiders doing a complete 180 midseason, it’s also hard to imagine things will continue as they have. We’ll get our first look at the Olson-led offense in Week 13 when the Raiders face the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b71b-d82c-a79a-b79ff1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</link>
      <description>Officially fired on his day off, Gabriel will spend Week 13 backing up Shedeur Sanders after missing Week 12’s game due to his brain injury. Gabriel’s lack of a vertical passing game, as evidenced by a 6.4 ADOT and eight deep throw attempts over eight games, may have proven to be his downfall. Gabriel topped 200 passing yards just once in the six starts he made this season while ranking near the bottom of the league in both dropback success rate and EPA per dropback. Barring injury or a complete implosion by Sanders, there’s a good chance this is the last we have seen of Gabriel in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b72f-db57-afda-f73f47cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders designated WR Noah Brown (groin) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b73e-db57-afda-f73e23bc0000</link>
      <description>Browns’ 21-day practice window has now been opened, meaning the Commanders can officially activate him off injured reserve whenever they believe he’s ready to go. Brown hasn’t played since Week 2 and has just three catches for 36 yards this season. He caught just 35 passes for 453 yards and one touchdown last season, and has little to no fantasy upside whenever he’s activated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b73e-db57-afda-f73e23bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayen Daniels (elbow) is unlikely to play in Week 13 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b74a-d413-ad9f-b7df182d0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, a source familiar with the situation believes Daniels playing in Week 13 is “a long-shot.” That said, the second-year quarterback is expected to practice this week, meaning a return could be near. Daniels has missed five games this season due to a mixed bag of injuries, but has thrown for 1,183-8-2 in his six starts. Fantasy managers looking for a boost at quarterback ahead of the fantasy playoffs should consider stashing Daniels where available, as he remains a strong QB1 candidate any week when he is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b74a-d413-ad9f-b7df182d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders HC Pete Carroll said Ashton Jeanty’s ankle injury is not considered serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b755-db57-afda-f777c67b0000</link>
      <description>When asked whether the injury could limit Jeanty in practice this week, Carroll said he hasn’t “heard that it would yet.” The Raiders’ RB1 totaled 108 yards from scrimmage and a touchdown in Week 12’s loss to the Browns and is one of the very few bright spots for the offense. It doesn’t sound like Carroll is overly concerned about Jeanty’s injury sidelining him for Week 13 against the Chargers. If he were to miss this week’s game, Zamir White would figure to step in on early downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b755-db57-afda-f777c67b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles S Andrew Mukuba suffered a fractured leg in Week 12’s loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b76d-d413-ad9f-b7fd647d0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo, Mukuba’s injury will most likely require surgery. The timeline for his return is unclear at this point, but Mukuba has made an immediate impact for the Eagles this season. The rookie second-rounder has started 10 of the 11 games he’s appeared in while notching two interceptions, three pass breakups, and 46 tackles. Mukuba will land on injured reserve, while backup Sydney Brown is expected to takeover for him as the starter opposite Reed Blankenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b76d-d413-ad9f-b7fd647d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
