<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said the team is “hopeful but not sure on Week 1" when asked about Jauan Jennings (calf).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed4a-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bd5cb0000</link>
      <description>He additionally noted that the 49ers would not be trading Jennings. It certainly looks like it’s up in the air who will start next to Ricky Pearsall in Week 1, with Marquez Valdes-Scantling and Russell Gage looking like the most likely names at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed4a-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bd5cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed QB Brett Rypien to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed75-d332-a1fd-ff7714700000</link>
      <description>He’ll be the third quarterback in Cincinnati this year behind Joe Burrow and Jake Browning. Also joining the Cincinnati practice squad are: RB Gary Brightwell, S Russ Yeast, OT Devin Cochran, OT Andrew Coker, CB Jalen Davis, LB Joe Giles-Harris, G Jaxson Kirkland, CB Bralyn Lux, C Seth McLaughlin, RB Kendall Milton, WR Jordan Moore, LB Maema Njongmeta, DE Isaiah Thomas and WR Isaiah Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed75-d332-a1fd-ff7714700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (groin) left Wednesday’s practice with an injury and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb95680000</link>
      <description>Per Adam Schefter, the team is “not overly concerned.” Still, it wouldn’t be surprising if his practice time were limited leading up to Week 1. Should Mims be ruled out, Troy Franklin or Pat Bryant could assume a bigger role against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb95680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed96-db7b-a5dd-ed96b3f50000</link>
      <description>A tale as true as time: the third quarterback was released at last cuts and found his way to the practice squad. Joining Ehlinger on the Broncos practice squad are: G Calvin Throckmorton, CB Reese Taylor, LB Jordan Turner, FB Adam Prentice, WR Michael Bandy, WR A.T. Perry, CB Jaden Robinson, S Delarrin Turner-Yell, ILB Garret Wallow, TE Caleb Lohner, OL Joe Michalski, LB Levelle Bailey and CB Quinton Newsome.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed96-db7b-a5dd-ed96b3f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars GM James Gladstone said Travis Hunter (upper body) is “rolling full speed.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee28-db7b-a5dd-ee2c6f650000</link>
      <description>There was never any real concern about Hunter missing Week 1 despite sitting the third game of the preseason. He’ll start off as a WR3 against a rough Panthers defense next Sunday. Gladstone said the plan remains for Hunter to play on both sides of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee28-db7b-a5dd-ee2c6f650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed K Riley Patterson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee2c-de13-afdc-eeef3fa00000</link>
      <description>He’s expected to be elevated and kick for the Dolphins in Week 1 against the Colts. As long as Patterson doesn’t leave points off the field, he should have a chance to replace Jason Sanders throughout his entire IR stint. Sanders is expected back in 4-5 weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee2c-de13-afdc-eeef3fa00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders claimed OLB Brennan Jackson off waivers from the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee2f-db7b-a5dd-ee2f274a0000</link>
      <description>The 2024 fifth-rounder flashed as a pass rusher this preseason and the Raiders need all the help at EDGE they can get. Jackson should be a part of the rotation after playing just 47 defensive snaps for the Rams in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee2f-db7b-a5dd-ee2f274a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders placed Aidan O’Connell (wrist) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee32-d332-a1fd-fe36906f0000</link>
      <description>He was expected to miss 6-8 weeks after getting hurt in the preseason finale, so while he can theoretically be back for Week 5, O’Connell’s timeline is probably a little deeper than that. After the Raiders acquired Kenny Pickett, there’s little reason to believe O’Connell will throw a pass for the team this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee32-d332-a1fd-fe36906f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (foot) returned to practice but said Week 1 “still feels uncertain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee36-dbe3-a9bb-fe77e1010000</link>
      <description>Reed apparently isn’t yet running routes without pain. We’ll be monitoring Reed’s practice status ahead of Week 1’s game against the Lions, but with both Reed himself and Matt LaFleur setting early expectations that Reed will miss the game, fantasy managers should be prepared to pivot away from Reed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee36-dbe3-a9bb-fe77e1010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Michael Carter to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee3d-dbe3-a9bb-fe7f4fe10000</link>
      <description>Carter surprisingly lost out to Zonovan Knight for the final roster spot at running back, but decided to remain with the Cardinals practice squad. Joining him so far are: WR Andre Baccellia, LB Elliott Brown, OL Jeremiah Byers, OL Jake Curhan, TE Josiah Deguara, WR Simi Fehoko, DL Anthony Goodlow, CB Darren Hall, OL Sincere Haynesworth, OL Nick Leverett, WR Tejhaun Palmer and DL Elijah Simmons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee3d-dbe3-a9bb-fe7f4fe10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
