<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said he needs “to call more runs” and make sure RB Kyle Monangai “has more carries going forward.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3536-d332-a1fd-b736c8e30000</link>
      <description>Johnson estimates that the Bears were “under 20" called run plays against the Vikings in Week 1, and stated his intention to increase that number so as to further involve the rookie, Monangai. Johnson actually called exactly 20 run plays, with D’Andre Swift handling 17 and DJ Moore handling three. Coaches frequently make comments like this regarding intriguing backups but the intentions often fail to materialize. With an offensive mastermind like Johnson, we should at least take note. Monangai remains a worthwhile bench stash to see how things play out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3536-d332-a1fd-b736c8e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Tre’Davious White (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3540-dbe3-a9bb-35531daa0000</link>
      <description>White did not practice last week and was listed as doubtful on Friday. As expected, he was ruled out before kickoff. It looks like the veteran corner is nearing a return after getting in a limited session to open the week. White will likely take over as Buffalo’s CB2 once healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3540-dbe3-a9bb-35531daa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Brock Purdy (shoulder/toe) is a “long shot” to play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3546-db7b-a5dd-b5463b6d0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan also mentioned that it could be a multi-week injury for Purdy, though he didn’t give an exact timeline for his return. Purdy won’t practice on Wednesday after sustaining multiple injuries in Week 1 against the Seahawks. Jauan Jennings also suffered a shoulder injury in that game and George Kittle landed on injured reserve with a hamstring issue. Mac Jones is in line to make his first start as a 49er and will do so in a relatively easy matchup versus the Saints. Though he is far from a one-for-one replacement for Purdy, Jones should be able to execute the basics of Shanahan’s scheme. He will register as a low-end QB2 for fantasy purposes, making him worth an add in Superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3546-db7b-a5dd-b5463b6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (glute) is practicing in full for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-353c-db7b-a5dd-b53c29940000</link>
      <description>This is a new injury for Pittman, though his full participation should assuage concerns about his Week 2 availability. Pittman is also known for playing through pain, having dealt with a fracture in his back for much of last year. The Colts steamrolled the Dolphins in Week 2 but they face a far stiffer test against the Broncos’ elite defense in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-353c-db7b-a5dd-b53c29940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (knee) is practicing fully for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3545-dbe3-a9bb-3557837f0000</link>
      <description>The Colts should have their field-stretching wide receiver available to them when they take on the vaunted Broncos defense in Week 2. Pierce’s usage is too unreliable for weekly FLEX consideration and this matchup does him no favors. He is just a dart-throw FLEX option in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3545-dbe3-a9bb-3557837f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3554-db7b-a5dd-b554acef0000</link>
      <description>Taylor played every single snap for the Jets in Week 1 but only earned one target. It’s possible he was laboring through the ankle issue for the entire game. Taylor also suffered a high-ankle sprain early in training camp, though it’s unclear if the new ankle injury is related. Either way, fantasy managers will want to watch his practice status throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3554-db7b-a5dd-b554acef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3554-dbe3-a9bb-35570b4b0000</link>
      <description>Saints OG Trevor Penning (toe) and EDGE Chase Young (calf) were absent as well. Fuaga mans the right side of the line while Penning mans the inner left. This unit will be in bad shape if they are asked to take on the 49ers’ pass rush without two of its starters. Both Penning and Young missed Week 1 as well, while Fuaga was forced from play against the Cardinals last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3554-dbe3-a9bb-35570b4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3561-d93a-abbb-7d7be43d0000</link>
      <description>Boutte is coming off his second 100-yard game in a row, dating back to the end of the 2024 season. He operated as Drake Maye’s No. 1 receiver in Week 1 and turned eight targets into six catches for 103 yards. A limited session to start the week isn’t cause for concern just yet, though fantasy managers who scooped Boutte off the waiver wire will want to keep an eye on his practice status going forward. If healthy, Boutte looks like a potential WR4 for Week 2 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3561-d93a-abbb-7d7be43d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports that “the NFL has begun a review of the recent domestic violence allegations against Dolphins receiver Tyreek Hill.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3558-d93a-abbb-7d5a06a00000</link>
      <description>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel also indicated that the “in-house disciplinary process,” which involves “an effort” to interview the alleged victim, has been activated. Hill was recently accused of eight instances of domestic violence “in a court filing submitted in connection with a divorce case.” Florio notes that Hill pleaded guilty to “domestic assault and battery by strangulation” 10 years ago, which could count as “an aggravating factor in connection with any punishment Hill may face,” if the league deems he violated the Personal Conduct Policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3558-d93a-abbb-7d5a06a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RT Morgan Moses (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3566-dbe3-a9bb-357720260000</link>
      <description>The last thing Drake Maye needed was to lose one of the bookends to his offensive line. Moses was brought in as a free agent to help improve one of the league’s worst lines in 2024. Though the veteran tackle is a few years past his prime, he was still set to be a stabilizing force for the unit. Losing Moses would be a tough blow for a New England offense that already came out flat-footed in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3566-dbe3-a9bb-357720260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
