<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 02:30:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 10-of-11 targets for 115 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 11 loss against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f84-d45b-affe-df96d4c90000</link>
      <description>McBride showed perhaps the most fight of any Cardinals player in a blowout loss to the 49ers. The 25-year-old drew an unnecessary roughness penalty in the first half, following it up with a taunting penalty on the next play and playing aggressively throughout the game. He scored a garbage time touchdown in the second half and was Jacoby Brissett’s main target. However, with a negative game script and passes needing to go downfield more frequently, Michael Wilson out-targeted McBride on the day. Still, McBride is seeing elite volume with Brissett at quarterback and will be a fantasy TE1 for Week 12 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f84-d45b-affe-df96d4c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 10-of-11 targets for 77 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 11 loss against the Rams, adding two rushes for one yard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f85-d713-ad9e-efd5d6170000</link>
      <description>Barner headed into Week 11 had never had more than seven targets or seven receptions in a game. His profile was immaculate against the Rams: Barner ran a route on 40 of the Seahawks’ 49 drop backs and was second on the team in targets, drawing a target on 27.5 percent of his routes, a (very) strong rate for a tight end. He showed no ill effects from the calf injury he dealt with last week. Elijah Arroyo, meanwhile, ran 16 routes and caught one of his three targets. If Barner has seized the TE1 role in the Seattle offense, he could be an intriguing addition to fantasy rosters in Week 12 and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f85-d713-ad9e-efd5d6170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 3-of-7 targets for 21 yards in the Browns’ Week 11 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f81-d713-ad9e-efd56d9c0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy entered the game with a 43.8 percent season-long catch rate and somehow managed to lower it tick with a 42.9 percent catch rate against the Ravens. He showed up late with a 10-yard gain on 3rd-and-10 to keep the Browns’ final, futile drive alive, but it was not enough to salvage his dreary outing. Jeudy remains a zero-floor FLEX in Week 12 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f81-d713-ad9e-efd56d9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dortch caught all six of his targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 11 loss against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f89-d673-a39e-af999c060000</link>
      <description>If the Cardinals want to have successful plays with Dortch, they need to reduce the offensive penalties that happen when using him. Twice the Cardinals ran a direct snap play to him and twice the play was called back for a penalty. He hit paydirt with a garbage time touchdown in the fourth quarter. Dortch is primarily used in motion and in space; his strength is creating yards after the catch. If Marvin Harrison Jr. and Emari Demercado remain out in Week 12, expect Dortch to be on the fantasy WR4/5 bordeline. Otherwise, he should be off fantasy radars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f89-d673-a39e-af999c060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Drake London “is not believed to have suffered a major knee injury” in Week 11’s loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f74-d1e7-a1fa-dffe136a0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that London “could miss some time,” but we’ll learn more about that on Monday after the star receiver undergoes further tests. The Falcons could be without their top receiver and quarterback if London and Penix (knee) can’t suit up for Week 12 against the Saints, which could set the stage for both Bijan Robinson and Tyler Allgeier to see significant work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f74-d1e7-a1fa-dffe136a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 4-of-5 targets for 33 yards in Denver’s Week 11 win over the Chiefs</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f71-d45b-affe-dff70f460000</link>
      <description>Engram only played 25 snaps to Adam Trautman’s 41. At this point it has to be said that Engram simply is only going to find TE1 usage if the Broncos are actually forced into a passing script. No team has done that since the Giants in Week 7, and even then he only returned 5/42 on eight targets. The real joker were the offseason blurbs we wrote about the joker along the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f71-d45b-affe-dff70f460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 3-of-7 targets for 23 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 11 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f8c-d713-ad9e-efdc38920000</link>
      <description>Kupp’s long-awaited revenge game against his former mates didn’t lead to much, as Jaxon Smith-Njigba continued dominating looks (12 targets) in the Seattle passing attack and AJ Barner came out of nowhere to see 11 targets against LA. It’s possible Kupp was slowed by the hamstring and wrist injuries that kept him sidelined for parts of practice last week. Kupp, who doesn’t have more than three catches in a game since Week 5, is little more than a flex option in deep fantasy formats going forward. He gets the Bucs in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f8c-d713-ad9e-efdc38920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 5-of-6 targets for 82 yards in Denver’s Week 11 win over the Chiefs</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df9608900000</link>
      <description>Career highs in catches, targets, and yards are following Bryant’s somewhat expanded role since Week 5. He’s played at least 30 snaps in every game since then, and the Chiefs let him get free for a 48-yarder that momentarily landed Bryant in concussion protocol before he returned later in the game. Heading into the bye, we don’t think Bryant is necessarily a good bet to explode on to the scene in the fantasy playoffs, but he’s building a case that it’s in the range of outcomes. He’s banished Marvin Mims (15 snaps in return from a concussion) to an ancillary gadget role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df9608900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 1-of-8 targets for one yard and one touchdown in the Rams’ Week 11 win against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df96ee380000</link>
      <description>Adams gritted it out after suffering an oblique injury in Week 10 against the 49ers and tied for the team lead with eight targets. His lone catch came on a first half one-yard touchdown. It was his tenth touchdown grab of the season, working as the Rams’ primary weapon inside the five yard line. Adams also had a brutal over-the-middle drop on a perfectly thrown ball from Matthew Stafford in the second half. Adams’ touchdown-based upside makes him a weekly top-12 fantasy option. He’ll have plenty of fantasy appeal in Week 12 against a fading Tampa defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df96ee380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum had eight carries for ten yards in the Rams’ Week 11 win against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f96-d713-ad9e-efd689060000</link>
      <description>Kyren Williams once again led the Rams backfield with 12 rushes for 91 yards and a touchdown. Williams also ran far more routes than Corum, who was targeted once on three routes against Seattle. Corum coming into this game had seen 38 rushing attempts over the past three games. Corum isn’t a viable fantasy option unless Williams misses time down the stretch. He should be rostered in most fantasy leagues though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f96-d713-ad9e-efd689060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
