<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts K Spencer Shrader suffered a right leg injury in Indianapolis’ Week 5 game against the Raiders and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a0-d95b-addb-fde6b31d0000</link>
      <description>Officially, Shrader has been ruled out with a knee issue after a defender crashed into his kicking leg following an extra point, but it also looked like it could be a severe leg or ankle issue. Either way, the Colts won’t have a kicker for the second half, and will be on the market for a replacement this week. Shrader competed with Matt Gay in training camp, but Gay is now the kicker in Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a0-d95b-addb-fde6b31d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerome Ford rushed five times for 18 yards in the Browns’ Week 5 loss to the Vikings, adding two catches for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a4-deb6-a7fd-f7ff34770000</link>
      <description>Ford hasn’t seen more than seven touches in a game since Week 3. Quinshon Judkins has fully taken over the Browns’ backfield, leaving some work on passing downs for Ford. Needless to say, Ford is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a4-deb6-a7fd-f7ff34770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (knee/elbow) is active for Week 5 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a3-deb6-a7fd-f7ffa0730000</link>
      <description>Also active is RB Tyjae Spears (ankle), who was just activated off injured reserve. Ridley came in with a questionable tag due to knee and elbow injuries that limited him in Week 4. Still dealing with the injuries, we may see more of Elic Ayomanor as the No. 1 wideout this week. Spears will play his first game of the season, looking to inject burst into the Titans backfield. Both Spears and Ridley are FLEX options this week. Inactive for the Titans are RT JC Latham, WR Bryce Oliver, OT John Ojukwu, OL Blake Hance, CB Samuel Womack, WR James Proche, and OL Brant Banks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a3-deb6-a7fd-f7ffa0730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs declared WR Mike Evans, RB Bucky Irving, CB Jamel Dean, CB Benjamin Morrison, and S Christian Izien inactive for Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a8-deb6-a7fd-f7ff27e80000</link>
      <description>No surprises here. All five of these players are injured, and it sounds like the Bucs will be without Evans and Irving next week as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a8-deb6-a7fd-f7ff27e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LB Demarcus Lawrence, S Julian Love, CB Devon Witherspoon, LB Jared Ivey, OL Josh Jones, WR Cody White, and TE Nick Kallerup inactive for Week 5 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5aa-d95b-addb-fdee738e0000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as all of Lawrence, Love, and Witherspoon were ruled out earlier in the week. The Bucs will also be without Mike Evans and Bucky Irving, but these are some big losses for the Seattle defense</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5aa-d95b-addb-fdee738e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 2-of-5 targets for 15 yards in the Browns’ Week 5 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a9-deb6-a7fd-f7ffb31a0000</link>
      <description>As expected, Dillon Gabriel replacing Joe Flacco sent Jeudy’s fantasy output from disappointing to completely unusable. Jeudy caught nine passes for 117 yards in the first two games of the year. He has six grabs for 80 yards in his three subsequent games. Jeudy dropped a low pass from Gabriel on a third down that would’ve moved the chains with 17 yards. There’s no reason to expect things to turn around for Jeudy in Week 6 versus the Steelers, relegating him to the WR5 ranks going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a9-deb6-a7fd-f7ffb31a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals declared CB Max Melton, LB Xavier Thomas, DL Darius Robinson, OL Evan Brown, OL Demontrey Jacobs, OL Josh Fryar, WR Xavier Weaver inactive for Week 5 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a9-d95b-addb-fdef679c0000</link>
      <description>Melton will miss Week 5 with a hamstring injury, though Will Johnson (groin) will return to the secondary. Darius Robinson (pectoral) and Evan Brown (hamstring) are also out due to injury. DT Bilal Nichols (neck) and OL Will Hernandez (ACL) are both active for the first time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5a9-d95b-addb-fdef679c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Bond caught 2-of-7 targets for 29 yards in the Browns’ Week 5 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5b2-d6e9-af9d-bfb2f10d0000</link>
      <description>Bond’s role continued to grow with Cedric Tillman on injured reserve. The increase in opportunities didn’t do anything for his fantasy output. He and rookie quarterback Dillon Gabriel failed to get on the same page at almost any point in this game, as evidenced by Bond’s 29 percent catch rate. Bond has already flashed big-play potential and now his role is on the rise, but it’s hard to expect Gabriel’s check-down-heavy style to mesh well with Bond’s speedster skill set. Fantasy managers should look elsewhere for a FLEX play in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5b2-d6e9-af9d-bfb2f10d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall returned to the field in Week 5’s game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b597-d6e9-af9d-bf9736330000</link>
      <description>We never received an official word on Hall’s injury following his second quarter fumble. The Jets’ RB1 was spotted on the sideline before the end of the first half but took the first backfield touch for the Jets to open the second half. Whatever injury he was dealing with appears to have been minor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b597-d6e9-af9d-bf9736330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
