<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports several executives believe “the Eagles could look to move” A.J. Brown in the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ddf-d005-a9bf-fdffd2110000</link>
      <description>As Fowler notes, the Eagles would eat a $20 million cap hit if he is traded before June 1st. They would gain $7 million in cap space if he were moved after that date. Brown has made his discontent with the Philly offense public on many occasions this year and in previous seasons. His play has also dropped in 2025. He played 13 games in 2024 and just hit 13 this season. Brown had over 200 more yards on just three extra catches at this point last year. Whether or not a trade happens, you better believe it will be one of the biggest talking points of the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ddf-d005-a9bf-fdffd2110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll said there is a “good chance” that QB Geno Smith (shoulder/back) starts in Week 16 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2de7-d8cf-affb-bdef3b920000</link>
      <description>Smith missed the Raiders’ Week 15 game against the Eagles, in which Las Vegas’ offense totaled 75 yards. Hopefully, Smith is feeling ready to play. He entered Week 15 with a foot injury, suffered abrasions on his throwing hand’s ring and pinky fingers, plus injured his throwing shoulder and back. The Texans’ elite pass rush will be a problem for him, if he is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2de7-d8cf-affb-bdef3b920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2df2-d1bc-a3fb-adf680b10000</link>
      <description>Rome Odunze also remained out of practice on Wednesday. Odunze was always likely to miss Week 16 after being a late scratch on Sunday. Burden, on the other hand, could’ve had a more optimistic outlook if he returned to practice today. Instead, he is now likely to join Odunze on the bench this week. D.J. Moore and Olamide Zaccheaus will serve as the team’s top wideouts this week. Moore will sit on the WR2/3 border while Zaccheaus is set for a WR4 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2df2-d1bc-a3fb-adf680b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dfc-d005-a9bf-fdfcdcc50000</link>
      <description>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said “all options are on the table” when talking about possibly shutting Odunze down earlier in the week. While we do expect to see him again at some point this year, that won’t happen in Week 16. With Luther Burden also banged up, D.J. Moore will run as the team’s top wideout versus the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dfc-d005-a9bf-fdfcdcc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e00-d005-a9bf-fe347c130000</link>
      <description>Swift was not on the injury report yesterday. The veteran runner has been dealing with the groin issue for a while. He appeared to be over it in recent weeks, but a mid-week addition now puts him at risk of missing Saturday’s game. Kyle Monangai would be in line for a massive workload and an RB1 ranking if Swift cannot suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e00-d005-a9bf-fe347c130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Kmet (ankle/knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e04-d77b-adfb-ee8777c60000</link>
      <description>Kmet was limited yesterday as well. We fully expected him to suit up for Saturday’s game versus the Packers. With Rome Odunze and Luther Burden likely to miss Week 16, expect a heavy dose of 12-personnel from Chicago’s offense. That will keep Kmet on the edge of the TE2 ranks this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e04-d77b-adfb-ee8777c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow said he “can’t see” a scenario in which he leaves the Bengals in 2026, but he has thought about playing elsewhere in his career.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dfc-d77b-adfb-efffdea20000</link>
      <description>Reporters questioned Burrow about his future with the team. He offered multiple answers of varying length. While addressing a question about lessons learned by watching Peyton Manning and Tom Brady switch teams, Burrow compared those situations to the Packers trading away Micah Parsons earlier this year, saying, “crazy things happen.” As things currently stand, we expect Burrow to remain a Bengal next season. If the organization continues to struggle, Burrow’s displeasure will ostensibly grow. It’s anyone’s guess as to how things go in that scenario, though he is under contract through 2029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dfc-d77b-adfb-efffdea20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e0d-d77b-adfb-ee8f47850000</link>
      <description>Johnston was a late addition to the injury report last week. He didn’t appear on the report until Friday, when the team listed him as questionable after a limited practice. A DNP today puts him on the wrong side of questionable for Week 16. Keenan Allen and Ladd McConkey will handle the bulk of the receiving work in his absence. Tight end Oronde Gadsden should also see a continued uptick in targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e0d-d77b-adfb-ee8f47850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (chest/shoulder) said he “should be good” to play in Week 16 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e17-d77b-adfb-ee971ccb0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Watson will play at less than 100.0 percent health. The 26-year-old wide receiver acknowledged that the Packers are “at the point in the season where you [have to] fight through some stuff.” Watson could aggravate the new injury by falling hard in-game, but he should be available for WR3 and offers his typical, big-play-based ceiling as the Packers (9-4-1) challenge the Bears (10-4) for control of the NFC North. Watson was promisingly limited at Wednesday’s practice after resting on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e17-d77b-adfb-ee971ccb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (personal) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e17-d005-a9bf-fe37dc2d0000</link>
      <description>Reed is a mid-week addition to the practice report, though not for an injury-related reason. Players tend to play after missing practice for personal reasons, so we aren’t panicking just yet. Assuming he gets back on the field tomorrow, Reed will be good to go as a low-end WR3. If he misses the final session of the week, there will be some risk of him not suiting up versus the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e17-d005-a9bf-fe37dc2d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
