<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OLB Khalil Mack (elbow) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ed-da18-a39b-fbffc6090000</link>
      <description>Mack was limited all week. If he is active, it would be unsurprising to see him used as a situational pass rusher. The team could keep him sidelined for one more week, just to be safe, though. Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) is listed as doubtful to play after practicing in a limited capacity twice, and RT Trey Pipkins III (knee) has been ruled out. He did not practice this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ed-da18-a39b-fbffc6090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said the 49ers will activate George Kittle (hamstring) from injured reserve before Week 7’s game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3f9-d99b-a1dd-fbfd497e0000</link>
      <description>Mac Jones does get a small reinforcement in Week 7 with Kittle over the middle. This move effectively ends Jake Tonges’ fantasy value and pushes Kendrick Bourne into a more of a supporting role. Kittle should be fired up as a high-end TE1 in all fantasy leagues immediately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3f9-d99b-a1dd-fbfd497e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out Brock Purdy (toe) for Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3fa-df81-ab9b-ffff1f0a0000</link>
      <description>Purdy was limited on Wednesday and Thursday. His Friday participation level is currently unknown. Purdy re-injured his toe in Week 4 and the 49ers (4-2) have playoff plans this season. The fact that they are allowing Purdy to get fully healthy before letting him return this time around makes sense. Mac Jones (knee/oblique) will start once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3fa-df81-ab9b-ffff1f0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee/oblique) was removed from the injury report and will start in Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3dd-d99b-a1dd-fbddc4d70000</link>
      <description>Jones was limited on Wednesday before being upgraded to full on Thursday. The 49ers’ fill-in starter has thrown for at least 279 passing yards in four games this season while twice totaling multiple passing touchdowns. He cleared 340-plus passing yards in each of the last two weeks. Jones is a borderline QB1/2, helming head coach Kyle Shanahan’s efficiently schemed offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3dd-d99b-a1dd-fbddc4d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3fc-da18-a39b-fbff82ce0000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know if Pearsall returned to practice on Friday, but we suspect he remains sidelined. The 49ers will be without their talented boundary wide receiver for the third straight week. Pearsall sprained his PCL in Week 4, but was looking like a weekly WR2 before that. Hopefully, he can return for the 49ers’ away game against the Texans in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3fc-da18-a39b-fbff82ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs/shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 7 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f409-d99b-a1dd-fe0df3b40000</link>
      <description>Jennings is very difficult to trust after last week’s meltdown. He was limited twice to begin the week, and we do not yet know his Friday participation level. At this point, the big-bodied wide receiver can only be viewed as a boom-bust WR4/FLEX option. If and when he resumes practicing in full consistently, we will be able to upgrade him to WR3 status. 49ers rookie WR Jordan Watkins (calf) is also expected to play this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f409-d99b-a1dd-fe0df3b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is doubtful to play in Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f410-d99b-a1dd-fe1c7ad60000</link>
      <description>Bowers returned to practice on Friday, practicing in a limited capacity. All signs point toward Bowers sitting out in Week 7, though with head coach Pete Carroll, anything is possible. If Bowers is active, he has decent odds of finishing as a mid-to-low TE1, though he would, of course, be at risk of re-injury and is unlikely to produce a ceiling game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f410-d99b-a1dd-fe1c7ad60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f409-da18-a39b-fe1b6aea0000</link>
      <description>Meyers practiced just once this week, participating in a limited capacity on Friday. He should be truly questionable to suit up this week, which means fantasy managers must closely monitor reports on Saturday and Sunday, if they plan to start him. He has a tough matchup if he is active, though his target volume could help him deliver FLEX results with TE Brock Bowers (knee) doubtful to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f409-da18-a39b-fe1b6aea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said he feels “good” about WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) playing in Week 7 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f419-df81-ab9b-fedfa2ee0000</link>
      <description>Frankly, this is a little surprising. Mooney began the week with two limited practices before sitting out on Friday. Perhaps it was a scheduled day off as Mooney attempts to return from a hamstring strain suffered in Week 4. Despite Morris’ good vibes, the team lists Mooney as questionable to play on the official injury report. If he is active, he can be treated as a boom-bust FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f419-df81-ab9b-fedfa2ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (illness/calf) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f413-d99b-a1dd-fe1f6e6b0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was listed with an illness on Wednesday and Thursday, before having the calf designation added sometime late on Friday. For what it is worth, he did manage to practice in full today, so this could be a non-issue. Fantasy managers should closely monitor news on the matter this weekend, though. Packers RBs Emanuel Wilson and Chris Brooks are next in line if Jacobs cannot play. Wilson has out-touched Brooks 22-7 this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f413-d99b-a1dd-fe1f6e6b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
