<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Parker Washington (hip) inactive for Jacksonville’s Week 14 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d8cf-affb-fdab5d970000</link>
      <description>As expected based on earlier reporting, Washington will be scratched. He’s droppable if you have a late move you need to get in ahead of Sunday kickoff. Also inactive for the Jaguars are: S Andrew Wingard (concussion), Yasir Abdullah, OL Walker Little (concussion), TE Johnny Mundt, DL Emmanuel Ogbah and DL Austin Johnson. DL Travon Walker (knee), S Eric Murray (neck) and Arik Armstead (hand) are playing despite questionable tags in a huge game for the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d8cf-affb-fdab5d970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is active for Week 14 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bda9dc0000</link>
      <description>Both Darrisaw and LG Donovan Jackson are active after entering the weekend with questionable tags. In addition to both linemen being active, the Vikings will also have J.J. McCarthy back under center against a 3-9 Commanders team that will have Jayden Daniels back under center. The Vikings did declare QB John Wolford, S Theo Jackson, DL Levi Drake Rodriguez, OG Joe Huber, OT Walter Rouse, TE Ben Yurosek, and DL Elijah Williams inactive for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bda9dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Adam Thielen is active for Week 14 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9aa-d77b-adfa-fbaba8b10000</link>
      <description>That was quick. Five days after signing the former Vikings wideout, the Steelers will have him active in the biggest game of the season. It would be a surprise if Thielen was used as anything more than a rotational slot receiver for now. He appears to have surpassed Roman Wilson on the Pittsburgh depth chart. Steelers declared WR Roman Wilson, DT Derrick Harmon, SS Kyle Dugger, OT Calvin Anderson, DT Brodric Martin, WR Ke’Shawn Williams, and QB Will Howard inactive for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9aa-d77b-adfa-fbaba8b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declared WR Jamari Thrash, OG Wyatt Teller, RB Raheim Sanders, TE Braeden Bates, OT Jack Conklin and DT Adin Huntington.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-d005-a9bf-f9bf26290000</link>
      <description>It’s a healthy scratch for second-year fifth-rounder Thrash, who has not played since Week 10. About to turn 25 years old, Thrash is looking like someone who can be cut loose from the end of deep dynasty league benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-d005-a9bf-f9bf26290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets declared QB Justin Fields, WR Tyler Johnson, TE Jelani Woods, DL Mazi Smith, EDGE Braiden McGregor, DB Ja’Sir Taylor, and S Tony Adams inactive for Week 14 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a6-d005-a9bf-f9b604b80000</link>
      <description>The Jets don’t have too many significant inactives for Week 14 against the Dolphins. The biggest is Justin Fields, who was ruled out due to a knee issue this week. Brady Cook was signed from the practice squad to be Tyrod Taylor’s backup. Tony Adams will also be out due to a groin injury, leaving the Jets defense reaching for depth against the Dolphins passing game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a6-d005-a9bf-f9b604b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce Jr. (back) is active for Week 14 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bdd93d0000</link>
      <description>Right guard Chris Lindstrom is also active. Pearce Jr. was a surprise addition to the injury report on Friday because of a back issue. He was listed as questionable but is good to go. Inactive for the Falcons are WR Drake London, CB Cobee Bryant, RB Nathan Carter, DL Brandon Dorlus, OL Michael Jerrell, and WR Casey Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9a9-d005-a9bf-f9bdd93d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared CB Sauce Gardner (calf), RB DJ Giddens, DE Tyquan Lewis (ankle), S Reuben Lowery III, TE Will Mallory, S George Odum and OT Luke Tenuta inactive for Indianapolis’ Week 14 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-da9b-a9bf-ffafbd4f0000</link>
      <description>Gardner and Lewis were ruled out on Friday. Everyone else is a healthy scratch. Giddens has fallen behind a now-healthy Tyler Goodson in the battle to be the caddy that Jonathan Taylor doesn’t actually have.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ab-da9b-a9bf-ffafbd4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewers, WR Tahj Washington, OT Kendall Lamm, DT Matthew Butler, LB Andre Carter II, and CB A.J. Green III inactive for Week 14 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d77b-adfa-fbaf61a60000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have a set of healthy inactives for Week 14. Quinn Ewers will serve as the team’s emergency third quarterback with Zach Wilson (illness) officially active against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d77b-adfa-fbaf61a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared CB Jalyn Armour-Davis (Achilles), S Jerrick Reed II, G Drew Moss, C Lloyd Cushenberry III (foot) and DT Shy Tuttle (concussion) inactive for Tennessee’s Week 14 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9af-d8cf-affb-fdaf482a0000</link>
      <description>Tuttle was the only one of the three injured players on the questionable line, and he’s inactive despite practicing in full all week. Moss and Reed are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9af-d8cf-affb-fdaf482a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (ankle) is active for Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d8cf-affb-fdaf9c670000</link>
      <description>Jackson returned to practice Friday after being downgraded with his lingering ankle issue on Thursday. He hasn’t been himself for more than a month now as the Ravens offense stagnates in ways we haven’t seen since Jackson became the team’s starting quarterback. They’ll look to get back on track against a Steelers defense sporting one of the NFL’s most porous rush defenses. Ravens declared WR Devontez Walker, QB Cooper Rush, DT Aeneas Peebles, G Ben Cleveland, and T Joseph Noteboom inactive for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f9ad-d8cf-affb-fdaf9c670000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
