<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals elevated WR Jalen Brooks from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5fe-d77b-adfa-ffff2d9e0000</link>
      <description>Brooks is one of two wideouts who were elevated from the practice squad for Week 14 against the Rams. The 2023 seventh-round pick is unlikely to much of an impact, even in a room that is not exactly crowded with quality wideouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f5fe-d77b-adfa-ffff2d9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived WR Malik Heath</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f609-d8cf-affb-fe2b3c420000</link>
      <description>With Jayden Reed (hamstring) activated off injured reserve, the Packers clear the needed room with the waiving of Heath. The 25-year-old will likely revert to the practice squad if he goes unclaimed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f609-d8cf-affb-fe2b3c420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons sign WR Deven Thompkins from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f617-d8cf-affb-fe3fd8160000</link>
      <description>Thompkins, 25, has been elevated from the practice squad twice. He likely will contribute on special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f617-d8cf-affb-fe3fd8160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Steelers “are not going to fire Mike Tomlin.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8f2-d8cf-affb-fcfa52940000</link>
      <description>At 6-6 with a spiraling offense and a defense that has failed to live up to the hype, the Steelers are seemingly headed for, at best, another short-lived playoff run. They still need to make the postseason, likely by winning the AFC North, to even see another Wild Card Round loss. Pittsburgh fans have yet to experience a losing season under Tomlin. On the other hand, they haven’t seen a playoff win since 2017. His defense-first approach worked wonders when the offense took care of itself. That hasn’t been the case since Ben Roethlisberger retired, and it might be time for the team to try something new. Schefter notes that Tomlin is under contract through 20226 and his contract has a team option for 2027. The Steelers need to decide on that option by March 1. Declining the option could mark the beginning of the end for one of the most successful coaches in NFL history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8f2-d8cf-affb-fcfa52940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Browns DT Mason Graham (ribs) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8fa-da9b-a9bf-feffe3be0000</link>
      <description>Graham was listed as questionable after being added to the injury report in the middle of the week. He appears to be good to go now. Graham has five TFLs and .5 sacks this year. The rookie will look to get on board with his first solo sack of the year against fellow top-five pick Cam Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8fa-da9b-a9bf-feffe3be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni “has been more involved in the offensive preparations this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8fd-d77b-adfa-faff393c0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are currently 19th in points per game and 14th in EPA per play. They ranked seventh and sixth in those metrics last year. There has been significant turnover along their offensive line, in part because of injuries, but not enough to warrant this drastic a falloff. The biggest change Philly was forced to make over the past offseason was at offensive coordinator. Kevin Patullo took over the job after Kellen Moore departed for the head coaching gig in Atlanta. Patullo has been unable to get Saquon Barkley going after he set records in 2024. The passing game has also struggled at times and the Eagles are now on a two-game losing streak. Sirianni said after last week’s loss to Chicago that Patullo will retain play-calling duties this week. His increased involvement in the offense, however, is undoubtedly a sign that Patullo is on the hot seat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f8fd-d77b-adfa-faff393c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f903-d77b-adfa-fb83ff2c0000</link>
      <description>Reed was activated from injured reserve over the weekend. The team then listed him as questionable, largely as a procedural measure. Reed will be active today, though we fully expect his role to be limited in his first game since Week 2. The Packers have been looking for a No. 1 receiver all year. Reed has a clear path to that role in the long run, making him a great stash for the fantasy football playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f903-d77b-adfa-fb83ff2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Chris Olave (back) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90a-d005-a9bf-f93e87590000</link>
      <description>Olave dealt with back spasms in practice two weeks ago. He played through them versus the Dolphins and caught four passes for 47 yards and a score. It wasn’t his best showing of the year, but he looked fine. He missed Wednesday’s practice this week but was on the field for the following two sessions before being listed a questionable. Per usual, Olave is on track for volume-based WR2 numbers versus the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90a-d005-a9bf-f93e87590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Dalton Kincaid (knee/hamstring) “plans to try to play” in Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90e-d8cf-affb-fd2edb2e0000</link>
      <description>When a player is ready to go, Schefter and most other reporters will say they are “expected to play.” That Schefter didn’t use those words means Kincaid still has some hurdles to clear before getting the green light. The team will likely test out his hamstring and knee during warmups before making a final call. Assuming all goes well, Kincaid will return for a game teeming without shootout potential. Even in his first game since Week 10, Kincaid will push for a TE1 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f90e-d8cf-affb-fd2edb2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mike Evans is “pushing to play as soon as Thursday night vs. the Falcons.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f915-d005-a9bf-f93548bd0000</link>
      <description>Evans is currently on injured reserve while recovering from the broken clavicle he suffered in Week 7. The team opened his practice window earlier this week, allowing him to return to the practice field as he prepares to play. Evans has been ruled out for Week 14 already, but it sounds like Week 15 is on the table. If not, fantasy managers can assume he will be back in the lineup for Week 16 versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f915-d005-a9bf-f93548bd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
