<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed CB Kaiir Elam, formerly of the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c147-db57-afda-d7772fe20000</link>
      <description>Elam is a former first-round pick (23rd overall) of the Bills in the 2022 NFL Draft. He has played in 39 career NFL games, with 19 starts while playing with the Bills and the Cowboys. Elam had 19 solo tackles and one defended pass in seven games for Dallas this season. He’s been credited with 110 tackles and two interceptions in his career. Elam will join a Titans defense allowing the league’s eighth lowest drop back success rate in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c147-db57-afda-d7772fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco does not have an injury designation for Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c14b-d90e-a9da-df4f56b00000</link>
      <description>Pacheco will make his return to the Kansas City lineup after missing a few weeks with a knee injury. He’ll likely split the backfield workload with Kareem Hunt against the Cowboys in the Chiefs’ Thanksgiving Day game in Dallas. Hunt could be a flex option since he remains the team’s preferred red zone back. Pacheco should remain benched in normal sized fantasy leagues this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c14b-d90e-a9da-df4f56b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 13 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c153-d6c4-abfb-d75390680000</link>
      <description>Dart has missed the past two weeks after suffering a concussion in Week 10. The rookie quarterback has been pulled from a game for a concussion check several times this year, so it made sense to sit Dart down for multiple weeks before throwing him back into the lineup. A full practice on Wednesday puts him on track to clear the league’s concussion protocol before Sunday’s game versus the Pats. Dart will return to the QB1/2 border for his first game back in action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c153-d6c4-abfb-d75390680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots placed LT Will Campbell (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c15c-d90e-a9da-df5f912d0000</link>
      <description>As expected, Campbell will miss at least four games. Campebll suffered a torn MCL in Week 12 and may be out until the playoffs, if not longer. Vederian Lowe took Campbell’s spot in the lineup last week. Head coach Mike Vrabel was noncommittal earlier in the week when asked about Campbell’s replacement. Rookie Marcus Bryant could also get a shot at the job. Either way, expect Drake Maye to be pressured far more often without his starting left tackle on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c15c-d90e-a9da-df5f912d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith (shoulder/chest) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c163-db57-afda-d773416b0000</link>
      <description>Smith could get in some light work later in the session and officially be listed as limited. For now, it looks like Smith will be a DNP for his second straight practice. His availability for Week 13 versus the Bears is up in the air, to say the least. A.J. Brown posted one of his best games of the year last week, racking up 110 yards and a score on eight receptions. He would be in line for an even larger workload if Smith is unable to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c163-db57-afda-d773416b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens (knee/calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c16a-db57-afda-d77a0aa00000</link>
      <description>KaVontae Turpin was also cleared to play. Pickens was held out of practice on Monday but returned for a limited session on Tuesday. He was full-go today before being removed from the injury report entirely. Pickens has worked himself into a weekly WR1 ranking and is even threatening to overtake CeeDee Lamb. Both he and Lamb are elite fantasy options for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c16a-db57-afda-d77a0aa00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c175-d82c-a79a-f3f571c40000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as Worthy played through the ankle issue last week and was practicing in full as of yesterday. Rashee Rice has taken over as the team’s No. 1 receiver since returning from his suspension and Travis Kelce is still a high-volume check-down option for Mahomes. That has left Worthy without much of a role over the past month. A shootout with the Cowboys could temporarily revive his fantasy outlook, but it’s hard to move him beyond a WR4 ranking for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c175-d82c-a79a-f3f571c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c177-d82c-a79a-f3f7b7130000</link>
      <description>Rice took some snaps off late in Week 12 to have his hamstring looked at, but he was on the field for the team’s final drive. He practiced in full twice this week, meaning the hamstring issue is not a concern. In a likely shootout with the Cowboys, Rice is a locked-in WR1 for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c177-d82c-a79a-f3f7b7130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curtis Samuel (elbow/neck) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17a-d90e-a9da-df7fc5d30000</link>
      <description>Samuel missed last week’s game with the pair of injuries. A DNP on Wednesday suggests he will be sidelined for at least one more contest. With Dalton Kincaid also on the wrong side of questionable to start the week, Khalil Shakir is set to dominate targets in Buffalo once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17a-d90e-a9da-df7fc5d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud (concussion) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17e-d82c-a79a-f3feab4f0000</link>
      <description>Stroud returned to practice last Tuesday but was downgraded to a DNP on Wednesday, the Texans’ final official practice before Thursday’s game. It seems like that was just maintenance for a player who had already been ruled out. Barring a setback, Stroud is on track to play in Week 13 against the Colts. Stroud will be a low-end QB2 in his first game since Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17e-d82c-a79a-f3feab4f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
