<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92c8-d673-a39e-b6d9b80c0000</link>
      <description>Jets HC Aaron Glenn confirmed the report shortly after Russini broke the news. The move to Taylor as the starter felt inevitable after Justin Fields again struggled through the air in Week 11’s loss to the Patriots. It’s a move that probably should have come much sooner, but Taylor is a seasoned vet who, despite his flaws, has proven to be the more capable starter in limited action this season. In three appearances, including one start, Taylor has thrown for 379-3-3 on 69 passes while completing 62.3 percent of his attempts. He’ll have his work cut out for him playing with a depleted receiving corps, but Taylor should provide a little more upside for a passing game in need of help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92c8-d673-a39e-b6d9b80c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs’ knee is “structurally sound” after Week 11’s injury against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ca-d713-ad9e-fede5ab90000</link>
      <description>It’s about the best outcome we could hope for. Testing on Jacobs’ knee revealed no structural damage, and the Packers’ RB1 is not expected to need surgery at this time. While it’s good news overall, Jacobs could still be looking at a short-term absence, although the team hasn’t jumped to rule him out just yet for Week 12 against the Vikings. His status will be one to monitor throughout the week, but if Jacobs is unable to go, backup Emanuel Wilson, who rushed for 11-40-1 against the Giants, would serve as the starter against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ca-d713-ad9e-fede5ab90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn has informed the team that Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92d0-d1e7-a1fa-dafae0430000</link>
      <description>Were it not for an injury to Tyrod Taylor earlier this season, this may have happened much sooner than Week 12. However, the injury to Taylor in Week 8 bought Fields some extra time, and the Jets won back-to-back games in Weeks 8 and 10, generating some hope that the team may be turning a corner. That hope, however, was quickly dashed in Week 11’s loss to the Patriots, when Fields, who struggled mightily in Week 10 despite the victory, threw for 116 yards and one touchdown while also losing a key fumble late in the game. Fields signed a two-year, $40 million contract with the Jets this offseason and carries a $22 million dead cap hit in 2026 if released. The Jets will likely take on that hit as they look to again rebuild their QB room in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92d0-d1e7-a1fa-dafae0430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans HC DeMeco Ryans said C.J. Stroud’s (concussion) status for Week 12 against the Bills is uncertain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92dd-d1e7-a1fa-daff07380000</link>
      <description>Something similar was reported on Sunday morning, but speaking on Monday, Ryans confirmed that Stroud may not return this week. The Texans’ QB1 remains in the league’s concussion protocol, but the Texans playing on Thursday night only adds to the complications. Stroud has missed two straight games due to his concussion, but the Texans have managed to go 2-0 in his absence with Davis Mills under center. Mills has thrown for 566 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in his two starts this season, but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a desperation play in 2QB/superflex leads if he draws the start. Ryans said S Jalen Pitre, who is also in the concussion protocol, is uncertain for Thursday night’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92dd-d1e7-a1fa-daff07380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons placed QB Michael Penix (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92e4-d1e7-a1fa-daee89bb0000</link>
      <description>According to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Penix aggravated a bone bruise and knee sprain he suffered earlier in the season, but also added, “there has been damage to the ACL, which could mean a full reconstruction.” There’s still some uncertainty regarding Penix’s ACL injury, but we expect a more definitive diagnosis once Penix has had a chance to seek a second opinion — which he is reportedly in the process of doing. Regardless, it sounds like this is shaping up to be a season-ender for Penix, who has thrown for 1,982-9-3 this season while completing 60.1 percent of his passes. For now, Penix is out for a minimum of four games, putting Kirk Cousins in the driver’s seat going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92e4-d1e7-a1fa-daee89bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Jamel Dean is day-to-day with a hip flexor injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ec-d1e7-a1fa-daee72fd0000</link>
      <description>Dean exited Sunday’s game against the Bills and will be evaluated later in the week, according to Bowles. This sounds like a minor injury to Dean, who has already notched a career-high three interceptions this season while also totaling six pass breakups and 28 tackles on the year. The Bucs will hope he’ll have enough time to get right ahead of a big Sunday night matchup against the Rams in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92ec-d1e7-a1fa-daee72fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said Dillon Gabriel remains in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92f8-d713-ad9e-fefc2a6d0000</link>
      <description>It’s not often a player clears concussion protocol less than 24 hours after entering it, so this news doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Stefanski said he will wait until Wednesday to discuss how the team is preparing for the Raiders in Week 12, but things could be shaping up for Shedeur Sanders to make his first career start if Gabriel is unable to clear protocol. We’ll have a better sense of where things are headed once the Browns release their first injury report on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-92f8-d713-ad9e-fefc2a6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports multiple teams have expressed interest in free agent DT Khalen Saunders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9302-d673-a39e-b7934d8f0000</link>
      <description>Saunders was released by the Jaguars last week and has reportedly heard calls from the Ravens, Colts, Jets, and Cardinals. The Jets went out and traded for Saunders this offseason, but the veteran lineman has appeared in only two games this year. Saunders started 10 of the 13 games he appeared in for the Saints last season, totaling 43 tackles, two sacks, and three pass breakups. He should have plenty to offer a contender in need of an added boost to its defensive front during the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9302-d673-a39e-b7934d8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said he does not have an update on Bryce Young’s ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9313-d45b-affe-d7977eaa0000</link>
      <description>As Panthers beat writer Joe Person notes, this is par for the course for Canales, who doesn’t offer injury updates during Monday’s presser. Young played through his injury in Sunday’s win over the Falcons, and churned out a career-high 448 yards in the victory. It was undoubtedly his best game as a pro, and gave the Panthers a much-needed win as they aim to keep pace with the Buccaneers in the NFC South. Given how he played on Sunday, it seems unlikely that this injury would sideline Young for Week 12’s game against the 49ers, but his status will be one to monitor throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9313-d45b-affe-d7977eaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed DT Khalen Saunders, formerly of the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-931e-d673-a39e-b79fce9c0000</link>
      <description>Saunders had interest from multiple teams, including the Ravens, Colts, and Cardinals. However, to avoid interrupting any plans of an early offseason, the veteran tackle has opted to sign with the Jets. Saunders, 29, has 32 games of starting experience under his belt and totaled 43 tackles, two sacks, and three pass breakups for the Saints last season. He should have a chance to make an immediate impact for the Jets over the final seven weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-931e-d673-a39e-b79fce9c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
