<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (calf) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d97-d35e-a1bf-4dd7ab800000</link>
      <description>Mitchell is dealing with a calf issue and got a limited designation after the Ravens’ walkthrough practice. The speedy 23-year-old is second in the Ravens’ running back rotations, but Derrick Henry will get even more carries should Mitchell miss time. However, fantasy managers can plan on Mitchell still playing in Week 17 against the Packers for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d97-d35e-a1bf-4dd7ab800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d99-d35e-a1bf-4ddbc08c0000</link>
      <description>Though he did not practice at all last week, Jacobs played through his knee injury in Week 16. He was inefficient and sidelined late with the injury still clearly hampering him. It is an encouraging sign that Jacobs is listed as limited Tuesday, though the practice report should be taken with a grain of salt as the Packers held a walkthrough and an ankle injury was added to his designation. Jacobs plays through injury as much as possible, so the limited designation indicates he is planning to play again in Week 17 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d99-d35e-a1bf-4ddbc08c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d9f-d56e-afff-efff81930000</link>
      <description>McDuffie is listed as DNP for the second straight day. He has been dealing with the knee issue since Week 14 and may not play the rest of this season with the Chiefs eliminated from playoff contention. Fellow CB Jaylen Watson (groin) was also DNP for the second straight day. Both are on the wrong side of questionable with a Christmas game against the Broncos on the horizon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d9f-d56e-afff-efff81930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Steelers WR DK Metcalf’s two-game suspension was upheld upon appeal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4dcb-dc7a-af9b-cfff362d0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf was suspended by the NFL for the final two games of the regular season after an altercation with a fan in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions. He appealed the ruling, having previously reported the fan to Seahawks team security prior to his trade to the Steelers. An appeals officer jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA upheld Metcalf’s suspension and he will now miss Weeks 17 and 18 against the Browns and Ravens. It is costly in two ways for Metcalf; he will lose $555K in salary and has $45 million guaranteed voided, while the Steelers will not have him for a stretch run in which a win clinches the AFC North for them. Roman Wilson is in line for increased opportunities with Metcalf out, though we do not recommend him for fantasy lineups in the fantasy championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4dcb-dc7a-af9b-cfff362d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Jordy Nelson, jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA, upheld Chargers LB Denzel Perryman’s two-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4e0c-d35e-a1bf-4fce08080000</link>
      <description>Perryman was suspended for repeated violations of the playing rules intended to protect the health and safety of players. The NFL dealt out his punishment given Perryman’s history of suspension due to rule safety violations, with a previous two-game suspension coming in 2023 for the same reason. The NFL has made it clear they will not tolerate repeated risky hits from players. Perryman will miss the final two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4e0c-d35e-a1bf-4fce08080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Willis (shoulder) said he believes he’ll be ready for Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-507a-dc7a-af9b-dfff65060000</link>
      <description>“I try to take it one day at a time, but I would assume that I’m going to be ready,” Willis said Tuesday. Willis sustained a shoulder injury late in the Packers’ Week 16 loss to the Bears. He was estimated to have a limited practice on Tuesday and would seem likely to suit up against Baltimore on Thursday. Jordan Love was also listed as a limited practice participant on Tuesday with a shoulder injury and a concussion he suffered in Week 16. If Love is sidelined, Willis becomes an interesting superflex play thanks to his rushing upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-507a-dc7a-af9b-dfff65060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Amon-Ra St. Brown (knee) is expected to play in Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-50ca-d968-a19b-58fb68a60000</link>
      <description>Lions head coach Dan Campbell described St. Brown’s injury as “a little irritation” that should not sideline him for Christmas Day against the Vikings. St. Brown, who plays through all manner of injuries — including a high ankle sprain a few weeks ago — should be a full go against Minnesota. He had nine catches for 97 yards on 13 targets the last time the Lions played the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-50ca-d968-a19b-58fb68a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio reports the NFL is still investigating the fan involved in Week 16’s DK Metcalf incident.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-50df-d35e-a1bf-55df66020000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said on Tuesday that the league “and the Lions will not take action against the fan involved in the altercation with Steelers WR DK Metcalf on Sunday in Detroit because ‘there was no violation of the fan code of conduct,’ per source.” Metcalf was seen throwing a punch at the fan, Ryan Kennedy, after the two exchanged words during the Steelers’ Week 16 game against the Lions. The league refuted the report from its employee, Rapoport. “The report about the fan and discipline was not accurate,” and NFL spokesperson told Pro Football Talk. “The matter remains under review and the league is following up with the club.” Metcalf alleged Kennedy used a racial slur and insulted his mother before the skirmish took place. Kennedy denies this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-50df-d35e-a1bf-55df66020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mercury News’ Jerry McDonald reports 49ers TE Jake Tonges will see an increase in playing time if George Kittle (ankle) is out in Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-510c-d968-a19b-59fd49f60000</link>
      <description>Tonges operated as the Niners’ primary pass-catching tight end earlier this season when Kittle was sidelined with an injury, and could find himself in that role again this week against the Bears if Kittle — who sustained a “low to mid” ankle sprain on Monday night — is sidelined. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said he’s confident Tonges can take on the role and be a productive part of the team’s red-hot passing offense. Tonges had 22 receptions over five games with Kittle out in the first half of the season. He would be a viable 14-team league option against the Bears if Kittle can’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-510c-d968-a19b-59fd49f60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
