<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 22:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans head coach Brian Callahan said he’s turning over offensive play-calling duties to QB coach Bo Hardegree.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7751-d93f-ad9d-7fd7a0250000</link>
      <description>The move comes after a miserable start to the 2025 season for Callahan’s offense, which ranks last in yards per play (3.2), second to last in first downs, and second to last in offensive success rate. Cam Ward has struggled mightily in a predictable and somewhat vanilla offensive scheme. Ward has been among the most inaccurate quarterbacks through three games. It’s unclear how the offense might shift under Hardegree, but it would hardly be a surprise if Callahan is fired in the next week weeks, barring a miraculous turnaround for the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7751-d93f-ad9d-7fd7a0250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Mike Evans (hamstring) is expected to miss 3-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7758-d6a5-adff-f7ddfe520000</link>
      <description>Evans reportedly has a “low grade” hamstring issue, the latest in a long string of hamstring woes for the 32-year-old wideout. Evans would seem unlikely to land on injured reserve if the team believes he can come back for Week 7. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler said the hamstring injury “is not considered as bad as last year’s” — which cost Evans three games — and that Evans “plans to work to get back as soon as possible, possibly beating the timeline.” With Evans sidelined, Emeka Egbuka should be an uptick in targets and air yards as the Bucs’ de facto WR1, and a top-12 weekly wideout. Sterling Shepard, who had four receptions for 80 yards last week against the Jets, would likely work as the team’s No. 2 wideout for the next few weeks. Shepard should be rostered in most 12-team leagues for the time being. Chris Godwin (ankle), meanwhile, could make his return to action while Evans is sidelined, further complicating Tampa’s target distribution and pass-catching pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7758-d6a5-adff-f7ddfe520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports QB Jaxson Dart will start in Week 4 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7769-d1b3-a5dd-7779c1730000</link>
      <description>Russell Wilson may have sealed his fate with a fourth quarter throwaway on fourth down on the red zone as the Giants tried to mount a comeback against the Chiefs. Wilson completed just 56 percent of his throws against KC for 160 scoreless yards and two picks. Dart instantly becomes fantasy viable in superflex formats and even some deeper one-QB leagues thanks to his rushing and aggressive play style. Dart completed 32 of 46 passes for 372 yards, three touchdowns, and no interceptions over three preseason affairs. His adjusted completion rate was 78 percent, according to Pro Football Focus. The rookie should provide a boost for Malik Nabers — who leads the NFL in air yards — and Wan’Dale Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7769-d1b3-a5dd-7779c1730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Terry McLaurin “is getting additional opinions” on his injured quad and could miss Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7772-d1b3-a5dd-7773232a0000</link>
      <description>One of the league’s healthiest teams in 2024, Washington is dealing with a string of injuries to important players, including Austin Ekeler (Achilles), Jayden Daniels (knee), and now McLaurin, who left Sunday’s win against the Raiders with a quad issue. That McLaurin, 30, is seeking additional opinions on the injury could mean that he’s in for a multi-week absence. If McLaurin is out for Week 4, Luke McCaffrey could have some deep league appeal after catching three passes for 56 yards and a touchdown against the Raiders. McCaffrey was targeted on a strong 30 percent of his routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7772-d1b3-a5dd-7773232a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor reports the Chiefs are “optimistic” that Xavier Worthy (shoulder) “will be able to play a limited role for the offense while wearing a small harness” in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-779e-d1b3-a5dd-77ff2d260000</link>
      <description>Does that sound like a role that elevates beyond decoy? Not to us. Even if Worthy is active for Week 4 after missing the last two weeks following a Week 1 dislocated shoulder, this indicates he could be eased back into the offense slowly. This line comes from a piece about Tyquan Thornton, who deservedly is getting major waiver wire love this week. We might rather start Thornton than Worthy this week even if both of them are active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-779e-d1b3-a5dd-77ff2d260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed K Younghoe Koo to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77bf-dfde-a1bd-7fbff36f0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like a vote of confidence for the health of incumbent Graham Gano (groin), who kicked through injury on Sunday night. Koo could be the Giants kicker this week against the Chargers in what some are calling “not exactly a smash spot for a kicker” in Jaxson Dart’s season debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77bf-dfde-a1bd-7fbff36f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released S C.J. Gardner-Johnson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77c2-d6a5-adff-f7c717d60000</link>
      <description>What was your favorite moment of the Gardner-Johnson era in Houston? He did play 96 percent of the snaps for the Texans in three weeks, so it’s a loss. NBC’s Aaron Wilson reports there was “friction behind the scenes” behind the release, with Gardner-Johnson “complaining about his role, wanting to blitz more, per league sources, and even communicating that he wanted to be traded.” M.J. Stewart will take over at safety for the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77c2-d6a5-adff-f7c717d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed LB Quincy Williams (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77d0-d1b3-a5dd-77f12b180000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least four weeks and NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said he’d be “down for a while.” The Jets signed Mark Robinson off New England’s practice squad to take his roster spot. Marcelino McCrary-Ball replaced Williams in the lineup if you’re looking for an IDP waiver pickup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77d0-d1b3-a5dd-77f12b180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired CB Jarvis Brownlee and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Titans for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7811-d6a5-adff-fed5a4960000</link>
      <description>Brownlee, who had started 16 games while being active for 18 games for the Titans in his rookie season and this year, was a surprise inactive in Week 3 and was spotted in a walking boot pre-game. It appears the Titans tired of how grabby he was being on the outside. The Jets will try to channel his outside coverage ability and take a cheap chance on a good tackler with mediocre PFF coverage grades (61 this year, 55.9 in 2024) on the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7811-d6a5-adff-fed5a4960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Shilo Sanders visited the 49ers on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7872-d93f-ad9d-7af7a3c00000</link>
      <description>Deion’s other son played for the Buccaneers in training camp and was waived well ahead of final cuts. This is the first time we’ve seen him on the league’s transaction wire since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7872-d93f-ad9d-7af7a3c00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
