<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:08:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts GM Chris Ballard said “any suggestion that” Michael Pittman isn’t going to remain a Colt is “a pure hypothetical in my mind.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91bb-d57c-a1dd-95bb5fa40000</link>
      <description>Ballard would almost certainly have to restructure Pittman’s contract to retain both Daniel Jones and Alec Pierce. Entering his age-29 season, there was some beat writer smoke around the Colts parting ways with Pittman — it does seem like Ballard would rather hang on to him than not. If the Colts run back last year’s receiver room, Pittman will likely be on the WR3 line in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91bb-d57c-a1dd-95bb5fa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs GM Brett Veach said he’d like to have CB Trent McDuffie “back for the long-term.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c0-d89c-a1be-bfdf82be0000</link>
      <description>McDuffie is entering the fifth-year option season on his rookie contract and the Chiefs could chop down his cap number for 2026 with an extension. Forced to play outside more over the past few years, McDuffie finally managed to be left off an All-Pro team in 2025. He managed a 75.6 PFF grade — as opposed to 82.0 and 84.8 the two seasons before that — in 688 snaps with the Chiefs while dealing with a knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c0-d89c-a1be-bfdf82be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports Kyler Murray and Cardinals GM Monti Ossenfort have not talked since the season ended.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c6-d629-a1bc-b1df461c0000</link>
      <description>Well, not much to talk about, is there? The Cardinals projected some “all options are on the table” stuff at Ossenfort’s presser ahead of questions, trying to pre-empt them. It seems more likely than not that the Cardinals will release Murray before his contract guarantees kick in. All that’s left is trying to bait a team in to trading for him before that happens. The fact that the two sides haven’t even talked says a lot about the odds of Arizona actually retaining Murray, making it appear that there is one less option on the theoretical table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91c6-d629-a1bc-b1df461c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said he thinks the 49ers are “on the right track” in contract talks with LT Trent Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91cd-d57c-a1dd-95cd10a30000</link>
      <description>It’s certainly a vibes shift from Adam Schefter’s report that the two sides were struggling to find a contractual solution. Williams’ contract is indeed very tricky, tricky enough that moving on from it doesn’t really free up significant space for the 49ers. We’d be surprised if the 49ers moved on from Williams despite Schefter’s report, but it certainly isn’t completely off the table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91cd-d57c-a1dd-95cd10a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said the team signed LS Jon Weeks to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e2-d629-a1bc-b1ff7b800000</link>
      <description>Weeks signed with the 49ers last offseason and was a pending free agent. The contract terms are not yet disclosed, but it is likely a short-term deal for the 40-ear old long snapper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e2-d629-a1bc-b1ff7b800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said “nothing will happen” with WR Brandon Aiyuk “until the new league year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e5-d042-afbc-fdf779f80000</link>
      <description>It is all but certain Aiyuk will not be a 49er for next season. The new league year will be coming up in March, making any kind of trade/release with the 27-year-old more doable. A release is more likely, but Lynch added, “who knows...maybe someone this week will have some interest.” Aiyuk will be a new addition to the receiver market as suitable teams like the Commanders and Steelers start making moves in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e5-d042-afbc-fdf779f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos general manager George Paton said CB Ja’Quan McMillian is “one of our core players.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91f9-d042-afbc-fdfb4fd20000</link>
      <description>McMillian is a pending restricted free agent come March. Paton added that a team could call the Broncos to make a run for him, but the team would like to keep him. The 25-year-old former UDFA most tallied four sacks and two interceptions in a key role for a Broncos defense that led the team to an AFC Championship berth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91f9-d042-afbc-fdfb4fd20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said the 49ers are hiring former Vikings general manager Kwesi Adofo-Mensah as a personnel executive.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91fd-d57c-a1dd-95fd97e70000</link>
      <description>Adofo-Mensah spent four seasons as the Vikings’ general manager, most notably helping build a Vikings team that went 14-3 in 2024 with Sam Darnold at quarterback. However, the team’s struggles with 2024 first-rounder J.J. McCarthy starting last season while Darnold won a Super Bowl in Seattle likely contributed to the end of his tenure in Minnesota. Adofo-Mensah spent 2013-2019 with the 49ers in the football research and development department. He now returns to the spot his football executive career began as a personnel executive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91fd-d57c-a1dd-95fd97e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers general manager Dan Morgan said, “we’ll explore” signing EDGE Bradley Chubb in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9204-d629-a1bc-b21d3a310000</link>
      <description>The possibility of signing Chubb was brought up at Morgan’s press conference at the NFL Scouting Combine; Morgan said the 29-year-old is still “still playing at a really good level” and indicated the Panthers are exploring the idea of signing him. Chubb tallied 8.5 sacks for the Dolphins last season after missing 2024 with a torn ACL. Miami released Chubb after the playoffs, making him eligible to sign at any point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9204-d629-a1bc-b21d3a310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said the team is “not anticipating” using the franchise tag on K Eddy Pineiro.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9215-d89c-a1be-bfdf80390000</link>
      <description>Pineiro had an efficient season for the 49ers, missing just one of his 29 regular season attempts. Lynch said, “we got a couple weeks before free agency to continue to work towards something.” Pineiro is a pending free agent and eligible for the franchise tag should the 49ers not reach a deal with the 30-year-old. Lynch indicated it is not likely the team will tag Pineiro and there is interest to reaching a new deal with the kicker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9215-d89c-a1be-bfdf80390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
