<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt had 13 rushes for 24 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding one catch for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933c-dca3-a9fb-bfbdb3fe0000</link>
      <description>Hunt easily led the KC backfield with 14 touches while Isiah Pacheco had seven carries and caught a short touchdown in the team’s blowout win. Hunt and Pacheco largely split route running duties against the Ravens, though rookie RB Brashad Smith mixed in with three receptions for 27 yards on four targets. Hunt, the team’s primary goal line back in the early season, is a low-ceiling weekly option in deeper leagues for as long as Smith doesn’t take on a larger role in the KC offense. Hunt has 36 rushes over the season’s first four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933c-dca3-a9fb-bfbdb3fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Miles Sanders (ankle) is questionable to return to Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933e-dca3-a9fb-bfbf298d0000</link>
      <description>Sanders was escorted to the locker room ahead of the half with an ankle injury and was deemed questionable to return after the break. Sideline reporter Melissa Stark said he is going to try to return to the game. Sanders managed eight yards on two carries and 17 yards on two receptions prior to departing. Backfield depth is an issue if Sanders can’t make it back on the field with only Javonte Williams and fullback Hunter Luepke active for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933e-dca3-a9fb-bfbf298d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said that making a change at quarterback is “not our focus” at this time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9342-deb6-a7fd-d3df96c50000</link>
      <description>Stefanski refused to blame Joe Flacco for today’s loss to the Lions, saying losses are “never going to be about one person” and that all involved, including himself, “have to be better.” The Browns face the Vikings’ top-tier defense in Week 5, which would make for a brutal first opponent for rookie QB Dillon Gabriel, who took three snaps in today’s game. They face the struggling Steelers’ defense in Week 6. A change after next week’s game seems likely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9342-deb6-a7fd-d3df96c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JuJu Smith-Schuster caught 4-of-6 targets for 36 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-936b-d95b-addb-fb6fe1ac0000</link>
      <description>Smith-Schuster logged a route on 37 of Patrick Mahomes’ 44 drop backs and caught on of Mahomes’ four touchdowns in the easy win over a beat-up Baltimore defense. Smith-Schuster caught his touchdown — the first of his 2025 season — between two defenders from four yards out. An every-down player in the pass-heavy KC offense, Smith-Schuster — with 14 catches through Week 4 — should be rostered in deep fantasy leagues. He gets the Jaguars in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-936b-d95b-addb-fb6fe1ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 3-of-5 targets for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9371-dca3-a9fb-bff904e80000</link>
      <description>Brown’s touchdown — his first of the 2025 season — came on a fourth and one in the red zone with the game out of reach for Baltimore. After a big opening night game against the Chargers, Brown has mostly been an afterthought in the Kansas City offense, though he has drawn a target on 24 percent of his pass routes, the highest rate on the team. Brown will be a passable WR4 option next week against the pass-funnel Jacksonville defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9371-dca3-a9fb-bff904e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely did not catch a pass in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-937d-dca3-a9fb-bffd22fc0000</link>
      <description>Returning from a foot injury that kept him sidelined for the season’s first three games, Likely ran 20 routes to Mark Andrews’ 27 routes and was not targeted.Look for Likely to work his way into the offense in the coming weeks. The potential loss of Lamar Jackson (hamstring) would be a blow to Likely and the rest of the Baltimore pass catchers, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-937d-dca3-a9fb-bffd22fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 7-of-8 targets for 30 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9385-dca3-a9fb-bf9d90300000</link>
      <description>Isaiah Likely was back from a foot injury but it was Andrews who dominated tight end work for the Ravens, running 27 routes and seeing a team-high eight targets while Likely was not targeted on 20 routes. Andrews has had an up and down start to the season, but now has 13 receptions over his past two games. He remains a full-time player in a high-powered offense, though the potential loss of Lamar Jackson to a hamstring injury could be a major blow to Andrews in Week 5 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9385-dca3-a9fb-bf9d90300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 1-of-2 targets for 24 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9389-deb6-a7fd-d3df07640000</link>
      <description>Bateman was invisible in this one, a week after going for 63 yards and a touchdown on five receptions against the Lions. Bateman now has three quiet games in the season’s first four weeks and profiles as a high-variance weekly option in a run-first offense. The potential loss of Lamar Jackson (hamstring) could be a setback for Bateman as a WR4 option in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9389-deb6-a7fd-d3df07640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Hill had three rushes for 76 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs, adding five catches for 41 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-938b-dca3-a9fb-bf9be2f40000</link>
      <description>Hill broke off a 71-yard touchdown scamper in garbage time, after Derrick Henry had been pulled from the lopsided affair, accounting for most of his rushing production on the day. His receiving score came in the first quarter as he subbed in for Henry in the red zone. Hill has operated as the clear No. 2 back behind Henry this season and would be a solid fantasy option should the indestructible Henry ever miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-938b-dca3-a9fb-bf9be2f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Rush completed 9-of-13 attempts for 52 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-938f-d95b-addb-fbcf1e660000</link>
      <description>Rush came in for Lamar Jackson after Jackson left the game in the first quarter with a hamstring injury. Rush mostly peppered short-area targets with the Chiefs playing prevent defense. If Rush starts in Week 5 against the Jaguars, the Ravens are likely to be slightly more pass heavy than they are with Lamar at the helm. Rush, a career 61 percent passer with 20 touchdowns and ten interceptions over 39 NFL appearances, can be added in superflex formats over the next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-938f-d95b-addb-fbcf1e660000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
