<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin (groin) is questionable to return for Week 17 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-663b-dc7a-af9b-efbf54610000</link>
      <description>CBS Sports’ sideline reporter Tracy Wolfson reported that Fannin re-aggravated his groin injury after hauling in a touchdown in the first quarter. According to Wolfson, Fannin tried to test the injury out on the sideline but didn’t feel well enough to go back out on the field. Fannin is now in the locker room and is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-663b-dc7a-af9b-efbf54610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (rib) is questionable to return Week 17 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-664d-d35e-a1bf-67cf761e0000</link>
      <description>Waddle exited in the second quarter against the Buccaneers, heading to the locker room with a rib injury. The 27-year-old has a history of getting banged-up mid-game, so we would not be surprised if he returned. He had one carry for seven yards prior to his exit. Waddle is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-664d-d35e-a1bf-67cf761e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders suffered an ankle injury in Carolina’s Week 17 game against the Seahawks and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6657-d968-a19b-7ef726830000</link>
      <description>Sanders’ right foot got rolled up run blocking on the literal first play of the game. He was in a world of pain before being carted to the locker room. It’s quite possible the 22-year-old’s season is through. The second-year pro entered today sitting on a 29/190/1 line, with the touchdown coming last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6657-d968-a19b-7ef726830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington (forearm) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 17’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6653-dc7a-af9b-effff50e0000</link>
      <description>Washington went down in the second quarter and attempted to come back in for a play. After his lone attempt to gut it out, he left for the sidelines and was ruled out shortly after leaving the field. Washington’s day ends with two receptions for 15 yards on two targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6653-dc7a-af9b-effff50e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Collins (illness) is questionable to play against the Pistons on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/basketball/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6663-d56e-afff-e6eb8c450000</link>
      <description>Collins is a late addition to the injury report and could end up missing a game for the first time this season. Derrick Jones Jr. (knee) is set to play for the first time in over a month, and he could immediately start if Collins is unavailable. Nicolas Batum would also take on extra minutes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/basketball/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6663-d56e-afff-e6eb8c450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared WR Jack Bech, RB Raheem Mostert, WR Phillip Dorsett, S Terrell Edmunds, RB Chris Collier, DT Brodric Martin and QB Aidan O’Connell inactive for Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62bd-d56e-afff-e6fd6a640000</link>
      <description>Bech injured his back on Friday. Although the Raiders’ (2-13) season is lost, a Week 17 absence could be consequential for Bech down the road. This was an opportunity for the underwhelming rookie to put a positive performance on film. He produced career highs in targets (six), receptions (six) and receiving yards (50) in Week 14. Hopefully, he can get healthy enough to play in Week 18 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62bd-d56e-afff-e6fd6a640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin (groin) will not return in Week 17’s game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-667a-d968-a19b-7efbd8940000</link>
      <description>Fannin re-aggravated his groin injury on a play where he hauled in a 28-yard receiving touchdown in the first quarter. The star rookie left for the sidelines after the play and later the locker room. He was ruled out shortly after halftime, as his day ends with a 2-30-1 line on two targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-667a-d968-a19b-7efbd8940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed suffered a concussion in the Seahawks’ Week 17 game against the Panthers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-d968-a19b-7ef32f340000</link>
      <description>Shaheed took a huge hit on the Panthers’ sideline in the second quarter and remained down for several moments. He eventually made his way to the Seahawks’ bench unassisted but was obviously worse for the wear. He now figures to be shut down for Week 18 with an eye toward getting healthy for the postseason. The big-play threat had just one catch for eight yards before departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-d968-a19b-7ef32f340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Raheem Mostert (knee/ankle) inactive for Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1c80000</link>
      <description>Mostert entered Week 17 questionable to play due to knee and ankle injuries. He is not fantasy-relevant on his own. His absence could result in a few late-game touches for RB Zamir White and RB Dylan Laube. Neither player should be anywhere near fantasy lineups, though. Starting RB Ashton Jeanty could feasibly handle all backfield touches against the Giants today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6683-dc7a-af9b-efbfd1c80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
