<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:18:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said “nothing will happen” with WR Brandon Aiyuk “until the new league year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e5-d042-afbc-fdf779f80000</link>
      <description>It is all but certain Aiyuk will not be a 49er for next season. The new league year will be coming up in March, making any kind of trade/release with the 27-year-old more doable. A release is more likely, but Lynch added, “who knows...maybe someone this week will have some interest.” Aiyuk will be a new addition to the receiver market as suitable teams like the Commanders and Steelers start making moves in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91e5-d042-afbc-fdf779f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos general manager George Paton said CB Ja’Quan McMillian is “one of our core players.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91f9-d042-afbc-fdfb4fd20000</link>
      <description>McMillian is a pending restricted free agent come March. Paton added that a team could call the Broncos to make a run for him, but the team would like to keep him. The 25-year-old former UDFA tallied four sacks and two interceptions in the regular season and most notably wrestled away an interception from Brandin Cooks to defeat the Bills in the AFC Divisional Round. McMillian plays a key secondary role for a Broncos defense that led the team to an AFC Championship berth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91f9-d042-afbc-fdfb4fd20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers are hiring former Vikings general manager Kwesi Adofo-Mensah as a personnel executive.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91fd-d57c-a1dd-95fd97e70000</link>
      <description>Adofo-Mensah spent four seasons as the Vikings’ general manager, most notably helping build a Vikings team that went 14-3 in 2024 with Sam Darnold at quarterback. However, the team’s struggles with 2024 first-rounder J.J. McCarthy starting last season while Darnold won a Super Bowl in Seattle likely contributed to the end of his tenure in Minnesota. Adofo-Mensah spent 2013-2019 with the 49ers in the football research and development department. 49ers general manager John Lynch announced that Adofo-Mensah will now return to the spot his football executive career began as a personnel executive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-91fd-d57c-a1dd-95fd97e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers general manager Dan Morgan said “we’ll explore” signing EDGE Bradley Chubb in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9204-d629-a1bc-b21d3a310000</link>
      <description>The possibility of signing Chubb was brought up at Morgan’s press conference at the NFL Scouting Combine; Morgan said the 29-year-old is “still playing at a really good level” and indicated the Panthers are exploring the idea of signing him. Chubb tallied 8.5 sacks for the Dolphins last season after missing 2024 with a torn ACL. Miami released Chubb after the playoffs, making him eligible to sign at any point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9204-d629-a1bc-b21d3a310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said the team is “not anticipating” using the franchise tag on K Eddy Pineiro.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9215-d89c-a1be-bfdf80390000</link>
      <description>Pineiro had an efficient season for the 49ers, missing just one of his 29 regular season attempts. Lynch said, “we got a couple weeks before free agency to continue to work towards something.” Pineiro is a pending free agent and eligible for the franchise tag should the 49ers not reach a deal with the 30-year-old. Lynch indicated it is not likely the team will tag Pineiro and there is interest to reaching a new deal with the kicker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9215-d89c-a1be-bfdf80390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers general manager John Lynch said, “somebody would have to come with something fairly strong for us to consider” trading QB Mac Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-921f-d57c-a1dd-961fbdf80000</link>
      <description>Jones started a few games for the 49ers in 2025, putting himself on the radar for quarterback-needy teams. However, Lynch said Jones has been “really good for us and we value that...I think we’re a better team with him on it.” The 49ers value Jones as a capable backup quarterback behind Brock Purdy, who has missed time due to injury over the last couple seasons. If a team values Jones as a starter and crafts a strong offer, Lynch and the 49ers would at least consider trading the 27-year-old.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-921f-d57c-a1dd-961fbdf80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When asked about using the franchise tag on EDGE Trey Hendrickson, Bengals executive Duke Tobin said, “I don’t throw anything on or off the table with Trey.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-923c-d042-afbc-fffe12de0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals and Hendrickson have been in contentious contract talks for a while with all options still on the table, according to director of player personnel and de facto general manager Duke Tobin. The franchise tag is still a possibility and theCincinnati Enquirer’sKelsey Conway reported last week the Bengals will get a feel for the 31-year-old’s market at this week’s NFL Combine. The tag would guarantee $30.2 million to Hendrickson in 2026, making it difficult to afford for the Bengals. However, the team still won’t publicly deny the franchise tag as an option, likely in an effort to generate value in possible trade scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-923c-d042-afbc-fffe12de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Penn State QB Drew Allar (ankle) will throw at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9255-d629-a1bc-b25d840d0000</link>
      <description>Allar is recovering from season-ending ankle surgery but will throw at the NFL Combine this week. The 21-year-old will get the chance to show off his arm strength, though his mobility may not be at full strength just yet. Allar started the past three seasons at Penn State, choosing to return instead of declaring for the draft last season. His ankle surgery came after an ankle injury sustained in October, prohibiting from showcasing his skillset to NFL teams later in the season. Allar is on the radar as a mid-round prospect for now, with the chance to improve his stock with a strong showing at the NFL Combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9255-d629-a1bc-b25d840d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports Cowboys K Brandon Aubrey is seeking $10 million per season in a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-92e6-d57c-a1dd-96eedaa90000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys have already offered Aubrey the league’s highest-paid kicker contract. Watkins reports the 30-year-old “was offered a deal with an average salary of close to $7.5 million but is looking for nearly $10 million per season.” Despite exceeding Chiefs kicker Harrison Butker’s $6.4 million average annual salary with this contract offer, the Cowboys are still below Aubrey’s desired number. He has one first-team All-Pro and two second-team All-Pro selections over the last three years, a resume certainly worth demanding the highest kicker salary in the league. The Cowboys can still place a first- or second-round tender on Aubrey if an extension does not happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-92e6-d57c-a1dd-96eedaa90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders will play a 2026 regular season game in London.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</link>
      <description>Jayden Daniels, coming off an injury-plagued 2025 season in which he threw eight touchdowns and three interceptions over seven games, will lead Washington into London for one of the NFL’s many international games in 2026. The Commanders will look to get back to their 2024 offensive form after scoring points on just 37 percent of their offensive possessions in 2025, the tenth lowest rate in the league. Daniels last season had a drop back EPA on par with Tyler Shough and Kirk Cousins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
