<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 04:16:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (shoulder) returned in the second half of Week 15 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ffb-d1bc-a3fb-9fff90010000</link>
      <description>Williams departed after the team’s first possession and missed the remainder of the first half. He returned after the break to take a handoff from quarterback Dak Prescott on the first play from scrimmage in the third quarter. Fantasy managers can breath a collective sigh of relief, at least for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ffb-d1bc-a3fb-9fff90010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle rushed 16 times for 49 yards and one touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 15 loss to the Saints, adding one reception for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1feb-d77b-adfb-dfeb82200000</link>
      <description>Dowdle missed a few snaps on his team’s first drive, but he returned in time to punch in a short touchdown. The Saints deserve credit for limiting Dowdle to 3.1 yards per carry, though play volume was also an issue for the Panthers. The Saints’ 11-minute, 22-second first-half drive was their longest drive since at least the year 2000, going 95 yards on 17 plays and keeping the football away from the Panthers. Dowdle is an RB2 against the Buccaneers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1feb-d77b-adfb-dfeb82200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard rushed eight times for 29 yards in the Panthers’ Week 15 loss to the Saints, adding one reception for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2000-d77b-adfb-ea8310430000</link>
      <description>Hubbard was seemingly headed toward a featured role after RB Rico Dowdle was escorted off the field by Panthers trainers, but Dowdle returned after a few plays, in time to score a touchdown. Hubbard was then stuck in his rotational role. He has a nice first-down gain on the Panthers’ fourth drive, traversing the field after securing a screen pass on 3rd-and-7. He is just a low-floor FLEX against the Buccaneers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2000-d77b-adfb-ea8310430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Myers converted all six of his field goal attempts in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2016-d8cf-affb-bc3ed2570000</link>
      <description>Seattle won without scoring a touchdown against the Philip Rivers-led Colts thanks to Myers’ deadly long-range accuracy. Myers in Week 15 continued a season full of clutch kicking with a four quarter field goal to take the lead and another one to win the game after the Colts took a late lead with a 60-yard Blake Grupe bomb. Myers has now made 37 of 42 field goal tries this season and should be started in all formats next week against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2016-d8cf-affb-bc3ed2570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Grupe converted all three of his field goal attempts in the Colts’ Week 15 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2019-d1bc-a3fb-a53d7b0c0000</link>
      <description>Grupe, who was released by the Saints in early December after making just 18 of his 26 field goal tries, came through big time for Indy in their near-upset of the Seahawks. Grupe nailed a 60-yarder to take the lead in the fourth quarter — a kick that would have been good from at least 65 yards. Grupe will be a decent streaming option in Week 16 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2019-d1bc-a3fb-a53d7b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught 5-of-7 targets for 74 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win against the Colts, adding one rush for -3 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-201d-d77b-adfb-ea9fcbe50000</link>
      <description>Shaheed now has two straight decent statistical outings as the Seahawks’ No. 3 receiver. Sam Darnold locked on to Shaheed in the fourth quarter of the team’s narrow win against the Colts, and Shaheed’s highlight came on a 27 yard catch and run reception in which he showed off his impressive speed. He was targeted on 21 percent of his routes. Shaheed could have some fantasy intrigue in Week 16 against the Rams if LA forces the Seahawks into negative game script the way they did in the team’s first meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-201d-d77b-adfb-ea9fcbe50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ameer Abdullah had four rushes for 15 yards in the Colts’ Week 15 loss against the Seahawks, adding five catches for 32 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2022-d005-a9bf-f8361de50000</link>
      <description>Abdullah was very much involved as a pass catcher, though he only ran six pass routes and saw a target on five of those routes. Jonathan Taylor, meanwhile, logged 18 routes and saw four targets from check-down artist Philip Rivers, 44, who made his first start since 2020 on Sunday against Seattle. With short-area pass catchers set to feast with Rivers under center, Abdullah could have some value in deeper formats next week against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2022-d005-a9bf-f8361de50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet had eight rushes for 31 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-202a-d005-a9bf-f83eb6830000</link>
      <description>It was another frustrating day for both Seattle backs. Charbonnet did next to nothing with his eight carries (and did not see a target) while Ken Walker had 17 yards on nine carries (while seeing one target). Charbonnet has more weekly touchdown upside because he’s been the team’s primary inside-the-ten option for most of the 2025 season. Even so, he won’t be playable in Week 16 against the Rams. He had 11 carries for 37 yards in the Hawks’ first meeting with the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-202a-d005-a9bf-f83eb6830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 2-of-3 targets for 47 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 15 loss against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-202d-d1bc-a3fb-a52da2a10000</link>
      <description>Thornton easily led the team in air yards and nearly came down with a Patrick Mahomes deep shot before Mahomes left the game with a season-ending knee injury. Thornton ran a route on about half of the Chiefs’ drop backs and operated as the team’s only real downfield threat. It’s hard to imagine Thornton holding much value with Gardner Minshew under center for the Chiefs in Week 16 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-202d-d1bc-a3fb-a52da2a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 3-of-5 targets for 49 yards in the Chargers’ Week 15 win against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2030-d77b-adfb-eab377880000</link>
      <description>Harris got the start with Quentin Johnston (groin) sidelined and saw the second most targets among Bolts pass catchers in yet another run-heavy game plan for LA. Harris ran a route on 29 of the team’s 31 drop backs — more than slot WR Keenan Allen, who had 36 yards on seven targets against the Chiefs. Harris would be interesting as a desperation flex in Week 16 against the Cowboys if Johnston remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2030-d77b-adfb-eab377880000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
