<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived LB Baylon Spector (calf) with an injury settlement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95e2-d45c-a7fc-97fa41ac0000</link>
      <description>Spector dealt with injuries in both calves this year. It’s a tough break for a player coming off a season in which he tallied multiple career highs. Spector will likely be invited to try out for backup linebacker/special teams roles once he is in good health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95e2-d45c-a7fc-97fa41ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shane Steichen said Daniel Jones will play “a few series” as the Colts’ preseason Week 2 starter but Anthony Richardson will get the “bulk of the work” in the first half.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95c9-d45c-a7fc-97dbe9ae0000</link>
      <description>Steichen emphasized “consistency,” particularly in joint practices this week, as the key factor in determining who wins the starting role. This can be read as a call to Richardson specifically, who possesses immense talent but continues to be plagued by injuries and errors. If he can simply execute the offense as asked in the coming weeks, the job is likely his.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95c9-d45c-a7fc-97dbe9ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed LB Duke Riley, formerly of the Dolphins, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ec-df63-a199-ddef17170000</link>
      <description>Riley served as a defensive backup in his age-30 season last year, totaling just three tackles along the way. He can still contribute on special teams, though, having just tied his career-best qualifying tackles tally with six.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ec-df63-a199-ddef17170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 5-of-6 passes for 27 yards in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-960f-df63-a199-df2f85ee0000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa played one drive, and kept things very close to the line of scrimmage via a 4.7-yard aDOT. He averaged just 4.5 yards per attempt. Ideally, we would like to see the Dolphins’ starters successfully all depths of the field next week. Speedsters, Tyreek Hill and Jaylen Waddle, did not play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-960f-df63-a199-df2f85ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 4-of-4 targets for 18 yards and rushed once for six yards in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d05a-adda-be93d7c50000</link>
      <description>Washington touched the ball on five of the Dolphins’ first 10 plays. He was then bubble-wrapped on the sideline, preserving him for future use. Washington forced two missed tackles overall and looked good navigating the short area of the field. He did, unfortunately, fumble on his lone carry but the ball went out of bounds, preserving the Dolphins’ possession. Washington appears to be in contention for No. 3 wide receiver duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d05a-adda-be93d7c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed three times for 22 yards in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d45c-a7fc-961be1930000</link>
      <description>Achane had an eight-yard run called back as well. The story of the day was Wright’s red zone flop. Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel subbed Wright in when the first-team offense entered the red zone. He took his second carry six yards into enemy territory, being brought down at the Bears’ two-yard line. He then gained one yard, zero yards and lost three, resulting in a turnover on downs. Wright later scored with the backups, finishing the day rushing nine times for 16 yards and one touchdown. His goal-line chops need work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d45c-a7fc-961be1930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Miami Herald’s Omar Kelly reports that Alexander Mattison “is experiencing neck and shoulder soreness” after leaving the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears early.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9632-d90d-a5bd-b67b8e810000</link>
      <description>Kelly adds that Mattison is “not in concussion protocol currently, [but that] doesn’t mean he won’t be.” Mattison landed hard on his head and neck while being tackled. Before that, he rushed three times for eight yards and one touchdown and caught 1-of-2 targets for 21 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9632-d90d-a5bd-b67b8e810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bub Means was carted away from the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers after suffering an apparent lower-leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-964d-df63-a199-df6fd1ca0000</link>
      <description>A high-ankle sprain ended Means’ 2024 rookie year prematurely. Hopefully, this is unrelated. Before exiting, Means caught 1-of-2 targets for 12 yards. He is competing for the Saints’ No. 3 wide receiver role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-964d-df63-a199-df6fd1ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears head coach Ben Johnson said Luther Burden “is working his tail off behind the scenes.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-965a-d05a-adda-beda6ba60000</link>
      <description>Johnson acknowledges that Burden’s play is “not where it needs to be yet,” but he “loves how hard” Burden is working. That’s encouraging. Burden is a talented, young player. If he can get up to speed, after missing significant practice time due to a strained hamstring, he could return flex value in year one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-965a-d05a-adda-beda6ba60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 7-of-11 passes for 53 yards and rushed three times for 22 yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 1 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9661-d05a-adda-bee3f5550000</link>
      <description>Rattler got the start but did little with it, producing two glaring low points. The Saints’ second drive started on the Chargers’ 17-yard line after the returner muffed the Saints’ punt. The drive stalled out with a turnover on downs at the Chargers’ one-yard line. Rattler later added a lost fumble to the box score when he was sacked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9661-d05a-adda-bee3f5550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
