<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:29:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bbd-dc7a-af9b-ffbffce10000</link>
      <description>Shaheed suffered a concussion in Week 17, but kicked off Week 18 practices with a limited session on Tuesday. He upgraded to full on Wednesday and continued practicing fully today. The Seahawks’ speedy receiver and return specialist could rip off a few long gains this week against the 49ers’ fantasy-friendly defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bbd-dc7a-af9b-ffbffce10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) is questionable to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bc0-d35e-a1bf-7fc2d14c0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall is on track after logging three consecutive limited practice sessions this week. He played through the pain last week, meeting with team trainers at times along the sideline. Despite the injuries, he caught 5-of-8 targets for 85 yards. Pearsall is a WR3 with big-play upside against the Seahawks’ top-tier defense this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bc0-d35e-a1bf-7fc2d14c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (hamstring) is questionable to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb2-d56e-afff-fffa73440000</link>
      <description>The 37-year-old Williams suffered his first career hamstring injury, running 17.6 miles per hour on the 49ers’ first play from scrimmage last week. He was entirely unable to practice, but we expect him to give it a go in pre-game warmups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb2-d56e-afff-fffa73440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Seahawks ruled out LT Charles Cross (hamstring) for Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bd5-d35e-a1bf-7fd7da210000</link>
      <description>Cross was unable to resume practicing this week, theoretically leaving OL Josh Jones (knee/ankle) as the team’s fill-in starter. Unfortunately, Jones is questionable to play this week, though he reportedly “just got banged up” in Week 17 and is expected to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bd5-d35e-a1bf-7fd7da210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Dolphins hired “Hall-of-Fame QB and ESPN analyst Troy Aikman as a consultant” to assist in the team’s search for a new general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bd8-d35e-a1bf-7fda95110000</link>
      <description>This “is not a permanent role” for Aikman. He is expected to continue providing insights for ESPN. Per Schefter, the Dolphins’ ownership wants “an outside respected perspective from someone who had strong relationships across the league.” That latter part could be key. Aikman is undoubtedly plugged into multiple front offices and may be able to help the Dolphins identify an up-and-comer from another personnel department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bd8-d35e-a1bf-7fda95110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RB Kyren Williams (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7be6-d35e-a1bf-7fe6c1210000</link>
      <description>Williams’ backup, RB Blake Corum (ankle), has not yet practiced this week and the Rams are already headed to the playoffs. Rams rookie RB Jarquez Hunter could see live action this week against the Cardinals, if the coaching staff opts to preserve Williams’ health for the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7be6-d35e-a1bf-7fe6c1210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RB Blake Corum (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7be6-dc7a-af9b-ffffca280000</link>
      <description>Corum is firmly on the wrong side of questionable at this point and the Rams have already secured a playoff spot. Starting RB Kyren Williams (ankle) is nursing an ankle injury. If both players are declared inactive, rookie RB Jarquez Hunter could get the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7be6-dc7a-af9b-ffffca280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c29-d56e-afff-fee97a450000</link>
      <description>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh told reporters earlier this week that getting his injured players healthy is his priority. With two absences to begin the week, Hampton seems unlikely to play this week. It is unclear whether rotational backup Jaret Patterson will get the start. Chargers No. 2 RB Kimani Vidal (neck) upgraded to full today while RB Hassan Haskins (concussion) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c29-d56e-afff-fee97a450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bdb-d968-a19b-7bfb69c10000</link>
      <description>Vidal could get the start this week with RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) sidelined by an ankle injury. The team could choose to preserve Vidal’s health for the postseason, though. Rotational RB Jaret Patterson is healthy and Hassan Haskins (concussion) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bdb-d968-a19b-7bfb69c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c30-d968-a19b-7cf1a3300000</link>
      <description>Bryant is progressing through the NFL’s concussion protocol and should be able to play in Week 18 against the Chargers, though the Chargers are expected to rest some starters, which could result in an easy run-heavy win for the Broncos. The Broncos (13-3) currently hold the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. They can retain it with a win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7c30-d968-a19b-7cf1a3300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
