<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:07:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Kuharsky reports the Titans will interview former Buccaneers QB coach Thad Lewis for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc9-d35e-a1bf-ffcb8f290000</link>
      <description>The list of names linked to the Titans OC role so far are Kliff Kingsbury, Brian Daboll, Adam Stenavich, and now Lewis. Lewis got interviewed by the Texans for their OC vacancy in the 2025 offseason, as well as an in-house look from the Buccaneers. He also was interviewed for Buffalo’s OC vacancy in 2024. The Buccaneers fired Lewis earlier this offseason and this is his first known interview since that happened — we bet he’ll pick up a lower-level role elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbc9-d35e-a1bf-ffcb8f290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Titans will interview former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury and Packers OC Adam Stenavich for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd1-dc7a-af9b-fffff26d0000</link>
      <description>We can imagine Stenavich being someone that appeals to Robert Saleh’s defensive coach instincts, though Stenavich has not called plays under Matt LaFleur. Kingsbury had head-coaching interest from the Titans — as well as several other teams — so it’s not surprising they’re interested in pursuing him for this role as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd1-dc7a-af9b-fffff26d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins interviewed Eagles defensive line coach Clint Hurtt for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd6-dc7a-af9b-ffff5e6e0000</link>
      <description>Hurtt coordinated Seattle’s defense in 2022 and 2023 before being swept away in the Pete Carroll firing. He had formerly been Carroll’s defensive line coach and worked with Seattle from 2018-2023. He was previously Chicago’s linebackers coach under Vic Fangio. Hurtt’s coordinating experience wasn’t positive, but he’s potentially worthy of a second chance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fbd6-dc7a-af9b-ffff5e6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Giants interim coach Mike Kafka will join the Lions in a “high-ranking offensive staff role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</link>
      <description>He’s not the offensive coordinator — that’s Drew Petzing — but Kafka will apparently be another offensive mind in the room for Dan Campbell. It’s a coup for the Lions considering Kafka had interviewed to be an offensive coordinator in Detroit, Philadelphia, Tampa, and with the Giants this offseason. He’ll hope to rehab his coaching image after a fairly benign interim coach showing after Brian Daboll was swept out of power in New Jersey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested permission to interview Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase is reportedly meeting with the Browns right now in Los Angeles and Cleveland beat writers are picking out words carefully so they aren’t the ones saying he’s the favorite for the job despite the long interview, so perhaps this is a leverage play. It’s certainly no surprise to see the Bills interested, and they’ll reportedly have an in-person interview with Scheelhaase tonight. Scheelhaase also completed interviews with the Ravens, Raiders and Steelers this offseason. Scheelhaase would be yet another Sean McVay coaching tree disciple wherever he lands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed a second interview with Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc23-d968-a19b-fcf3ba750000</link>
      <description>Brady’s second interview with the Raiders was reportedly an in-person interview. The Bills’ offensive coordinator remains in play for head coaching openings with the Bills, Raiders, and Cardinals, although we can’t say with any amount of certainty if he has the inside edge for any of these jobs. Brady has been calling plays for the Bills since taking over for Ken Dorsey during the mid-way point of the 2023 season and also spent time calling plays for the Panthers from 2020-2021. If Brady doesn’t get a head coaching job, he should have plenty of suitors for offensive coordinator vacancies and may even return to the Bills in the right situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc23-d968-a19b-fcf3ba750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed a second interview with Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc87-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b6a30000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase is clearly one of the frontrunners for the head coach position in Cleveland but is also interviewing with the Bills for the same position later in the day. A copycat league continues to show great interest in the Sean McVay and Kyle Shanahan coaching trees, with Scheelhaase the next man up for a potential massive bump in responsibility. He has also interviewed with the Ravens, Raiders, and Steelers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc87-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b6a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed former Vikings defensive pass game coordinator Daronte Jones as their next defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd25-d56e-afff-ffed09550000</link>
      <description>Jones booked no less than six interviews for defensive coordinator vacancies in the past two weeks, ultimately landing with the Commanders. Details of the signing are not yet available. Jones had a significant hand in a Minnesota defense that held opponents to the fewest pass yards per game in 2025 and now gets his first shot at defensive play calling duties in the Nation’s capitol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd25-d56e-afff-ffed09550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed a second interview with Broncos passing game coordinator Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy,</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd2b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf14bf0000</link>
      <description>Although an unlikely hire, Webb gained traction with the Raiders after a successful first interview and completed a second, in-person, interview with the franchise Monday. The 31-year-old has three years of coaching experience at the NFL level after a six-year career and would be attempting to make the leap from passing game coordinator to head coach, without ever having called offensive plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd2b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf14bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former NFL general manager said Jets head coach Aaron Glenn “did nothing” to change the team’s culture of losing.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffbc-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc9860000</link>
      <description>The former front office official told ESPN’s Rich Cimini that the lackluster effort on the part of Jets players was a telltale sign of a head coach who had not done anything to shift the team’s miserable culture, like his former boss, Dan Campbell, did in his first year with the Lions. Glenn “talked about swagger and toughness, but I didn’t see any of that. They played like a bunch of guys punching time clocks; they didn’t want to be there,” the former GM said. Glenn’s Jets struggled through a hopeless 3-14 season in 2025, posting one of the most lopsided scoring margins in recent NFL history. Glenn, a defensive specialist, gave total control of the defense to Steve Wilks, who was fired late in the season. New York was the first team in NFL history to go an entire season without an interception. Jets owner Woody Johnson will give Glenn another season to turn things around, Cimini said, because he was very much involved in hiring Glenn last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffbc-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc9860000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
