<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields was benched in Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd8-da18-a39b-ffdb47bb0000</link>
      <description>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn didn’t have much of a choice after Fields once again struggled to complete the most basic throws and often stood in the pocket and took easily-avoidable sacks against a Panthers pass rush that ranks among the league’s worst. Fields had 46 scoreless yards on 12 attempts before he was sent to he pine. New York’s offense has been much more productive with Taylor under center this season. He should be a massive upgrade for the team’s pass catchers if he hangs on to the job long term. One of the worst passers in recent league history, Fields’ days as an NFL starter are effectively over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd8-da18-a39b-ffdb47bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared DE Marshawn Kneeland, G Trevor Keegan, CB Trevon Diggs, S Juanyeh Thomas, T Ajani Cornelius and DT Jay Toia inactive for Dallas’ Week 7 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdda-da18-a39b-ffdb23d20000</link>
      <description>Kneeland (ankle), Thomas (migraine), and Cornelius (knee) were all questionable and none of the three will play. Diggs was ruled out on Friday after suffering an injury in an accident in his house.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdda-da18-a39b-ffdb23d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers K Brandon McManus (quad) is inactive for Week 7 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd7-d651-a9df-fdd7f6ad0000</link>
      <description>Also inactive for the Packers are RB Pierre Strong Jr., G Donovan Jennings, T Anthony Belton, TE Ben Sims, DL Lukas Van Ness, and DL Devonte Wyatt. McManus will miss another game due to his quad issue, meaning Lucas Havrisik will kick for Green Bay against the Cardinals. Strong was elevated from the practice squad, but with Josh Jacobs (calf/illness) active, he is inactive this week. Meanwhile, Van Ness will miss this game due to a foot issue that kept him out of practice all week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd7-d651-a9df-fdd7f6ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) is inactive for Week 7 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fddc-d651-a9df-fddd285c0000</link>
      <description>Murray will miss his second straight game due to a foot issue, he is expected to return after the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye. Jacoby Brissett is starting again for the Cardinals, after a strong 320-yard performance in Week 6. Also inactive for the Cardinals are CB Elijah Jones, S Kitan Crawford, RB Emari Demercado, OL Demontrey Jacobs, and OL Josh Fryer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fddc-d651-a9df-fddd285c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught 3-of-6 targets for 19 yards in the Rams’ Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd9-d651-a9df-fdddc5910000</link>
      <description>Higbee earned a season-high in targets in Puka Nacua’s first missed game of the year. Nacua also missed much of Week 6, a game in which Higbee earned his season-high in receiving yards. The bad news is that Nacua is expected to return after the team’s Week 8 bye. Fantasy managers don’t need to hold Higbee through the bye, even if he has some low-end TE2 value veruss the Saints in two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd9-d651-a9df-fdddc5910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Whittington caught 2-of-4 tarfets for nine yards in the Rams’ Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde0-da18-a39b-fff35c960000</link>
      <description>Whittington was one of many players tasked with replacing Puka Nacua’s production. He finished second among the team’s wideouts in targets, but Nacua’s vacated looks were spready throughout the lineup. With Nacua expected to return after the Rams’ upcoming bye, Whittington can be sent to waivers on the next run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde0-da18-a39b-fff35c960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles CB Adoree Jackson (concussion) left Week 7’s game against the Eagles and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde2-d99b-a1dd-ffee851a0000</link>
      <description>He laid on the field for a few minutes motionless and was instantly ruled out even after seeming to come off the turf fine. It was a scary-looking injury, and we wouldn’t be surprised if Jackson missed multiple weeks. Kelee Ringo will likely take over at outside cornerback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde2-d99b-a1dd-ffee851a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konata Mumpfield caught his only target for a five-yard touchdown in the Rams’ Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde2-d99b-a1dd-ffee81330000</link>
      <description>Mumpfield made his first NFL catch a week ago and then got in the end zone for the first time on a five-yard strike from Stafford today. He ran 10 routes to Tutu Atwell’s nine. With Puka Nacua expected to return after the team’s upcoming bye, fantasy managers can ignore the Rams’ depth receivers going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fde2-d99b-a1dd-ffee81330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young exited the Panthers’ Week 7 game with an apparent ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdf5-d651-a9df-fdf555d50000</link>
      <description>Young’s foot seemed to stick in the turf on a fourth quarter sack and he was escorted to the Carolina locker room soon thereafter. Any Dalton took over for Young and would likely start for the Panthers if Young misses time with the injury. Young threw for 128 yards and a touchdown before he went down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdf5-d651-a9df-fdf555d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 10-of-16 passes for 67 yards in the Raiders’ 31-0, Week 7 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fded-d99b-a1dd-ffed2fa90000</link>
      <description>Perhaps the most surprising numbers, of which there are many, is the fact that Smith took only one sack on the afternoon. The Chiefs, who totaled only eight pressures on the day per the early PFF data, opted to stay back and let Smith find open receivers, a seemingly impossible task. With Brock Bowers (knee) and Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) both inactive, Smith and the Raiders were unable to get anything going through the air. At one point, Smith went nearly two full quarters without completing a pass before a four-yard completion to Tre Tucker late in the third quarter gave Smith his first completion since the first quarter. Smith and the Raiders are hurting both literally and physically, but now enter a Week 8 bye. The hope is that both Meyers and. Bowers will be back for Week 9’s game against the Jaguars, which should provide some help to an offense that has totaled just 26 points in its last three games combined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fded-d99b-a1dd-ffed2fa90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
