<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Greg Dortch (chest) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebab-dce4-a1da-fbbfa3ea0000</link>
      <description>Dortch is seemingly heading toward an absence for the Cardinals’ Week 14 game against the Rams. The veteran wide receiver was working his way into FLEX territory just a few weeks ago. He does not need to be rostered at this time. Cardinals WR Xavier Weaver (hamstring) was added to the injury report on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebab-dce4-a1da-fbbfa3ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebb5-d005-a9bf-fbb5b6690000</link>
      <description>Hampton’s limited participation is encouraging. The Chargers’ starting running back had his 21-day practice window opened on November 25th, though, so the team still has a way to go before they have to make an official decision on his status. Hampton has a chance to play this week. Hopefully, we will have word by the end of the day on Saturday regarding his Week 14 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebb5-d005-a9bf-fbb5b6690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebb5-da9b-a9bf-ffbdbd4a0000</link>
      <description>Johnston is on track to play this week, despite being listed with a new injury. The streaky perimeter wide receiver remains a weekly FLEX candidate, and his team’s Week 14 game against the Eagles should be a fantasy-friendly environment. Hopefully, he practices fully tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebb5-da9b-a9bf-ffbdbd4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) gave him “the thumbs up that he is indeed playing” in Week 14 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebbc-d005-a9bf-fbbcf13a0000</link>
      <description>The Lions will announce the official inactive list shortly, but for now, it appears as though they will have their star slot receiver on the field for their Thursday Night Football game against the Cowboys. St. Brown should be in fantasy lineups if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebbc-d005-a9bf-fbbcf13a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) is active for Week 14 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebc2-dce4-a1da-fbd6d04f0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown was unable to practice this week after injuring his ankle last Thursday against the Packers. While he possesses some re-injury risk, he was moving very well during warmups and should be started against the Cowboys this evening. The Lions declared S Kerby Joseph, WR Kalif Raymond, OG Kayode Awosika, TE Hayden Rucci, DL Mekhi Wingo and DL Tyler Lacy inactive for Week 14 against the Cowboys. Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder), LT Taylor Decker (shoulder/rest) and C Graham Glasgow (knee) are active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebc2-dce4-a1da-fbd6d04f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared DE Jadeveon Clowney, WR Jalen Tolbert, RB Jaydon Blue, DT Jay Toia, DT Perrion Winfrey and OT Tyler Guyton inactive for Week 14 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebc8-d005-a9bf-fbfc10680000</link>
      <description>Clowney (hamstring) attempted to give it a go in warmups after practicing once, a limited session on Wednesday, this week. He will be missed against the Lions’ top-notch offense. The Cowboys have once again declared Blue, the once-exciting rookie, inactive this week. He does not need to be stashed at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebc8-d005-a9bf-fbfc10680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker (glute) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebce-d77b-adfa-ebcf2d170000</link>
      <description>Walker has been dealing with the glute issue for nearly two weeks. He was not on Wednesday’s initial injury report but the Seahawks ended up adding him to it later in the day. The fact that he continued practicing, albeit in a limited capacity, puts him on track to face the Falcons in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebce-d77b-adfa-ebcf2d170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (knee/shoulder) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebe1-d005-a9bf-fbf551e60000</link>
      <description>Barner is good to go for the Seahawks’ Week 14 game against the Falcons. Seattle’s low passing volume keeps Barner from the weekly TE1 ranks, but he has proven himself as a capable player and remains a touchdown-scoring candidate each week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ebe1-d005-a9bf-fbf551e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb exited in the third quarter of Week 14’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ec5b-da9b-a9bf-fe5fbf980000</link>
      <description>Lamb attempted to make an acrobatic catch in the end zone and came down hard on his head. He appeared to be in the fencing position, which occurs after a player has suffered a serious head injury, and was eventually helped off the field by trainers. He leaves the field with a season-high 121 receiving yards on eight targets. We’ll check back once the team provides a status update on the star receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ec5b-da9b-a9bf-fe5fbf980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (concussion) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 14’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ec84-d005-a9bf-fcb416390000</link>
      <description>That didn’t take long. Just minutes after being reviewed by the Cowboys’ independent neurologists for a concussion, Lamb has been ruled out for the game. His day ends with a 6-121-0 receiving line on eight targets, setting a new season-high in receiving yards. Lamb ripped off several big gains in this one, with his longest reception coming on a 37-yard catch-and-run. With this injury occurring on a Thursday, Lamb will have some extra time to clear protocol ahead of Week 15’s game against the Vikings, but his status will be one to watch next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ec84-d005-a9bf-fcb416390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
