<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (toe) was limited in practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e6f-d6a5-adff-feef24460000</link>
      <description>Mid-week injury report additions are never good news, so we’ll have to see how this unfolds on Friday. It’s possible that this is just maintenance. It’s also possible Pitts hurt his toe mid-practice and might be facing a fight to play this week. Pitts has had a nice season thus far and is on the TE1 line despite his offense barely passing at all in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e6f-d6a5-adff-feef24460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e72-dfde-a1bd-5effbc930000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign for his availability (and health) to see the mid-week upgrade after playing in his debut in Week 2. Mooney will likely have more success in Week 3 after a 2/20 debut against the Vikings — Carolina is one of the worst defenses in the NFL so far — the only worry is that things get so far out of hand that Atlanta effectively grinds the clock out. Mooney should be on the WR3/FLEX line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e72-dfde-a1bd-5effbc930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce (groin) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e74-dfde-a1bd-5efdcffb0000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session, but it’s a good sign for his chances of playing against the Panthers in Week 3. A.J. Terrell (hamstring) remained out of practice, but it looks like Atlanta could at least have both of their rookie EDGE players available to chase Bryce Young on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e74-dfde-a1bd-5efdcffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) is “expected” to play in Week 3 against the Bills and “be a big factor.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e71-d6a5-adff-fef581c70000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe, ever the optimistic reporter, said there is “not much doubt” about Waddle’s availability despite being questionable with a “minor shoulder injury.” We expect Waddle to play in a likely pass-heavy effort against the Bills this evening, although he has been expected to be a big factor in the Dolphins’ offense for quite some time now, yet he has just 11 targets through two games. Waddle is best treated as a borderline WR2/3 in what should be a favorable game script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e71-d6a5-adff-fef581c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Packers TE Tucker Kraft injured his knee in Thursday’s practice, but the belief is it’s not “a long-term issue.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e76-d6a5-adff-fef793620000</link>
      <description>He was officially limited. That doesn’t necessarily mean we should expect Kraft to play this week — what is long-term, anyway? — but at least it’s not as serious as it could have been. Fantasy managers reliant on Kraft should start making alternate plans at tight end, or at least scouring the wire thinking about who they’d pick up, if in fact this does keep Kraft out of Week 3’s game against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e76-d6a5-adff-fef793620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e78-dfde-a1bd-5efdc0290000</link>
      <description>Wednesday absences often become non-issues. Thursday absences have a much worse track record. It’s possible the Buccaneers are just exercising an abundance of caution, but fantasy managers should expect to be without Egbuka in Week 3. If the talented rookie wide receiver can somehow practice in full tomorrow, he can be started as usual. If he graduates to limited participation, this could come down to being a game-time decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e78-dfde-a1bd-5efdc0290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (ankle) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e7e-d93f-ad9d-5eff5fce0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like there’s much concern that Jacobs will miss Week 3, and he’ll be an easy RB1 against the Browns should he suit up. Backup runner Chris Brooks played on only 13 snaps and 11 of them were passing routes. Emanuel Wilson would likely be the head of a committee on running downs if Jacobs, for whatever reason, did not play in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e7e-d93f-ad9d-5eff5fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers placed RT Luke Goedeke (foot) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e5b-d93f-ad9d-5edf795d0000</link>
      <description>Goedeke is expected to return later this season. He will be eligible to do so after missing four games. It’s a brutal development for a Buccaneers offensive line that also lost RG Cody Mauch to a season-ending knee injury. Buccaneers LT Tristan Wirfs (knee) has not yet suited up on game day. He remains limited in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e5b-d93f-ad9d-5edf795d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e80-d1b3-a5dd-5ff1e6b50000</link>
      <description>It would be nice to see Worthy graduate to full practice participation, but he has at least logged four straight limited sessions, dating back to last week. We expect the Chiefs to require him to practice in full before he retakes the field on game day, but it’s possible they ease him in on a limited snap count.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e80-d1b3-a5dd-5ff1e6b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8a-dfde-a1bd-5e8f8c300000</link>
      <description>Royals’ tendinitis has responded positively after a few weeks of rehab and he is now on track to at least be available for the Chiefs’ Week 3 game against the Giants. He can be speculatively stashed on fantasy benches this week, to see how things shake out. Kansas City’s passing offense is in need of reliable weapons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8a-dfde-a1bd-5e8f8c300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
