<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:20:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 15 times for 48 yards in the 49ers’ Wild Card win over the Eagles, adding six receptions for 66 yards and two touchdowns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afda-d35e-a1bf-efdafca30000</link>
      <description>Again middling on the ground, McCaffrey was again sensational through the air, catching touchdown passes from both Brock Purdy and Jauan Jennings. The latter was a 29-yard trick play (obviously) strike that required McCaffrey to make an acrobatic grab at the goal line. McCaffrey’s rushing efficiency is in undeniable decline, but his receiving becomes even more of a Divisional Round X-factor with George Kittle (Achilles) lost for the season. We have no doubt coach Klye Shanahan will do everything he can to put CMC in position to make plays through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afda-d35e-a1bf-efdafca30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 4-of-7 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers, adding a one-yard rushing score.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afe2-d35e-a1bf-efe290780000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career-best regular season scoring binge as he led all tight ends with 11 touchdown receptions, Goedert added two more after turning 31 eight days ago. Although his receiving efficiency waned somewhat in 2025, Goedert had the best season of his career when it came to making big plays. In addition to the scores, he was constantly extending drives with first down grabs. It makes him a fascinating offseason case, as he is headed to free agency after restructuring his contract last spring. With A.J. Brown seemingly on the outs in Philadelphia, perhaps Goedert actually ends up returning after he somehow avoided a 2025 trade. Wherever he ends up, Goedert seems likely to stick in the low-end TE1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afe2-d35e-a1bf-efe290780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 26 times for 106 yards in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers, adding three receptions for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afe7-d968-a19b-fff7172d0000</link>
      <description>Coming off an historic 2024 season, Barkley was a 2025 mortal behind an Eagles’ offensive line that was nowhere near as good as we’ve grown accustomed to. He averaged 54 fewer rushing yards per game this season as he posted a replacement-level 4.1 yards per carry. Today was just his fourth 100-yard rushing effort of the year. Barkley did remain a net positive in terms of rush yards over expected, per NextGenStats. Although he is aging — 29 next month — Barkley could still easily “bounce back” next season if the Eagles’ blocking gets back closer to what we are used to seeing. He remains an RB1, if now more of a risk/reward option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afe7-d968-a19b-fff7172d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 1-of-3 targets for 14 yards in the 49ers’ Wild Card win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aff8-d56e-afff-eff8ddbf0000</link>
      <description>Tonges had a surprisingly quiet box score after coming on in relief of an injured George Kittle in the second quarter. With Kittle devastatingly suffering a torn achilles’ tendon, Tonges will resume fill-in duties as the Niners’ primary pass-catching seam stretcher. He could be needed for in the neighborhood of 5-7 looks against the Seahawks in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aff8-d56e-afff-eff8ddbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 6-of-7 targets for 111 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Wild Card win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b000-d968-a19b-f8f1515d0000</link>
      <description>Well hello there. Entering the postseason with zero 50-yard efforts all season, Robinson caught a 61-yard pass on the Niners’ second play from scrimmage. He went on to lead the team in receiving with Ricky Pearsall (knee) inactive and George Kittle (Achilles) soon joining him. With Kittle out for the Divisional Round in Seattle, D-Rob is going to be needed for another pop-up performance if the Niners are to have any hopes of springing another road upset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b000-d968-a19b-f8f1515d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahan Dotson was held without a catch in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b006-d35e-a1bf-f5c631930000</link>
      <description>Finishing up his second year as the Eagles’ sparingly-used No. 3 wideout, Dotston was sporadically productive in a dysfunctional passing attack. Headed to free agency after Philly declined his fifth-year team option, Dotson could end up back with the Eagles on a non-guaranteed contract. The 2022 draft bust’s two years in the Eagles’ system probably make him worth more to Philly than anybody else. That being said, we doubt Dotson would be a candidate to ascend to No. 2 status if A.J. Brown is traded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b006-d35e-a1bf-f5c631930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley caught a six-yard pass in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b00a-dc7a-af9b-ffbfaf250000</link>
      <description>Shipley was the Eagles’ clear No. 3 back in what ended up a season-ending loss. Originally ticketed for No. 2 duties this season, Shipley’s insurance back life grew more complicated when Tank Bigsby arrived in a Week 2 trade. Although the move seemed to have as much to do with Bigsby’s special teams prowess as anything else, Shipley ended up getting out-touched 61-23 behind Saquon Barkley. Heading into the third year of his rookie contract, Shipley is still only 23 years old, but his dynasty league future is not looking particularly bright.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b00a-dc7a-af9b-ffbfaf250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank Bigsby rushed four times for 19 yards in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b00f-d35e-a1bf-f5cf3b710000</link>
      <description>Bigsby was not targeted in the passing game. Surprisingly acquired from the Jags following Week 1, Bigsby ended up easily surpassing Will Shipley as the Eagles’ No. 2 back, but it amounted to only 61 offensive touches. Bigsby did feature on special teams, but neither he nor Shipley made much of an impression behind Saquon Barkley. The Eagles’ No. 1 back isn’t going anywhere for 2026, but they might think about an upgrade in the No. 2 spot. Bigsby, who turns 24 in August, is heading into the final year of his rookie deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b00f-d35e-a1bf-f5cf3b710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grant Calcaterra was not targeted in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b013-d35e-a1bf-f5d300a60000</link>
      <description>The only time Calcaterra managed a mention was when he drew Eagles fans’ ire for his poor blocking in the running game. Dallas Goedert is headed to free agency, but could end up back in Philadelphia depending on what happens with disgruntled No. 1 wideout A.J. Brown. In theory, that could lead to more opportunities for Calcaterra, but he’s 27 years old with 42 career receptions, only nine of which came this year. He himself is also a free agent, though he’s the kind of role player who typically ends up re-signing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b013-d35e-a1bf-f5d300a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (head) did not return to New England’s Wild Card win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b002-dc7a-af9b-ffbf20e90000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez took a tumble after getting tangled up with Chargers WR Quentin Johnston in the second half, slamming the back of his helmet onto the turf as he fell. Gonzalez remained on the field for the following play but was later called for a locker room examination by the sideline concussion spotter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b002-dc7a-af9b-ffbf20e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
