<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers hired former Dolphins quarterbacks coach Darrell Bevell as the team’s associate head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4d7c-d89c-a1be-efff0a7a0000</link>
      <description>Bevell will operate as the Panthers’ new offensive specialist, according to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. Bevell, who was the pass game coordinator and QBs coach in Miami from 2022 to 2025, will reunite with Panthers head coach Dave Canales, the wide receivers coach for the Seahawks when Bevell was the team’s offensive coordinator. After bouncing around the league for the past 20 years, Bevell will look to maximize Bryce Young’s abilities in 2026 for a Carolina offense that last season ranked 26th in EPA per play and 18th in success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4d7c-d89c-a1be-efff0a7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers named former Raiders offensive coordinator Luke Getsy as the team’s quarterbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4db3-d89c-a1be-efffed0a0000</link>
      <description>Getsy makes his return to the Packers after offensive coordinator stints with the Bears and Raiders, both of which went terribly for Getsy and his quarterbacks. In Green Bay Getsy will work with Jordan Love, who in 2025 had the league’s second best adjusted drop back EPA and a top-five drop back success rate. The Packers QB room will likely be without Malik Willis, who is reportedly being pursued by the Dolphins and Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4db3-d89c-a1be-efffed0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Ravens are expected to hire former Broncos wide receivers coach Keary Colbert as their wide receivers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ddf-d042-afbc-7ddf1e3a0000</link>
      <description>Colbert was with the Broncos for three seasons. He previously coached in the college ranks, getting most of his experience at USC as a position coach and an assistant. Colbert will lead a receiver room headlined by Zay Flowers, who just went for a career-high 1,211 yards. The hope will be that Colbert can also get more out of Rashod Bateman, who logged a pitiful 224 yards and two scores in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ddf-d042-afbc-7ddf1e3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Detroit’s Rachel Hopmeyer reports former Lions OT Dan Skipper will join the team’s coaching staff.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4e4b-d89c-a1be-efdf48f20000</link>
      <description>Unsurprisingly, Hopmeyer notes that Skipper will coach the offensive linemen in some capacity, though his official title hasn’t been announced. Detroit’s long-time sixth offensive lineman hung up the cleats after the 2025 season at the age of 31. It didn’t take him long to return to football, as Skipper volunteered to coach at the East-West Shrine Bowl right after the season. Now he will stay in Detroit as a staff member.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4e4b-d89c-a1be-efdf48f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Seahawks are interviewing assistant offensive line coach Justin Outten for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4e5c-d355-a5bd-cf5ceb870000</link>
      <description>Outten is one of four internal candidates who will interview for the opening. Tight ends coach Mack Brown, pass game coordinator Jake Peetz, and quarterbacks coach Andrew Janocko are the other three names. With one of those coaches getting promoted, another one or two will likely follow Klint Kubiak to Vegas. Per usual, the price to pay for winning the Super Bowl is a brain drain, which will primarily come on the offensive side of the ball for Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4e5c-d355-a5bd-cf5ceb870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Eagles coach Kevin Patullo as their pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ebd-d042-afbc-7fff2c460000</link>
      <description>As NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero notes, Philly retained Patullo after demoting him from offensive coordinator. The uncomfortable arrangement was not long for this world and Patullo will now head to South Beach. Patullo served as the Eagles’ OC for one year. The team went from seventh in scoring in 2024 to 19th in Patullo’s lone season on the headset. Between Patullo and offensive coordinator Bobby Slowik, who was also fired as an OC at his last stop, the Dolphins are putting together an awfully underwhelming staff under first-time head coach Jeff Hafley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ebd-d042-afbc-7fff2c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired former Rams special teams coordinator Chase Blackburn as their assistant special teams coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4f03-d629-a1bc-ff1fdcb90000</link>
      <description>Blackburn was fired by the Rams towards the end of the regular season after several losses were influenced by blunders on special teams. He had been with the team since 2023 but poor special teams showings marked a rough ending to his tenure. Blackburn will get a fresh start as an assistant in the special teams room with the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4f03-d629-a1bc-ff1fdcb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed RB Elijah Mitchell to a reserve-future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4f71-d89c-a1be-efff89b60000</link>
      <description>Mitchell played just one game with the Chiefs in 2025 before being released in December. He ended the season on the Patriots’ practice squad and the team has decided to bring him back for the offseason. Mitchell rushed for 963 yards and five touchdowns as a rookie with the 49ers but has struggled to find a role since. Rhamondre Stevenson and TreVeyon Henderson headline the Pats’ backfield, but Mitchell will get a chance to compete for a depth role this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4f71-d89c-a1be-efff89b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired Vikings assistant wide receivers coach Tony Sorrentino as their wide receivers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fcb-d89c-a1be-efdfe1840000</link>
      <description>Sorrentino spent the past four seasons with the Vikings, spending four seasons as the assistant wide receivers coach to a group consisting of Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison. New Cardinals head coach Mike LaFleur is building out his offensive staff and now adds Sorrentino to coach a wide receivers group hoping to get more out of Marvin Harrison Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fcb-d89c-a1be-efdfe1840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs hired former NFL RB DeMarco Murray as their running backs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fd2-d629-a1bc-ffdfadb90000</link>
      <description>Murray is known for his prolific seven-year NFL career, lasting from 2011-2017. He won NFL Offensive Player of the Year in 2014 with the Cowboys, also playing for the Eagles and Titans throughout his career. Murray has been a running backs coach at the college level, first for Arizona in 2019, and next for Oklahoma since 2020. The Chiefs will give him his first shot at coaching in the NFL. Murray will be the team’s new running backs coach under offensive coordinator Eric Bieniemy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fd2-d629-a1bc-ffdfadb90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
