<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Chig Okonkwo (foot) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4e2-d6c4-abfb-d6e337d60000</link>
      <description>Elic Ayomanor, who missed last week’s game with a hamstring injury, is also expected to suit up. Okonkwo has been losing work to Gunnar Helm lately, with the rookie tight end going for 51 yards on six grabs last week. Okokwo has caught more than three passes once in his past five games. Ayomanor scored twice in the first three weeks of the season and has since gone quiet. He has seen plenty of targets and air yards as of late, but Cam Ward’s struggles have drained the fantasy value from this offense. Neither Ayomanor nor Okonkwo should make it into fantasy lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4e2-d6c4-abfb-d6e337d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bam Knight (knee) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4e8-db57-afda-d6fa5e440000</link>
      <description>Knight got in three limited sessions this week before being listed as questionable. Trey Benson was ruled out on Friday, leaving Knight and Michael Carter to split the backfield. Knight will see the early-down work this week with Carter operating as the primary back on passing plays. Knight is a low-end RB3 for Week 13 while Carter has some FLEX appeal in full PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4e8-db57-afda-d6fa5e440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4ea-db57-afda-d6fac7380000</link>
      <description>Irving practiced in full throughout the week. He always seemed likely to play on Sunday, even though the team gave him a questionable tag on Friday. Schefter noted, “Bucs don’t want to overdo it with Irving, but he will get his touches.” Irving hasn’t played since Week 4 and the Bucs had a similar situation with Chris Godwin last week. Playing in his first game back from a lengthy injury, Godwin was on the field for just 25-of-70 snaps. The Bucs will likely limit Irving’s snaps as well, but they could lean on him if he gets hot. Head coach Todd Bowles talked earlier in the week about getting all three backs touches and riding the hot hand from there. If that’s Irving, he might not be on a pitch count for long.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4ea-db57-afda-d6fac7380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Saints expect Chris Olave (back) to play in Week 13 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4ef-d90e-a9da-dfefd7ab0000</link>
      <description>Olave left Wednesday’s practice early because of back spasms. He missed the following practice but returned on Friday for a limited session before being listed as questionable. Hopefully this issue doesn’t crop up during today’s game. Olave is known for dealing with mid-game injuries. He is also more than used to playing through them. There is a little more risk with Olave this week, but he is still dominating targets on a surprisingly functional Saints offense. Olave remains in the WR2 ranks for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4ef-d90e-a9da-dfefd7ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns are “open to giving [Shedeur] Sanders an extended look.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4f4-d82c-a79a-f7f40dcd0000</link>
      <description>Schefter goes on to say, “But much of that decision will be dictated by how Sanders plays, starting Sunday.” Basically, the Browns want to see more of Sanders, unless he struggles. Then they reserve the right to pull the plug at any moment. Sanders made his first start last week, throwing for 209 yards, one touchdown, and one interception. Dillon Gabriel has already proven not to be the team’s quarterback of the future. There is no reason not to let Sanders get a crack at the job over the final two months of the season. Even if the team goes in a different direction in the offseason, Sanders could play himself into a long-term backup role for the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4f4-d82c-a79a-f7f40dcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “defensive coordinators likened the Raiders offense this season more to Shane Waldron’s offense with the Seahawks in 2023.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4fa-d90e-a9da-dfff35a30000</link>
      <description>That was, of course, Pete Carroll’s final season in Seattle. Rapoport went even further, saying, “One previous opponent even had their scout team prepare cards based on Seattle plays of the past under Carroll, sources say.” This report comes just a few days after Tom Pelissero, Rapoport’s NFL Network colleague, said that Chip Kelly botched his own play calls during games and even called plays that hadn’t been installed during practice. As tends to happen in disaster seasons, everyone in Vegas is fighting to blame someone else through the media. Assuming Carroll is a one-and-done in Vegas, it’s a sad end to a legendary career. The game had left Carroll behind in his final years with the Seahawks, but he just couldn’t stay away. The Raiders, in turn, will have to blow things up and start from scratch this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d4fa-d90e-a9da-dfff35a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Aaron Rodgers has “several broken bones in his left wrist.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d500-d90e-a9da-df0fd0bb0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers has been cleared to play this week after missing Week 12’s game against Chicago because of the wrist injury. Per Rapoport, “Rodgers has at least 3 fractures, one of which is a more consequential break that can only happen with significant force.” There was no way Rodgers was playing this week without letting national media members know the gruesome details of his injury. Expect the Steelers to lean on their ground game versus a Buffalo defense that is among the league’s worst at defending the run. Rodgers is barely on the QB2 radar for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d500-d90e-a9da-df0fd0bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jalen McMillan (neck) “could begin practicing this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d505-d82c-a79a-f79569db0000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, McMillan received clearance to return to practice from spine specialist Dr. Robert Watkins. McMillan landed on his head during a preseason game and suffered a severe neck injury. The good news is that, for as scary as the injury was, it was not expected to end his season. He was placed on injured reserve and has been out ever since. The Bucs will open his practice window this week, giving them three weeks to officially activate him from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d505-d82c-a79a-f79569db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings EDGE Jonathan Greenard (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d509-d82c-a79a-f79dc1140000</link>
      <description>Vikings left tackle Christian Darrisaw remains a game-time decision. Greenard has missed the past two weeks with the shoulder issue. He was listed as questionable for Week 13 after getting in three limited practices. The veteran defender has two sacks and 19 total tackles this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d509-d82c-a79a-f79dc1140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports there is “cautious optimism” Tyler Warren (illness) will play in Week 13 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d52a-d90e-a9da-df2fc6b20000</link>
      <description>Per Pelissero, Warren is battling a stomach virus. He was added to the injury report over the weekend, being listed as questionable for today’s game. Players tend to play through illnesses, but the late addition puts Warren at risk of missing Week 13. For now, fantasy managers can likely plan on him playing. They should, however, have a contingency plan just in case Warren is a surprise inactive 90 minutes before kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d52a-d90e-a9da-df2fc6b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
