<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d77-d6e9-af9d-9ff78b460000</link>
      <description>Higbee was listed as a non-participant for the second straight day with a hip injury that first popped up last week. He played in Week 4, catching 2-of-5 targets for 25 yards after suffering the hip injury last Thursday. Higbee was active after missing last Friday’s practice, so this may be precautionary, but it is a short week for the Rams. Wednesday’s report will show if Higbee is ready to play Thursday against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d77-d6e9-af9d-9ff78b460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns QB Dillon Gabriel will start Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9fbf-d6e9-af9d-9fbf84280000</link>
      <description>After largely dodging questions about Joe Flacco as the Browns’ starter, head coach Kevin Stefanski was left with no choice but to bench the grizzled veteran after a miserable first four games of the regular season in which Flacco completed just 58 percent of his passes for two touchdowns and six interceptions. Flacco’s drop back success rate was lower than every quarterback but Cam Ward through Week 4. Enter Gabriel, who acquitted himself well in the preseason, completing 68 percent of his attempts for 262 yards, one touchdown, and one pick over two games. Gabriel’s 7.4 yards per attempt in the preseason was well above Flacco’s 5.1 YPA through four regular season games. It’s hard to imagine Gabriel, the 94th pick in the 2025 NFL Draft, being any worse than Flacco. He’ll likely be an upgrade for Cleveland pass catchers against a Minnesota defense running the league’s most complex and inscrutable blitz and coverage schemes. Flacco will serve as Gabriel’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9fbf-d6e9-af9d-9fbf84280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shedeur Sanders will remain the Browns’ No. 3 quarterback in Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9fd2-dca3-a9fb-bfdbc5290000</link>
      <description>Joe Flacco was benched for Dillion Gabriel ahead of Cleveland’s Week 5 game against the Vikings, and will serve as Grabiel’s backup for now. Sanders will remain as the emergency QB3, as he has for the first four weeks of the regular season. It’s uncertain whether Sanders would get a chance to start if Gabriel goes down with injury or struggles mightily in the coming weeks. Sanders can remain on waiver wires for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9fd2-dca3-a9fb-bfdbc5290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is considered “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a010-d95b-addb-e8568de50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport said Jackson, who suffered the hamstring injury in Week 4 against the Chiefs, will “try” to play in Week 5 against the Texans. That seems like a long shot unless Jackson can log at least a limited practice late in the week. The Baltimore Sun on Tuesday reported that Jackson is “likely” out for Sunday’s game. That would mean Cooper Rush would get the start against Houston. All of the Ravens skill position players would take a marked hit if Crush is under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a010-d95b-addb-e8568de50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OG Chandler Zavala (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a034-deb6-a7fd-f3ff0e950000</link>
      <description>Zavala will miss at least four games on IR after picking up the knee injury in Week 4 against the Patriots. It’s yet another blow to a Carolina offensive line graded by Pro Football Focus as the NFL’s 12th worst pass-blocking unit. Bryce Young could be under even more duress in the coming weeks with Zavala sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a034-deb6-a7fd-f3ff0e950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Jalen Coker (quad) is eligible for the active roster in Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a03c-dca3-a9fb-bdbd02550000</link>
      <description>Coker, according to head coach Dave Canales, is still considered week to week as he works his way back from a serious quad injury he sustained in late August, just after the team had committed to him as their full-time slot wideout. A fantasy folk hero of sorts due mostly to his last name, Coker last year had 32 catches for 478 yards and two touchdowns in Carolina. When Coker is able to return, he should instantly be the Panthers’ No. 2 receiver, though he should remain on 12-team league waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a03c-dca3-a9fb-bdbd02550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports’ Greg Auman reports Bucky Irving (ankle) was seen Wednesday with crutches and a walking boot.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a040-dca3-a9fb-bdd9cfd60000</link>
      <description>This report along with a Tuesday report that Irving is “gathering medical opinions” on the ankle/foot injury he sustained in Week 4 against the Eagles suggest a potential long-term absence for Tampa’s No. 1 back. Unless Irving is able to shed the boot and practice Thursday or Friday, Rachaad White will likely step into the team’s RB1 role in Week 5 against the Seahawks. White would be a top-20 fantasy option in that role thanks largely to his pass-game involvement. Sean Tucker would serve as the Bucs’ RB2 and could take goal line touches from White if Irving is sidelined. Tucker should be rostered in deeper formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a040-dca3-a9fb-bdd9cfd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) is “in question” for Week 5 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a057-dca3-a9fb-bddfeb270000</link>
      <description>Schefter added that the injury — sustained near the end of last Thursday’s loss to the Seahawks — “is not thought to be serious,” though it could limit him this week in practice and could cost him Week 5. Benson in Week 4 operated as the team’s lead back with James Conner (ankle) done for the season. He lost most pass-catching duties to Emari Demercado, however, who would slide in to Arizona’s RB1 role should Benson be sidelined this week. Demercado should be rostered in all leagues in case Benson sits. He would make for a solid flex option against a porous Tennessee defense allowing the seventh most rushing yards in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a057-dca3-a9fb-bddfeb270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bucky Irving’s foot sprain is not expected to be a long-term injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</link>
      <description>The sprain, per Schefter, is a “week to week” injury. It could keep Irving sidelined in Week 5 against Seattle after Tampa’s lead back was seen in a walking boot on Wednesday. Irving is reportedly seeking medical opinions this week. If he sits in Week 5, Rachaad White would serve as Tampa’s RB1 with Sean Tucker possibly taking a solid RB2 role behind White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
