<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 18:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared QB Sean Clifford, RB Samaje Perine, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DE Trey Hendrickson, and DE Cam Sample inactive for Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b192-d90e-a9da-bf9f29a70000</link>
      <description>Perine was listed as doubtful with an ankle injury, so this doesn’t come as a huge surprise, but it is now official. Without him in the lineup, Chase Brown should see the vast majority of the carries and also get an uptick in receiving work. He’s locked in as a top 10 option this week, even if the Bengals trail the Patriots for much of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b192-d90e-a9da-bf9f29a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (shoulder/wrist) is inactive for Green Bay’s Week 12 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b193-d413-ad9f-b5df4ae50000</link>
      <description>The rookie season continues to go south for Golden, who has not cleared 40 receiving yards in a game since Week 6. He’s droppable in re-draft leagues at this point. Active off the questionable line for the Packers are Dontayvion Wicks (calf), Savion Williams (foot), and Lukas Van Ness (foot) — Van Ness is making his first appearance since Week 6. Also inactive for Green Bay are: RB Josh Jacobs (knee), LB Quay Walker (neck), CB Nate Hobbs (knee), K Lucas Havrisik, LB Jamon Johnson and OL Donovan Jennings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b193-d413-ad9f-b5df4ae50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared WR Rashod Bateman, RB Rasheen Ali, CB Kenyon Martin, OG Ben Cleveland, OT Carson Vinson, DT Aeneas Peebles, and QB Cooper Rush inactive for Week 12 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b193-d90e-a9da-bf9fccd70000</link>
      <description>There are no players of note inactive for the Ravens, with all due respect to Bateman, who was ruled out before the weekend. The Ravens will be operating at full strength against a Jets team that will start Tyrod Taylor for the first time this season. DeAndre Hopkins, who ran the second-most routes of any Ravens receiver in Week 11, will take over in Bateman’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b193-d90e-a9da-bf9fccd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared WR/KR Efton Chism III, TE C.J. Dippre, DT Joshua Farmer, G Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito, and LB Jahlani Tavai inactive for Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b195-d90e-a9da-bf9fa6330000</link>
      <description>No huge surprises here; however, with Chism out for the game, the Patriots may turn to TreVeyon Henderson or Terrell Jennings to return kicks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b195-d90e-a9da-bf9fa6330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared LB T.J. Edwards, LB Noah Sewell, LT Theo Benedet, RB Travis Homer, DT Jonathan Ford, QB Case Keenum, WR Jahdae Walker for Chicago’s Week 12 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b199-d413-ad9f-b5dd1ee20000</link>
      <description>Benedet was questionable with a quad injury that he picked up in practice on Thursday. It may be wise to downgrade Chicago’s rushing attack slightly given how effective it became when Benedet took over at left tackle. Ozzy Trapilo is set to start in his stead. Edwards, Sewell and Homer were declared out on Friday from their various injuries. The other three are healthy scratches, with Keenum serving as the third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b199-d413-ad9f-b5dd1ee20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson is officially active for week 12 against the Bengals</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1a1-db57-afda-f7b370370000</link>
      <description>It was trending this way for much of the week, but Stevenson will officially return to the field on Sunday. Rookie TreVeyon Henderson has played well in Stevenson’s absence, but we should expect some form of a committee here. With the Patriots heavy favorites against a banged up Bengals team, it’s possible that they can ease Stevenson back in durinf his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1a1-db57-afda-f7b370370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jordan Love is playing through an AC joint sprain in his left shoulder.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d90e-a9da-bfaf9a370000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, the injury would have sidelined him for Week 12 if it had been to his right (throwing) shoulder. Love practiced in full this week despite the injury and was never at risk of missing today’s game. As was the case last year, expect the Packers to establish the run early and often until Love is back at full strength. That will mean plenty of Emanuel Wilson this week. Wilson is drawing the start in place of an injured Josh Jacobs. Love is sliding to the back of the QB2 ranks for Week 12, while Wilson is a strong RB2 candidate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d90e-a9da-bfaf9a370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Falcons could be “conservative” with playing Drake London (knee) in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d82c-a79a-b3be66fc0000</link>
      <description>It’s potentially bad new for London drafters who expected him back in Week 13 and beyond after head coach Raheem Morris said on Wednesday that he was hopeful the star wideout could come back after a one-week absence. Pelissero said London’s knee issue is considered “tricky” to manage. The Falcons could drop out of postseason contention if they lose to the Saints in Week 12, making it more likely the team would rest London and not rush him back into game action. Until his return, Darnell Mooney will function as the de facto WR1 for Atlanta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1aa-d82c-a79a-b3be66fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports “there is a good chance” that Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) is good to go for Week 13 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1c9-db57-afda-f7fb62ff0000</link>
      <description>Thomas is missing his third straight game because of the ankle injury today. He has been back at practice for two weeks but has never progressed beyond a limited session. It seems like he may need to get in a full practice before the team clears him for action. If that happens next week, BTJ will return for a WR2 fantasy outlook against a weak Tennessee defense. Jakobi Meyers will hold down the fort as the team’s top wideout for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b1c9-db57-afda-f7fb62ff0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
