<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 12:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts TE Tyler Warren (toe) was removed from the injury for Week 3 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-67d7-d93f-ad9d-7fd7fb100000</link>
      <description>Warren’s toe prevented him from getting in a full practice all week. The 23-year-old tight end missed practice Wednesday before finishing the week with two limited practice sessions. That Warren has been removed from the injury report is bullish for the rookie from Penn State and he should be starting in all formats against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-67d7-d93f-ad9d-7fd7fb100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) is expected to play in Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-67fe-dfde-a1bd-7fff990c0000</link>
      <description>Despite only getting in one limited practice this week, Egbuka is expected to be available for the Buccaneers according to Fowler. The 22-year-old receiver has been everything the Buccaneers could have hoped for with three touchdowns and 96 yards in his first two games. Egbuka is a WR2 going up against the Jets in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-67fe-dfde-a1bd-7fff990c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers TE Tucker Kraft (knee) is expected to play in Week 3 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6817-d6a5-adff-fed7a7b50000</link>
      <description>Kraft was added to the team’s injury report Thursday after suffering the injury during the training session. He would miss practice Friday before drawing a questionable tag, but it appears as if he’ll be available for the Packers against the Browns. Kraft has quickly developed into one of Jordan Love’s primary targets in an offense that typically spreads the ball around through the air, making his expected presence a big boost to the team’s offensive expectations in a difficult matchup in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6817-d6a5-adff-fed7a7b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears placed CB Jaylon Johnson (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6827-d93f-ad9d-7ae7d55f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson is likely to miss the remainder of the regular season after it was reported he requires surgery to repair a groin injury. The standout corner could return late in the season if the Bears are in contention. Tyrique Stevenson, Nick McCloud, and Nahshon Wright will be charged with locking down the cornerback positions in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6827-d93f-ad9d-7ae7d55f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots downgraded CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) to out in Week 3 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-688d-d1b3-a5dd-69fd03200000</link>
      <description>The young cornerback has yet to play in 2025 after suffering a hamstring injury in camp. He managed to practice all week as a limited participant but ultimately failed to do enough to play against the Steelers. Expect him to be active in Week 4 when the Patriots host the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-688d-d1b3-a5dd-69fd03200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6893-d93f-ad9d-7ad7575e0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw’s absence is a significant blow to a Broncos defense that has underperformed expectations through two weeks. He will now miss the next four games, at minimum, with a torn quad sustained this offseason. He aggravated the injury later in the offseason before missing the team’s first two games, and subsequently being placed on injured reserve. His Broncos debut could be pushed to the tail end of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6893-d93f-ad9d-7ad7575e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee) was added to the injury report Saturday as questionable for Week 3 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-689f-d6a5-adff-fedfd2f60000</link>
      <description>Late week additions to the injury report are never a good sign for a player’s availability, particularly a knee injury. The Cowboys are already down lockdown corner DaRon Bland, making a potential absence from Diggs a big deal against the Bears. The team elevated two cornerbacks, Zion Childress and Robert Rochell, from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-689f-d6a5-adff-fedfd2f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens ruled out TE Isaiah Likely (foot) for Week 3 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68a5-d6a5-adff-fee55d180000</link>
      <description>Likely has yet to play in 2025 while tending to a foot injury. Mark Andrews has done little with the added opportunity through two games, something fantasy managers will hope changes when the Ravens face a difficult opponent capable of pushing them on the scoreboard in the Lions. Likely’s next chance to take the field comes in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68a5-d6a5-adff-fee55d180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans placed NT T’Vondre Sweat (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68b0-d1b3-a5dd-69f17ac90000</link>
      <description>The Titans will now be without their big man against the run for the next four games, at minimum. Expect Shy Tuttle to fill in in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68b0-d1b3-a5dd-69f17ac90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks added WR Jaxon Smith-Njigba (illness) to injury report with questionable tag for Week 3 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68c3-d6a5-adff-fec7ef790000</link>
      <description>This is the first we’ve heard of an ailment for Seattle’s top pass-catcher, and while it doesn’t appear to place him in danger of missing the team’s Week 3 contest against the Saints, late-week additions to the injury report are never a good sign. Expect Smith-Njigba to suit up for the Seahawks, potentially at less than full strength physically.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-68c3-d6a5-adff-fec7ef790000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
