<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OL Kevin Zeitler (elbow) left Tennessee’s Week 2 game against the Rams and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe70da50000</link>
      <description>Blake Hance played in his stead. The Titans have now allowed 11 sacks in two games after emphasizing the offensive line this offseason. It was against two playoff teams from last year, but that sack pace has Cam Ward looking like someone to stream defenses against right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe70da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans told an in-house radio show that he would like to get Nick Chubb more touches.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e85-d294-a19b-eef5f7890000</link>
      <description>Chubb took 13 carries for 60 yards last week and seems primed to be a volume-heavy low-end RB2 or FLEX this week. He likely won’t play passing downs, so the Texans will need to be in good game scripts for Chubb to deliver. The Texans certainly seemed to like what they saw from Chubb in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e85-d294-a19b-eef5f7890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson “is likely to miss the rest of the regular season with a groin injury that will require surgery.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe7db770000</link>
      <description>Things felt like they were trending in this direction after previous reports that Johnson would be out indefinitely while the team explores whether or not the star corner will require surgery. With those questions now answered, Johnson is now slated to miss the rest of the season, but Schultz reports there’s “an outside chance he could return if Chicago is in contention.” That seems unlikely, however, as the Bears are 0-2 and looked like one of the worst defenses in the league even when Johnson was active. Johnson has been voted to the Pro Bowl in back-to-back seasons and was named a Second-Team All-Pro in 2023. If all goes well with his recovery, we would expect him to be ready in time for training camp next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4e81-dc44-a9d9-4fe7db770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jayden Daniels suffered a sprained knee in Week 2’s loss to the Packers and that his Week 3 status against the Raiders is in doubt.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea0-dc44-a9d9-4fe696240000</link>
      <description>Daniels underwent an MRI following Thursday’s loss to the Packers and met with a team physician on Monday. According to Rapoport, tests revealed the knee sprain Daniels suffered, which immediately puts his status for Week 3’s game against the Raiders up in the air. We’ll see how his week of practice goes, but if Daniels is unable to go, the Commanders would be in line to start Marcus Mariota against his former team at home. Mariota threw for 364-4-0 in three games for the Commanders last season but has not made a start for the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea0-dc44-a9d9-4fe696240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said Brian Thomas “had a wrist injury” going into Week 2 and speculated that it may have “played a part in some of this stuff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea2-dc44-a9d9-4fe6d4650000</link>
      <description>OK. Leaving aside the bit where Coen seemed to incriminate the organization for not following injury reporting protocol — Thomas didn’t show up on the injury report at any point in Week 2 — there’s a somewhat ominous tone to the idea that he and Thomas are “going to have a conversation here shortly.” It sounds like those of you on the Thomas train are not entirely out of the woods just yet. This will probably be hit multiple times over the next few days and is the sort of story that will eventually get sourced reporting, but it doesn’t sound like Coen is entirely happy with what he saw from Thomas on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea2-dc44-a9d9-4fe6d4650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OL Austin Corbett (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea7-d294-a19b-eef78ba80000</link>
      <description>Per Dave Canales, the Panthers will be placing Corbett on injured reserve and he is “leaving open the possibility” that Corbett could return this season. Losing both Corbett and Hunt is a big blow for Chuba Hubbard and the Panthers offense as a whole. Torn MCLs are not necessarily season-enders, and Corbett will be eligible to return in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea7-d294-a19b-eef78ba80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OG Robert Hunt (torn biceps) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea6-d294-a19b-eef68e550000</link>
      <description>Hunt didn’t seem optimistic about his injury following the Panthers’ Week 2 loss to the Cardinals. On Monday, the worst was confirmed, as an MRI revealed a torn left biceps for Hunt, who will now land on injured reserve and hope to make it back at some point in the season. Hunt made his first Pro Bowl with the Panthers last season and has become a staple along the offensive line. Backup guard Chandler Zavala replaced Hunt in Sunday’s contest and will likely draw the start in Hunt’s place for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ea6-d294-a19b-eef68e550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy suffered a sprained ankle in Week 2’s loss to the Falcons and is unlikely to play vs. the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eac-d86f-abdd-4fbdf4d30000</link>
      <description>O’Connell said McCarthy came into the facilities on Monday sore with an ankle sprain and added that the team doesn’t anticipate him playing in Week 3’s game against the Bengals. McCarthy struggled again in his second career start on Sunday night against the Falcons, throwing for 158 yards and two interceptions while also taking six sacks and losing one of his three fumbles on the night. O’Connell has already said the team is preparing Carson Wentz to start on Sunday, suggesting McCarthy missing this week is all but a lock. We’ll see if anything changes when the team’s first injury report is released, but for now, we would expect to see Wentz into center into a game that is now the battle between backup QBs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eac-d86f-abdd-4fbdf4d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) is unlikely to play against the Bengals in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ead-d294-a19b-eefd767c0000</link>
      <description>It’s full steam ahead for Jordan Mason as a locked-in volume starter this week, although there’s now a big (bigger?) question mark under center for the Vikings. The Bengals have been one of the best teams for runners to face over the past few years. Jones remains remarkably hard to keep healthy and will likely be questionable for Week 4 as well. Zavier Scott is the only other healthy back on the roster and figures to take on a role of some sort behind Mason in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ead-d294-a19b-eefd767c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said the team is preparing Carson Wentz to start Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eb2-d294-a19b-eef27ff30000</link>
      <description>Wentz signed with the Vikings in late August after opting out of the Sam Howell experiment following training camp. The former first-round pick will suit up for his fifth different team in five seasons when he lines up under center for the Vikings against the Bengals, and has thrown for just 281-2-1 over the last two seasons. Wentz has a chance to do the funniest thing here in taking over for McCarthy, who has visibly struggled in his first two games outside of one good quarter of football against the Bears. It will take more than one strong outing for Wentz to take McCarthy’s starting role, but an impressive performance on Sunday could lead to some requesting another look at him if he’s able to flourish in an O’Connell offense that several other quarterbacks have excelled in in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eb2-d294-a19b-eef27ff30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
