<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:02:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes believes the Jets could trade Breece Hall at the deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b5-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf2a60000</link>
      <description>In the assumption that the team is not competitive this year, Hughes believes the head of the Jets’ RB committee could be a trade candidate in the final year of his rookie deal. Hall put up an amazing Week 1 but has just 90 total yards in two games since. Hall would be an upgrade for several teams at running back, and would probably not carry a high cost given how much the Jets seem to like Braelon Allen. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87b5-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf2a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Week 4 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c2-d95b-addb-efc69f920000</link>
      <description>Despite the listing, we’d say it sounds more dire than that. Higbee appears to have suffered a hip injury in practice on Thursday, and did not practice at all on Friday. Colby Parkinson (shoulder) joins Higbee on the questionable line. Is it Terrance Ferguson time in LA? Or will Davis Allen catch a touchdown for the third time this season? We live in interesting Rams tight end depth chart times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c2-d95b-addb-efc69f920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (back) said he is “good to go” for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c9-d6e9-af9d-8fd9020a0000</link>
      <description>Engram began the week as a full practice participant. His back injury is evidently behind him. The Broncos’ matchup against the Bengals’ pushover defense theoretically puts Engram on the streaming radar, though his play in 2025 leaves a lot to be desired. He does not need to be started this week, but he is a viable option, based on the matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c9-d6e9-af9d-8fd9020a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) won’t play in Las Vegas’ Week 4 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-deb6-a7fd-d7df74010000</link>
      <description>Mayer’s absence may open up things for Brock Bowers to be used more as a traditional tight end instead of as a wideout — which is where he spent a lot of the first three weeks of the season. Maybe that can get Bowers going after a slow start. Mayer did not practice at any point this week and will enter Week 5 on the questionable line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-deb6-a7fd-d7df74010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-dca3-a9fb-bfdfb2750000</link>
      <description>Purdy kicked off the week with a pair of limited sessions. He promisingly practiced in full on Friday. Purdy typically threatens defenses with short scrambles, but that aspect of his game will likely be limited for some time. Purdy’s passing prowess, coupled with the 49ers’ brilliant play designs, keeps him on the QB2 radar nonetheless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87cf-dca3-a9fb-bfdfb2750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) is questionable to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c4-d6e9-af9d-8fd4921a0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall took the day off on Wednesday before practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday and Friday. Pearsall reportedly dealt with knee soreness after his eight-catch, 117-yard outing in Week 3. The second-year wide receiver leads all 49ers pass catchers with 281 receiving yards. The sum ranks third among all NFL wide receivers. Assuming Pearsall is good to go against the Jaguars on Sunday, he can be started as a low-end WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87c4-d6e9-af9d-8fd4921a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875c-d95b-addb-ef5ec8f80000</link>
      <description>Jennings was sidelined through the week’s first two practices before logging a limited session on Friday. He registered the same participation levels back in Week 2. He was active on game day and caught 5-of-9 targets for 89 yards and one touchdown. He was only dealing with the shoulder injury at that point but Jennings tends to play through ailments whenever possible. He is a WR3/FLEX if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875c-d95b-addb-ef5ec8f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee) is questionable for Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87e9-deb6-a7fd-d7fff4f80000</link>
      <description>49ers starting QB Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) has been cleared to play, so Jones has been put back into the No. 2 spot. He played admirably in his two starts, completing 53-of-80 passes for 563 yards, four touchdowns and one interception and rushing seven times for five yards despite aggravating a summer PCL sprain in Week 3. For fantasy managers in two-quarterback leagues with no one better to stash, he can be left on the bench this week to see how Purdy’s health holds up. For everyone else, he can be dropped. The 49ers also ruled out WR Jordan Watkins (calf) and DT CJ West (thumb). FB Kyle Juszczyk passed the NFL’s concussion protocol and will be active for Week 4 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87e9-deb6-a7fd-d7fff4f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 4 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87f2-dca3-a9fb-bffb85a00000</link>
      <description>Tuten was seen sporting a red non-contact jersey in practice again this week, but the Jaguars are just being smart with their spry rookie running back. The team continues to employ a three-player rotation in the backfield, hampering Tuten’s upside. In the two games since Jacksonville traded away Tank Bigsby, Tuten is averaging seven carries and 1.5 targets per game, which is enough to keep him in the FLEX spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87f2-dca3-a9fb-bffb85a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) is questionable for Week 4 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87fc-deb6-a7fd-d7ff9eed0000</link>
      <description>Brown was sidelined on Wednesday, but returned for limited practice sessions on Thursday and Friday. The 25-year-old seemingly has decent odds of suiting up, but he could be frequently subbed out for backup WR Parker Washington, who led the team with 11 targets last week. Brown is just a boom-bust FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87fc-deb6-a7fd-d7ff9eed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
