<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:03:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall reports Tyler Allgeier “will be seeking a contract in the neighborhood of three-years, $22 million” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fff-d042-afbc-ffff96b70000</link>
      <description>Kendall reported earlier this month that it would be “hard to imagine” Allgeier returning to the Falcons in 2026. With that kind of money, it’s easy to understand why. The former fifth-round back is seeking starting RB money, and should have plenty of suitors after impressing during his first four years in the league. Allgeier rushed 210 times for 1,035 yards and three touchdowns as a rookie before being replaced by Bijan Robinson in 2023. He’s averaged over 4.0 YPC just once in his last three seasons, but has forced a missed tackle on 21.7 percent of his carries over that span while also converting nine of his 22 carries inside the opponent’s five-yard line into scores. While he doesn’t offer much as a pass-catcher, Allgeier can help several teams in need of an early down back who can pick up short yards and punch the ball in down near the goal line. He should have plenty of suitors when free agency opens next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fff-d042-afbc-ffff96b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall says we should “expect Kyle Pitts to play this season on the franchise tag.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a00a-d629-a1bc-b01f7aee0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons officially placed the franchise tag on Pitts on Tuesday. While the two sides could still come to terms on a long-term deal to keep Pitts in Atlanta beyond next season, Kendall says “the vibe Atlanta is giving when it comes to Pitts” suggests a new deal is unlikely. Pitts caught 88 passes for 928 yards and five touchdowns last season, turning in what was arguably the best year of his five-year career. Still only 25 years old, it’s fair to assume the Falcons will want to keep Pitts under contract for years to come if he can replicate that success again next season. That said, with a new regime in place and head coach Kevin Stefanski still getting a sense of what he can do with his roster, it’s understandable if the team would prefer to see how Pitts performs in 2026 before making any long-term commitments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a00a-d629-a1bc-b01f7aee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Broncos placed a second-round tender on CB Ja’Quan McMillian.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a011-d629-a1bc-b01d03bc0000</link>
      <description>McMillian is a restricted free agent who has quickly turned into one of the team’s top defenders after making the roster as a UDFA in 2022. The Broncos’ decision to tender McMillian means he can negotiate with other teams in free agency, but the Broncos have the right of refusal to match any offer he receives. Should the Broncos match that offer, McMillian would remain with the team, however, if they let him walk, the Broncos would receive a second-round pick as compensation. McMillian has started 16 of the 51 games he’s appeared in for the Broncos, but has played on over 700 defensive snaps each of the last two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a011-d629-a1bc-b01d03bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced the league salary cap will increase to $301.2 million for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a018-d629-a1bc-b01d5de30000</link>
      <description>Each club will get an additional $22 million in spending money for this season as a result of the increase. This marks the first time in league history that the cap has gone beyond $300 million, and it is a massive increase from the $208.2 million the league hit in 2022 after cutting back on cap space due to COVID in 2020/2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a018-d629-a1bc-b01d5de30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports “if the Jets can’t sign Breece Hall by Tuesday they will use a tag.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a064-dbf6-abdd-ee75aa280000</link>
      <description>What kind of tag the Jets place on Hall remains up in the air. Regardless, it doesn’t sound like the veteran running back will be hitting the open market when free agency opens next month. Hall rushed for 243-1065-4 last season while adding another 36-350-1 through the air. Once tagged, the question shifts to whether or not Hall would be willing to play on the tag and/or sign a new deal with the Jets, or if he will try to force his way out of town via trade. There’s been some belief that Hall would like to move on from the team that has gone 22-46 since drafting him in 2022, so it will be interesting to see how things develop once he is tagged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a064-dbf6-abdd-ee75aa280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team is “not putting any time frame” on getting a new deal done with George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a074-d629-a1bc-b07d36ad0000</link>
      <description>Perhaps even more importantly, Jones added, “the most important thing is live in the present.” Inspirational words from the co-owner of a team who seemingly botched its last big-time negotiation with a superstar less than a year ago. Pickens was officially franchise tagged by the Cowboys on Friday and will earn just under $28 million on the tag if he is unable to secure a long-term deal. Jones said Pickens was “fired up” to learn he would be returning to the Cowboys for next season. We’ll see if he maintains that same enthusiasm if a long-term deal isn’t in place as training camp draws closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a074-d629-a1bc-b07d36ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos non-tendered RB Jaleel McLaughlin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07a-dbf6-abdd-ee7b96f50000</link>
      <description>It’ll make him a free agent. Entering his age-26 season, McLaughlin has averaged 4.8 yards per rush and caught 59-of-69 targets for 263 yards over three years in the league. McLaughlin is built like a third-down back and will likely resurface elsewhere to attempt to snag that role for a new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07a-dbf6-abdd-ee7b96f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans parted ways with QB coach Jerrod Johnson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07e-d89c-a1be-affffe360000</link>
      <description>Technically, the Texans let his contract expire. They’re reportedly elevating senior offensive assistant-pass game specialist Jerry Schuplinski — yet another John Carroll / Patriots legacy guy — to quarterbacks coach. It’s an uninspiring move considering Johnson has interviewed for several OC vacancies over the past few years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a07e-d89c-a1be-affffe360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports Anthony Richardson and the Vikings have “mutual interest” in a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a087-d042-afbc-fdd7a0780000</link>
      <description>It’s the first team we’ve seen linked to Richardson, though we’re not really sure what the Vikings would get out of adding a quarterback who has missed a lot of games and struggled to be accurate when he has been on the field to a room that already has a rookie-contract quarterback doing those things. We’ll see where this goes. It would not be surprising if Richardson surfaces as a backup option somewhere in 2026, as he seems locked out of the role in Indianapolis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a087-d042-afbc-fdd7a0780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes the Chiefs “loom as an interesting suitor” for Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker if he makes it to free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a08c-d89c-a1be-afdf89f20000</link>
      <description>Breer adds the Broncos and Texans as teams he’d “assume” would be interested in Walker coming off a Super Bowl MVP performance. With Breece Hall likely to be franchise or transition tagged if a deal isn’t worked out with the Jets, Walker appears set to be the best running back to hit the market. Seahawks GM John Schneider did not comment on the idea of franchise tagging Walker at his combine presser, while Adam Schefter called it “unlikely” earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a08c-d89c-a1be-afdf89f20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
