<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 12 times for 62 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills, adding seven receptions for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6004-dfde-a1bd-7e8d75900000</link>
      <description>Achane’s 12 carries and 62 yards on the ground were both new season highs even as rookie No. 2 Ollie Gordon finally got involved in a meaningful fashion. Up to 15 receptions over the past two weeks, Achane has been one of the Dolphins’ most effective players, but ceiling is proving hard to come by in this collapsing offense, while it’s never ideal when a running back’s floor involves catching at least five passes. This is going to be a rocky road, but Achane’s usage is still enough to keep him in the top 12-15 on a weekly basis. Managers just need to be prepared for the bottom to fall out every once in a while. That is probably unlikely for Week 4, where the ‘Fins will find themselves on 11 days rest for Monday Night Football against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6004-dfde-a1bd-7e8d75900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon rushed nine times for 38 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6008-d6a5-adff-f6cd57b00000</link>
      <description>Gordon was not targeted in the passing game as De’Von Achane soaked up nine looks. No matter, as the rookie’s nine handles were nearly double his combined total from Weeks 1 and 2. Gordon was looking mighty powerful when he got a head of steam, though it’s true that 16 of his 38 yards came on one carry. Featured over Achane in the red zone on the Dolphins’ opening drive, Gordon capped it off with a two-yard scoring plunge. This is the usage fantasy managers have been expecting all along, and it should be something of a necessity for a Dolphins team hurting for answers on offense. They need to get the run game ramped up, as there is only so much Achane can do between the tackles. Gordon remains an intriguing bench stash ahead of Week 4 vs. the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6008-d6a5-adff-f6cd57b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill caught 5-of-10 targets for 49 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600c-d93f-ad9d-7acf26210000</link>
      <description>Hill’s 10 targets were a new season high, though he’s now been held below 50 yards receiving in 2-of-3 contests. The touchdown was his first of 2025. It was a fourth quarter lollipop pass from Tua Tagovailoa. Hill could have had a sixth reception, but fell down on slippery “Highmark Stadium” turf. On the other hand, his first reception probably wasn’t actually a catch, but the Bills didn’t challenge. Hill still looks springy and fast, but Tagovailoa’s play has been dismal through the season’s first three contests. The Jets await for Monday Night Football in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600c-d93f-ad9d-7acf26210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 5-of-6 targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600f-d93f-ad9d-7acf9d0d0000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers will take Waddle’s second touchdown in as many weeks, though he’s now been held under 40 yards receiving in 2-of-3 appearances. Waddle has yet to command more than six targets in a game. Disappointing, especially since the Dolphins’ offense has become so horizontal. Coach Mike McDaniel and Tua Tagovailoa have a strikingly difficult time getting the ball to their No. 2 wideout despite his underneath skill-set. Struggling to rise above middling WR3 status, Waddle faces the Jets in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-600f-d93f-ad9d-7acf9d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 4-of-4 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6013-d93f-ad9d-7ad7add20000</link>
      <description>In theory this was a nice bounce-back effort after Shakir’s two-target Week 2, though he now has just six total looks since commanding nine in Week 1. The season opener, of course, was the only game where the Bills have found themselves in a shootout. They were surprisingly forced to match points with the Dolphins this evening, but both teams were grinding out slow, methodical drives. Shakir’s fourth quarter score, which proved to be the game-winner, was a 12-yard catch-and-run on a swing pass. With the Bills content to play safe, station-to-station football when not being challenged, Shakir isn’t looking like a particularly high-upside WR4 for Week 4 against the rebuilding Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6013-d93f-ad9d-7ad7add20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 3-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Bills’ Week 3 win over teh Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6019-d6a5-adff-f6ddb1ae0000</link>
      <description>Coleman also drew a 20-yard DPI on Buffalo’s opening possession. Nevertheless, with the Bills opting for safe, underneath football, Coleman was limited to three catches for the second time in five days. He is now sitting on 6/46 in two contests since his 8/112/1 Week 1 blowup. Week 1, of course, was the only time the Bills found themselves in a shootout. They were actually forced to match points with the Dolphins this evening, but both teams opted for grind-it-out football. That’s not a game you are typically going to win against Josh Allen. Coleman has a plus Week 4 matchup in the Saints, but it doesn’t exactly profile as a game where the Bills will open things up. Coleman is a low-floor WR4 for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6019-d6a5-adff-f6ddb1ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 5-of-6 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6021-d1b3-a5dd-6171e5430000</link>
      <description>Kincaid made a nifty, in-air adjustment on his 20-yard score in the first quarter. Both the catches and yards were new season highs, while the touchdown was Kincaid’s second in three games. Good stuff, though he’s yet to command more than six targets, and is averaging just a little over five. He was Josh Allen’s leading target commander and receiver this evening. That’s despite losing a second score to No. 3 tight end “Jackson Hawes.” Kincaid continues to incrementally increase his floor without ever really establishing a ceiling despite his high-powered offense. There’s just too much target competition, including at his own position. Kincaid will check into the TE9-12 range for Week 4 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6021-d1b3-a5dd-6171e5430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Palmer caught a five-yard pass in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6025-d6a5-adff-f6e5fddd0000</link>
      <description>Palmer’s fourth quarter reception ended up being his lone target. Palmer’s targets have now fallen from nine to three to one as the Bills have gone from the sugar high of their Week 1 Ravens shootout to more sober-minded affairs with the Jets and Dolphins. The Saints are a pushover Week 4 opponent, but that could just mean the Bills keep things bottled up again. Through three games in a Bills uniform, Palmer has not established a WR4 floor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6025-d6a5-adff-f6e5fddd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 4-of-6 targets for 27 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 loss to the Bills, adding a six-yard rush.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6028-d93f-ad9d-7aef828d0000</link>
      <description>A hyped 2024 Day 3 pick who ended up doing very little as a rookie, 24-year-old Washington has come out much stronger this season, quickly establishing himself as the Dolphins’ No. 3 receiver and No. 4 passing-game weapon. It’s just hard for that to mean much in a hard-capped offense with compilers Tyreek Hill, De’Von Achane and Jaylen Waddle all ahead of Washington in the pecking order. He’s an intriguing end-of-bench stash in Dynasty leagues, but would need injury ahead of him to make 2025 re-draft noise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6028-d93f-ad9d-7aef828d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Johnson rushed three times for 13 yards in the Bills’ Week 3 win over the Dolphins, adding an eight-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-602a-d93f-ad9d-7aefba4d0000</link>
      <description>With Ray Davis off to a poor start, Johnson was the Bills’ No. 2 running back this evening, out-touching Davis 4-0. Pro Football Focus charted Johnson with a 15-4 snaps advantage. Noteworthy for the Bills in “real life,” but still inconsequential in fantasy. Neither back is going to carve out standalone fantasy value behind James Cook, while a committee would form were Cook to go down with injury. This could also just be a one-week aberration. For now, Cook’s insurance backs can be ignored in re-draft leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-602a-d93f-ad9d-7aefba4d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
