<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Chuba Hubbard and Rico Dowdle will split the workload in the team’s backfield.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e89a-db72-a199-fadbc36d0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers, per Fowler, “are taking the approach that both players will get their touches regardless of who gets the first snap. Both fit the Panthers’ tough-minded, grind-it-out mold.” The Panthers “want to be a run-first team, and since it’s a long season, they will need both players.” The Panthers before Hubbard’s calf injury would give him two drives, them Dowdle would get one. Those “rotations will inevitably change due to Dowdle’s star turn,” Fowlers said. It’ll be tough for the Panthers to sideline Dowdle after he racked up 473 total yards over his two starts. It wouldn’t be a shock if Dowdle functioned as the team’s nominal lead back for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e89a-db72-a199-fadbc36d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Reynolds (undisclosed) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3fb7d0000</link>
      <description>We’re not quite sure what injury Reynolds is dealing with ahead of the Jets’ Week 7 game against the Panthers. He was set to operate as the team’s WR1 over the next couple weeks with Garrett Wilson (knee) sidelined. If he’s unable to practice later in the week, the Jets could enter Week 7 with Arian Smith as their top wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8a2-dd4c-afb9-efe3fb7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Puka Nacua (ankle) is a “long shot” to play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b2-dd4c-afb9-eff3cb120000</link>
      <description>Nacua in Week 6 against the Ravens “avoided major damage to his ankle ... but the people I’ve talked to believe he is a long shot Sunday against Jacksonville.” The team, according to Fowlers, is considering holding him out this week due to his physical playing style that might lead to further injury. Davante Adams, who leads the NFL in air yards, will be a top-10 fantasy option if Nacua is sidelined. The Rams could lean on Kyren Williams in a more run-heavy game plan if Nacua is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b2-dd4c-afb9-eff3cb120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowlers reports NFL teams “believe the Raiders are open to trading wide receiver Jakobi Meyers but are not actively trying to move him.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b7-d94a-a79d-e9bf29eb0000</link>
      <description>Meyers requested a trade back in August and has since played in all six of the team’s regular season game as a secondary and tertiary option for Geno Smith. “The sense is the Raiders would prefer to play out the season before making major determinations about the roster,” Fowlers said. Meyers hasn’t eclipsed 60 receiving yards since Week 3 and doesn’t have more than four receptions in any of his past three outings. Unless he’s dealt in the coming weeks, Meyers will be nothing more than a desperation flex play in a massively run-heavy Vegas offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8b7-d94a-a79d-e9bf29eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8bb-d94a-a79d-e9bfe51a0000</link>
      <description>It’s yet to be determined whether McLaurin will be a full or limited practice participant ahead of the Commanders’ Week 7 game against the Cowboys. With his status very much up in the air, fantasy managers should have backup plans in case they have to go one more week with McLaurin sidelined. If he suits up, he’ll be a solid option against the league’s worst coverage unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8bb-d94a-a79d-e9bfe51a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals designated DT Walter Nolen (calf) to return from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8d1-db72-a199-fadb0da20000</link>
      <description>Nolen suffered the calf injury in training camp and has been on the PUP list ever since. He now has 21 days to be activated from the PUP list and will practice for the first time today. The No. 16 overall pick was a force to be reckoned with against both the run and pass in college. He was expected to help revamp Arizona’s front seven, but the injury has prevented him from doing so thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8d1-db72-a199-fadb0da20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants restructured Paulson Adebo’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8dd-db72-a199-fadf6cdc0000</link>
      <description>The team also reworked Jevon Holland’s contract, creating over $4.8 million in cap space, according to ESPN’s Field Yates. Simple restructures are common practice in the NFL and teams typically have the option to do so whenever they want to. The moves could be intended to clear up space for a trade, but NFL trades are rarer than fans want to admit. It’s more likely that they were done to create some freedom for minor free agent moves as the season progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8dd-db72-a199-fadf6cdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said CeeDee Lamb (ankle) is expected to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8e8-dd4c-afb9-efe9d2f20000</link>
      <description>Lamb has missed the past three weeks with a high-ankle sprain. Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said earlier this week that Lamb could play on Sunday. Even a limited practice to start the week is a good sign for his Week 7 availability. If practice goes well this week, Lamb will return to the WR1 ranks for a good matchup versus the Commanders. George Pickens, on the other hand, will tumble back into the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8e8-dd4c-afb9-efe9d2f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) is expected to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8f6-db72-a199-faffb7f80000</link>
      <description>Right guard Tyler Booker is also expected to practice. With CeeDee Lamb looking likely to return this week as well, the Cowboys are getting healthy just as they head into a crucial NFC East matchup against the Commanders. Turpin isn’t on the fantasy radar, but he does bring a level of dynamism to the Cowboys’ offense and special teams that can’t be replicated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8f6-db72-a199-faffb7f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed WR Noah Brown (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fb-db72-a199-fafba4660000</link>
      <description>Brown will miss at least four games now. If Terry McLaurin is back this week, Chris Moore will operate as the team’s No. 3 receiver behind him and Deebo Samuel. He could hold onto the No. 2 role if McLaurin remains sidelined. Moore caught three passes for 46 yards and a score in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e8fb-db72-a199-fafba4660000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
