<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner has cleared the league’s concussion protocol and is expected to play in Week 10 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-59d9-d673-a39e-fdd9f0e70000</link>
      <description>Head coach Shane Steichen told reporters earlier in the week that the plan was for Gardner to suit up this week if he cleared concussion protocol in time. He should be in the starting lineup on Sunday. Gardner will be tasked with covering Drake London in his Colts debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-59d9-d673-a39e-fdd9f0e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a18-d673-a39e-fe993ae80000</link>
      <description>Irving hasn’t played since Week 4 and a Week 9 bye was not enough to get him back on the practice field. Two DNPs to open the week all but guarantee another missed game for the young back. Rachaad White will likely draw the start again this week. Facing a New England defense that is giving up the fewest rushing yards in the league to opposing running backs, White will be a low-end RB2 at best for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a18-d673-a39e-fe993ae80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a1b-d1e7-a1fa-5afbf2540000</link>
      <description>It looks like Godwin will miss another week while dealing with the fibula issue. At this point, it’s unclear when he will return to action. With Mike Evans also sidelined, Emeka Egbuka will continue to go unchallenged as the Bucs’ WR1. Sterlin Shepard and Tez Johnson will round out the team’s starting wide receiver trio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a1b-d1e7-a1fa-5afbf2540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden (shoulder) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a3e-d45b-affe-5fbe7be60000</link>
      <description>The news comes directly from head coach Matt LaFleur, who called Golden day to day earlier this week. Golden left Week 9 with a shoulder injury and did not return. It doesn’t seem like a long-term issue, but fantasy managers will still want to keep an eye on the Packers’ injury report throughout the week. His absence would free up a few more deep shots for Christian Watson. Golden had been struggling to make an impact before the shoulder injury. Fantasy managers should look elsewhere for a FLEX play, even if he is cleared from the injury report by the end of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a3e-d45b-affe-5fbe7be60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (calf) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a47-d673-a39e-fed768dc0000</link>
      <description>It’s Wicks’ first practice since suffering the calf injury in Week 7. He may still need to get up to a full session before being cleared to return, but it’s a step in the right direction. With Christian Watson back in the mix, Wicks will be relegated to the No. 4 receiver role once healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a47-d673-a39e-fed768dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5612-d1e7-a1fa-5efa997f0000</link>
      <description>Both Sewell and LT Taylor Decker were sidelined by shoulder injuries on Wednesday while LG Christian Mahogany (knee) was placed on injured reserve. Sewell is not guaranteed to suit up this weekend, but his return is a great sign. Decker has been managing the issue for some time, and should be considered likely to play in Week 10 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5612-d1e7-a1fa-5efa997f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB James Cook (ankle/foot) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-566b-d1e7-a1fa-5eebf9670000</link>
      <description>We expect Cook to be listed as a limited participant today, but his return puts him on track to play in Week 10 against the Dolphins, whose run defense is among the league’s worst. Backup RBs Ray Davis and Ty Johnson are still worth stashing on benches, just in case Cook’s injury flares up, but at this time, neither one appears to be a locked-in FLEX-worthy starter this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-566b-d1e7-a1fa-5eebf9670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a5d-d673-a39e-fedd7dac0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Last week, Bills slot CB Taron Johnson was sidelined by a groin injury of his own. Benford nursed a groin injury earlier this season, but has not missed any games. Bills EDGE Joey Bosa is playing through a wrist issue and is visibly bothered by it in-game. He should be on the field in Week 10, unless he is downgraded tomorrow, though. The Bills face the Dolphins this weekend. Bills DT DaQuan Jones (calf) also resumed practicing today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a5d-d673-a39e-fedd7dac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (glute) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a6f-d45b-affe-5fff8fc00000</link>
      <description>The Colts sometimes give injured players a full day off rather than allowing them to practice in a limited capacity, with the goal of practicing in full soon thereafter. We do not yet know Pittman’s practice participation level, but it would be unsurprising to see him labeled as a full-go today. Pittman is no stranger to playing through injury. His return to practice today puts him on track to play in Week 10 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a6f-d45b-affe-5fff8fc00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
