<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5971-dfde-a1bd-5ffd4de90000</link>
      <description>Harmon’s return to practice could not have come at a better time. Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin already said CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) is “questionable at best” to play in Week 3 against the Patriots. He was unable to practice, as was S DeShon Elliott (knee). Steelers LB Alex Highsmith (ankle) is likely due for an extended absence, though he was able to avoid being placed on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5971-dfde-a1bd-5ffd4de90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kirk (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-597b-d1b3-a5dd-597b8ca00000</link>
      <description>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said earlier this week that he expects Kirk to suit up in Week 3. A limited practice is a step in the right direction for the veteran wideout. Kirk’s return can’t come soon enough for a Houston offense that has been held below 20 points in both games to open the year. Houston has been playing veterans Justin Watson and Xavier Hutchinson over the pair of rookies they selected on Day Two of the draft. Kirk should slot into a starting role right away. Fantasy managers should check their waiver wires for him as a potential WR4 versus the Jags this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-597b-d1b3-a5dd-597b8ca00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (wrist) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5982-d93f-ad9d-5bc781910000</link>
      <description>Jags coach Liam Coen told reporters after the team’s Week 2 that Thomas had a wrist injury going into Sunday’s game. If only there were some sort of report on which teams were required to list the injuries of their players. Alas. A full practice today suggests the issue is truly minor, though Thomas uncharacteristically gave up on a few plays in Week 2, possibly in an effort to avoid big hits that could further injure his wrist. Despite the poor showing, there’s no reason to fade BTJ in fantasy after he saw 12 targets last week. He remains a WR1, though a frustrating one to say the least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5982-d93f-ad9d-5bc781910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Bhayshul Tuten (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5989-d1b3-a5dd-59f994450000</link>
      <description>Tuten went from three touches in Week 1 to 10 in Week 2. He ran through contact with power and showed off his feed on a shifty receiving touchdown in the red zone. The increased workload, combined with a few big hits, likely left him sore coming out of Sunday’s game, but a limited session to open the week is usually not a big deal. Barring a setback, the rookie should be able to play in Week 3 versus Houston. He makes for an intriguing FLEX play as the Jags’ change-of-pace back, even if his touch ceiling is limited by Travis Etienne.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5989-d1b3-a5dd-59f994450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce Jr. (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-598d-dfde-a1bd-5f8da1000000</link>
      <description>The first-round rookie has already made his presence known with two QB hits, eight pressures, and half-credit on a sack. Losing him this early in the year would be a frustrating blow for a young Atlanta defense. With cornerback A.J. Terrell also banged up, the Falcons could be without multiple starters on defense heading into Week 3 versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-598d-dfde-a1bd-5f8da1000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5991-dfde-a1bd-5f9dfa5e0000</link>
      <description>Mooney missed most of training camp and Week 1 with the shoulder injury. He was back for Week 2 but will likely be a mainstay of the Falcons’ injury report as the team attempts to keep him fresh. Mooney ran every single route for the Falcons last week and earned four targets. He only turned that into two catches for 20 yards, but better days should be ahead for the veteran receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5991-dfde-a1bd-5f9dfa5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5995-dfde-a1bd-5f9d31ec0000</link>
      <description>This isn’t Darrisaw’s first full session of the year and The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reported earlier this week that there’s “no guarantee” the star left tackle is back for Week 3. Darrisaw is still working his way back from the torn ACL he suffered in 2024 and the Vikings are not going to take any risks by rushing him back into the lineup. Vikings Center Ryan Kelly missed Wednesday’s practice with a concussion and is unlikely to suit up this week. Carson Wentz is set to play behind a greatly diminished offensive line for his first start in Purple and Gold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5995-dfde-a1bd-5f9d31ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5998-d1b3-a5dd-59f999a10000</link>
      <description>Stewart went down in the Bengals’ Week 2 win over the Jags and was spotted on crutches after the game. NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reported earlier this week that Stewart is considered week-to-week. A DNP on Wednesday all but guarantees he will miss the Bengals’ Week 3 date with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5998-d1b3-a5dd-59f999a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC 2 Houston’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans WR Justin Watson will be “sidelined indefinitely” with an Achilles injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-599d-d1b3-a5dd-59fd15310000</link>
      <description>Per Wilson, it’s not a torn Achilles for Watson and he is expected to return at some point this season. Watson was placed on injured reserve, meaning he will miss at least four weeks. Watson was playing ahead of rookies Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins. With Christian Kirk expected to return this week, the rookies may have to wait a little longer to see the field more often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-599d-d1b3-a5dd-59fd15310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks released CB Shaquill Griffin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59aa-d1b3-a5dd-59fb4ced0000</link>
      <description>Griffin was immediately signed to the Seahawks’ practice squad. The team signed wide receiver Cody White from their practice squad to the active roster in a corresponding move. They made the opposite pair of moves last week. This is what peak roster management looks like.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59aa-d1b3-a5dd-59fb4ced0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
