<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3598-d332-a1fd-b7be92c40000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said yesterday that he was hopeful Porter Jr. will play this week. The team called up cornerback James Pierre from the practice squad this morning, indicating at least a slight level of concern on JPJ’s availability. Thursday’s practice report will be more telling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3598-d332-a1fd-b7be92c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35bf-dbe3-a9bb-35fffcfd0000</link>
      <description>Engram left the Broncos’ Week 1 game against the Titans with a calf injury. He caught three passes for 21 yards before exiting in the fourth quarter. Getting in a limited practice to start the week is a good sign his injury is not major, but fantasy managers should monitor his status throughout the week. Engram is a low-end TE1 for Week 2 against the Colts if he plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35bf-dbe3-a9bb-35fffcfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35c5-dbe3-a9bb-35d7433a0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw is dealing with a quad issue that has lingered from the summer. The 28-year-old is no stranger to leg injuries, having suffered an Achilles rupture in the Super Bowl back in February 2024. He has yet to practice this season, indicating he is not close to returning for Week 2. Also sidelined on Wednesday was DE John Franklin-Myers (knee). Franklin-Myers did play in Week 1 but now begins Week 2 by missing the first practice of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35c5-dbe3-a9bb-35d7433a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (concussion) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5864c0000</link>
      <description>Bobo missed Week 1 against the 49ers with a concussion he suffered in the Seahawks’ final preseason game. He starts out this week as a full participant, indicating he is on track to return in Week 2 against the Steelers. Bobo will compete for WR3 snaps upon his return. Meanwhile, WR Dareke Young (hamstring) was a limited participant on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5864c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35e0-dbe3-a9bb-35f3bccf0000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon played all of the Seahawks’ Week 1 game against the 49ers, though he did seem to hurt his knee after a Josh Jobe interception. The 24-year-old starts out Week 2 missing Wednesday’s practice, putting his status for Sunday against the Steelers in question. Derion Kendrick is next man up in the secondary if Witherspoon does miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35e0-dbe3-a9bb-35f3bccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ee-d332-a1fd-b7fe51480000</link>
      <description>Nwosu’s full participation is great news for the Seahawks’ pass rush. The 28-year-old opened training camp on the PUP list after undergoing a cleanup procedure on his knee in the offseason. He was limited all of last week in practice and missed Week 1 against the 49ers. Nwosu now starts Week 2 with a full participation and is headed towards making his 2025 debut against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ee-d332-a1fd-b7fe51480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE Josh Oliver (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35f7-dbe3-a9bb-35f7add10000</link>
      <description>Oliver popped up on the injury report with an ankle injury and did not practice on Wednesday. Center Ryan Kelly (toe) also did not practice on Wednesday. Both players are key to the Vikings’ blocking schemes and Jordan Mason and Aaron Jones may have less rushing lanes against the Falcons if neither can play Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35f7-dbe3-a9bb-35f7add10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Jonathan Taylor (neck) is absent from the Week 2 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ff-dbe3-a9bb-35ff843b0000</link>
      <description>Taylor seemed to tweak his neck towards the end of the Colts’ Week 1 victory over the Dolphins. He was a workhorse in that game, totaling 21 touches before exiting in the third quarter. The Colts were up big, which may have contributed towards Taylor not returning to the game. The neck looks to be a minor issue as Taylor is not listed on the Colts’ injury report to start out Week 2. Fantasy managers can fire him up as an RB1 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ff-dbe3-a9bb-35ff843b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Kalel Mullings (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3603-dbe3-a9bb-3653ca1f0000</link>
      <description>Mullings suffered the injury in the Titans’ Week 1 loss to the Broncos, playing three special teams snaps before exiting. Julius Chestnut is the only remaining backup to Tony Pollard, with Tyjae Spears (ankle) still sidelined. Expect Pollard to take on a workhorse role for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3603-dbe3-a9bb-3653ca1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-360d-db7b-a5dd-b60d25130000</link>
      <description>Latham aggravated a preseason hip injury in Week 1 against the Broncos. The 22-year-old tackle played 45 snaps before exiting, with Oli Udoh replacing him at right tackle. Latham’s status for Week 2 and the foreseeable future remains in doubt. Also not practicing for the Titans Wednesday were S Quandre Diggs (hand) and DT T’Vondre Sweat (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-360d-db7b-a5dd-b60d25130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
