<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:04:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) is not on Las Vegas’ final injury report for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</link>
      <description>With Brock Bowers out, Mayer will serve as the clear No. 1 tight end against Tennessee. It’s not exactly a smash spot, but Mayer went 4/38 against the Patriots in the opener and has had some TE1-worthy games in the past. Mayer probably is more of a TE2 until we see a ceiling game again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe0-def2-abdb-dfe14a760000</link>
      <description>Lawrence and LB Ernest Jones (shoulder) are good to go. The Seahawks’ defense will be without LB Derick Hall (oblique). S Julian Love (hamstring), CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and CB Riq Woolen (concussion) are listed as doubtful to play in Week 6 against the Jaguars. All three defensive backs were limited on Friday. Jaguars WRs Brian Thomas Jr. and Travis Hunter have high ceilings in this one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe0-def2-abdb-dfe14a760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars DE Travon Walker (wrist) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cffd-d94a-a79d-cffdbab80000</link>
      <description>Walker sat out in Week 5 after undergoing surgery to correct the wrist injury he suffered in Week 5. Despite the absence, Walker ranks and/or ties for second on the team in quarterback pressures (14) and sacks (two). His return is a huge help to a Jaguars defense that is tasked with containing a Seahawks passing attack averaging an NFL-high 9.2 yards per passing attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cffd-d94a-a79d-cffdbab80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out QB Brock Purdy (toe) for Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d008-dd4c-afb9-f7c9626d0000</link>
      <description>Purdy remained sidelined all week, as did WR Ricky Pearsall, who is dealing with a PCL sprain in his knee. Just eight days ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that Purdy is considered week-to-week, so the starting quarterback’s absence is hardly surprising. Hopefully, Purdy can remain setback-free and return for the 49ers’ Week 7 game against the Falcons, though that outcome should not be viewed as guaranteed. The 49ers also ruled out WR Jordan Watkins (calf), DL Kevin Givens (pectoral) and EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (knee/hamstring).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d008-dd4c-afb9-f7c9626d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cff3-def2-abdb-dff39e360000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported last week that Pearsall “could be back” for Week 6. Unfortunately, Pearsall failed to practice even once in a limited capacity this week. Despite missing the 49ers’ Week 5 game against the Rams, Pearsall ranks 16th, positionally, with 327 receiving yards. Hopefully, he can return for next week’s game against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cff3-def2-abdb-dff39e360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee/oblique) is questionable to play in Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4e-def2-abdb-df6f7a8c0000</link>
      <description>Jones remained limited through all three practices this week and was able to participate in throwing drills on Friday. With starting QB Brock Purdy already ruled out and Jones able to practice, the 49ers’ No. 2 quarterback is in line to start, pending good health on Sunday. Jones has two QB1 finishes and one QB2 finish in three games played this season. He deserves to be treated as a borderline QB1/2 against the Buccaneers’ pass-funnel defense this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cf4e-def2-abdb-df6f7a8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) is questionable to play in Week 6 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d012-db72-a199-fa5b10d00000</link>
      <description>Jennings took the day off on Wednesday before practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday and Friday. Fantasy managers can expect him to play on Sunday against the Buccaneers’ pass-funnel defense, though it will be worth monitoring the news for any updates on him. If active, Jennings can be started as a borderline WR2/3, operating as the 49ers’ No. 1 wide receiver with Ricky Pearsall (knee) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d012-db72-a199-fa5b10d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin is “expected” to be week-to-week, “depending on how he progresses,” after suffering a new fibula injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d058-d94a-a79d-d95d00c40000</link>
      <description>Godwin missed the first three weeks of the 2025 season after dislocating his ankle and fracturing his fibula in Week 7, 2024. This week, he appeared on Wednesday’s injury report with a fibula injury, prompting speculation that he had suffered a re-injury. However, per the Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Godwin has injured his fibula in an entirely different location, though it may be on the same, previously injured lower leg. Stroud notes that “there are no plans for him to go on injured reserve at this time,” but his use of “expected” and “plans” is hardly reassuring. The Buccaneers are on bye in Week 9, so an injured reserve placement would render him ineligible to return until Week 11. One can only guess as to when Godwin will return, but allowing him to rest and rehab the injury through the Week 9 bye seems reasonable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d058-d94a-a79d-d95d00c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed DE K.J. Henry, formerly of the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d078-def2-abdb-dd79cd930000</link>
      <description>Henry last took regular season snaps as a member of the Cowboys in 2024, totaling two quarterback pressures and one sack. He joins the Steelers’ practice squad after spending last week on the Eagles’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d078-def2-abdb-dd79cd930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Ja’Marr Chase (illness) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d07d-d94a-a79d-d97d6b9c0000</link>
      <description>The illness caused Chase to leave practice early, during walkthroughs this morning, but sources say he will be on the field for Joe Flacco’s first game as a Cincinnati Bengal. Chase should be treated as an elite WR1 this week, hopefully, with vastly improved quarterback play. The superstar wide receiver caught 6-of-9 targets for 110 yards and two touchdowns en route to the overall WR1 finish last week after frustratingly finishing as the half-PPR WR36 and WR57 in Weeks 3 and 4, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d07d-d94a-a79d-d97d6b9c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
