<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 2-of-5 targets for 19 yards in the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bda-d45b-affe-7fde97bc0000</link>
      <description>Allen set the Chargers’ franchise record for most receptions with his two-catch night, tying longtime great tight end Antonio Gates in the third quarter before breaking the record on a pop-pass on the team’s final possession. He is also the only player in NFL history to catch more than 400 passes from multiple quarterbacks. Allen’s fantasy stock has trended townward in recent weeks as his snap rates have taken a hit, something easily overshadowed by his record-setting night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bda-d45b-affe-7fde97bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 20-of-33 passes for 220 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ 25-10, Week 10 win over the Steelers, adding 19 yards on five carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c0a-d1e7-a1fa-7eea16170000</link>
      <description>Herbert managed a mistake-free game as the defense dominated by holding the Steelers to just 221 yards of total offense. The two teams played to a 5-3 game until the final play of the first half, when Herbert found second-year receiver Ladd McConkey for his only passing score of the evening. Most impressive for the franchise quarterback was his ability to shake off unrelenting pressure from the Steelers. He would get both ankles taped in the third quarter following a scramble, something that has become a common sight considering Herbert has taken more hits than any quarterback in the league this season and is now playing without both starting offensive tackles. The Chargers improve to 7-3 and just one game behind the division-leading Broncos as we hit the home stretch of the 2025 regular season. Up next for the Chargers is a road matchup with the pass-funnel Jaguars in Week 11, where Herbert likely returns to QB1 status in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c0a-d1e7-a1fa-7eea16170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal rushed 25 times for 95 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers, adding 13 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c10-d45b-affe-7d963b670000</link>
      <description>Vidal mostly found the sledding difficult against a stout Pittsburgh front, eventually grinding out 95 yards on 25 carries in the lopsided victory. The first half played to a true defensive struggle as the two teams traded defensive blows. It wasn’t until a last-minute touchdown by Ladd McConkey at the end of the first half allowed the Chargers to control the game environment, after which Vidal was fed increased volume as the Los Angeles defense held the Steelers to a lone field goal until under three minutes remaining. Vidal remains the unquestioned lead back in the absence of Omarion Hampton, the latter of whom got in his first practice Friday since hitting injured reserve following Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c10-d45b-affe-7d963b670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 4-of-6 targets for 107 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c25-d45b-affe-7db716120000</link>
      <description>The two teams played to a 5-3, defensive struggle in the first half until quarterback Justin Herbert found McConkey streaking open up the middle of the field with 13 seconds to play in the first half to break the game open. The standout second-year receiver would add a 58-yard reception after the break to send him over the 100-yard threshold for only the second time this season. The fantasy returns have been a far cry from his breakout rookie campaign, but McConkey continues to operate as the team’s top pass-catcher for one of the most pass-heavy units in the league. That trend appears likely to continue as the Chargers turn their focus to the pass-funnel Jaguars in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c25-d45b-affe-7db716120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 5-of-10 targets for 42 yards in the Chargers’ Week 10 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c29-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb2e0c0000</link>
      <description>Johnston has now been held to 53 yards or fewer in each of the previous five games after a torrid start to the season in which he caught four touchdowns and went over 70 yards in each of his first four starts. Whether the added target competition from rookie tight end Oronde Gadsden is causal factor for the reduced production remains to be seen, although Gadsden did depart Week 10 with a knee injury. Johnston and the Chargers get the pass-funnel Jaguars in Week 10, where he could return to WR2 status, pending the status of Gadsden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c29-d1e7-a1fa-7eeb2e0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 16-of-31 passes for 161 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Steelers’ 25-10, Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee776f0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was far from sharp in this one, sailing his first interception over the head of alpha wide receiver DK Metcalf in addition to committing a fumble that would lead to a first half safety for the Los Angeles defense. His second interception was a deflection off the hands of Calvin Austin, so we’ll give him a pass on that one, but the theme of the game was inaccuracy and indecision for the veteran signal caller. The Chargers held the Steelers to only 221 yards of total offense as Rodgers failed to get anything going on offense, playing over 57 minutes of football before the team’s only touchdown of the game. Kicker Chris Boswell connected on a 59-yard field goal on the team’s second possession but missed another from 45 yards in the second quarter. Rodgers nearly doubled up on his interception total for the season, now sitting at five through nine games. The Steelers fall to 5-4, now just one game ahead of the surging Ravens, ahead of a divisional matchup with the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c2c-d1e7-a1fa-7eee776f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 14 times for 70 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers, adding 21 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c32-d713-ad9e-6c760db00000</link>
      <description>Warren accounted for 91 of the 221 yards of total offense from the Steelers as they struggled to move the football throughout against the Chargers. Even so, the team trailed only 5-3 until the last minute of the first half when Ladd McConkey broke the game open with a touchdown from 15 yards out. Warren also handily led the backfield, ceding only two carries to rookie Kaleb Johnson on back-to-back plays in the third quarter and three targets to Kenneth Gainwell, keeping him entrenched as an RB2 ahead of a plus matchup with the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c32-d713-ad9e-6c760db00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roman Wilson caught 2-of-3 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c34-d673-a39e-ecb5f3bb0000</link>
      <description>Wilson also led the team in receiving with a paltry 35 yards, highlighting the struggles of the Pittsburgh offense in the loss. The team managed just 221 yards of total offense while scoring a lone field goal until under three minutes remaining in the fourth quarter when Wilson willed his way into the end zone on a slant. Wilson remains off the fantasy radar even with the team in dire need of secondary production behind alpha receiver DK Metcalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c34-d673-a39e-ecb5f3bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-7 targets for 35 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Aaron Rodgers narrowly missed Metcalf for what would have been an easy touchdown on the team’s second possession, which was one of many overthrows by Rodgers on the evening. Another such overthrow resulted in a Los Angeles interception in the second quarter. Metcalf continues to be hamstrung by a low-volume pass offense, leaving his fantasy value lacking in any game he’s held out of the end zone. He gets a matchup boost in Week 11 when the Steelers take on the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c36-d673-a39e-ecb7ef760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught all three targets for 33 yards in the Steelers’ Week 10 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</link>
      <description>The “Muth” chants from the well-traveled Pittsburgh fans weren’t enough to return any semblance of fantasy value for the veteran tight end on a night the offense managed only 221 yards of total offense on the road. Freiermuth remains a touchdown-dependent dart throw in fantasy circles ahead of a plus matchup against the Bengals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6c39-d673-a39e-ecb9f5610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
