<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 04:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaydon Blue rushed four times for seven yards in the Cowboys’ Week 5 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b703-dca3-a9fb-bf9bddbe0000</link>
      <description>Blue played well behind Javonte Williams in his pro debut. The rookie fifth-rounder saw just four of the Cowboys’ 24 rush attempts on the day, with his longest gain coming on a six-yard carry. Fantasy managers stashing Blue can continue to do so while Miles Sanders (ankle) remains sidelined, but they shouldn’t expect much from him in Week 6 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b703-dca3-a9fb-bf9bddbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 4-of-5 targets for 98 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 5 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b704-deb6-a7fd-f7dfec630000</link>
      <description>Harrison was clicking with Kyler Murray early on, catching three of his four total receptions on the first two drives of the game. He caught a sky ball in double coverage for a 43-yard gain, landing just shy of the goal line on the team’s first possession. After that, he was hardly heard from again as the Cardinals offense turned anemic. Fantasy managers will be hoping for big plays or a score from Harrison for good fantasy output. He is a high-end WR3 against the Colts for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b704-deb6-a7fd-f7dfec630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Tolbert failed to catch his lone target in the Cowboys’ Week 5 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b706-d6e9-af9d-bf96ba2e0000</link>
      <description>Tolbert was a non-factor in this one. The early PFF data credits Tolbert with 46 offensive snaps to Ryan Flournoy’s 36, but it was Flournoy who tied for the team-high nine targets in Sunday’s win, while Tolbert was an afterthought. Tolbert is sitting on a 10-101-0 line on 19 targets through the first five weeks. Fantasy managers can’t depend on him in Week 6 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b706-d6e9-af9d-bf96ba2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught his lone target for a 12-yard touchdown in the Lions’ Week 5 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-d95b-addb-ff4f3b140000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa’s touchdown came in the fourth quarter. With the Bengals getting off the mat to pull within 11 points, the Lions led another touchdown drive. TeSlaa finished it off catching a 12-yard pass from Jared Goff. It’s just his third career catch in five games and first that necessitated him using both hands. It’ll take an injury to another Lions pass catcher for TeSlaa to make fantasy starting lineups this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-d95b-addb-ff4f3b140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Davis rushed once for five yards in the Jets’ Week 5 loss to the Cowboys, adding four receptions for 28 additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-d6e9-af9d-bf99d3770000</link>
      <description>Davis did most of his damage through the air in Sunday’s loss. The second-year back consistently picked up chunk gains on his four receptions, but his light work in the rushing game won’t do much to excite fantasy managers heading into Week 6 against the Broncos. Davis remains an interesting stash as the next man in line behind Breece Hall, but we’ll need to see more consistent touches before putting him in our fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-d6e9-af9d-bf99d3770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey McBride caught 5-of-7 targets for 41 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 5 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-dca3-a9fb-bf99646c0000</link>
      <description>McBride continued to be Kyler Murray’s target between the sticks, leading the team with 7 total targets. He totaled just 41 yards and is still suffering from lack of touchdowns. McBride has an elite floor from his usage and will be in the TE1 range for Week 6 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b709-dca3-a9fb-bf99646c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Antonio Gibson (knee) limped off the field in the second quarter of Week 5 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b719-dca3-a9fb-bf9928bd0000</link>
      <description>Gibson was hit low on a kickoff return in the second quarter and remained down on the field as the two teams scrambled to gain possession of his fumble. He was not carted off and there was no immediate update passed by the broadcast team, but the area of the leg he was grabbing is typically indicative of ligament stress in the knee. It would be shocking if he returned to the game in Week 5. Gibson took six carries for 21 yards and caught his lone target for five yards prior to departing, with the increase in workload induced by yet another lost fumble by Rhamondre Stevenson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b719-dca3-a9fb-bf9928bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 5 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b71c-d95b-addb-ff5ef5bd0000</link>
      <description>Wilson continues to be involved as the Cardinals’ No. 2 wide receiver. However, the offense’s inconsistencies make that role low value for fantasy purposes. It was technically a season-high in yards for Wilson, but that just shows the low ceiling he has for fantasy purposes. Wilson should be off fantasy radars for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b71c-d95b-addb-ff5ef5bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 22-of-30 passes for 273 yards in the Patriots’ 23-20, Week 5 win over the Bills, adding 12 yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b71e-deb6-a7fd-f7dfd5970000</link>
      <description>Even though the box scores appear lacking from a fantasy perspective, this was Maye’s best game as a professional. Maye escaped unrelenting pressure from an aggressive Bills defense throughout the night as he led the Patriots to the upset win over the last remaining undefeated team in the league, throwing just one incompletion in the second half. He leaned on his top target, Stefon Diggs, by peppering the veteran wide receiver with 12 targets on his way to his second consecutive 100-yard performance. The highlight of Maye’s night came on the team’s final possession when he held off an advancing defender in the backfield to not only avoid a sack, but complete a pass to Diggs to kickstart their drive. Fantasy managers have to be pleased with the breakout performance, knowing full well the touchdowns are likely to follow if he keeps playing like he did against the Bills. Up next for the 3-2 Patriots are the Saints on the road in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b71e-deb6-a7fd-f7dfd5970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed seven times for 14 yards and two touchdowns in the Patriots’ Week 5 win over the Bills, adding 13 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b796-d95b-addb-ffd6fc800000</link>
      <description>Stevenson fumbled early in the first quarter, his league-leading 10th fumble since the start of the 2024 season. The ball security issues paved the way for Antonio Gibson to serve as the lead back for the next 15 minutes of play until he suffered a knee injury on a kick return in the second quarter, after which Stevenson rotated in with rookie TreVeyon Henderson. Even after losing his third fumble in two games, Stevenson handled the bulk of the work in the green zone, resulting in his two scores on the ground. Head coach Mike Vrabel continues to feed Stevenson a longer rope but the ball is sure to find its way into other hands if the fumbling issues persist much longer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b796-d95b-addb-ffd6fc800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
