<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants named OLB coach Charlie Bullen as interim DC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b63b-d82c-a79a-b7bfce6c0000</link>
      <description>Bullen, 41, will call the plays on the defensive side of the ball for the Giants for the rest of the season. Boasting 12 years of NFL coaching experience, Bullen got his start with the Dolphins as a defensive assistant in 2012, and rose through the ranks in Miami before taking a job with the Cardinals as their assistant linebackers coach in 2019. Bullen has never held a role as a defensive coordinator and will now have five games to show his chops for a team in need of help at defensive play-calling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b63b-d82c-a79a-b7bfce6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Elliott missed his only field goal attempt and made all three of his extra point attempts in the Eagles’ Week 12 loss against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b655-d90e-a9da-bf5f69190000</link>
      <description>Elliott narrowly missed on a 52-yard attempt in the second half as the Eagles choked away a big lead to the Cowboys. He’s now missed three of his 14 field goal tries on the season. The Eagles’ red zone aggressiveness and use of the tush push near the goal line makes Elliott a dicey weekly bet for fantasy purposes. Elliott has one or zero field goal attempts in eight games this season. He should remain on waiver wires in Week 13 against Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b655-d90e-a9da-bf5f69190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Saints will host free agent K Justin Tucker for a tryout this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b68f-d413-ad9f-b7df8b2c0000</link>
      <description>Tucker’s 10-game suspension for violating the league’s personal conduct policy due to his involvement in sexually inappropriate behavior was lifted two weeks ago. Now, the 36-year-old kicker will have a chance to try out for the Saints, who are looking for a potential upgrade over Blake Grupe after his two missed field goals in Week 12’s loss to the Falcons. Tucker had his worst season as a pro in 2024, converting on a career-low 73.3 percent of his field goal attempts while going 11-for-19 from 40-plus yards. Among other participants in the tryout will be Cade York, who last kicked for the Commanders in 2024, going 0-for-2 on his attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b68f-d413-ad9f-b7df8b2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots LG Jared Wilson suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12’s win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b69e-d90e-a9da-bf9fe9860000</link>
      <description>Rapoport reports the Patriots hope Wilson’s recovery time “is on the shorter side” of a 4-6 week recovery window, but the team will be without the rookie for the next few weeks. Wilson is one of two Patriots rookies to suffer multi-week injuries in Sunday’s win, as left tackle Will Campbell is feared to have suffered a torn MCL in the same game. The Patriots will have some work to do to figure out their offensive line entering Week 13 against the Giants, but backup Caedan Wallace figures to be first in line to replace Wilson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b69e-d90e-a9da-bf9fe9860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said the team will open Darren Waller’s (pec) 21-day return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6a4-d90e-a9da-bfafcabc0000</link>
      <description>Waller has appeared in just four games for the Dolphins this season, but the veteran receiver caught 10 passes for 117 yards and four touchdowns in those games, and was quickly developing into a key player for the offense. The Dolphins will have 21 days to either activate Waller or rule him out for the season. With matchups against the Saints and Jets on tap, Waller’s return could come at just the right time as the Dolphins hope to make a postseason push over the final month of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6a4-d90e-a9da-bfafcabc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chiefs RG Trey Smith “is dealing with both high- and low-ankle sprains.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc41720000</link>
      <description>The sprain is too low to be high, but too high to be low. According to Rapoport, Smith “is expected to miss some time,” which would include Thursday’s game against the Cowboys. The fifth-year guard has played in all 11 games for the Chiefs this season, earning a PFF grade of 71.4 on 577 snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc41720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said he hopes Tutu Atwell (hamstring) is “ready to roll” for Week 13 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6d7-d82c-a79a-b7d798470000</link>
      <description>This came just moments after McVay announced that the Rams will open Atwell’s 21-day practice window this week. Atwell was placed on injured reserve after attempting to play through his hamstring injury in Week 8, but it sounds like the team doesn’t expect him to need to miss more than the four-game minimum before returning. Atwell has caught just four passes for 164 yards and one touchdown this season and can be left on waivers for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6d7-d82c-a79a-b7d798470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “there was no fracture and no structural damage” to Baker Mayfield’s shoulder after Week 12’s loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6e9-d82c-a79a-b7fd39cb0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Todd Bowles said after the game that the team believed Mayfield suffered a shoulder sprain. That remains the case, but an MRI will confirm the full extent of Mayfield’s injury. According to Schefter, a source familiar with the situation told him the team is “not ruling out” Mayfield just yet for Week 13’s game against the Cardinals, but that still depends on what the MRI reveals. If Mayfield is unable to go against the Cards, the Buccaneers would turn to Teddy Bridgewater, who threw for 62 yards on 15 attempts in relief of Mayfield in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6e9-d82c-a79a-b7fd39cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons CB Billy Bowman suffered a torn Achilles last week and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6f2-d90e-a9da-bfff299b0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Raheem Morris said last week of Bowman’s injury that it was “not good.” He was right. The fourth-round rookie who has played on 300 snaps for the defense this season now sees his rookie campaign come to an end thanks to the devastating injury. Bowman played 232 of his snaps from the slot this season and earned a PFF coverage grade of 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6f2-d90e-a9da-bfff299b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (toe/shoulder) will practice all week ahead of Week 13’s game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6fe-d413-ad9f-b7ff9c4d0000</link>
      <description>Bowles said that if Irving is fine after Friday’s practice, he will be slated to play on Sunday against the Cardinals. This was the belief dating back to last Friday when Bowles said the team was eyeing a Week 13 return for Irving after ruling him out against the Rams. Irving is sitting on a 71-237-0 rushing line through four games this season and was averaging 22.5 touches per game over that span. While he’s expected to step back into his starting role, it’s hard to predict what his touch totals could look like after the string of success Sean Tucker has had in his absence. Regardless of what his role may look like, Irving still figures to lead the Bucs’ backfield by a wide margin, putting him in the RB1/RB2 mix if he’s activated this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6fe-d413-ad9f-b7ff9c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
