<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson had two rushes for three yards in the Browns’ Week 3 preseason game against the Rams, adding one catch for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9fe-d332-a1fd-dffe712c0000</link>
      <description>Sampson started the game with the Browns’ first-team offense following a Friday report from ESPN that the rookie would “push” veteran RB Jerome Ford for touches out of the backfield early in the regular season. Sampson had a nice catch against the Rams, shedding two tacklers to pick up a few extra yards. Sampson appears to have a shot at the RB1 role in the Cleveland backfield, though Ford will likely figure in until the coaching staff has total confidence in the rookie. Quinshon Judkins, meanwhile, has not participated in training camp and has yet to sign his rookie deal. Judkins is likely weeks away from getting up to speed. Look for Sampson, who had nearly 1,500 rushing yards and 22 rushing scores last year at Tennessee, to play an outsized role in the Cleveland offense in Week 1 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d9fe-d332-a1fd-dffe712c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright is “week to week” with a left leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb497c0000</link>
      <description>The “week to week” tag is via coach Mike McDaniel. Wright’s injury has been unclear, but the Miami Herald reported he had a compression sleeve on his left leg for Saturday’s preseason finale. Wright, of course, did not dress for that one. Sixth-round rookie Ollie Gordon did and had an impressive night. It’s been a rough August for Wright, who seemed to be at risk of losing work to replacement-level veteran Alexander Mattison before the vet suffered a serious neck injury. It would appear he might now actually be in some danger of Gordon coming for the No. 2 spot behind De’Von Achane. Fantasy managers need to follow this one closely between now and Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb497c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon had eight rushes for 43 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 3 preseason game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb8b250000</link>
      <description>Gordon ends the preseason averaging almost five yards per carry, logging a few impressive runs along the way and possibly carving out a spot in the Miami backfield. Gordon has been an efficient producer this preseason while Jaylen Wright has struggled mightily as a rusher and as a pass catcher. Wright is deal with a leg injury that has been described as “week to week.” De’Von Achane, meanwhile, has a calf injury that could keep him sidelined until Week 1. Head coach Mike McDaniel said the team would be cautious with Achane leading up to the season opener. Gordon, a hyper-productive college back who had 1,721 rushing yards and 21 touchdowns at Oklahoma State in 2023, should be drafted in most 12-team fantasy leagues in case Achane and Wright continue struggling through injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-da10-de13-afdc-dedb8b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said Brian Robinson will be the team’s No. 2 running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc2a-db7b-a5dd-fc2efa0b0000</link>
      <description>After missing several weeks with a shoulder injury and apparently falling out of favor with the Niners’ coaching staff, Isaac Guerendo will enter the season as the team’s RB3 behind Christian McCaffrey and Robinson, who was acquired on Friday in exchange for draft compensation. “We brought him here to be our (No.) 2 back,” Shanahan said of Robinson, who last year in Washington had 799 rushing yards and eight touchdowns as the Commanders’ lead back. “I’ve always been a big fan of Brian. Loved him coming out college... We were pumped that he was available and pumped that we were able to get him.” That’s as much confirmation as fantasy managers are going to need in understanding the San Francisco backfield pecking order. Robinson should be drafted in all fantasy formats in case McCaffrey misses time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc2a-db7b-a5dd-fc2efa0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers GM Joe Hortiz said RB Najee Harris “could play” in Week 1 vs. Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc53-dbe3-a9bb-fc5307630000</link>
      <description>Harris has yet to do anything meaningful on the practice field aside from “running off to the side,” making this report stand out from the rest considering the stark shift in sentiment. Week 1 marks 10 weeks since the July 4 incident that injured Harris’ eye and realistically provides enough time to heal, but that doesn’t change the lack of practice for the veteran running back on a new team. It is prudent to continue to view Harris with a rather wide range of outcomes as far as early-season involvement is concerned, with everything from PUP to IR to being active in Week 1 still firmly on the table. Harris has yet to miss a regular season game in his four-year NFL career, something that could influence his expectations in two weeks time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc53-dbe3-a9bb-fc5307630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings traded QB Sam Howell to the Eagles for a 2026 fifth-round pick and 2027 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc59-dbe3-a9bb-fc5be9320000</link>
      <description>The Eagles also get a 2026 sixth-round in addition to Howell, who brings a veteran presence to compete with Tanner McKee behind Jalen Hurts. The trade likely seals the fate of Dorian Thompson-Robinson and provides the runway for rookie sixth-round quarterback Kyle McCord to be kept on the Vikings’ practice squad, should he clear waivers. It also wouldn’t be a surprise to see the Vikings sign Carson Wentz in the coming hours after the veteran worked out for the team Saturday. Another aspect of this trade is the addition of a late-round pick, which the Vikings could use to add wide receiver help for the start of the season considering Jordan Addison’s suspension and injuries to Justin Jefferson and Jalen Nailor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc59-dbe3-a9bb-fc5be9320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB Carson Wentz.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc7d-de13-afdc-deffb7ec0000</link>
      <description>Wentz completed a workout for the Vikings Saturday and quickly signed with the team Sunday. The Vikings dealt former backup Sam Howell to the Eagles in a corresponding move. Wentz offers a considerable upgrade to Howell behind starter J.J. McCarthy and also has a play style that more closely aligns with that of McCarthy, providing an easier transition should the Vikings be hit by the dreaded quarterback injury bug at any point in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc7d-de13-afdc-deffb7ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released WR Samori Toure.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc86-de13-afdc-decf4f8c0000</link>
      <description>The former Packer joined the Bears this offseason but ultimately missed the cut amidst a massive overhaul of key offensive pieces this offseason. The team invested heavily in this year’s draft to improve their pass-catching options, rendering Toure expendable in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc86-de13-afdc-decf4f8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Jaydon Blue suffered a low ankle sprain Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc98-d332-a1fd-debeaeae0000</link>
      <description>Blue was removed from the team’s final preseason game with a low extremity injury, which has now been ruled a low ankle sprain. The team relayed that he could still be ready for Week 1 to fight for carries with Javonte Williams and Miles Sanders. Blue’s uncertainty for the start of the regular season could influence personnel decisions as roster cuts loom, potentially leading to the retention of either Phil Mafah or Deuce Vaughn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc98-d332-a1fd-debeaeae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers waived S Shilo Sanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc9c-dbe3-a9bb-fcdfdcdc0000</link>
      <description>Sanders will now head to waivers, where he can be claimed by teams in need of safety play. There are multiple teams in need of positional help currently but there is no guarantee he will land on his feet, which would then make him available to be added to the Buccaneers’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc9c-dbe3-a9bb-fcdfdcdc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
