<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremely Fowler reports one candidate for the Raiders’ head coaching vacancy predicted, “it’s probably (Kubiak’s) job to lose.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0ac7-dead-af9e-6ec71cfb0000</link>
      <description>Per Fowler, the Raiders are interviewing Klint Kubiak this weekend and will then make their final decision for their head coaching vacancy. Vegas has spent its top two picks in each of the past two drafts on offensive players. They are also about to spend the No. 1 overall pick on Indiana quarterback Fernando Mendoza. The team is built around offensive cornerstones and Kubiak is one of the hottest offensive-minded head coaching candidates on the market. Barring a last-second twist, all signs point to Kubiak getting this job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0ac7-dead-af9e-6ec71cfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers will interview Raiders DC Patrick Graham for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0aea-dfd7-a5dc-0febb7f10000</link>
      <description>Graham is currently on his way to Pittsburgh. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that “the expectation in some league circles” is that Graham will get the gig “if all goes well.” He previously interviewed for the Dolphins head-coaching vacancy and has been linked to the Commanders’ defensive coordinator vacancy as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0aea-dfd7-a5dc-0febb7f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills QB Josh Allen confirmed that he underwent surgery to repair a broken bone in his foot on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0afc-dfd7-a5dc-0fff3aab0000</link>
      <description>Allen revealed that he aggravated an “older injury” against the Browns in Week 16. It was a fracture in his fifth metatarsal. To correct the issue, doctors “went in, took it out and cleaned it up.” Yuck. Allen adds that he would “figure out” a way to play if the Bills had a game this week, and he will be ready to participate in organized team activities in May.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0afc-dfd7-a5dc-0fff3aab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Saints QB coach Scott Tolzien for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0afd-d355-a5bd-8ffd8fb50001</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler notes that Tolzien was on the Packers’ roster, as a quarterback, under current Steelers head coach Mike McCarthy. McCarthy also hired Tolzien as an offensive assistant with the Cowboys in 2020 and promoted him to quarterbacks coach in 2023, where he served for two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0afd-d355-a5bd-8ffd8fb50001</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens head coach Jesse Minter will call defensive plays</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b19-dead-af9e-6f9f81300000</link>
      <description>This makes sense. Minter was hired, in part, for his defensive prowess, having served as a long-time Jim Harbaugh understudy. The Ravens’ defensive coordinator has not yet been hired. Learning under Minter without having play-calling responsibilities could be appealing for some.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b19-dead-af9e-6f9f81300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) said he is “feeling good” and “does not anticipate” undergoing surgery this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b20-dfd7-a5dc-0f6377790000</link>
      <description>Kincaid confirmed that he played through the 2025 season with a torn PCL, which he initially injured in 2024. Per Kincaid, he “continued to tweak it in different situations” this season. The fact that he plans to avoid surgery is somewhat surprising after spending a year rehabbing the torn ligament unsuccessfully. Hopefully things work out better this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b20-dfd7-a5dc-0f6377790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles interviewed former Buccaneers OC Josh Grizzard for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b2d-dfd7-a5dc-0f6fdb560000</link>
      <description>Grizzard met with the Eagles in-person on Wednesday, having advanced to the second round of interviews for their offensive coordinator vacancy. NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports that Grizzard is “viewed as a legitimate candidate for the job.” He was fired by the Buccaneers earlier this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b2d-dfd7-a5dc-0f6fdb560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants will visit with Colts OC Jim Bob Cooter to discuss their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b3e-d042-afbc-7ffe40fd0000</link>
      <description>Cooter has also been linked to the Eagles this offseason and has interviewed with them twice. As a non-playcaller behind Shane Steichen in Indianapolis, it’s natural that he’d accept a lateral move that allows him to call plays. It’s also possible this is a leverage interview to try to draw an offer from Philadelphia, though that would just be speculation on our part.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b3e-d042-afbc-7ffe40fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills general manager Brandon Beane said he expects to pick up TE Dalton Kincaid’s fifth-year option.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b40-d355-a5bd-8f54f9e20000</link>
      <description>Specifically, Beane said he does not “see any reason why we wouldn’t pick that up,” adding that the Bills’ mission is to help Kincaid stay healthy. We expect them to follow through, but this falls short of a firm commitment. Kincaid has been plagued by injuries during his three years in the NFL and told reporters earlier today that he does not plan to undergo surgery to correct the PCL tear in his knee, instead opting for more rehab. He initially suffered the injury in 2024 and “continued to tweak it in different situations” this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b40-d355-a5bd-8f54f9e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Ben Baby reports Bengals RB Chase Brown is “in talks” with the Bengals regarding an extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b41-dfd7-a5dc-0f6300820000</link>
      <description>Brown had an uneven fantasy season as he was disastrous pre-Joe Flacco and the Bengals simply couldn’t get the ground game going, but came on strong in the second half of the season and wound up with a 69/437/5 receiving line. Entering his age-26 season and the final year of his rookie contract, an extension would seem to make sense given the Bengals don’t exactly have anyone waiting in the wings. 2025 sixth-rounder Tahj Brooks is the closest thing Cincinnati has to a prospect at the position, and he only managed 47 offensive snaps in his rookie season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b41-dfd7-a5dc-0f6300820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
