<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54b2-d654-a19b-d4f2a4650000</link>
      <description>Oliver hurt his ankle in practice last week and missed the Bills’ Week 2 victory over the Jets. Given reports last week that this may be a multi-week injury, it is unlikely Oliver will be ready to play the Dolphins on a short week for a Thursday game. Also sidelined Tuesday was LB Matt Milano (pectoral), who suffered the injury against the Jets. The likelihood of him suiting up for Thursday is also low and the Bills will turn to alternatives in their front seven against the Dolphins with Oliver and Milano both likely out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54b2-d654-a19b-d4f2a4650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54bd-d654-a19b-d4fd3da50000</link>
      <description>Waddle was not listed on Monday’s estimated practice report but showed up as limited on Tuesday. He suffered the shoulder injury in Week 1 and was limited throughout last week before playing in the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots. On a short week, it is likely Waddle is being limited in practice again heading into a Thursday showdown against the Bills. Expect the banged-up Waddle to play through injury again as a fantasy WR3 in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-54bd-d654-a19b-d4fd3da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed LB Ja’Whaun Bentley to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5505-d654-a19b-d565e1ca0000</link>
      <description>The Steelers added Bentley to the practice squad after a visit on Tuesday. Bentley spent each of the previous seven seasons with the Patriots, starting 68-of-83 games and tallying 509 combined tackles, 10.5 sacks, and 21 tackles for loss over that time. The veteran tore his pectoral muscle last season, limiting him to two games. Bentley was released by the Pats in March and the Steelers now take a flier on him as he re-joins former teammate Jabrill Peppers in Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5505-d654-a19b-d565e1ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers said the Steelers could get Jaylen Warren more involved in the team’s passing offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-57c9-d606-a5db-5fd900570000</link>
      <description>Warren in Week 2 against the Seahawks erupted for 86 yards on four receptions, thanks mostly to an incredible 65-yard catch and run in which he broke four tackles. Rodgers, for one, was impressed. “Jaylen is a great player,” Rodgers said after the team’s loss to Seattle. “That was an awesome catch and run. He brings a lot to the table. We might have to keep giving him more opportunities in the pass game, because every time he touches it, something good happens.” Kenneth Gainwell continues to be involved in the Steelers backfield, running 35 routes to 25 for Warren over two weeks. Rodgers, meanwhile, is checking down quite a bit, averaging a meager 5.7 air yards per attempt. The Athletic’s Mike DeFabo said “if Warren is going to continue to maximize his chances, especially in the passing game, the Steelers might reconsider that tactic.” Warren will be a top-15 fantasy option this week against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-57c9-d606-a5db-5fd900570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) is out for Week 3 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-57ef-d606-a5db-5fff73660000</link>
      <description>Oliver, who sustained an ankle injury last week against the Jets, wasn’t able to practice this week and will sit for Thursday night’s divisional showdown against Miami. The Bills’ rush defense — allowing the seventh highest success rate this season — could be somewhat vulnerable without Oliver in the lineup. It could be good news for De’Von Achane, the centerpiece of the Miami offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-57ef-d606-a5db-5fff73660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pec) is out for Week 3 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5819-dfa0-a9bb-db9f0b2f0000</link>
      <description>Buffalo’s defense will be shorthanded against the Dolphins on Thursday night. DT Ed Oliver will also be sidelined with an ankle injury he suffered in Week 2. The Bills’ defensive injuries could make things slightly less bleak for the Dolphins offense in Week 3, especially De’Von Achane, who leads the Miami backfield with 29 touches over two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5819-dfa0-a9bb-db9f0b2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chargers LB Khalil Mack (elbow) “is expected to be back in a few weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-581d-d654-a19b-d87db3070000</link>
      <description>Mack appeared to suffer a serious arm injury during Monday night’s win over the Raiders, and after evaluation, he should be able to avoid surgery and return to the LA lineup in October. It’s great news for a Chargers defense that has allowed the third lowest success rate to opposing offenses through two weeks, generating consistent pressure on enemy quarterbacks. Mack has one sack and two QB hits over the season’s first two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-581d-d654-a19b-d87db3070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said CB A.J. Terrell (hamstring) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5846-dfde-a1bd-5ecf331f0000</link>
      <description>“We’ll see how it goes,” Morris said of Terrell’s practice participation this week ahead of Atlanta’s Week 3 game against the Panthers. “Obviously those hamstrings are tricky.” Terrell sustained the hamstring injury on Sunday against the Vikings. Terrell’s absence could be a boon for Bryce Young, Tetairoa McMillan, and the rest of the Panthers wideouts. the Falcons have allowed an average of just ten receiver catches per week through Week 2, one of the league’s lowest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5846-dfde-a1bd-5ecf331f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (concussion) is out for Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-587a-d93f-ad9d-5aff701a0000</link>
      <description>Fields was ruled out Wednesday, which could mean he’ll be iffy for Week 4. The Jets will turn to 36-year-old journeyman QB Tyrod Taylor against a tough Bucs defense. Taylor last week completed seven of 11 attempts for 56 yards and a touchdown against Buffalo after Fields left the game with a brain injury. He’ll be a downgrade for Garrett Wilson, who profiles as a WR3 in 12-team leagues this week. Look for the Jets to be even more run heavy than usual against Tampa. Taylor’s rushing production could make him viable in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-587a-d93f-ad9d-5aff701a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said QB Jayden Daniels (knee) won’t practice until Friday at the earliest.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5890-d93f-ad9d-5ad7c20b0000</link>
      <description>Quinn added Daniels had a good rehab session on Wednesday but would not practice. There’s almost no chance Daniels will suit up for Week 3 against the Raiders after sustaining a knee sprain last week in a loss to the Packers. That means Marcus Mariota will get the starting nod against Vegas. Mariota will be a marked downgrade for Terry McLaurin, Zach Ertz, and Deebo Samuel. Last year in a Week 7 start against Carolina, Mariota threw just 23 passes while rushing 11 times for 34 yards. The Commanders were 7 percent below their expected pass rate that day. Mariota will be usable in superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5890-d93f-ad9d-5ad7c20b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
