<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions listed TE Brock Wright (neck) as DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd1-d6c4-abfb-dfd3484e0000</link>
      <description>Wright missed Week 12’s game against the Packers with a neck injury and is on the wrong side of being active for Thursday night’s game against the Cowboys. It’s only an estimated practice report, so we’ll see if things change between now and Wednesday, but if Wright is unable to go, the Lions would be down their third-string tight end as they look to keep their postseason hopes alive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd1-d6c4-abfb-dfd3484e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Trey Lance will get first-team practice reps in goal-line scenarios this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe5-db57-afda-dff7d44c0000</link>
      <description>Justin Herbert’s hand injury, which he is getting surgery for today, hampered him enough that the Chargers didn’t have him take any snaps under center. It’s possible that Lance handles some goal-line work for the Chargers this week even if Herbert starts the game, cutting into Herbert’s fantasy ceiling. We’d be a little surprised if such a scenario comes to pass, but the fact that the Chargers are openly admitting they’re doing due diligence on it says plenty on its own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe5-db57-afda-dff7d44c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR George Pickens (calf/knee) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe9-d82c-a79a-fbfdb24b0000</link>
      <description>Pickens played under this designation on Thanksgiving, showing no ill effects with a 13-target, 88-yard day. He should be a confident start in Week 14 against a Lions secondary that made Jordan Love come alive. We’d be extremely surprised if he didn’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbe9-d82c-a79a-fbfdb24b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said the team will not open Kyler Murray’s (foot) 21-day return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</link>
      <description>Kedon Slovis will get at least one more game as Jacoby Brissett’s backup. Murray hasn’t played since Week 5 and was eventually benched for Jacoby Brissett, who outperformed Murray during his multi-week absence. Murray is under contract through the 2028 season, but there’s a good chance his time with the team will come to an end this offseason. The same can be said of Jonathan Gannon, but that’s a conversation for another day. The Cardinals don’t have anything to play for at this point, and any decisions to part with Murray could factor into whether the team decides to activate him at all over the final five weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys listed Tyler Guyton (ankle) as a DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbeb-d6c4-abfb-dfebfd510000</link>
      <description>Guyton suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12’s win over the Eagles and was sidelined for Week 13’s game against the Chiefs. Given the nature of his injury, it seems unlikely that he would be ready to go with less than two weeks of recovery time. We’ll see if his status changes later in the week, but we could be looking at another start for Nate Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbeb-d6c4-abfb-dfebfd510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys listed WR KaVontae Turpin (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbef-d6c4-abfb-dfefc22c0000</link>
      <description>Turpin played through the same shoulder injury in Week 13’s win over the Chiefs. The Cowboys’ special teams ace has posted a meager 19-260-1 receiving line this season and isn’t on the fantasy radar for Week 14 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbef-d6c4-abfb-dfefc22c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) “still has to be given final medical clearance to play.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbf6-d6c4-abfb-dff7334b0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said the “plan is to see where Reed is at by the end of the week.” The Packers opened Reed’s 21-day return window ahead of Week 12’s game against the Vikings, and still have time before they need to decide whether to activate him or shut him down for the season. Reed suffered a broken collarbone in Week 2’s game against the Commanders and has caught just three passes for 45 yards and one touchdown this season. Reed continues to practice with the team in hopes of being cleared soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbf6-d6c4-abfb-dff7334b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions placed CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc10-d6c4-abfb-de13c78a0000</link>
      <description>Arnold suffered a shoulder injury in Week 13’s loss to the Packers and will now miss at least the next four games as a result. The second-year corner has appeared in eight games this season while making seven starts, and registered his first career interception in Week 9 against the Vikings. Arnold has allowed just 23 receptions on 41 targets this season, per PFF, earning a coverage grade of 53.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc10-d6c4-abfb-de13c78a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers designated RB MarShawn Lloyd (hamstring) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc12-d90e-a9da-df1f6c730000</link>
      <description>Lloyd has yet to take a snap in 2025. The second-year back landed on injured reserve with a hamstring injury to start the season, and has been working his way back ever since. Injuries have completely derailed the start to Lloyd’s career, as he’s appeared in just one game since being drafted 88th overall by the Packers last season. Even if he does work his way back to the field this season, he’ll likely be buried behind both Josh Jacobs and Emanuel Wilson on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc12-d90e-a9da-df1f6c730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Kyle Juszczyk is dealing with a fractured rib.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc22-db57-afda-de32752b0000</link>
      <description>Juszczyk will be evaluated after the 49ers’ Week 14 bye. The veteran fullback has totaled 20 receptions for 187 yards and one touchdown this season, and continues to serve primarily as a run blocker in Shanahan’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc22-db57-afda-de32752b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
