<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio told reporters Joe Mixon (ankle) will be re-evaluated after four weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebed-d332-a1fd-ffff1d7f0000</link>
      <description>Caserio was noncommittal when discussing the 29-year-old running back with reporters. Mixon was placed on the reserve/non-football injury list and is set to miss at least the first four weeks of the season, at which point he’ll be re-evaluated. When asked if he anticipates Mixon playing at all this season, Caserio said, “We’ll see, we’ll take it one day at a time.” Mixon should be off fantasy draft boards at this point. Nick Chubb will begin the year as the Texans’ starting running back with Dameon Pierce and Woody Marks waiting in the wings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebed-d332-a1fd-ffff1d7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins GM Chris Grier told reporters De’Von Achane (calf) is expected to play in Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebf6-dbe3-a9bb-fbf783c10000</link>
      <description>Achane hasn’t been practicing as a preventative measure, but the 23-year-old running back is expected to play against the Colts in Week 1. Surely he’ll be back on the practice field by next week if he’s going to be active against the Colts. While nothing has changed with Achane’s status, the Dolphins continue to project confidence in the third-year back. With the fantasy community well aware of Achane’s calf issue, he could be a value in the middle of the second round as long as he doesn’t suffer a setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebf6-dbe3-a9bb-fbf783c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports NFL is aiming for at least a six-game suspension for WR Rashee Rice for violating the league’s personal conduct policy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec36-db7b-a5dd-ec3654a70000</link>
      <description>According to a previous report from NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero, the NFL initially proposed a 10-game suspension for Rice, which his representatives rebuffed. With the sides unable to reach a settlement on the length of the suspension, his case will be heard by Judge Sue L. Robinson. Rice is going to end up serving the suspension in the middle of the season and the league is still aiming for him to miss a significant portion of the season at potentially six games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec36-db7b-a5dd-ec3654a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports S Kyle Hamilton has agreed to a four-year, $100 million extension with the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec46-db7b-a5dd-ec46000f0000</link>
      <description>Hamilton instantly becomes the highest-paid safety in NFL history. The 24-year-old agreed to a deal with $82 million in guaranteed money, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, which is nearly twice as much as the previous high of $45 million in guarantees. His $25.1 million in average salary surpassed Lions safety Kerby Joseph ($21.25 million) for the most at the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec46-db7b-a5dd-ec46000f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports WR Rashee Rice accepted and will serve a six-game suspension to start the 2025 regular season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec4b-dbe3-a9bb-fc5b524c0000</link>
      <description>Our long national nightmare appears over as the NFL and NFLPA work to finalize this settlement. Rice has accepted and will serve a six-game suspension to start the season. He’ll be eligible to return when the Chiefs take on the Raiders in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec4b-dbe3-a9bb-fc5b524c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec50-dbe3-a9bb-fc5344950000</link>
      <description>Valdes-Scantling was cut earlier this week after losing out on the WR3 job with the Seahawks as he was outplayed by Tory Horton. The 49ers are at the point with all the injuries and contract disputes in their wide receiver room that the 30-year-old looks pretty good as a depth option. Valdes-Scantling likely doesn’t have much fantasy value with the 49ers, but with Jauan Jennings among others potentially unavailable early in the season he might get a decent amount of snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec50-dbe3-a9bb-fc5344950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs coach Todd Bowles told reporters TE Cade Otton (leg) has a leg injury and will be out for a little bit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec54-db7b-a5dd-ec5474d40000</link>
      <description>Otton was already dealing with a hamstring injury. Now the 26-year-old tight end also is dealing with a leg injury. While Bowles told reporters Otton will be out for a little bit, he stopped short of saying the tight end will miss Week 1. If healthy, Otton could be in line for increased targets early in the season with Chris Godwin and Jalen McMillan sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec54-db7b-a5dd-ec5474d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released WR Kendrick Bourne.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec59-db7b-a5dd-ec5d19ff0000</link>
      <description>The ink was barely dry on Bourne’s release before reports emerged that the 49ers are interested in signing the 30-year-old veteran receiver. Bourne was looking at a WR5 role with the Patriots, but his familiarity with the 49ers and their depleted wide receiver room could offer him a more significant role if he does end up back with the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec59-db7b-a5dd-ec5d19ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens GM Eric DeCosta told reporters TE Isaiah Likely (foot) is expected to return in the early part of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec5c-d332-a1fd-fe7e29c80000</link>
      <description>Nothing earth-shattering here. Likely is out with a foot injury that required surgery, but if he was going to miss extended time the Ravens would’ve placed him on injured reserve earlier this week. Now we have confirmation from the GM. Expect Likely back on the field sometime in the first four weeks of the season and keep him stashed on your fantasy bench.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec5c-d332-a1fd-fe7e29c80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
