<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 16:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a869-db57-afda-fe7b7c290000</link>
      <description>Neither is Emeka Egbuka. Whatever was going around in Tampa Bay earlier this week has dissipated, as all six players listed with illness recovered and are not on the final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a869-db57-afda-fe7b7c290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) is questionable for Week 12.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a86b-d90e-a9da-bf6f016a0000</link>
      <description>Todd Bowles said that Godwin is “trending toward playing” earlier today. He went limited-full-limited in his three practice sessions this week and seems to be on the optimistic side of questionable. Godwin will probably be more of a FLEX than a WR3 in Week 13 due to a tough opponent (Rams) and the re-injury risk, but he could be startable in the playoffs if everything breaks right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a86b-d90e-a9da-bf6f016a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 12 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a88b-d82c-a79a-bb9f16910000</link>
      <description>Crosby practiced fully on Friday, restoring faith in the Raiders D/ST unit. Browns rookie QB Shedeur Sanders will make his first career start and Crosby and Co. this weekend. Sanders notched a 20.0 percent pressure-to-sack rate on 21 dropbacks in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a88b-d82c-a79a-bb9f16910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed K Wil Lutz to a three-year extension through 2028.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8ac-d413-ad9f-bdfd33cd0000</link>
      <description>Lutz earned AFC Special Teams Player of the Week honors last week by converting 5-of-5 field goals in the Broncos’ Week 11 win over the Chiefs. Lutz has converted 17-of-20 field goals and 24-of-24 extra points this season. The deal keeps him with the Broncos through his age-34 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8ac-d413-ad9f-bdfd33cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports that Giants QB Jaxson Dart (concussion) did not suffer any setbacks this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8b7-d90e-a9da-bfbff1590000</link>
      <description>Per Raanan, the decision to hold Dart out for another week “was made by the doctors to play it safe with the young quarterback.” Good for them. Bad for the fantasy managers who had hoped to start him this week. Aside from saying Dart is “feeling better,” Raanan has not yet reported whether Dart is still experiencing symptoms. That part remains unclear. Hopefully, he returns for the team’s Week 13 matchup with the Patriots. The Giants notably go on bye in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8b7-d90e-a9da-bfbff1590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver and Dianna Russini report that the 49ers voided WR Brandon Aiyuk’s 2026 contract guarantees and “appear headed toward a stunning divorce.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8b8-db57-afda-febacc970000</link>
      <description>According to sources, it is likely that Aiyuk “has played his last game with the franchise,” though “some in the organization are holding out hope.” Aiyuk has reportedly “failed to attend meetings and declined to participate in other team activities.” Frustrated by Aiyuk’s lack of communication, the 49ers responded by voiding his 2026 guarantees, “asserting that the absences amounted to a failure to fulfill his contractual obligations.” Aiyuk reportedly told NFLPA reps “that he did not want to fight the move via an official grievance,” which “would clear the way for his expected release at season’s end.” The move allows the 49ers to recoup a significant sum. Aiyuk’s 2026 option bonus would have paid out $24.935 million. Silver and Russini’s report details unresolved issues between Aiyuk and the 49ers’ brass, dating back to the 2023 season. The star wide receiver was very nearly traded to the Steelers in August 2024, but ultimately agreed to sign the 49ers’ standing offer. The deal, unfortunately, failed to mend the damaged relationships. While Aiyuk would surely draw interest as a free agent, unknowns remain regarding Aiyuk’s health. The veteran wide receiver has not played since tearing his ACL, MCL and meniscus in October 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8b8-db57-afda-febacc970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce told reporters that he “plans to decide on whether to return to the Chiefs by early March, before NFL free agency begins.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8f1-d82c-a79a-bbf5696c0000</link>
      <description>Kelce is currently in his 13th NFL season and is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. The veteran tight end said he will not be making any decisions about his future until after the 2025 season concludes, and intends to give the Chiefs the “opportunity” to prepare for the draft and free agency with his decision in mind. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a8f1-d82c-a79a-bbf5696c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Browns built the game plan for Week 12 against the Raiders around QB Shedeur Sanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a91e-d413-ad9f-bddfb3310000</link>
      <description>The game plan will reportedly let Sanders “move the pocket a little bit more and use that play-making ability.” Wolfe also said the coaching staff has been helping Sanders work on his arm angles and reads, while trying to keep his footwork from drifting. The broadcast played lowlight clips of Sanders repeatedly failing to evade the Ravens’ pass rush last week as the segment progressed. Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski is a capable quarterback developer, but reworking Sanders’ bad habits over the course of a week is a tall task, especially with a matchup against Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby looming. If Stefanski really does feature Sanders, as opposed to employing a run-heavy approach featuring RB Quinshon Judkins, we should get a read on Sanders’ development fairly quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a91e-d413-ad9f-bddfb3310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals QB Joe Burrow won’t be activated for Week 12’s matchup with the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aa05-db57-afda-fe3752d80000</link>
      <description>Burrow practiced all week and was even taking first-team reps by the end of the week. Still, the Bengals are making the call to hold him out for one more game with a short week coming up, leaving Joe Flacco to make another start against the Patriots in Week 12. Burrow, who will remain on injured reserve, appears to be on track to return from a toe injury that’s kept him out since Week 2 in Week 13 against the Ravens on Thanksgiving Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-aa05-db57-afda-fe3752d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) is expected to play in Week 12’s matchup with the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ac1d-d82c-a79a-bf9d3ab60000</link>
      <description>Russini’s report comes on the heels of Bucs coach Todd Bowles admitting that Godwin was trending towards playing as of Friday. The 29-year-old wide receiver was mostly limited in practice this week. Godwin is a desperation FLEX play for fantasy managers given the difficult matchup with the Rams on Sunday Night Football on NBC. If Godwin can return to form before the fantasy playoffs, he could turn out to be one of the better players to stash this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ac1d-d82c-a79a-bf9d3ab60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
