<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Najee Harris (eye) said he’s ‘ramping up to it’ when asked if he will play Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0749-dbe3-a9bb-375b4ddc0000</link>
      <description>Speaking to reporters Monday, Harris said “I feel good though, and we’ll just see where it leads.” Harris has been on the practice field for almost a week now as he works his way back into football shape following a July 4 fireworks incident. He continues to claim the injuries to be superficial, insisting he is doing everything he can to be on the field Friday in Brazil against the Chiefs. He also noted that his vision has not been affected but did not want to go into details about the circumstances of the incident. While Harris is certainly trending in the right direction to play in the team’s season opener, his potential workload is a topic of another discussion considering the time he has missed during camp and preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0749-dbe3-a9bb-375b4ddc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (ankle) resumed practicing last week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0865-db7b-a5dd-a8658fde0000</link>
      <description>Not much has been made of Shakir’s return to practice last Wednesday, but it’s a very promising development. Shakir suffered a high-ankle sprain on August 1st, and the Bills smartly chose to hold him out for nearly the entire month of practice so the ankle could fully heal. Shakir may have to shake off a little rust but Josh Allen should have his most proven pass catcher on the field with him when the Bills host the Ravens in Week 1. He’s a WR3/4 with decent upside in PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0865-db7b-a5dd-a8658fde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Kendrick Bourne is visiting with the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ab8-dbe3-a9bb-3afb9a490000</link>
      <description>Bourne recently visited with the 49ers, who have struggled with various wideout injuries and enter the regular season bereft of receiver depth. Bourne, who has never surpassed 800 yards in a season and was phased out by the Patriots this offseason, would make sense in Washington, where there’s not much depth behind Deebo Samuel and Terry McLaurin. Bourne, 30, is widely expected to sign with a team ahead of Week 1. He likely won’t see much action, if any, on opening day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ab8-dbe3-a9bb-3afb9a490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas, Jr. said his chemistry with Trevor Lawrence grew throughout the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b14-de13-afdd-4fdf69040000</link>
      <description>It’s good to hear from the second-year wideout after Lawrence struggled in 2024 and missed seven games with shoulder and head injuries. “I feel like we’ve definitely got a lot closer, whether it’s football or off the field, like all the little things,” Thomas said of his relationship with Lawrence. “I feel like our chemistry is growing on the field, and I feel like it’s going to continue to grow throughout the season.” The offseason work between Thomas and Lawrence wasn’t without some hiccups, however. Thomas was seen during training camp “punching a padded wall or kicking a football” after offensive miscues and miscommunications between quarterback and pass catcher. Head coach Liam Coen has said Thomas — who went for 1,282 yards and ten touchdowns as a rookie — will play more from the slot in 2025. That’s a positive development for Thomas, who was the league’s third most efficient pass catcher from the slot in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b14-de13-afdd-4fdf69040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart will start the regular season as the Giants’ No. 2 quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b42-dbe3-a9bb-3b53511a0000</link>
      <description>Dart was bumped to the QB2 spot behind Russell Wilson ahead of the team’s Week 1 matchup against the Commanders following a highly impressive training camp and preseason. Dart completed 32 of 46 passes for 372 yards, three touchdowns, and no interceptions over three preseason affairs. His adjusted completion rate was 78 percent, according to Pro Football Focus. Dart is sure to take over as New York’s starter sometime this season, perhaps in the first half of the season should Wilson struggle. Dart should be rostered in all superflex leagues and can be stashed on benches in 14-team one-QB formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b42-dbe3-a9bb-3b53511a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed LB Kyzir White, formerly of the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b5770110000</link>
      <description>White last season in Arizona had 137 tackles, 2.5 sacks and 9 tackles for a loss as a starting linebacker. He should instantly become a starter in a Tennessee defense that struggled to stop the run and the pass in 2024, and should struggle once again in 2025. White, 29, has 7.5 sacks over 92 regular season games since entering the NFL in 2018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b5770110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed WR Gabe Davis, formerly of the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b54-de13-afdd-4fdff1350000</link>
      <description>Davis will reunite with Josh Allen and the Bills after a disastrous 2024 season in Jacksonville, where he managed 20 catches for 239 yards and two touchdowns over ten games before injuring his knee. Davis is expected to continue rehabbing that knee injury ahead of Week 1, and could be sidelined for the first part of the regular season. Before he left for the Jaguars, Davis scored 27 touchdowns over four seasons with the Bills as Allen’s primary downfield threat. Davis, 26, will likely function as a rotational receiver in the Buffalo offense this season unless the team struggles with wideout injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b54-de13-afdd-4fdff1350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OC Nick Holz said Tony Pollard is in a “good place” but added “we’ll have to get other backs in the mix, whether it’s Julius Chestnut or Kalel Mullings.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b60-de13-afdd-4feb4f3d0000</link>
      <description>Tennessee gave Pollard a 1980s style workload while Tyjae Spears was sidelined last year and rarely used Chestnut, so we’d wager we’ll see Mullings as the main backup on non-passing downs while Spears nurses his high-ankle sprain. Pollard should still see the overwhelming majority of the work, just bet on it being more like 75 percent of the snaps than 80 or 90 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b60-de13-afdd-4feb4f3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Kaleb Johnson is listed behind Jaylen Warren and Kenneth Gainwell on the team’s official depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b6f-de13-afdd-4fefe0bc0000</link>
      <description>We’d expect Johnson to be mixed in and play a bigger part at some point this season, but for now at least it appears he’ll have only a minor role in the rushing attack. With Warren recently signed to an extension and Johnson off to a relatively slow start in taking a share of the backfield, Johnson’s fantasy stock has declined precipitously since the draft. He’s still the best between-the-tackles fit the team has, so we’d bet he creates a role for himself eventually in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b6f-de13-afdd-4fefe0bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes DeVonta Smith could “near” his 2022 totals of 95 catches for 1,196 yards and seven touchdowns in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b8f-d332-a1fd-9fbf02460000</link>
      <description>“Look for an uptick in production from Smith,” Berman writes. It certainly would make some sense for the Eagles to throw more in 2025 so long as Saquon Barkley actually takes a regression step somewhere along the line, though that obviously is not guaranteed. Smith’s lengthy injury history causes fantasy football managers their own pains, but it’s hard to deny that there’s a path for him to improve on last year’s numbers — at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0b8f-d332-a1fd-9fbf02460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
