<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 3-of-5 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5a-dc7a-af9b-efffb12c0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid got on the board with a touchdown in the fourth quarter, giving the Bills a temporary lead. He would go on to finish second on the team in targets and catches. The Bills are incredibly thin at receiver, meaning Kincaid gets to operate as a de facto WR2 behind Khalil Shakir. While he doesn’t run every route, he gets on the field enough to put up usable fantasy numbers and score the occasional touchdown. He will be a touchdown-or-bust fantasy option in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af5a-dc7a-af9b-efffb12c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught all three of his targets for 30 yards in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d35e-a1bf-efe200fb0000</link>
      <description>Knox, Brandin Cooks, and Dalton Kincaid all tied for second on the team in catches. Khalil Shakir led the way with 12 grabs and 82 yards. Knox is a reliable backup tight end and a plus blocker, but his fantasy outlook is limited. He needs to get in the end zone to pay off and that has only happened four times this year. Knox is only worth a look in large-field DFS tournaments for the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d35e-a1bf-efe200fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) is active for the Wild Card Round against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d968-a19b-fff3f3500000</link>
      <description>As is EDGE Harold Landry (knee). With Mack Hollins out at least several more weeks with an abdominal injury, Boutte enters the postseason as the Pats’ primary deep threat. It’s been a profitable role this season, and is perhaps one worth betting on in playoff DFS. That being said, you might not want to do vs. the Chargers’ elite pass defense. Inactive for the Patriots are WR Jeremiah Webb, EDGE Bradyn Swinson, OT Marcus Bryant, OG Caedan Wallace, TE C.J. Dippre, QB Tommy DeVito and DT Khyiris Tonga.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af62-d968-a19b-fff3f3500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton (ankle) is active for the Wild Card Round against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af78-d35e-a1bf-effa3c5d0000</link>
      <description>Hampton got in only one “limited” practice during the week, one where he was spotted wearing a “big brace.” That’s the long way of saying we have no idea of how “healthy” he might be in New England, but we would bet on him leading the Chargers’ backfield in touches. The Pats’ run defense has taken on water of late, making Hampton a nice risk/reward DFS option. Inactive for the Bolts are CB Isas Waxter, S Kendall Williamson, EDGE Bud Dupree, EDGE Kyle Kennard, OT Austin Deculus, WR Dalevon Campbell and TE Tyler Conklin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af78-d35e-a1bf-effa3c5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 18-of-31 passes for 262 yards, two touchdowns and a pair of interceptions in the 49ers’ 23-19, Wild Card win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afaf-d968-a19b-ffffdd1c0000</link>
      <description>Battling the wind and an elite defense, Purdy had his first multi-pick start since before Thanksgiving, but the 49ers still managed to spring the upset thanks to surprisingly feisty defense and some well-timed big plays on offense. That included a third passing score via former college quarterback recruit Jauan Jennings on a fourth quarter trick play. Both of Purdy’s giveaways were bad decisions in the vicinity of DB Quinyon Mitchell, but he rode hot connections with Christian McCaffrey and DeMarcus Robinson to keep the Niners in the game. Another massive test now awaits for the Divisional Round, as the Niners must venture back to Seattle for Part 3 of their Seahawks trilogy, this time without George Kittle (Achilles). It can be done, but will take a much better performance than Purdy delivered in Philly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afaf-d968-a19b-ffffdd1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Hurts completed 20-of-35 passes for 168 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ 23-19, Wild Card loss to the 49ers, adding five rushes for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afb4-d56e-afff-effcf5b50000</link>
      <description>It’s a performance the Eagles’ oft-debated signal caller would like to have back. Facing one of the league’s worst defenses, Hurts generated his fewest passing yards since ... Week 17. It was the culmination of a quiet finish to the year. Hurts heads into the offseason averaging just 160 yards over his final four appearances. Part of that is by design in this conservative, run-based offense, but you need to do better when you have A.J. Brown, DeVonta Smith and Dallas Goedert at your disposal. Then again, Brown had another crippling down, this time late in the fourth quarter. If Hurts failed to make big plays, so did his weapons. 2025 was Hurts’ least effective year on the ground since his rookie campaign in 2020. Going on age 28, you do wonder if all Hurts’ lower-body hits might already be catching up with him. With the Eagles likely to fire OC Kevin Patullo, Hurts figures to have another voice in his ear next season. Despite this year’s disappointment and signs of trouble, Hurts will remain a top-five fantasy quarterback until proven otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afb4-d56e-afff-effcf5b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers president and CEO Ed Policy is expected to decide on head coach Matt LaFleur’s future with the team by Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af9c-d56e-afff-effc58900000</link>
      <description>LaFleur told reporters that he will meet with Policy “either the night of Jan. 11 or sometime Jan. 12, indicating a decision on his future will come soon.” The Packers’ head coach has just one year remaining on his contract and it is “Policy who faces the decision on whether to extend or fire” him. Policy previously stated he prefers to avoid a “lame-duck situation” where LaFleur coaches the Packers in 2026 on an expiring contract. This is a difficult decision. Coaches like LaFleur, capable of guiding a franchise to a 76-41 record, are tough to replace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af9c-d56e-afff-effc58900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 3-of-7 targets for 35 yards in the Eagles’ Wild Card loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afbc-d35e-a1bf-effee91e0000</link>
      <description>Brown heads into the offseason with a performance emblematic of his 2025 struggles and frustrations. One of his missed connections was a brutal fourth quarter drop with the Eagles trying to stave off defeat, while he was caught on camera having yet another heated argument with coach Nick Sirianni. Brown was probably putting in his best effort, but there were too many times this season where you couldn’t be sure that was the case. Going on 29 with one more season of guaranteed money ($29 million) remaining on his contract, Brown seems like a strong candidate to be traded and extended/restructured elsewhere. He is too visibly over his fit in this run-first Eagles offense. Brown seems like he also badly needs the offseason to get healthier. Always playing through something or other — Brown’s toughness isn’t in doubt — he didn’t always seem to have his typical explosiveness this season. Wherever Brown is playing his 2026 football, it’s doubtful he falls out of the top 12 at wideout in offseason fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afbc-d35e-a1bf-effee91e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings notched a 45-yard reception in the 49ers’ Wild Card win over the Eagles, adding a 29-yard touchdown pass to Christian McCaffrey in the fourth quarter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afc1-d968-a19b-fff197440000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ 45-yard second quarter catch-and-run was his only reception on three targets, though he atoned with a far bigger play in the final frame, adding to his trick play legend when he took an end-around pitch then found CMC in the end zone. Jennings was under pressure and had to deliver a seed to the goal line. McCaffrey then made a spectacular catch. Awesome stuff, though Jennings is going to be needed for more as a pass catcher against the Seahawks in the Divisional Round as the 49ers adjust to life without George Kittle (Achilles).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-afc1-d968-a19b-fff197440000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
