<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 01:29:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts waived K Michael Badgley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d2-db57-afda-f6f26f070000</link>
      <description>The Money Badger missed a huge extra point against the Texans in Week 13 and had missed three of his 21 extra points in total. It’ll be a different kicker for the Colts after today’s tryouts resolve, and whoever they pick will find themselves in a favorable Week 14 situation against the Jaguars. Blake Grupe was one name publicly identified from the tryouts earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d2-db57-afda-f6f26f070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR George Pickens (calf/knee) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d6-d90e-a9da-ffdfe2430000</link>
      <description>As expected. Pickens should be good to go on Thursday after a limited session on Monday. He’ll be a WR1 against the Lions on Thursday night. He played through this listing during Thanksgiving’s game against the Chiefs and put up an 88-yard day on 13 targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d6-d90e-a9da-ffdfe2430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers claimed WR Adam Thielen off waivers from the Minnesota Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0ef-d6c4-abfb-f6ef11800000</link>
      <description>Huge news for the 2022 Steelers. The 2025 Steelers? Well, it’s not like Calvin Austin was necessarily killing it as their No. 2 receiver, but Thielen had fallen well behind Jalen Nailor on the Vikings depth chart and Pittsburgh’s passing offense has major trouble completing anything further than 10 yards downfield. Unless Thielen is going to reinvent himself as a major tackle-breaking threat, he’s probably of no immediate fantasy football use.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0ef-d6c4-abfb-f6ef11800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans waived G Laken Tomlinson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e034-d90e-a9da-ff3f77b60000</link>
      <description>A healthy scratch for each of the last two games, Tomlinson played 284 snaps over seven weeks with the Texans, creating a 56.1 PFF blocking grade before the team finally demoted him. He’ll try to catch on elsewhere as a veteran stopgap for the last few weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e034-d90e-a9da-ff3f77b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Corey Kiner off the Vikings’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0fa-d6c4-abfb-f6fb273f0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals released RB Jermar Jefferson in a related move. We’d love to say this doesn’t matter, but sadly, all Cardinals running back news is real news. Kiner spent time with the 49ers in training camp before getting hurt, he was a priority UDFA signing this offseason. It’s possible he may be fantasy-relevant at some point given how banged up the Cardinals RB room is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0fa-d6c4-abfb-f6fb273f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed K Blake Grupe to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0fe-d90e-a9da-ffff8f6a0000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be elevated a few times as roster manipulation while the Colts figure out if he’s the answer. Grupe struggled this year for the Saints, hitting just 18-of-26 field goals, including two inside of 40 yards. He’ll be a worthwhile fantasy play if the Colts can get their offense back on track against the Jaguars in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0fe-d90e-a9da-ffff8f6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent K Justin Tucker visited with the Colts on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e11a-db57-afda-f73a60800000</link>
      <description>We can see why the Colts wouldn’t have wanted that to get out ahead of signing Blake Grupe. Still, this is two teams in two weeks that have kicked the tires on Tucker despite his 10-game suspension over sexual misconduct allegations. He’s probably going to continue to get work on the kicker tryout circuit. The Colts also brought in Maddux Trujillo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e11a-db57-afda-f73a60800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks waived RB Myles Gaskin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e157-db57-afda-f77710000000</link>
      <description>Gaskin was active on the Seahawks’ 53-man roster last week, seeing three carries for six yards against the Vikings. He is now waived as the Seahawks make room on the roster for other moves; Gaskin could be brought back on the practice squad. The Seahawks also released WR Brenden Rice and C Doug Kramer from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e157-db57-afda-f77710000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions TE Brock Wright (neck) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e195-d6c4-abfb-f79730d60000</link>
      <description>Wright was listed as a non-participant on Monday is still a DNP Tuesday after missing Week 12 due to a neck injury. Fellow tight end Shane Zylstra was listed as limited on Monday due to a knee injury, but was downgraded to DNP on Tuesday. Both tight ends are in jeopardy of missing Thursday against the Cowboys, leaving the Lions scarce at the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e195-d6c4-abfb-f79730d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e19f-d90e-a9da-ff9f56940000</link>
      <description>Sewell was not on the injury report Monday, but popped up with a shoulder injury Tuesday and did not practice. Meanwhile, LT Taylor Decker has also been listed with a DNP tag due to a shoulder issue Tuesday, after initially being listed as limited Monday. Though it is possible both tackles could play Thursday against the Cowboys without practicing, any level of practice on Wednesday would provide some relief as it pertains to Jared Goff’s blocking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e19f-d90e-a9da-ff9f56940000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
