<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 19:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26b9-d5d8-a3ff-fff901480000</link>
      <description>Based on that update, we’re not too concerned about Judkins missing time after Cleveland’s Week 9 bye. We’re sure he’ll be listed on the injury report ahead of Week 10, but ‘day to day’ is about as good an update as we could have seen on Judkins and this saps any reason to hold Dylan Sampson as an injury hedge through the bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26b9-d5d8-a3ff-fff901480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos HC Sean Payton did not have an update on Patrick Surtain’s shoulder injury after Week 8’s win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26ae-d245-adfb-b7ff1ae00000</link>
      <description>Payton may opt to play this one close to the vest ahead of Week 9’s game against the Texans. Surtain was initially listed as questionable to return after exiting, but never made it back to the field. Surtain’s status will be one to monitor when the team releases its first injury report on Wednesday, but any DNPs late in the week could point to him missing Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26ae-d245-adfb-b7ff1ae00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said Cedric Tillman (hamstring/IR) is expected to return after the team’s bye week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26bc-deb1-a39b-27be98a90000</link>
      <description>Unfortunately, with Joe Flacco gone, there’s not much of a reason to actually want Tillman starting for your fantasy team. Dillon Gabriel simply can’t connect with wideouts right now, and Tillman’s high-target floor is meaningless if Gabriel can’t even make Jerry Jeudy productive. Anyone who stashed Tillman in a non-keeper league can probably freely cut bait for a better injury hold at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26bc-deb1-a39b-27be98a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said that Carolina “cannot ignore the fact that Rico (Dowdle) has been exceptional.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c5-d245-adfb-b7dfcb630000</link>
      <description>Canales said that he hasn’t discussed with Chuba Hubbard “what it might possibly look like with him taking a lesser role.” It’s been hard to believe how much Dowdle has outproduced Hubbard, who may still be dealing with a calf injury. It does sound like Dowdle will be closer to an RB1 role going forward and he should stumble into a pretty decent spot against Green Bay in Week 9, even if the defensive matchup isn’t a clear boost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c5-d245-adfb-b7dfcb630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz was not spotted at Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c7-deb1-a39b-27cfcdc00000</link>
      <description>This absence is presumably due to the injury to his non-throwing shoulder he dealt with ahead of Thursday night’s game against the Chargers. Wentz took a bit of a beating from the Chargers’ defense in that game, so his absence on Monday is notable. Monday’s practice won’t show up on the team’s injury report, which is released on Wednesday, but even if he is able to play in Week 9, Wentz is most likely to backup J.J. McCarthy, who is making his long-awaited return from an ankle injury he suffered in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c7-deb1-a39b-27cfcdc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Bryce Young (ankle) could practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c9-d245-adfb-b7dfe6e80000</link>
      <description>We remain a little more skeptical on Young returning this week given they’ll only speak in possibilities, but Andy Dalton’s performance yesterday is certainly extra fuel to get Young up and ready as soon as possible. Young didn’t practice all last week after suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26c9-d245-adfb-b7dfe6e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ankle) is expected to practice this week and play in Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26cf-deb1-a39b-27cf10010000</link>
      <description>This was mostly expected after McVay said last week that Nacua would be good to go following the team’s Week 8 bye. Nacua attempted to play through the injury when he went down in Week 6 against the Ravens, which led many to believe the injury was relatively minor. We’ll monitor Nacua’s status throughout the week, but we would expect him to play even if he’s listed as a limited participant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26cf-deb1-a39b-27cf10010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said he expects Rob Havenstein (ankle) to practice and play in Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26d8-dab4-a3fb-bff837f00000</link>
      <description>Havenstein has missed the last three games with an ankle injury. That time away, coupled with the team’s Week 8 bye, has proven to be enough for the veteran tackle to return in Week 9 against the Saints. Havenstein has allowed one sack and 16 pressures on 154 pass blocking snaps this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26d8-dab4-a3fb-bff837f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said CB Storm Duck (knee) will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dc-dab4-a3fb-bffcb6850000</link>
      <description>A huge loss for those of us who believe in the power of names. Duck played only 44 snaps over two games as he dealt with an oblique injury early in the season. The 2024 UDFA should have a role in the 2026 Dolphins DB room, although with mass leadership changes looking somewhat likely, perhaps things could change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dc-dab4-a3fb-bffcb6850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports “teams have had a hard time getting a clear read” on whether or not the Raiders want to trade Jakobi Meyers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dd-d245-adfb-b7df2d2a0000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, multiple teams have shown interest in acquiring Meyers, who is in the final year of his contract. However, he also adds that “the belief is it would take at least a Day 2 pick for the Raiders to even consider [a trade].” A Day 2 pick would be close to top-100 territory, which feels like a steep price for a solid player who is on an expiring deal. The right offer could still get it done, but the Raiders would likely have to settle for something less than a Day 2 pick if they hope to get any kind of return for a player who has been vocal about wanting a trade and is a near lock to not re-sign with the team next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-26dd-d245-adfb-b7df2d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
