<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Terrell Jennings (knee) is questionable for Week 11 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f3-d45b-affe-7df7122e0000</link>
      <description>Jennings left Week 10 in the first quarter because of a knee injury and did not return. He has been limited in practice this week and appears to be a true game-time call for Week 11. Jennings will back up rookie TreVeyon Henderson if he is active, but could also steal some work at the goal line. He will be, at best, an RB5 for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f3-d45b-affe-7df7122e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f5-d1e7-a1fa-7bfff41b0000</link>
      <description>It’s Ridley’s first practice since going down with the hamstring injury in Week 6. He got a Week 10 bye to rest and now has a shot at returning for Sunday’s game against the Texans. Ridley topped 57 yards once in six games to open the year. A date with one of the league’s best defenses will relegate him to the WR4 ranks if he is active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f5-d1e7-a1fa-7bfff41b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79fa-d713-ad9e-7dfe5b430000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo played through the foot issue in Week 9 and then got the Titans’ bye week to rest. It’s a little surprising to see him listed as limited after the week off, but it still doesn’t look like he is at any risk of missing time because of the foot injury. Now splitting work with rookie Gunnar Helm, Okonkwo is barely on the TE2 radar for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79fa-d713-ad9e-7dfe5b430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions EDGE Aidan Hutchinson (elbow) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f8-d45b-affe-7dfed9f50000</link>
      <description>Hutchinson leads the NFL with 57 quarterback pressures, and his eight sacks tie for seventh, so an absence against the Eagles this weekend would be significant. The Lions’ star defensive lineman still has time to get right, but this is one worth watching. Lions EDGE Al-Quadin Muhammad is second on the team with just 37 quarterback pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f8-d45b-affe-7dfed9f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants placed K Graham Gano (neck) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f0-d673-a39e-fdf1d26d0000</link>
      <description>Gano missed Week 10 with the neck issue. He will now be sidelined for at least the next four weeks. Younghoe Koo, who was cut by the Falcons earlier this year, is the next man up in New York. Koo made both of his field goal attempts and both of his PAT kicks in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f0-d673-a39e-fdf1d26d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f9-d713-ad9e-7dfd52690000</link>
      <description>Sewell entered Week 10 with a shoulder injury and exited with an ankle injury. Fortunately, Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is practicing in a limited capacity to begin the week. He has been playing through a shoulder injury for much of the season. The Lions will need their offensive tackles against the Eagles’ pass rush this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-79f9-d713-ad9e-7dfd52690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a02-d673-a39e-fe9353700000</link>
      <description>Mitchell has been encroaching on RB Justice Hill’s role in recent weeks and Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reporters on Monday that he wants to get Mitchell even more involved. While Mitchell’s limited session is less than ideal, Hill was unable to practice at all while dealing with a toe injury. Mitchell is a high-upside stash option. He should be rostered in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a02-d673-a39e-fe9353700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a08-d1e7-a1fa-7aeaf6990000</link>
      <description>Players almost always play through the “illness” injury designation, especially when it pops up this early in the week. Still, fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on this situation just to be sure. Barring a surprise, London will be a WR1 like he always is for the Falcons Week 11 date with the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a08-d1e7-a1fa-7aeaf6990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RG Chris Lindstrom (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a0b-d45b-affe-7f9fc78d0000</link>
      <description>Lindstrom played through the foot issue last week and only missed one snap in the overtime loss to Indianapolis. The DNP today is hopefully just a maintenance day. If the foot issue got worse in Week 10, Jovaughn Gwyn would seemingly be in line to start in his place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a0b-d45b-affe-7f9fc78d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (hip) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a09-d673-a39e-fe991ab80000</link>
      <description>Likely is on track to play, but his status is worth following for fantasy managers who roster TE Mark Andrews. The latter player could see a decent target share increase if Likely were to sit out in Week 11 against the Browns. Andrews has largely been relying on touchdowns to score his fantasy points in recent weeks. An uptick in targets between the 20s would be helpful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7a09-d673-a39e-fe991ab80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
