<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed 15 times for 79 yards in the Commanders’ Week 11 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e14-d45b-affe-df9658080000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez drew the start last week but left early with a shoulder injury. He played a full four quarters today and easily led the team in carries and rushing yards. Jacory Croskey-Merritt saw nine attempts and Jeremy McNichols rushed four times. The Commanders have thrown in the towel on Bill, elevating Rodriguez to lead back duties. He will be a two-down RB3 versus the Broncos coming out of Washington’s upcoming bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e14-d45b-affe-df9658080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed nine times for 28 yards in the Commanders’ Week 11 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e1d-d1e7-a1fa-deff318f0000</link>
      <description>Chris Rodriguez drew the start in this game and saw 15 carries. Bill didn’t see his first touch of the day until the Commanders’ third drive. Rodriguez already had eight carries to his name. Croskey-Merritt has been fully relegated to a backup role. He will barely register as an RB5 when the Commanders take on the Broncos after their Week 12 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e1d-d1e7-a1fa-deff318f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy McNichols rushed four times for 13 yards in the Commanders’ Week 11 loss to the Dolphins, adding two catches for 16 tards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e29-d45b-affe-dfbfd5190000</link>
      <description>McNichols led the Washington backs in catches but finished third on the team in rush attempts. He has a minor role through the air and doesn’t see much work on the ground. McNichols is more of a thorn in the side of the other Washington backs than a standalone fantasy asset. He is not worth holding onto through the team’s Week 12 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e29-d45b-affe-dfbfd5190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared CB Deommodore Lenoir (calf) active for Week 11 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e29-d713-ad9e-ee7d85910000</link>
      <description>Lenoir entered the weekend with a questionable tag due to a calf injury. He suffered the injury in Thursday’s practice but is active after experiencing some tightness. The 49ers declared RB Jordan James, WR Jordan Watkins, OL Connor Colby, DL Clelin Ferrell, DL Kevin Givens, and CB Eli Apple inactive for Week 11 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e29-d713-ad9e-ee7d85910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon rushed nine times for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 11 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e2d-d45b-affe-dfbffc2b0000</link>
      <description>Gordon played through an ankle injury last week but operated as the Dolphins’ RB3 behind Jaylen Wright. Likely in a better spot this week health-wise, Gordon reclaimed the RB2 role and punched in a one-yard score in the fourth quarter. The Dolphins could keep their run game going after their Week 12 bye versus the Saints. Gordon will get a week of rest before returning as a touchdown-based FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e2d-d45b-affe-dfbffc2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Chimere Dike (concussion protocol) left Tennessee’s Week 11 game against the Texans and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ded-d673-a39e-adfdb4490000</link>
      <description>He was hammered on a punt return that he muffed and that the Titans were lucky to corral. Mason Kinsey has started getting snaps in his place in the second half. Dike had two catches for 14 yards before leaving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ded-d673-a39e-adfdb4490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers HC Mike Tomlin said Aaron Rodgers (wrist) is being evaluated at halftime.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e32-d45b-affe-dfb66b0e0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers was slammed to the ground by two defenders late in the second quarter and was immediately seen grabbing his left wrist after the play. He played out the remainder of the first half but backup Mason Rudolph was seen warming up on the sideline at the start of the third quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e32-d45b-affe-dfb66b0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals declared LB Baron Browning, WR Marvin Harrison, OL Demontrey Jacobs, CB Will Johnson, DL Bilal Nichols, DB Dadrion Taylor-Demerson, and OL Jonah Williams inactive for Week 11 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e30-d45b-affe-dfb6a2fe0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals are heading into Week 11 banged up. Harrison is dealing with appendicitis while Browning, Johnson, Taylor-Demerson, and Williams are all ruled out with injuries. The defense will be thin against a 49ers offense that is healing with Brock Purdy and Ricky Pearsall active this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e30-d45b-affe-dfb6a2fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 3-of-7 targets for 52 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 11 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e32-d713-ad9e-ee7654c30000</link>
      <description>Waddle was once again the focal point of the Dolphins’ passing attack. He led the team in receiving yards and racked up a 35 percent target share. Tua Tagovailoa locked in on his top wideout and even gave him an ill-advised jump ball in double-coverage that should have been intercepted. Waddle gets a tough matchup with the Broncos’ shutdown defense after the bye, but fantasy managers can’t afford to bench him, even if he is ranked as a WR2 for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8e32-d713-ad9e-ee7654c30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
