<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declared RB Raheim Sanders, CB Jarrick Bernard-Converse, DT Mike Hall Jr., OT Thayer Munford Jr., OG Zak Zinter, and OT Cornelius Lucas inactive for Week 6 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d910-db72-a199-fb5b5c460000</link>
      <description>There’s nothing surprising here. The Browns enter Week 6 against the Steelers as close to full strength as possible. Defensive tackle Mike Hall was the only player carrying an injury designation into the weekend and was ruled out on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d910-db72-a199-fb5b5c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) is active for Week 6 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d8ff-def2-abdb-ddff0b840000</link>
      <description>Kamara suffered the ankle injury in Week 5 but played through it. The Saints kept his practice reps limited but he was always expected to suit up today. He remains a volume-based RB2. Inactive for the Saints are S Ugo Amadi, CB Rejzohn Wright, OL Torricelli Simpkins III, OL Xavier Truss, DT Khristian Boy, and CB Isaac Yiadom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d8ff-def2-abdb-ddff0b840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Calvin Austin, DB Chuck Clark, OG Andrus Peat, DT Logan Lee, and DE Demarvin Leal inactive for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-db72-a199-fb5b883d0000</link>
      <description>Austin was ruled out before the weekend. The only player who was questionable for the Steelers was Jalen Ramsey, who is officially active for this week after logging a full practice on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-db72-a199-fb5b883d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared WR Quentin Johnston, WR Derius Davis, FB/DL Scott Matlock, CB Nikko Reed, OL Jamaree Salyer, T Joe Altm and G/T Trey Pipkins III inactive for Week 6 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-dd4c-afb9-ffd16dec0000</link>
      <description>Johnston will miss Week 6 with a hamstring issue he picked up last week. His absence should open up more targets for Keenan Allen and Ladd McConkey against a middling Dolphins secondary. McConkey should be in 12-team league fantasy lineups with Johnston sidelined. Justin Herbert’s upside takes a hit with Johnston out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-dd4c-afb9-ffd16dec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is active for Week 6 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d90e-db72-a199-fb4f50550000</link>
      <description>Defensive tackle Milton Williams is also active. Inactive for the Patriots are QB Tommy DeVito, OLB Anfernee Jennings, DE Keion White, S Jaylinn Hawkins, OL Caedan Wallace, and DT Eric Gregory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d90e-db72-a199-fb4f50550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Anthony Richardson is inactive for Week 6 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-def2-abdb-dd71612c0000</link>
      <description>Richardson is a surprise inactive as he moves to QB3 for the Colts. Rookie Riley Leonard will be Daniel Jones’ primary backup in his place. Richardson lost the starting job to Jones at the beginning of the season, but moving him down the depth chart may indicate trade interest or a general reset for the 23-year-old. Richardson has struggled to develop as a passer and has had trouble staying healthy, so a change in scenery may be coming soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d911-def2-abdb-dd71612c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Ramsey (hamstring) is active for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d916-d94a-a79d-d91f51230000</link>
      <description>Despite being a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday, Ramsey was able to log a full practice on Friday, hinting that the veteran corner would likely be active for this week. Ramsey was not listed on the team’s Week 6 inactives and is officially good to go against a Browns offense that will feature rookie Dillon Gabriel in his second career start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d916-d94a-a79d-d91f51230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared RB Jaylen Wright, CB Storm Duck, QB Quinn Ewers, DT Zeek Biggers, LB Tyrel Dodson, WR Cedrick Wilson Jr., and DB Elijah Campbell inactive for Week 6 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d917-dd4c-afb9-ffd714820000</link>
      <description>Wright is once again inactive while Ollie Gordon continues serving as the Dolphins’ No. 2 running back behind De’Von Achane. A game script dependent fantasy option, Gordon has 18 rushing attempts over the past three games, including some carries in the red zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d917-dd4c-afb9-ffd714820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared S Kahlef Hailassie, RB Cody Schrader, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Robert Hainsey, and DT Khalen Saunders Sr. inactive for Week 6 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5efaf0000</link>
      <description>The Jags are largely healthy heading into Week 6. Abdullah and Hainsey were the only players with injury designations heading into the weekend and both are out versus the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5efaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared WR Adonai Mitchell, RB Tyler Goodson, TE Will Mallory, CB Kenny Moore, QB Anthony Richardson, OT Luke Tenuta, and DE JT Tuimoloau inactive for Week 6 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5b0fb0000</link>
      <description>Mitchell had been trending downward after just six snaps last week. Ashton Dulin now has the WR4 job for the Colts, leading to Mitchell being a healthy scratch this week. He can be dropped in all but the deepest of redraft fantasy leagues. Kenny Moore (Achilles) remains out, while Anthony Richardson is a surprise inactive as Riley Leonard takes the backup job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d915-dd4c-afb9-ffd5b0fb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
