<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) will work out pre-game to determine his availability for Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc72-df81-ab9b-fef79e3c0000</link>
      <description>Meyers remains a game-time decision. If he misses, the Raiders will be down to Tre Tucker as their top pass-catcher. Brock Bowers is listed as doubtful and is not expected to play. Rookies Jack Bech and Dont’e Thornton will also be in line for more work if Meyers is ruled out. Tucker should be rostered in all fantasy formats while the rookies are deep-league flyers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc72-df81-ab9b-fef79e3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Brock Bowers (knee) is not expected to play in Week 7 against the Chiefs and has a “good chance to return after the bye.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc77-d99b-a1dd-fe7f4e740000</link>
      <description>Bowers was listed as doubtful heading into the weekend, so his absence isn’t a surprise. The Raiders get their bye in Week 8, giving Bowers a month of rest between his last game and a potential Week 9 return versus the Jaguars. Michael Mayer will take his place in the lineup for now. Mayers is a streaming TE2 for his date with Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc77-d99b-a1dd-fe7f4e740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jalen Carter (heel) is expected to play in Week 7 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc7d-d99b-a1dd-fe7d27c40000</link>
      <description>Carter practiced in full on Wednesday but was downgraded to limited sessions on the following two days before being listed as questionable. The team was likely managing his reps closely to ensure the injury didn’t get worse. Carter has had a quiet start to the year with one TFL, seven total tackles, and no sacks. A date with Carson Wentz will give him a good chance to get on the board.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc7d-d99b-a1dd-fe7d27c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Stefon Diggs (chest) is expected to play in Week 7 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc80-da18-a39b-fe93e5570000</link>
      <description>Diggs was a full participant in Friday’s practice, but the team still played things safe and listed him as questionable. He never seemed at much risk of missing Week 7. The injury, however, will likely prevent him from playing every snap, something the Patriots have been hesitant to do with their veteran wideout this year. Even with a limited route rate, Diggs is a WR2 for his Week 7 bout with the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc80-da18-a39b-fe93e5570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Titans are expected to “simplify their offense” for Cam Ward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc84-df81-ab9b-fec7b1140000</link>
      <description>The Titans fired Brian Callahan last week and replaced him with senior offensive assistant Mike McCoy as the interim head coach. Callahan’s offense wasn’t necessarily known for its abundance of bells and whistles, but Ward is at his best when given the opportunity to freelance, even if that can also get him in trouble. The hope will be that a simpler offense lets him execute the basics well while giving him the freedom to make plays when needed. For fantasy purposes, managers can give Ward a few weeks before considering him as a streaming option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc84-df81-ab9b-fec7b1140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports D’Andre Swift (groin) is expected to play in Week 7 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc8c-d99b-a1dd-fe8c117e0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes Bears DT Grady Jarrett (knee) is also expected to play. Swift was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice before being downgraded to limited sessions on the following two days. The team then listed him as questionable. Swift told reporters after Friday’s practice that the limited days were simply maintenance. He has been dealing with a myriad of injuries this year but has yet to miss any time. Swift should get plenty of work as a home favorite versus the Saints this week, vaulting him up the RB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc8c-d99b-a1dd-fe8c117e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Zach Ertz (shoulder/calf) is expected to play in Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc90-d651-a9df-fd9512430000</link>
      <description>Ertz was given a light workload in practice, per usual, this week. He was listed as questionable after being downgraded from a full practice on Thursday to limited on Friday. Though he never seemed at risk of missing Week 7, it’s still a good sign that the team expects him to play this early in the day. With Terry McLaurin and Deebo Samuel out this week, Ertz is a must-play TE1 in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc90-d651-a9df-fd9512430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (hamstring) is a game-time decision for Week 7 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc98-df81-ab9b-fedfcdf60000</link>
      <description>Carter was added to the injury report on Friday as a limited participant before being listed as questionable. That likely means he suffered the hamstring issue in practice. Per Rapoport, he will go through some work before inactives before the team makes a final decision on his status. The rookie has 24 pressures and .5 sacks this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc98-df81-ab9b-fedfcdf60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Titans told other teams DT Jeffery Simmons “is not available.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc9d-da18-a39b-fe9fb1330000</link>
      <description>Simmons has, once again, been the lone bright spot on an otherwise dreadful Titans team. He has 4.5 sacks and one forced fumble this year. Rapoport noted that, even with two years left on his current deal, Simmons could be in line for a big extension soon. He also named Arden Key, Roger McCreary, and Dre’Mont Jones as veterans who could be on the move for Tennessee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fc9d-da18-a39b-fe9fb1330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said, “Don’t be surprised” if Carson Wentz starts in Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fcae-d651-a9df-fdbfe4b70000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that McCarthy is still recovering from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 2. He said that the Vikings will continue to kick the question of who their starting quarterback is long-term down the road. The fact that the answer isn’t clearly J.J. McCarthy, whom they spent a first-round pick on last year, tells us all we need to know. If Wentz looks good over the next two weeks, he will likely hold onto the job for the foreseeable future. McCarthy, meanwhile, will get time to develop on the bench after a shaky two starts to open the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fcae-d651-a9df-fdbfe4b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
