<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 18:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports Chuba Hubbard took the first reps when the Panthers first lined up their starters for warmups.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd4c-df81-ab9b-ffcf477c0000</link>
      <description>Rico Dowdle was second in the order. This isn’t definitive proof that Hubbard is the starter, but it’s the best intel fantasy managers are going to get before kickoff. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler previously reported that the Carolina backs will trade series early in the game, with things potentially changing as the contest goes on. At this point, fantasy managers should treat both runners as high-risk RB3s in a good matchup with a putrid Jets defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd4c-df81-ab9b-ffcf477c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught 3-of-7 targets for 31 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 7 loss to the Rams before exiting with an apparent shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd56-df81-ab9b-ffd7da4f0000</link>
      <description>Thomas was laboring through an injury or two throughout this game and finally went down on a light push from a Rams defender with less than five minutes to play. He appeared to be in tremendous pain and was assisted off the field by trainers. Down by four touchdowns, BTJ had no chance of returning. It’s a nightmare end to a frustrating day for the young wideout. The Jags failed to get much going on offense and Thomas Jr. committed multiple drops. He gave one up early while trying to avoid contact on a middle-of-the-field strike from Trevor Lawrence. Another came on a much-needed deep shot later in the game. If Thomas misses any time, Travis Hunter is set to take over the No. 1 role in Jacksonville, putting him in the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd56-df81-ab9b-ffd7da4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Hunter caught 8-of-14 targets for 101 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 7 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6f76280000</link>
      <description>Liam Coen talked about getting Hunter more involved in the offense earlier this week and didn’t disappoint fantasy managers in London. Hunter accounted for 29 percent of the team’s targets and easily set a career-high in total opportunities. He also played sparingly on defense, though he did record a strong rep against Davante Adams on a deep shot from Matthew Stafford. Brian Thomas Jr. exited this game late with a shoulder injury and did not return. If he winds up missing time, Hunter would be locked in for the No. 1 role in Jacksonville, potentially making him a fantasy WR2 when the Jaguars return from their Week 8 bye to face the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6f76280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 21-of-33 passes for 182 yards and five touchdowns in the Rams’ 35-7, Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd72-da18-a39b-ff731e990000</link>
      <description>Stafford’s third of three passing scores to Davante Adams gave him the record for touchdown passes in an international game. It was also the third-fewest yards for a five-touchdown outing in the modern era, though that’s largely a testament to how efficient he was. With the benefit of an early game, Stafford now leads the league in passing touchdowns. He also leads the league in yardage and didn’t even need the London game to get there. The Rams now get a week of rest before taking on the Saints in Week 9. With Puka Nacua expected to be back, Stafford will push for a QB1 ranking for his next outing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd72-da18-a39b-ff731e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 5-of-8 targets for 35 yards and three touchdowns in the Rams’ Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd7e-d99b-a1dd-ff7ef3150000</link>
      <description>With Puka Nacua out this week, Adams was finally the focal point of the Rams’ offense. His 24 percent target share wasn’t anything to write home about, but it easily led the team. Adams was also Stafford’s go-to target in scoring position, as evidenced by the three touchdowns in his box score. Things should return to normal after the Rams’ Week 8 bye. Puka Nacua is expected to be back, meaning Adams will revert to his high-volume No. 2 role. That has still kept him in the WR2 ranks this year and nothing will change for his fantasy outlook in a good matchup with the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd7e-d99b-a1dd-ff7ef3150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 26-of-48 passes for 296 yards and one touchdown in the Jaguars’ 35-7, Week 7 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd86-df81-ab9b-ffc7bc250000</link>
      <description>The box score is far nicer to Lawrence than the film. Per usual, Lawrence sailed and short-changed plenty of passes, several of which could have been interceptions. He also took seven sacks, tying his career-high. The Jags were shut out for three quarters and did most of their damage on offense after the game was already decided. They were also called for 13 penalties in total and Lawrence’s receivers were responsible for a handful of drops once again. All of the Jaguars’ flaws were on full display in this game, resulting in a non-competitive beatdown in London. Liam Coen will attempt to rally the troops coming out of their Week 8 bye to face the Raiders. Lawrence will be nothing more than a low-end QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd86-df81-ab9b-ffc7bc250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (concussion) returned to the game against the Panthers in Week 7.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd97-df81-ab9b-ffd754d40000</link>
      <description>Fields took a wicked hit in the second quarter and was evaluated for a brain injury in the blue medical tent. He was reportedly cleared and will re-enter the game. Tyrod Taylor stepped in for Fields and moved the offense more efficiently than Fields had before the potential head injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd97-df81-ab9b-ffd754d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed eight times for 44 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 7 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd98-d99b-a1dd-ff9c17a60000</link>
      <description>Etienne was targeted three times but only brought in one for 11 yards. The Jags gave up 21 points on the Rams’ first four drives and failed to put up any of their own. The instant and insurmountable deficit proved disastrous for the team’s ground game. After a white hot start, Etienne has been held under 50 rushing yards in three straight games. He hasn’t scored since Week 4 either. With the Jaguars’ offense regressing in recent weeks, Etienne isn’t finding as much room to run and isn’t getting to tote the ball as often. He will fall to the end of the RB2 ranks when he returns from bye to face the Raiders in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd98-d99b-a1dd-ff9c17a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (knee) left Philadelphia’s Week 7 game against the Vikings and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd9c-d651-a9df-fd9d186e0000</link>
      <description>Brett Toth took over at center. The Eagles simply can’t seem to keep the interior of their line healthy. EDGE Azeez Ojulari (hamstring) and LB Jeremiah Trotter Jr. (hamstring) also left the game and are questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd9c-d651-a9df-fd9d186e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave (leg) was removed from the Week 7 game against the Bears and taken into the medical tent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd9d-d99b-a1dd-ff9d04ef0000</link>
      <description>Olave limped off the field before a third-down play in the second quarter and right into the medical tent. The oft-injured 25-year-old currently leads a dysfunctional Saints offense with two catches on three targets for six yards in what has become a high-volume, low-impact role with Spencer Rattler under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd9d-d99b-a1dd-ff9d04ef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
