<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) will not play in New Orleans’ Week 15 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13fb-d77b-adfb-dbfb14ef0000</link>
      <description>That makes it three weeks in a row with no practice or game for Kamara, who has been out since a Week 12 MCL sprain. It’s possible that he’ll make it back next week, but he certainly doesn’t have to be held at this point. He was playing like an RB3 in fantasy while playing through an ankle listing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-13fb-d77b-adfb-dbfb14ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints S Justin Reid (knee) is questionable for New Orleans’ Week 15 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1400-d8cf-affb-bc2af34b0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice on Wednesday, but the veteran probably has enough savvy to make it on to the field on Sunday if his knee cooperates. Reid had missed Week 14 and four straight practices before re-appearing on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1400-d8cf-affb-bc2af34b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (toe) is questionable for Buffalo’s Week 15 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1404-d1bc-a3fb-9524ecfd0000</link>
      <description>Benford picked up a toe injury in practice on Thursday and was a DNP on Friday. He was spotted without a walking boot on the sideline during Friday’s practice. He’s likely a true question mark at this point. LB Terrel Bernard (elbow) got in three limited sessions this week and was also put on the questionable line by Sean McDermott.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1404-d1bc-a3fb-9524ecfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox is not on Buffalo’s final Week 15 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1406-d1bc-a3fb-95265f280000</link>
      <description>Neither are Joey Bosa (hamstring/wrist) or Spencer Brown (shoulder) as the Bills look to be healthy in the trenches against the Patriots in a must-win game if they want any hope at the AFC East title this year. Joshua Palmer (ankle) is questionable after three limited sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1406-d1bc-a3fb-95265f280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Olamide Zaccheaus (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1405-d77b-adfb-de878c530000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus upgraded to full on Friday after logging two limited sessions. He has earned three targets in consecutive weeks and does not need to be in re-draft lineups, though he did manage to score a touchdown last week. He is just a touchdown-dependent WR5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1405-d77b-adfb-de878c530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (groin) is questionable for Week 15’s game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140a-d77b-adfb-de8b2fe70000</link>
      <description>A surprise questionable, at that. Johnston was limited in practice with the new designation. If Johnston were to miss this week’s game, he’d likely consolidate Justin Herbert’s target tree a bit rather than give his whole role over to rookie Tre Harris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140a-d77b-adfb-de8b2fe70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RT Trey Pipkins (ankle) is doubtful for Los Angeles’ Week 15 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140b-d8cf-affb-bc2b8e040000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week. The Chargers had Bobby Hart playing NFL snaps in 2025 after Pipkins went down in-game with the injury on Monday night. The good news is: It’s hard to imagine how the offensive line could protect Justin Herbert any worse at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140b-d8cf-affb-bc2b8e040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (abdomen) is not on New Orleans’ final Week 15 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140d-d005-a9bf-dc3df2430000</link>
      <description>He’ll be the lead back against the Panthers in Week 15 and is a borderline RB2/RB3 versus a Panthers defense that has operated as a pass funnel at times this season. Neal upgraded to a full practice today after two limited sessions to start the week. We don’t have any concerns about his injury at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140d-d005-a9bf-dc3df2430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said he “would be very surprised” if WR Davante Adams (hamstring) does not play in Week 15 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140c-d005-a9bf-dc3c43ca0000</link>
      <description>Adams is officially listed as questionable after sitting out on Wednesday and Thursday. His participation level on Friday has not yet been released. Adams ranks 26th in receiving yards (718) yet leads the NFL in receiving touchdowns (14) and is the only player to score more than nine times. If active, the Rams will continue to deploy him as a featured weapon in scoring position. He warrants WR1 treatment in an expectedly high-scoring game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-140c-d005-a9bf-dc3c43ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots G Jared Wilson (ankle) is not on New England’s final Week 15 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1410-d77b-adfb-de9371030000</link>
      <description>He was injured in Week 12’s win over the Bengals and missed two weeks of game action. Wilson practiced in full all week and his return should help the Pats get more consistent play inside while they continue to await the return of LT Will Campbell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1410-d77b-adfb-de9371030000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
