<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (back) said he’ll play against the Steelers in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b2c-d56e-afff-ffecda7a0000</link>
      <description>Jackson said he feels “great right now” and will wear extra padding in his back area on Sunday. The Ravens will just hope he can show them more of his 2024 form in his first game of the 2026 calendar year against the Steelers — a game they need to win to make the playoffs. Jackson practiced both Wednesday and Thursday. With some chance of re-injury, he’s likely a lower-end QB1 on the Week 18 slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b2c-d56e-afff-ffecda7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins claimed QB Cam Miller, formerly of the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b25-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50ef0000</link>
      <description>Miller became a bit of a dynasty darling after the Raiders drafted him in the sixth round last April. The former North Dakota State passer was on two FCS national championship squads and earned first-team FCS All-American honors in 2024. We do not expect Miller to steal the Dolphins’ starting job, but bringing him aboard makes sense for a team that is searching for long-term answers at the position. At the very least, he can serve as a functional contributor in training camp and the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b25-dc7a-af9b-ffbf50ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b2f-d35e-a1bf-7fef4fee0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid is on track to play in Week 18, though the knee issue is still seemingly bothering him. His backup, TE Dawson Knox, also remains limited by a knee injury of his own. The Bills (11-5) cannot overtake the Patriots (13-3), though they may be able to improve their Wild Card Weekend seeding. They face the Jets’ fantasy-friendly defense this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b2f-d35e-a1bf-7fef4fee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b3f-d35e-a1bf-7ffffc870000</link>
      <description>At this point, even if Odunze did practice on Friday, it’d be hard to trust him in fantasy lineups for Week 18. We expect the Bears to ramp him up next week to see if he can get involved in the playoffs. Odunze has not played since November 28.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b3f-d35e-a1bf-7ffffc870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (quad) practiced in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b41-d56e-afff-ffe972cc0000</link>
      <description>Burden should be in the top 25 in the wideout rankings this week as the Bears try to lock up the No. 2 seed against the Lions. The rookie wideout is on track to be removed from the injury report on Friday. He’s coming off a breakout 8/138/1 game against the 49ers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b41-d56e-afff-ffe972cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b51-d968-a19b-7bf1de150000</link>
      <description>The team opted not to place Kamara on injured reserve, though he has been sidelined since Week 12. Unless something drastic occurs, Saints RB Audric Estime will start in Kamara’s stead against the Falcons on Sunday. Both teams have been eliminated from the playoffs, but it still gives coaches a chance to evaluate key players one last time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b51-d968-a19b-7bf1de150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Breece Hall (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b4f-d968-a19b-7bff2c6c0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from a Wednesday DNP. With Isaiah Davis (concussion) unlikely to play in Week 18, it’s possible that Hall has the backfield mostly to himself as the main actual backup on the roster — not returner Kene Nwangwu — is journeyman Khalil Herbert. If Buffalo rests starters, it’s possible that Hall could do some fantasy damage in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b4f-d968-a19b-7bff2c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Mason Tipton (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b41-d56e-afff-ffe9285a0000</link>
      <description>Tipton is now on the wrong side of questionable, which is unfortunate. The Saints will be without WR Chris Olave, who is in the hospital, recovering from a blood clot in his lung. This likely leaves WRs Kevin Austin and Dante Pettis atop the depth chart against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b41-d56e-afff-ffe9285a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Isaiah Davis (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b5a-d56e-afff-fffa44fc0000</link>
      <description>It’s looking unlikely that Davis will be cleared for Week 18 given the lack of practice — it suggests he’s still in the beginning stages of the protocol. If he rests, Khalil Herbert will likely see backup reps behind Breece Hall against the Bills on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b5a-d56e-afff-fffa44fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (neck) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b5b-d35e-a1bf-7fdbdea20000</link>
      <description>It would be surprising if Taylor played in Week 18’s game after two DNPs to open up the week. He hasn’t played since Week 14. We anticipate writing his season wrap-up blurb on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b5b-d35e-a1bf-7fdbdea20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
