<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Juszczyk caught his only target for 11 yards in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf72-d968-a19b-dff340500000</link>
      <description>Juicecheck had his most prolific regular season in terms of catches and touches since 2021, recording a 24-213-2 receiving line in the regular season and a 4/49 performance in the Wild Card round against the Eagles. He’ll enter free agency again this offseason and figures to be a low-priority target for the 49ers entering his age-35 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf72-d968-a19b-dff340500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddy Pineiro made both of his field-goal attempts in San Francisco’s Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf73-d35e-a1bf-cff31d410000</link>
      <description>Pineiro missed just one of his 29 attempts on the season — 32 if you count the postseason — after the 49ers finally moved on from Jake Moody following Week 1. He now has hit 139-of-155 regular season attempts in six years in the league. It’s very funny that he was freely available to anyone before Week 2 and had a season this good. A 2026 free agent, the 49ers will probably prioritize re-signing him after this performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-cf73-d35e-a1bf-cff31d410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald told reporters the team believes Zach Charbonnet’s knee is structurally intact.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d137-d35e-a1bf-d5f797330000</link>
      <description>Charbonnett left the Seahawks’ Divisional Round win over the 49ers with a knee injury. The team listed him as questionable to return, but he never reappeared in the blowout game. Macdonald said Charbonnet will undergo an MRI on his knee and the team is optimistic. He at least has a shot at playing in the NFC Championship game. If he doesn’t, Kenneth Walker, who just ran for 116 yards and three scores, will be in line for another massive day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d137-d35e-a1bf-d5f797330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers defensive coordinator Jeff Hafley is meeting with the Dolphins and Titans this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d141-d968-a19b-d9f177480000</link>
      <description>Hafley will meet with Miami brass on Monday before talking to the Titans on Tuesday. He has already met with both virtually. These meetings will be in person. Schefter added, “As was the case with Kevin Stefanski in Atlanta, a deal could come together quickly.” It sounds like these two teams will have a bidding war early in the week before Hafley makes his decision. Hafley does have a connection to Miami via Dolphins GM Jon-Eric Sullivan. The latter was just hired by the Dolphins after spending over two decades in Green Bay’s front office. We suspect that’s where he winds up, but this is still an open race between the Titans and Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d141-d968-a19b-d9f177480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns will interview Ravens offensive coordinator Todd Monken for their head coaching vacancy a second time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1b9-d35e-a1bf-d5fb7e1b0000</link>
      <description>Monken will have an in-person interview with the Browns on Tuesday. Making it to the second round of interviews is a good sign for his odds of landing the job. Even if he doesn’t, Monken is a highly coveted offensive coordinator who will have no issues finding work for 2026. He is already considered one of the leading candidates for the Giants’ OC job. Browns defensive coordinator Jim Schwartz is also getting a second interview for their head coaching vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1b9-d35e-a1bf-d5fb7e1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Titans will interview Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy for their head coaching vacancy a second time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1bd-dc7a-af9b-dfbff20d0000</link>
      <description>The Titans already conducted a virtual interview with Nagy. They will now meet him in person later this week. They are also pursuing Packers DC Jeff Hafley, who is likely their first choice. If Hafley doesn’t take the job, Nagy could get a second chance at leading a team. He went 34-31 with the Bears after a successful run as the Chiefs’ quarterbacks coach and eventually offensive coordinator. His latest stint as the Chiefs’ OC has not gone as well. With the best quarterback on the planet at his disposal, Nagy’s Chiefs have topped out at 15th in points per game over the past three years. It’s hard to see him doing better with Cam Ward under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1bd-dc7a-af9b-dfbff20d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Steelers “are expected to speak with former Cowboys HC Mike McCarthy about their head coach vacancy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1c5-dc7a-af9b-dfff4f380000</link>
      <description>As Schefter notes, McCarthy was born in Pittsburgh and worked under Steelers GM Omar Khan during his time in New Orleans in the early 2000s. For a team that just moved on from Mike Tomlin because of his recent lack of playoff success, McCarthy would be a bit of an odd choice. He made the playoffs three times during five seasons in Dallas but managed to win just one postseason game. McCarthy was, however, more successful in Green Bay. He won a Super Bowl over the Steelers and made the NFC Championship three other times. His track record in the postseason is a mixed bag at best, but the Steelers could do worse in this head coaching cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1c5-dc7a-af9b-dfff4f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports, “The Eagles and special teams coach Michael Clay have agreed to terms on a new deal.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1cf-dc7a-af9b-dfff47540000</link>
      <description>Rapoport didn’t have the specifics of the deal, but Clay’s contract was set to expire and the team allowed him to interview for a lateral move in Tampa Bay. After exploring other options, the two sides reached a deal to keep Clay in Philly for the foreseeable future. Clay has held the role of special teams coordinator in Philadelphia for five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1cf-dc7a-af9b-dfff47540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Eagles are expected to interview former Giants head coach Brian Daboll for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1f3-d56e-afff-f7fb2dc70000</link>
      <description>Daboll also has an interview for the Chargers’ vacant OC gig lined up. The Titans met with him to discuss their head coach opening, but the team has started their second round of interviews and he hasn’t been called back. We will assume for now that he isn’t in the running for that job anymore. Still, Daboll shouldn’t have any issues landing a coordinator job given the initial interest he has received. Previous reports have Daboll at the top of the Eagles’ wishlist of OC candidates, along with Mike McDaniel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d1f3-d56e-afff-f7fb2dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Michael Silver reports Bills offensive line coach Aaron Kromer is expected to retire.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</link>
      <description>Kromer has been with the Bills for four seasons. He has been in the NFL for over 20 years, primarily as an offensive line coach, no matter the team. Pro Football Focus graded the Bills’ line as a top-10 unit in both run and pass protection this year. With Kromer hanging up the clipboard and multiple starters on expiring contracts, Buffalo’s line could look drastically different in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d204-d35e-a1bf-d7c66e5d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
