<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39ea-d5f6-abfd-b9ff42210000</link>
      <description>Oliver practiced in full yesterday. The development is a bad sign for his Week 2 availability. Oliver currently leads the team in quarterback pressures (four), ties for a team-high in sacks (one) and ranks second in tackles (five). The Bills are tasked with containing the Jets’ rushing attack this week. Losing Oliver would be consequential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39ea-d5f6-abfd-b9ff42210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB James Cook (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39ee-d214-a3b9-3ffeac580000</link>
      <description>Cook unexpectedly appeared on the Bills’ injury report as a limited participant yesterday. It was unclear when the injury occurred, but today’s full session suggests it is not a fresh strain and he should be good to go for his typical workload against the Jets on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39ee-d214-a3b9-3ffeac580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39f1-d214-a3b9-3ffd8c7f0000</link>
      <description>Knox is not a starter in 12-team fantasy leagues. If he were to miss time, though, it would positively impact Dalton Kincaid’s snap share. In Week 1, Knox logged 48 offensive snaps to Kincaid’s 43. A near-full-time role for Kincaid would work wonders for his fantasy-scoring potential. Knox’s continued limited participation puts him on track to play, but if he remains limited on Friday, Kincaid would have a chance to at least flip the snap shares between the two of them in Week 2 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39f1-d214-a3b9-3ffd8c7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will practice “in some capacity” on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39f2-d214-a3b9-3ffeefe20000</link>
      <description>We expect Worthy to be limited in today’s session. It’s a step in the right direction after Worthy sat out during Wednesday’s practice. If Worthy can practice in full tomorrow, he could be good to go for Week 2 against the Eagles, though sitting out at least one week seems likely. Stay tuned. Chiefs rookie WR Jalen Royals (knee tendinitis) will not practice today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-39f2-d214-a3b9-3ffeefe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-da68-ad9d-ff5f49380000</link>
      <description>On the heels of a report that Goedert’s status may be “up in the air” for Week 2 on Wednesday, this DNP feels ominous. Goedert will likely need to do something on Friday to hit the questionable line. His absence could help drag A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith into high-target territory against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-da68-ad9d-ff5f49380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley (ribs) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a15-da68-ad9d-ff5fd57f0000</link>
      <description>He was present at practice but did not participate. Even if he is questionable and practices on Friday, it feels likely that the Eagles will shift some workload off his plate with the addition of Tank Bigsby. Shipley is not the miracle desperation FLEX you’re looking for in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a15-da68-ad9d-ff5fd57f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed RB Ty Chandler (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a17-d8e3-affd-7bb7a5330000</link>
      <description>Blake Cashman (hamstring) joins him in missing at least the next four weeks. Zavier Scott will elevate to the team’s No. 3 back in Chandler’s absence. Cam Akers is undoubtedly leaving calls on Kevin O’Connell’s phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a17-d8e3-affd-7bb7a5330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio said the Chiefs and Steelers’ interest in trading for Tyreek Hill has been “complicated” by Hill’s most recent domestic violence allegations.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-d214-a3b9-3e7d1cc30000</link>
      <description>Florio opines that Hill will not be on the Dolphins’ roster next year, and with the Dolphins’ season already “off the rails,” jettisoning Hill sooner rather than later makes sense. The accusations made public from Hill’s current divorce case could result in a suspension, and Florio notes that “any team that would be interested in trading for Tyreek Hill wants to be sure that they’re not trading for a guy who’s going to be suspended before the end of the season.” If the Chiefs or Steelers are willing to bring him aboard, it stands to reason that they might choose to wait until after the NFL’s investigation concludes before making an offer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a0d-d214-a3b9-3e7d1cc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a1b-da68-ad9d-ff5b0a3d0000</link>
      <description>At this point it would be surprising if Likely played in Week 2, which should keep Mark Andrews’ usage boosted — for all the good that did on Sunday — and condense the target tree in Baltimore. Likely still hasn’t practiced since undergoing surgery towards the end of July after getting hurt in a training camp practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a1b-da68-ad9d-ff5b0a3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Goedeke (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a21-da68-ad9d-ff7b97ff0000</link>
      <description>Nine days after getting an extension, Tampa’s stalwart right tackle pops up on the injury report with a new injury. Coach Todd Bowles said he is “hopeful” Goedeke can play, and Goedeke did play all 58 snaps on Sunday. His absence would be huge for a line already missing Tristan Wirfs against a fearsome Texans front on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3a21-da68-ad9d-ff7b97ff0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
