<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:20:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe believes Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley will prioritize physicality and toughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said the Dolphins under Hafley will transition from a roster predicated on speed to one based on size and toughness. The team will also look to emulate the Packers in drafting and developing players instead of making splash signings in free agency, Wolfe said. Hafley, 46, who served as Green Bay’s defensive coordinator over the past two seasons, will look to revamp a Miami defense that last year allowed the NFL’s second highest drop back success rate and the ninth highest rushing success rate. Look for the Dolphins to invest heavily in defensive players in the 2026 NFL Draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbe0-d968-a19b-dbf10a200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens will interview Broncos special teams coordinator Darren Rizzi for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbea-dc7a-af9b-dfffdf650000</link>
      <description>Rizzi, a longtime in special teams coordinator in New Orleans before coming to the Broncos in 2025, reportedly impressed during interviews for the Giants head coaching vacancy and could be a dark horse to take over as Baltimore’s head coach after the Ravens parted ways with longtime coach John Harbaugh, who, like Rizzi, was a special teams coordinator before getting the top job in Baltimore. Rizzi’s Denver special teams unit has been among the league’s best this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dbea-dc7a-af9b-dfffdf650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC WGRZ’s Vic Carruci reports the firing of Bills head coach Sean McDermott is “being met with skepticism by players who held McDermott in high regard.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc03-d56e-afff-feeb85270000</link>
      <description>McDermott reportedly lost out in a massive power struggle with general manager Brandon Beane, who not only kept his job after assembling a mediocre roster, but was promoted to president of football operations. Beane will oversee the evaluation and hiring of McDermott’s replacement after nine successful years at the helm. Carruci said that during a meeting held five weeks ago between McDermott, Beane and Bills owner Terry Pegula, “the coach pointed out what the roster lacked to win a Super Bowl. I don’t know the specifics McDermott mentioned, but I’m told neither Beane nor Pegula was pleased with McDermott’s assessment.” Having won the power struggle, Beane will now have the chance to shape the franchise in his image as Josh Allen turns 30 in May.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc03-d56e-afff-feeb85270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connor Hughes reports Giants head coach John Harbaugh is expected “to be aggressive in targeting ex-Ravens in free agency.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc35-d35e-a1bf-ddf7af2a0000</link>
      <description>After coaching the Ravens for 18 years, it’s no surprise Harbaugh would try to get the band back together in New York. That could include C Tyler Linderbaum, who played under Harbaugh in Baltimore from 2022 to 2025. Linderbaum, 26, is an unrestricted free agent this offseason and a potential upgrade for a Giants offensive line that struggled throughout 2025. Harbaugh could also pursue Patrick Ricard and Isaiah Likely in free agency. Harbaugh could also bring in coaches he had during his time in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc35-d35e-a1bf-ddf7af2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud said he’s “still getting adjusted to” the team’s offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</link>
      <description>Stroud said after the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots that “there are no excuses” for throwing four interceptions on 47 attempts against New England, but that he was still getting comfortable in an offensive scheme installed by first-year offensive coordinator Nick Caley. Stroud in 2025 completed 64.5 percent of his passes for 3,041 yards and 19 touchdowns with eight interceptions, improving in most categories after a letdown of a 2024 season following his outstanding 2023 rookie campaign. The Texans will have to make a decision on Stroud’s fifth-year contract option by May 1, and head coach DeMeco Ryans said after the team’s postseason loss that he would not discuss the team’s plans for Stroud, who turns 25 in October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the probable cause trespassing charges against Vikings WR Jordan Addison won’t be filed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</link>
      <description>Addison, who was arrested last week, “will prepare for the filing of a civil claim arising from the alleged wrongful arrest,” according to Garafolo. “As Mr. Addison’s agent has advised, from the very outset of this incident and arrest, Mr. Addison committed no legal wrong doing,” Addison’s attorney said in a statement. “We are thrilled that the truth was finally revealed and this poor man’s name was not besmirched any longer. I am thankful we were able to bring this to light as quickly as possible.” Addison has had other run-ins with the law, including a DUI, which led to a suspension. The Vikings will have to decide this offseason on extending a fifth-year option or beginning contract talks with Addison, entering his fourth season in the league in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired former Titans offensive line coach Bill Callahan as their offensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfecc80000</link>
      <description>It was a rumored move, and we’re a bit surprised because we expected Callahan to rejoin his son Brian in whatever offensive role the younger Callahan landed. The Falcons will let Dwayne Ledford, a well-respected offensive line coach, hit free agency. Ledford should be on several teams radars. There’s no disputing that Callahan is one of the best offensive line coaches in the business despite his relative struggles to fix the Titans’ woes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfecc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals are interviewing Bills offensive coordinator Joe Brady regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</link>
      <description>Brady, who Mike Garafolo adds has a second interview scheduled with the Ravens, is now on the radars of Arizona, Las Vegas, and Baltimore. He had interviewed for the Miami and Tennessee jobs before they were filled yesterday, as well. Brady had seemed to have a down season on paper as Bills offensive coordinator. He struggled to create downfield pass plays with Josh Allen. But it doesn’t seem like the NFL as a whole has agreed that it was his fault.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</link>
      <description>Baltimore’s process drags on. The Ravens had a 16-coach list (that we know of), and are beginning the second interview phase shortly. Of Baltimore’s interviews, Kevin Stefanski and Robert Saleh have come off the board already. It looks like Anthony Weaver, Jesse Minter, and Joe Brady are early finalists for the position. It’s Campanile’s second head coaching interview, and with the Dolphins job now secured, his only active lead towards being a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired former Steelers special teams coach Danny Smith as their special teams coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</link>
      <description>The 72-year-old had been with the Steelers for the past 13 years, but was allowed to walk after Mike Tomlin stepped down. He should bring some stability to one of the worst special-teams units in the NFL last year. Todd Bowles has at least gotten off to a good start on fixing some of the issues his team had in 2025 through staff changes here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
