<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (concussion) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b1-dd4c-afb9-eff1cd6f0000</link>
      <description>Both Downs and WR Ashton Dulin (chest) were absent during the portion of practice that is open to the media. We expect both players to be listed as non-participants. This is bad news. Players must pass through all five phases of the NFL’s concussion protocol, while remaining setback-free, before they can return from a concussion. Even if a concussed player resumes practicing late in the week, the protocol adds a unique hurdle to the return-to-play process. Should Downs practice in full on Friday, he must then successfully meet post-practice observation standards. The Colts’ slot receiver has not yet been ruled out, and he does still have a chance to play, but he is trending toward a Week 7 absence. Colts WR Adonai Mitchell will seemingly get a shot at redemption against the Chargers with Dulin also ailing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e9b1-dd4c-afb9-eff1cd6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Ashton Dulin (chest) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edfe-d99b-a1dd-fffe53f80000</link>
      <description>Both Dulin and slot receiver Josh Downs (concussion) were not present during the portion of practice that is open to the media. Dulin could still get on the field this weekend by returning to practice on Friday, but both players appear to be heading toward a Week 7 absence. Embattled second-year WR Adonai Mitchell could get a chance to rebound from his costly Week 4 fumble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-edfe-d99b-a1dd-fffe53f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pauline reports that the Seahawks would be willing to trade CB Riq Woolen for Dolphins RB De’Von Achane “if the opportunity existed.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee02-da18-a39b-fe13d3470000</link>
      <description>Per Pauline, “even if no such deal [involving Woolen] is available, Seattle could make a move for the ball carrier if Miami continues to lose games and chooses to sell off pieces.” The Seahawks are apparently very interested in Achane’s “speed and home run-hitting ability not presently found at running back for the Seahawks.” Speed and home-run hitting ability sound an awful lot like RB Kenneth Walker III’s skillset. Walker is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. The 4-2 Seahawks are currently fifth in the NFC, and GM John Schneider spent the offseason harping on the importance of locker room harmony. Pauline does not address whether a follow-up trade involving one of the incumbent running backs could occur, and the Dolphins must first be willing to part ways with a talented, young running back under contract through 2026, for a second trade to even be considered. No reporter is perfect, but Pauline has reported accurately on Seahawks happenings during the Schneider era. Whether the Seahawks successfully acquire Achane remains to be seen, but it sounds like they could be in play for a speedy running back before the November 4th trade deadline, regardless. Achane’s fantasy-scoring ceiling would likely take a hit if he is thrust into a split backfield in Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee02-da18-a39b-fe13d3470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Terry McLaurin (quad) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee0f-da18-a39b-fe1fce240000</link>
      <description>McLaurin practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday after sitting out since Week 2. It is possible this is just a pre-planned rest day following McLaurin’s return to practice, though the fact that a Thursday rest day might be necessary suggests the team could be without him for another week. He should be considered truly questionable to play in Week 7 against the Cowboys. If active, a WR2 finish is within his range of potential outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee0f-da18-a39b-fe1fce240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee33-d99b-a1dd-fe3ff6220000</link>
      <description>Nacua is already viewed as a “long shot” to play this week, so his absence during the portion of practice that is open to the media is not surprising. The Rams go on bye in Week 8, so resting their injured star this week makes sense. Should Nacua indeed sit, WR Davante Adams will command an enormous target share. With No. 3 WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) rehabbing an injury of his own, WR Jordan Whittington could warrant FLEX consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee33-d99b-a1dd-fe3ff6220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee33-d99b-a1dd-fe3fcd890000</link>
      <description>Samuel has been practicing intermittently due to the heel issue since Week 5, and he’s turned in starkly contrasting performances since then. It would be nice to see Samuel graduate to full participation on Friday, since WR Terry McLaurin (quad) was downgraded to a DNP today after practicing in a limited capacity on Wednesday. The Commanders face the Cowboys’ fantasy-friendly defense in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee33-d99b-a1dd-fe3fcd890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee13-d99b-a1dd-fe1fe1340000</link>
      <description>We expect Jones to be listed as a non-participant on the team’s official injury report later today. With WRs Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) and Michael Wilson (foot) nursing injuries of their own, Jones seemingly had a chance to sneak onto the FLEX radar this week, but he is now on the wrong side of questionable for Arizona’s Week 7 game against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee13-d99b-a1dd-fe1fe1340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury said he was “still confident” in Jacory Croskey-Merritt despite his fumbles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee53-d651-a9df-ef57d4a00000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt put the ball on the turf in each of the last two games, while Jayden Daniels bobbled a handoff on a snap to “Bill” in the fourth quarter that also wound up as a Commanders turnover. It’s never a good sign when the offensive coordinator is being asked about the fumbles as a frequent problem, but it doesn’t sound like the Commanders have wavered from “Bill” despite this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee53-d651-a9df-ef57d4a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee55-d651-a9df-ef558e3b0000</link>
      <description>Demercado is heading toward a Week 7 absence. Assuming this is the case, and Bam Knight is able to play through his knee injury, the Cardinals will again employ a two-player backfield featuring Knight and RB Michael Carter. Knight handled primary rushing duties while Carter operated as the passing game specialist in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee55-d651-a9df-ef558e3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee56-d651-a9df-ef5703c70000</link>
      <description>Njoku is enough of a veteran to possibly get a Friday practice going, ride a questionable tag, and play on Sunday. We haven’t quite ruled him out yet, but odds are certainly dwindling that he’ll be active. If he were to be inactive, Harold Fannin would have a great matchup against the Dolphins and, along with Quinshon Judkins, would seem likely to take advantage of it on the surface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee56-d651-a9df-ef5703c70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
