<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:30:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 14-of-23 passes for 141 yards in the Broncos’ 19-3, Week 18 win over the Chargers, rushing eight times for 49 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b90-d968-a19b-dbf1ebdd0000</link>
      <description>Nix started his day in a fantasy-friendly manner, completing three passes for eight yards and rushing twice for 28 yards. Things slowed down from there. The game’s only touchdown was scored by the Broncos’ defense. The offense settled for four field goal attempts, all of which were converted. Despite the underwhelming outing, the Broncos have secured the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed and will go on bye next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b90-d968-a19b-dbf1ebdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grant Calcaterra caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 18 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb3-d968-a19b-dbf3afd30000</link>
      <description>Calcaterra took over as the Eagles’ starting tight end with Dallas Goedert out for Week 18. He made a 15-yard touchdown catch to open scoring in the second quarter and was available frequently in the intermediate area. He suffered ankle/knee injuries on an un-flagged hip drop tackle in the third quarter, leading to a locker room visit. Calcaterra returned to the sideline but Kylen Granson finished the game at tight end, catching 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards. Neither Calcaterra nor Granson are relevant when Goedert is playing, but Granson may see increased opportunities in the Wild Card against the 49ers if Calcaterra’s injury is serious.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb3-d968-a19b-dbf3afd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Williams caught 5-of-7 targets for 24 yards in the Jets’ Week 18 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb8-dc7a-af9b-cfbf17650000</link>
      <description>Those numbers were team highs in targets, catches, and receiving yards on the day. That says a lot about how bad this Jets offense looked. Williams is primarily a return man, but he was forced into a much larger role in the Jets’ passing attack late in the season and finished with 26 catches on 36 targets for 193 yards. The 24-year-old showed enough juice in that role to be a strong candidate to remain the fifth receiver on the Jets last year, due to his special teams value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb8-dc7a-af9b-cfbf17650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Beck caught 1-of-2 targets for two yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 18 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bba-d968-a19b-dbfb0b7c0000</link>
      <description>Cool. The fullback will finish the season with six catches on nine targets for 45 yards and two touchdowns. He also had one carry for five yards, but it did gain a first down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bba-d968-a19b-dbfb0b7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Williams completed 20-of-33 passes for 212 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Bears’ 19-16, Week 18 loss to the Lions, adding one yard on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb6-d56e-afff-effe27d90000</link>
      <description>The Bears failed to score through three quarters after gaining only four first downs in the first half. They would eventually break through in the fourth quarter to avoid being shut out at Soldier Field for the first time since 1982, taking on an additional score and two-point conversion with just over five minutes remaining to draw the game to an unlikely tie. Jared Goff and the Lions did their jobs in the two-minute offense to steal the victory away from a Bears team that has experienced no shortage of late-game magic this season. The Bears maintained the No. 2 seed in the NFC following a loss by the Eagles, meaning they’ll host a familiar opponent in the Packers in the Wildcard Round next weekend. Williams will need to buck this recent trend of poor performance early in games if they want to avoid a one-and-done postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb6-d56e-afff-effe27d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Ruckert didn’t have a single target in the Jets’ Week 18 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bbb-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0db0000</link>
      <description>Ruckert was poked in the eye early in this game, but the Jets only had 60 passing yards in the entire game. Even though Ruckert only had 23 catches on 29 targets for 179 yards and a touchdown this season, he was recently signed to an extension and will be back with the Jets in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bbb-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd0db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Johnson completed 14-of-22 passes for 131 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Commanders’ 24-17, Week 18 win over the Eagles, adding nine carries for 45 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb9-dc7a-af9b-cfbffa350000</link>
      <description>Career journeyman Josh Johnson made two starts for the Commanders, both at the end of the season after Jayden Daniels and Marcus Mariota were ruled out due to injuries and Washington was eliminated. The 39-year-old passed for 372 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions over two starts and five games, adding 55 yards and a touchdown on the ground. A touch pass to John Bates in the fourth quarter of Week 18 against the Eagles was Johnson’s first touchdown pass since 2021. Johnson has been in the NFL for 18 seasons as a backup quarterback. He could certainly find work in a quarterback room once again for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb9-dc7a-af9b-cfbffa350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku told reporters that he would like to re-sign with the Browns in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb9-d35e-a1bf-cffb6be20000</link>
      <description>Njoku, 29, will become a free agent once the 2025 season officially ends. In order for him to do so, he will likely have to sign a team-friendly deal, placing him firmly in the No. 2 spot behind breakout rookie TE Harold Fannin, who supplanted Njoku outright this season. Njoku was the subject of trade rumors earlier this year, but nothing came to fruition. Njoku exuberantly celebrated the outcome despite his diminishing role. Were he to remain in Cleveland, he would not be on the fantasy TE1 radar in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bb9-d35e-a1bf-cffb6be20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 2-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Bills’ Week 18 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bbd-d35e-a1bf-cfffe76b0000</link>
      <description>With the Bills sitting the majority of their starters, Keon Coleman was able to work himself back into a larger role in the passing game. It was also clear that the Bills, or Mitchell Trubisky, were making a concerted effort to give Coleman some key targets in the hopes of getting him into a bit of rhythm before the postseason. This year has certainly not gone the way Coleman and the Bills wanted, but he can go a long way towards redeeming himself with a strong postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bbd-d35e-a1bf-cfffe76b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 10-of-11 targets for 76 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 18 win over the Cardinals, adding two carries for 24 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8baa-dc7a-af9b-cfbf08e90000</link>
      <description>Nacua’s 10 catches in Week 18 made him the NFL’s receptions leader for the year, narrowly edging out Trey McBride in this same game. He also pulled ahead of Jaxson Smith-Njigba in receptions, though JSN somewhat easily led the league in yards. Nacua closed out the regular season as fantasy football’s WR1 overall for the year. Only Justin Jefferson has more receiving yards in the first three years of a player’s career. By every measure, Nacua is off to one of the greatest starts to a career in NFL history. Nacua will have more competition for targets in the Wild Card Round when Davante Adams returns, but that has yet to stop him from putting up monster numbers this year. Nacua will be the WR1 for next week’s slate of games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8baa-dc7a-af9b-cfbf08e90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
