<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:01:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-7 targets for 31 yards in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbb-da18-a39b-ffbb41c40000</link>
      <description>Jennings continues to gut through multiple injuries, this time finishing one target off the team lead behind running back Christian McCaffrey. Even so, a muted game environment in which the two teams combined for only 616 yards of total offense led to only 26 pass attempts from quarterback Mac Jones, leaving Jennings’ fantasy returns of little interest. Up next is a difficult matchup with a stout Houston defense in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbb-da18-a39b-ffbb41c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught 2-of-2 targets for 14 yards in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbd-d99b-a1dd-ffbdce820000</link>
      <description>After amassing 284 yards the previous two games while working as the top pass-catcher, the returns of Jauan Jennings and George Kittle left Bourne with only two targets on a night quarterback Mac Jones attempted only 26 passes. It is clear that Bourne is capable of returning solid counting stats when he serves as the top option through the air, but that might not be the case as the team continues inching closer to full health. Bourne should remain on fantasy benches ahead of a Week 8 meeting with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffbd-d99b-a1dd-ffbdce820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle failed to catch either of his two targets in the 49ers’ Week 7 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffc0-d651-a9df-ffd555420000</link>
      <description>Kittle left fantasy managers with a nice goose egg in his return from injured reserve but made his presence felt while helping to spring running back Christian McCaffrey for a season-high 129 yards on the ground. This was the first game all season in which the 49ers played with both Kittle and fullback Kyle Juszczyk for the duration of the game, and the returns were sparkling - at least as the team was concerned. Kittle remains unlikely to command elite volume but maintains a lofty weekly ceiling considering his per-catch upside, making him a wide range of outcomes play ahead of a meeting with the stout Texans in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ffc0-d651-a9df-ffd555420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “no changes are expected at this time” for the Dolphins this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0196-d99b-a1df-3b9e7a8e0000</link>
      <description>This could be in reference to the future of Mike McDaniel, whose Dolphins sit at 1-6 on the season, but the recent performances out of Tua Tagovailoa are also drawing plenty of criticism. Things have unraveled quickly for the fourth-year head coach, who is rapidly approaching a second-consecutive losing season after going 8-9 last season, and Tagovailoa is sitting on a 1,313-11-10 passing line and is coming off back-to-back three-interception performances. In Week 7’s loss to the Browns, the Dolphins looked completely disinterested in the 31-6 defeat, raising plenty of questions for all involved in this disaster. While changes aren’t expected at this time, it goes without saying that another performance like what we saw in Week 7 could force a big change in one way or another.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0196-d99b-a1df-3b9e7a8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he is undecided on who will start at quarterback in Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-01f9-da18-a39a-dbfbc2210000</link>
      <description>We would expect Glenn to eventually name Tyrod Taylor the starter for Week 8’s game against the Bengals, but given his often vague nature at the podium and steadfastness in defending Justin Fields, this may not be a decision we get until later in the week. Fields was benched favor of Taylor entering the second half of Sunday’s loss tot he Panthers, and while the offense as a whole didn’t fare much better, Taylor at least got the passing game moving in a forward direction. Regardless of who is under center for the Jets, we wouldn’t expect the end result to look much different when they take on Bengals team that has shown some life with Joe Flacco now at the helm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-01f9-da18-a39a-dbfbc2210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said “I hope that he plays” when asked about Garrett Wilson (knee) being available for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0216-d651-a9df-6b1771140000</link>
      <description>Hope don’t float, and Glenn was quick to follow up his semi-optimistic comment with acknowledging that he will wait to see what the doctors have to say about Wilson’s health entering the week. Wilson suffered a knee injury in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos and was a DNP in practice all of last week. It was reported a week ago by ESPN’s Adam Schefter that Wilson is expected to miss “a couple weeks,” suggesting he’s at least one more week removed from a return. It’s possible something has changed over that time, but Glenn, whose Jets sit at 0-7, is searching for answers in multiple areas, including this one. Wilson’s status will be one to watch for when the first injury report is released on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0216-d651-a9df-6b1771140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Sauce Gardner is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0224-da18-a39a-da37365a0000</link>
      <description>Gardner left Week 3’s game against the Buccaneers with what was believed to be a concussion but never entered the league’s protocol. Now, the fourth-year corner will enter concussion protocol and have to clear it in time to play in Week 8’s game against the Bengals lively passing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0224-da18-a39a-da37365a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Breece Hall should be “fine” ahead of Week 8’s game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0249-da18-a39a-da5b8b3c0000</link>
      <description>Whatever injuries Hall is dealing with appear to be from the normal wear and tear of the season. The Jets RB1 totaled 52 yards from scrimmage in Week 7’s loss to the Panthers, and has been noticeably limited in the passing game despite the constant negative game scripts the Jets find themselves in. Hall gets a generous Week 8 matchup against the Bengals and should have a chance at a decent fantasy day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0249-da18-a39a-da5b8b3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports an MRI revealed Bryce Young suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 7’s win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0254-df81-ab9b-7ed781ee0000</link>
      <description>According to Pelissero, Young’s injury is the type that “is generally a 2-4 week injury,” but he adds that the Panthers are hopeful he could be back after just one game. Young’s practice availability throughout the coming weeks will tell us everything we need to know regarding his outlook come game day, but it doesn’t come as much of a surprise to hear he is expected to miss Sunday’s game against the Bills. Assuming Young does miss, Andy Dalton would make his first start of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0254-df81-ab9b-7ed781ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys designated LB DeMarvion Overshown (knee) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-026c-df81-ab9b-7eeff1ed0000</link>
      <description>Overshown has been recovering from a knee injury he suffered in Week 14 of last season. The talented linebacker totaled 90 tackles and five sacks in the 13 games he appeared in during the 2024 campaign after missing all of 2023 with a knee injury he suffered during the preseason. Now that he’s designated for return, the Cowboys will have 21 days to activate Overshown to the 53-man roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-026c-df81-ab9b-7eeff1ed0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
