<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 20:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan Alexander reports there’s an “extremely low” chance C.J. Stroud (concussion) will play in Week 12 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-980c-d673-a39e-bc9de9140000</link>
      <description>Stroud is expected to return to practice Wednesday but has almost no chance to suit up Thursday night against the Bills, almost three weeks after suffering his head injury. Davis Mills will be in line to get another start for Houston. Over the past two weeks, Mills is fifth among all quarterbacks in passing yards, with three touchdown to one interception. He ranks 19th in accuracy over those two weeks. Mills will remain a decent superflex option in Week 12 against a suspect Buffalo defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-980c-d673-a39e-bc9de9140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982d-d713-ad9e-fc7d2bd40000</link>
      <description>No surprise here after the Monday DNP, Kincaid has not practiced since leaving Week 10’s game against the Dolphins. Perhaps the mini-bye will get him back in the right place, but this is trending towards another DNP and his status for Week 13 should be considered questionable as well at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982d-d713-ad9e-fc7d2bd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Curtis Samuel (elbow/neck) will not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982e-d45b-affe-ddbee9280000</link>
      <description>Neither will Mecole Hardman (calf), and with Buffalo’s wideout depth in trouble for Week 12, it looks like the sort of perfect storm to get Keon Coleman active again for Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-982e-d45b-affe-ddbee9280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans K Ka’imi Fairbairn practiced in full on Monday and is “expected back” for Week 12.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-983f-d673-a39e-bcbf31030000</link>
      <description>So long, Matthew Wright. Fairbairn will regain his spot in the K1 conversation this week as the Texans take on the Bills on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-983f-d673-a39e-bcbf31030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman believes Jayden Reed (collarbone) could return to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-984d-d45b-affe-dddf0f410000</link>
      <description>Such a move would involve opening his 21-day window to return from injured reserve. Reed has been on injured reserve since suffering a broken collarbone in Week 2 and apparently also underwent foot surgery to address a Jones fracture. Packers coach Matt LaFleur was less forthcoming about Reed when asked if anyone was coming back this week but “flashed a massive smile while saying, ‘I sure as heck hope so.’” Reed’s return, whenever it officially happens, would probably shake up Green Bay’s wideout pecking order for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-984d-d45b-affe-dddf0f410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said Kenneth Walker is “showing that he’s earning more opportunities to get the ball.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</link>
      <description>Walker out-snapped Zach Charbonnet on Sunday, playing 43 snaps to Charbonnet’s 36. Over the last three weeks, he has 99 snaps to Charbonnet’s 77. Macdonald’s comments create the possibility that there’s more ceiling to Walker going forward this season, perhaps something closer to 70-30 than 60-40 with Charbonnet. “I think you really felt Ken (Sunday),” Macdonald said. “And just, even in the pass game, too, on check-downs, finding him late in the play. Just shows you that he’s such an explosive player with the ball in his hands.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said “I wanted to get the ball to Brock a bunch and see what he could do. ... I’m responsible for that,” when asked about the Raiders’ pass-heavy approach in Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9859-d45b-affe-dddf3b1a0000</link>
      <description>He added, in words that are a dagger to Ashton Jeanty owners: “I don’t really care about pleasing people with our run/pass mix. I’m trying to move the football.” And as bad as Geno Smith has been this year, it’s hard to argue with the fact that Jeanty had nowhere to go on Sunday with just seven yards on his six carries. It’s possible the Raiders will lean into being a pass-first offense down the stretch, something that would be music to the ears of Bowers-reliant managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9859-d45b-affe-dddf3b1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Khalil Shakir (personal) was excused from practice for personal reasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9861-d673-a39e-bcf18cbb0000</link>
      <description>He also did not participate in Monday’s practice for personal reasons. If this were a non-TNF game, we probably wouldn’t post about this, but zero practices two days in to the week is mildly concerning even if Shakir isn’t hurt. It’s at least in the range of outcomes that he misses this game and further throws the Bills receiving corps into chaos in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9861-d673-a39e-bcf18cbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said C.J. Stroud (concussion) will not play in Houston’s Week 12 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</link>
      <description>This did seem to the way it was going for most of the week, even with Stroud returning to practice today. The good news is that a return against the Colts in Week 13 seems plausible for Stroud, who has now missed three full games with this concussion suffered against the Broncos in Week 9. Davis Mills will shepherd the Texans through Thursday Night Football against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said he’s “optimistic” about Jaylen Warren (ankle) playing in Week 12 but said he’ll be limited early in the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</link>
      <description>He added that Warren was cleared to return to the game by trainers, but that the Steelers opted not to chance anything. The story here seems to be the Steelers just taking it easy on their best back. We’ll probably see him limited on Wednesday, possibly Thursday as well, but we’re expecting him to play in Week 12 based on everything we’ve seen to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
