<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets ruled out TE Mason Taylor (neck) for Week 17 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5afc-d35e-a1bf-5ffedaaa0000</link>
      <description>Taylor has now missed three straight games as a result of his neck injury. The rookie tight end, who has caught 44 passes for 369 yards and one touchdown this season, will have one more chance to suit up for Week 18’s season finale against the Bills, but after missing three-straight weeks of practice, he could be a long shot for next week. In addition to Taylor the Jets also ruled out EDGE Will McDonald (knee), DL Jay Tufele (foot), and LB Kiko Mauigoa (neck) for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5afc-d35e-a1bf-5ffedaaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (foot) will play on Sunday against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b84-dc7a-af9b-dfbf2cf40000</link>
      <description>The soreness in Allen’s foot “has dissipated throughout the week,” according to McDermott. Allen has been dealing with a foot injury he suffered in Week 16’s win over the Browns, but this doesn’t seem like anything too serious. Allen did not miss a play after going down last week and has been limited throughout practice this week. The Bills have struggled to move the ball through the air as of late, but McDermott said on Friday he doesn’t expect Allen’s injury to slow him down this weekend. He will be in the QB1 mix despite a tough matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b84-dc7a-af9b-dfbf2cf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Prater (quad) will not play in Week 17 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b95-d35e-a1bf-5fd729dc0000</link>
      <description>Michael Badgley will again draw the start in place of Prater. Badgley went 2-for-3 on extra points last week and also made his only field goal attempt. Badgley has made 11-of-12 field goal attempts this season while splitting time between the Colts and Bills, and could be a worthwhile streaming option if needed. In addition to Prater, the Bills also ruled out DT Jordan Phillips and S Jordan Poyer. Backup safety Jordan Hancock will likely start in Poyer’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b95-d35e-a1bf-5fd729dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said Budda Baker (concussion) will not play in Week 17 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b9c-d35e-a1bf-5fde829a0000</link>
      <description>Baker entered the league’s concussion protocol earlier this week after going down in Week 16’s game against the Falcons. The star safety will miss at least one game due to his brain injury, with backup safety Kitan Crawford looking like the next man up to fill his role. In addition to Baker, the Cardinals also ruled out LT Paris Johnson (knee), and CB Kei’Tre Clark (knee) for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5b9c-d35e-a1bf-5fde829a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minkah Fitzpatrick (calf) will not play in Week 17 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ba2-d35e-a1bf-5fe200480000</link>
      <description>Fitzpatrick has been dealing with a calf injury since Week 15’s game against the Steelers. He will now miss back-to-back games due to the injury and will try to make it back for Week 18’s season finale against the Patriots. His absence should free up some room in the secondary for Mike Evans and company after the Bucs have struggled to get things going through the air as of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ba2-d35e-a1bf-5fe200480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said Aaron Brewer (neck) could have a chance to play in Week 17 against the Buccaneers</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ba5-d35e-a1bf-5fe7b4d20000</link>
      <description>Brewer was a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday but will practice in some capacity on Friday, per McDaniel. The veteran lineman has played through injuries for most of the season, so it wouldn’t be surprising if he did end up suiting up again this week. McDaniel said whether or not Brewer plays will depend on how the next two days go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ba5-d35e-a1bf-5fe7b4d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said George Kittle (ankle) will likely be a game-time decision for Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bb5-d968-a19b-5bf5d4e80000</link>
      <description>With the 49ers playing on Sunday night, Kittle being a game-time decision would create quite a conundrum for fantasy managers. Backup tight end Jake Tonges would make for a nice streaming option if Kittle were to be sidelined, but Tonges will be hard to trust if we have to wait up until inactive are announced to decided whether or not he can be played. Kittle has yet to practice this week but we have seen him play without practicing before. Fantasy managers will need to keep their options open and continue to monitor this situation throughout the weekend the longer Kittle’s status remains up in the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bb5-d968-a19b-5bf5d4e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said Trevin Wallace underwent season-ending shoulder surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bbc-d56e-afff-fffcbc820000</link>
      <description>Wallace has started all 12 games he’s appeared in for the Panthers this season, totaling 61 tackles, four pass breakups, and two sacks while earning a PFF grade of 54.2. Wallace was injured in Week 15 and missed last week’s game as a result. Now, the second-year linebacker will be shut down for the remainder of the season and look to come back healthy in time for training camp next season. Canales said linebacker Claudin Cherelus will continue to start in Wallace’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bbc-d56e-afff-fffcbc820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) was seen without a non-contact jersey during Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bc0-dc7a-af9b-dfff950e0000</link>
      <description>It’s the clearest signal we’ve had this week that Henderson will have a chance to clear concussion protocol before Week 17’s game against the Jets. The rookie running back was limited in both Wednesday and Thursday’s practices, but could be trending toward a return before the weekend. The Patriots should release their final injury report in the next couple of hours, so Henderson’s name will be one to watch when that is announced. If he is unable to go, Rhamondre Stevenson would be in line for a big workload against one of the league’s worst run defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5bc0-dc7a-af9b-dfff950e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
