<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith rushed once for four yards in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars, adding 32 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd2-def2-abdb-bdf3dab40000</link>
      <description>Reports surfaced earlier this week that Smith would be more involved in the offense moving forward, empty words that resulted in just four touches against the Jaguars. He continued to play well behind both Isiah Pacheco and Kareem Hunt and watched as the latter scored two touchdowns from inside the five in Week 5. Fantasy managers might want to take a “wait and see” approach with the seventh-round rookie, stashing him on benches until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd2-def2-abdb-bdf3dab40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 6-of-9 targets for 42 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars, adding nine yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd5-d94a-a79d-bdddc4c10000</link>
      <description>Worthy came into the contest listed as questionable after his ankle swelled up on him on the flight to Jacksonville, ultimately suiting up for the second consecutive game following a dislocated shoulder in Week 1. He functioned as the team’s primary option to the intermediate areas when on the field but saw his snaps monitored for the second game in a row. He briefly left the field of play in the third quarter with what appeared to be an aggravation of the ankle injury, but managed to finish the game while clearly hobbled. Fantasy managers will want to track his status closely as the team prepares for a potential shootout against the Lions in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd5-d94a-a79d-bdddc4c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 4-of-8 targets for 48 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 5 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd8-d94a-a79d-bddd9ccd0000</link>
      <description>The eight looks were the most he’s seen since his 16-target, Week 1 eruption due to the injury to Xavier Worthy. He made his presence in the offense felt early and continued the momentum into the final quarter, catching a toe-tapping ball down the sideline on the team’s penultimate possession, eventually leading to the team retaking the lead with under two minutes to play. Fantasy managers will want to track the status of Xavier Worthy, who briefly departed with an aggravation to the ankle injury that had him listed as questionable coming into the game, ahead of a Week 6 showdown with the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcd8-d94a-a79d-bddd9ccd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 18-of-25 passes for 221 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Jaguars’ 31-28, Week 5 win over the Chiefs, adding 54 yards and two touchdowns on 10 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcdc-db72-a199-fedf33fd0000</link>
      <description>This one was not pretty, but Lawrence found a way to get the job done when it mattered most. The Jaguars fell into an early 14-0 hole as their offense struggled to move the football before tying the game up in the third quarter. A 99-yard pick-six from Devin Lloyd gave the team their first lead of the game on Kansas City’s next possession. As they normally do, the Chiefs buckled down in crunch time to retake the lead with under two minutes remaining in the fourth quarter before Lawrence led the team down the field to be in position to retake the lead again. That final drive was a microcosm of Lawrence’s season as he made two perfect throws and committed two costly mistakes, including his second delay of game penalty of the game. A pass interference penalty in the end zone gave the Jaguars the ball on the one with no timeouts and just over 30 seconds remaining. Lawrence had his foot stepped on by the right guard on the next play but managed to stumble to his feet and carry it in for the go-ahead score without being touched. Lawrence has yet to live up to the hype in his first season with Liam Coen, but the two rushing scores at least give fantasy managers hope as we near the halfway point in the season. Up next is another difficult test against the 3-2 Seahawks in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcdc-db72-a199-fedf33fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 12 times for 49 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs, adding nine yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce2-d94a-a79d-bdef4f220000</link>
      <description>Etienne’s modest volume was a function of the game environment after the Jaguars feel behind 14-0 early. He handily led the backfield again while seeing 15 touches to the five of rookie Bayshul Tuten, but was out-gained by quarterback Trevor Lawrence on the ground. Either way, Etienne remains the lead back in one of the more dynamic run offenses in the league and should return better counting stats moving forward. The 4-1 Jaguars travel to Seattle for another difficult test in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce2-d94a-a79d-bdef4f220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught 4-of-6 targets for 80 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce5-dd4c-afb9-ffe50de80000</link>
      <description>Thomas has yet to rekindle the late-season magic from his rookie year with Trevor Lawrence under center, but the two had a deep connection down the sideline for a 33-yard gain on their final drive to put the team in position for the win. Fantasy managers continue to be left hanging after sinking a top-15 pick into the second-year receiver, something we are all holding out hope will improve as the season progresses. The modest six targets led the team on a night Lawrence attempted only 25 passes as their time of possession was dwarfed by the Chiefs, with their defense once again bailing them out as they improve to 4-1 in a tie atop the AFC South with the Colts. Thomas gets another difficult matchup with the Seahawks in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce5-dd4c-afb9-ffe50de80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed four times for six yards in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs, adding five yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce8-dd4c-afb9-ffe9f92b0000</link>
      <description>Tuten continues to play well behind lead back Travis Etienne, the latter of whom managed 15 touches on a night the team ran only 54 offensive plays. Fantasy managers holding out hope for a Tuten takeover are kept waiting, with the rookie nothing more than a deep-bench stash at present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bce8-dd4c-afb9-ffe9f92b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Hunter caught all three targets for 64 yards in the Jagaurs’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcea-db72-a199-feebfb470000</link>
      <description>Hunter continued to play both ways against the Chiefs, notably matching up with Kansas City tight end Travis Kelce on multiple occasions on the defensive side of the ball. He made a ridiculous 44-yard catch in the second half after briefly exiting with injury in which he elevated enough to rest on the shoulder of a defender before coming down with the ball, something head coach Liam Coen hinted at this week with talks of getting the electric rookie involved more down the field. Volume has not yet erupted in an offense built behind the run, but Hunter could continue his surge in production against the Seahawks in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcea-db72-a199-feebfb470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington caught 2-of-3 targets for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bced-db72-a199-feefdc010000</link>
      <description>Washington played sparingly behind both Dyami Brown and Tim Patrick, but made the most of his opportunity with a touchdown grab from three yards out in the second quarter for the team’s first points of the game. Washington can safely be returned to the waiver wire barring an injury ahead of him on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bced-db72-a199-feefdc010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown caught 2-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcf0-db72-a199-fefbec5e0000</link>
      <description>Brown’s four targets tied for second on the team on a night quarterback Trevor Lawrence attempted only 25 passes, keeping him on the fringes of fantasy consideration moving forward. He likely remains a touchdown-dependent potential FLEX option unless, or until, the team starts utilizing rookie Travis Hunter on offense for heavier rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcf0-db72-a199-fefbec5e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
