<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals are interviewing Bills offensive coordinator Joe Brady regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</link>
      <description>Brady, who Mike Garafolo adds has a second interview scheduled with the Ravens, is now on the radars of Arizona, Las Vegas, and Baltimore. He had interviewed for the Miami and Tennessee jobs before they were filled yesterday, as well. Brady had seemed to have a down season on paper as Bills offensive coordinator. He struggled to create downfield pass plays with Josh Allen. But it doesn’t seem like the NFL as a whole has agreed that it was his fault.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</link>
      <description>Baltimore’s process drags on. The Ravens had a 16-coach list (that we know of), and are beginning the second interview phase shortly. Of Baltimore’s interviews, Kevin Stefanski and Robert Saleh have come off the board already. It looks like Anthony Weaver, Jesse Minter, and Joe Brady are early finalists for the position. It’s Campanile’s second head coaching interview, and with the Dolphins job now secured, his only active lead towards being a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired former Steelers special teams coach Danny Smith as their special teams coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</link>
      <description>The 72-year-old had been with the Steelers for the past 13 years, but was allowed to walk after Mike Tomlin stepped down. He should bring some stability to one of the worst special-teams units in the NFL last year. Todd Bowles has at least gotten off to a good start on fixing some of the issues his team had in 2025 through staff changes here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed S Julian Blackmon to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcd9-d35e-a1bf-dddbfb180000</link>
      <description>Terms weren’t announced by the team. Blackmon was set to start for the Saints last year before he suffered a season-ending labrum tear in the team’s opening game. Assuming rehab goes fine, he should be in line to start next to Justin Reid at safety next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcd9-d35e-a1bf-dddbfb180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens DC Jesse Minter is expected to get an in-person second interview with the Ravens this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce5-dc7a-af9b-dfff83ec0000</link>
      <description>That would make three second interviews for Minter, who has also met with the Browns twice and Raiders twice. He’s also still an active candidate with the Steelers. He interviewed for the Dolphins, Titans, and Falcons jobs before they hired Jeff Hafley, Robert Saleh, and Kevin Stefanski respectively. Minter to the Ravens has felt like a natural fit for a bit and he was mentioned as a favorite early in the process, so it’s not surprising to see him get a second interview.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce5-dc7a-af9b-dfff83ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner believes that if Bengals OC Dan Pitcher takes a new job, former Titans head coach Brian Callahan would “be the leader in the clubhouse for the [Bengals OC job] by a wide margin.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce9-d35e-a1bf-ddebb08a0000</link>
      <description>Pitcher had an interview for the Browns head-coaching position and was also allowed to interview for a lateral move with the Buccaneers, a place where he’d actually get to call plays. To say the Bengals winding back up with Callahan after his stint as Titans head coach would be predictable is an insult to the word predictable. It would practically be written in the stars. Well, assuming Pitcher gets a new gig, anyway. Callahan has also interviewed for the Chargers and Buccaneers offensive coordinator jobs this cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce9-d35e-a1bf-ddebb08a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Herald’s Barry Jackson believes it’s “natural to keep several impending Packers free agents” in mind for the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcf7-d968-a19b-dcf760d30000</link>
      <description>Jackson starts with Malik Willis, who spent the last two years marinating in Packers culture. The Dolphins have a very clear need at the position after benching Tua Tagovailoa late last season. Money might be an issue with the Dolphins starting the offseason $30 million over the cap, but it’s easy to connect the dots here and see Willis in Miami. Quay Walker, Kingsley Enagbare, Romeo Doubs and Sean Rhyan are also potential fits per Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcf7-d968-a19b-dcf760d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) said he will not require offseason surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcff-d968-a19b-dcffe75a0000</link>
      <description>“It was rough, man. It was rough,” Odunze said. “I’m not going to sit here and say I can barely — you know, it is what it is. We play through injuries. It’s part of the game. I’m not going to sit here and make excuses about the foot, but something I was dealing with.” Odunze managed identical 2/44 lines in both Bears playoff games while playing through the foot injury. It’s great news that the injury won’t be a long-term concern for Odunze, who should be high in the Bears passing game pecking order again in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcff-d968-a19b-dcffe75a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants GM Joe Schoen said Malik Nabers (knee) is trending to “hopefully” be ready for the start of training camp.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd24-d35e-a1bf-dde6422e0000</link>
      <description>He added, “things can change.” Lot of caveats in this bit of hope, it sounds like. Nabers told reporters after the season that he was unsure about his return date. It wouldn’t be surprising if Nabers’ ACL and meniscus repairs keep him out well into training camp. He’ll be a caveat emptor all-star in offseason drafts — the talent is obviously there and he barely even got to play with Jaxson Dart. His health remains a big question mark at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd24-d35e-a1bf-dde6422e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed a second interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd27-dc7a-af9b-dfbf14820000</link>
      <description>Do take a minute to look at the linked graphic for “Jesse Minter 2nd Interview,” what a glorious expression of the NFL coaching silly season. Minter remains in play for the Ravens, Browns, and Raiders jobs. We’d be surprised if he didn’t land one of them considering he’s had multiple second interviews, but the Chargers would happily take him back if Minter struck out on the remaining vacancies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd27-dc7a-af9b-dfbf14820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
