<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens waived CB Jalyn Armour-Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7ca-d332-a1fd-f7fe0efa0000</link>
      <description>The 2022 fourth-rounder pick played well in the preseason, notching a 84.7 PFF coverage grade in 49 coverage snaps. He’s only started three games in three years with Baltimore, but was a key special-teams player. Armour-Davis could draw waiver wire interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7ca-d332-a1fd-f7fe0efa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released K Dustin Hopkins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7c9-d332-a1fd-f7ffbb300000</link>
      <description>Hopkins was vying for the kicking job with Andre Szmyt, and it appears Szmyt has won that battle. Hopkins could get a tryout with another club, but it’s also possible he’s kicked his last field goal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7c9-d332-a1fd-f7ffbb300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deshaun Watson (Achilles) will remain on the PUP list to begin the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7cc-d332-a1fd-f7fe9b9c0000</link>
      <description>Watson will not be able to play in the first four games of the 2025 season. He’s expected to miss significantly more time than that with his torn Achilles, and there’s no guarantee he’ll get his starting quarterback gig back after his atrocious play in 2024. And 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7cc-d332-a1fd-f7fe9b9c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints placed TE Taysom Hill (knee) on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7d0-de13-afdc-e7dbed8d0000</link>
      <description>After a late-season ACL tear, it would be surprising to see Hill get activated after he misses the mandatory four games. There is a chance he’ll return later in the season, but nothing we’ve seen so far has given us much optimism that it’ll be in the near future. Juwan Johnson figures to be New Orleans’ starting tight end in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7d0-de13-afdc-e7dbed8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers released S Tony Jefferson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7a2-db7b-a5dd-e7a63b0a0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson signed a one-year deal with the Chargers in March. He played extensively in all of the Chargers’ preseason games, logging one pass breakup, one interception, three tackles, one quarterback pressure and one sack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7a2-db7b-a5dd-e7a63b0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (hamstring) practiced on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7ba-dbe3-a9bb-f7fb35950000</link>
      <description>McMillan recently returned to practice after experiencing hamstring soreness last week. The rookie wide receiver is set to handle a significant workload this season, potentially operating as the Panthers’ top target earner. He profiles as a WR3 at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7ba-dbe3-a9bb-f7fb35950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette’s Gerry Dulac reports Will Howard (hand) will wind up on injured reserve “at some point.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7d2-dbe3-a9bb-f7d36c1b0000</link>
      <description>Assuming that “some point” is “sometime in the next week and change,” Howard will miss the first four games of the season. He probably could be ready earlier based on his timeline, but the Steelers can afford to send their third-string quarterback to IR and get a look at some of their fringe roster players in the regular season. Howard did not play in the preseason due to the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7d2-dbe3-a9bb-f7d36c1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos placed FB Michael Burton and LB Drew Sanders on injured reserve with a designation to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7e1-dbe3-a9bb-f7f39f3a0000</link>
      <description>Both Burton and Sanders will miss at least the first four weeks of the season before having a chance to return to their roles with Denver after October. Burton should return to his lead-blocking role once healthy, while Sanders adds to the linebacking depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7e1-dbe3-a9bb-f7f39f3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nakobe Dean (knee) is expected to be placed on the Physically Unable to Perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7e4-de13-afdc-e7efad540000</link>
      <description>Dean tor his patellar tendon in a playoff win over the Packers in January, and posted that he will “see y’all in Week 5" on his Instagram page. The 24-year-old linebacker will be a key cog in the Philadelphia defense when he’s able to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7e4-de13-afdc-e7efad540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL placed Texans S Jimmie Ward on the Commissioner Exempt List.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7f0-de13-afdc-e7fbaf770000</link>
      <description>Ward, who is dealing with a felony charge of assaulting a family/house member in June, will not practice or attend games while on the list. Houston will likely give MJ Stewart the snaps that Ward would have received until he is available to play this season. Ward, who had foot surgery this offseason, isn’t ready to practice yet even if he had been allowed to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e7f0-de13-afdc-e7fbaf770000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
