<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 19:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (undisclosed) is close to returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</link>
      <description>Quinn added that the “arrow is pointing up for him.” The oft-injured wideout hasn’t participated much in training camp to this point. This paints a picture of a return for Week 1, but Quinn did not exactly promise that with words. Brown should probably be the Commanders’ No. 3 receiver when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd83-de13-afdc-cfcb40bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR Johnny Wilson (knee/ankle) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</link>
      <description>Wilson suffered the injury at Tuesday’s practice and was carted off. While Wilson’s a fun player at 6-foot-6 and shaped like a tight end, he wasn’t expected to have a major role in the Eagles offense this year. The 2024 sixth-rounder will instead look to get ready for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd89-dbe3-a9bb-fddbab950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn says he “see[s] the ascension taking place” with Jaylin Lane.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders fourth-round pick this year, Lane reportedly can “apply it very quickly” when given coaching points. Lane has a chance to eventually take over for Noah Brown in three-wideout sets at some point this season, and should make for an intriguing stash in dynasty at the very least given his youth relative to the rest of the Commanders wideout room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd8e-de13-afdc-cfcf029c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions C Graham Glasgow (leg) left Friday’s joint practice against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</link>
      <description>No word yet on the severity of the injury, but it would be yet another blow to the Lions’ interior line if Glasgow missed real time. We’d expect an update from Detroit sometime in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd90-db7b-a5dd-ed9479b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond will play in preseason Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</link>
      <description>Bond has practiced three times since the Browns signed him on Monday. He needs all the reps he can get, and the Browns are in need of playmakers. He presumably has a long way to go before he is even moderately familiar with the playbook and is not a recommended re-draft bench stash. He could be worth a waiver wire add later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-rays of Lamar Jackson’s foot showed “no damage.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</link>
      <description>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said Jackson’s foot is “a little sore today,” but deemed the star quarterback “fine” after holding him out of Thursday’s practice. We can breathe a sigh of relief. Following his recovery will be worthwhile but fantasy managers can continue drafting Jackson as an elite QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Ja’Lynn Polk (shoulder) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal development for the second-year wide receiver. Polk was reportedly not a lock to make the Patriots’ roster after being outplayed by his teammates in spring practices. Hopefully, he can resume training individually before long. On 15 preseason snaps, Polk earned zero targets and rushed once for one yard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said the starters will play 20-25 snaps in preseason Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd94-dbe3-a9bb-fdd763c40000</link>
      <description>Joe Flacco will be backed up by Dillon Gabriel in the QB2 role while Shedeur Sanders serves as the QB3. Kenny Pickett (hamstring) will not play. Fantasy managers should pay attention to both the Browns’ first-team running back and tight end usage. Rookies, RB Dylan Sampson and TE Harold Fannin Jr., are on the late-round radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd94-dbe3-a9bb-fdd763c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR/CB Travis Hunter (upper body) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdb6-dbe3-a9bb-fdf73e120000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars eased Hunter into action via limited participation on Tuesday and Wednesday, with the goal of having him practice against the Dolphins in today’s joint practice. Jaguars head coach Liam Coen “considered” allowing Hunter to participate today, but “wanted to avoid any chance that Hunter could aggravate the injury.” Plans change, and no setbacks have been reported. Coen adds that if Thursday’s practice were a game, Hunter “probably” would have played. None of the starters will play in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 3 game against the Dolphins. Fantasy managers are advised to continue drafting Hunter as a WR3 with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdb6-dbe3-a9bb-fdf73e120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Matthew Stafford (back) is practicing in full this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cde7-db7b-a5dd-ede7373a0000</link>
      <description>McVay feels “good” about Stafford’s current participation level. Hopefully, Stafford can remain setback-free as he shakes off rust and develops rapport with his pass catchers. He makes for a shaky QB2 in fantasy. Unsurprisingly, Stafford will not participate in the Rams’ preseason Week 3 game against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cde7-db7b-a5dd-ede7373a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
