<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 12:02:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 17 times for 65 yards in the Lions’ Week 6 loss to the Chiefs, catching one pass for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db99-def2-abdb-dff9fd260000</link>
      <description>Gibbs significantly out-touched backfield mate David Montgomery, the latter of whom turned four carries into 24 yards and caught two targets for 37 yards through the air. The large disparity in backfield work was likely resultant from consistently negative game script after the Lions trailed for much of the game, leaving the offense more one-dimensional than they would otherwise like. The 4-2 Lions will look to shake off their loss in Week 7 with a home matchup against the Buccaneers on Monday Night Football, before getting a mid-season breather with a Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db99-def2-abdb-dff9fd260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 6-of-7 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 6 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db9e-dd4c-afb9-ffdf10790000</link>
      <description>Williams scored on a 22-yard dart from quarterback Jared Goff early in the second quarter, catching the ball over the middle of the field before getting popped by three defenders while adding six yards after the catch entering the end zone. It was an otherwise quiet night for the offense as they were unable to work the deep areas of the field against the 4-3, Cover-2-heavy Kansas City defense. Those alignments forced Goff and company to pepper the short and intermediate areas, capping their ability to generate any meaningful splash plays. It worked perfectly as the Detroit offense began to sputter while being forced to march the field. Even so, Williams proved he is much more than a simple field stretcher in this offense, something he will look to double up on next week when the Lions host the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-db9e-dd4c-afb9-ffdf10790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 5-of-6 targets for 55 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 6 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba1-d94a-a79d-dbadb04e0000</link>
      <description>LaPorta started off hot catching multiple passes on the team’s first possession, but was then largely invisible until an outrageous fourth quarter touchdown where he was able to secure the ball with one hand before getting both feet inbounds in the back of the end zone, with a defender draped over one arm. LaPorta now has touchdowns in consecutive games after scoring 17 total touchdowns in his first two seasons in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba1-d94a-a79d-dbadb04e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 9-of-10 targets for 45 yards in the Lions’ Week 6 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba4-def2-abdb-dfe562b60000</link>
      <description>St. Brown saw a pedestrian first half before the Lions were forced to attack the short-to-intermediate areas of the field against a 4-3, Cover-2-heavy Steve Spagnuolo defense that all but eliminating downfield passing. The 10 targets handily led the team but the modest yardage total ranked behind both Jameson Williams and Sam LaPorta, the latter two of whom each also found the end zone in the loss. St. Brown remains a WR1 in fantasy circles ahead of a Week 7 showdown with the Buccaneers on Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba4-def2-abdb-dfe562b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 22-of-30 passes for 257 yards and three touchdowns in the Chiefs’ 30-17, Week 6 win over the Lions, adding 32 yards and a touchdown on 10 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba8-d94a-a79d-dbadc9b90000</link>
      <description>Mahomes played an inspired game, marching the field and converting when he had to and delivering the grit in other situations. His second quarter rushing score from one yard out falls in the latter bucket, which allowed the Chiefs to double the Lions up around the break after tacking on another score on their first possession of the second half. It was that 14-point spurt that put the Chiefs up for good. Mahomes has continued to have to overcome a largely nonexistent run game as he still leads the team in rushing through six weeks, but the team gets standout wide receiver Rashee Rice back after his six-game suspension culminated with the win, giving Mahomes his top option through the air back ahead of a Week 7 divisional tilt against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dba8-d94a-a79d-dbadc9b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed 12 times for 51 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions, catching one target for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbad-d94a-a79d-dbadb1630000</link>
      <description>Pacheco’s earth-shaking running style was on full display in this one as positive game script allowed the Chiefs to give the veteran back second half carries as they began to ice the game. Pacheco was kept out of the end zone for the sixth consecutive game, this time watching as Mahomes scored from one yard out just before the half. With volume unlikely and a shrinking red zone role, Pacheco is nothing more than trade fodder in fantasy circles as we approach the halfway point in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbad-d94a-a79d-dbadb1630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed six times for 23 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions, adding 11 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb0-d94a-a79d-dbbde70b0000</link>
      <description>The team turned to Isiah Pacheco over Hunt as they looked to ice the game in the fourth quarter, but it was quarterback Patrick Mahomes that scored on the ground from one yard out just before the half for the team’s only rushing score of the game. Hunt can’t be treated as anything more than a touchdown-dependent FLEX unless there is an injury ahead of him this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb0-d94a-a79d-dbbde70b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 6-of-7 passes for 78 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb3-def2-abdb-dff375df0000</link>
      <description>Kelce caught Patrick Mahomes’ first pass attempt for a 15-yard gain on the team’s first possession to set the tone for the evening, shaking free up the middle on multiple occasions to return his best yards per reception and total yardage outing of the season. It will be interesting to see how the tam incorporates Rashee Rice back into the offense as the second-year wide receiver is due back from a six-game suspension in Week 7 against the Buccaneers. It could leave Kelce with a muted role until later in the season when games begin to bear more weight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb3-def2-abdb-dff375df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught all four targets for 45 yards and two touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb7-d94a-a79d-dbbfcb690000</link>
      <description>It was the first multi-touchdown game since the 2021 season for Brown, who shook free on two crossers near the end zone for easy scores in this one. Brown’s role is almost assuredly set to change with Rashee Rice due back to the field in Week 7 after serving his six-game suspension. Brown could be relegated to prayer FLEX status moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb7-d94a-a79d-dbbfcb690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 2-of-4 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions, adding six yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbbb-def2-abdb-dffb24a90000</link>
      <description>Worthy continues to gut out multiple injuries after playing through a dislocated shoulder and ankle injury for the previous three games, this time finding the end zone early in the first quarter to put the Chiefs on the board. It will be interesting to see how the team handles the return of Rashee Rice in Week 7 considering the state of the pass-catching corps at present. Worthy sees a slight bump down to WR4 range with the return of Rice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbbb-def2-abdb-dffb24a90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
