<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 6-of-9 targets for 79 yards in the Broncos’ Week 13 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d857-db57-afda-de770f170000</link>
      <description>Engram was the weapon of choice against a Dan Quinn defense that played almost exclusively from zone due to their defense’s inability to generate pressure in the backfield, routinely acting as the outlet behind the blitz on his way to team-high marks in targets, receptions, and yardage. As is consistently the case with Engram, the only blemish on his box score from a fantasy perspective was his failure to get into the end zone, with the team much more focused on their top wide receiver and backfield where it matters most. Engram has proven a difficult asset to trust considering his lack of red zone involvement but reminded us of his upside against zone-heavy opponents. He could return another usable stat line when the Broncos face the Cover-3-heavy Raiders in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d857-db57-afda-de770f170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 5-of-6 targets for 62 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 13 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d85b-d82c-a79a-fbdfb0770000</link>
      <description>Sutton has now gone five games without notching more than five catches or 67 yards, clearly seeing a dip in volume and production with the team in the midst of a nine-game winning streak. He continues to be emphasized in the red zone, evidenced by his fifth touchdown grab of the season, but fantasy managers continue to be left wanting more from their early-round selection this offseason. He’ll have another solid opportunity to crack into higher yardage totals when the Broncos face the Raiders in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d85b-d82c-a79a-fbdfb0770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards in the Broncos’ Week 13 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d85f-d82c-a79a-fbdf9c0a0000</link>
      <description>Franklin had been on a fantasy tear before being slowed by the zone-heavy Washington defense, which limited the team’s ability to attack aggressively downfield throughout the evening. It was the first game since Week 6 in which Franklin failed to see eight or more targets after emerging as a true downfield threat as the team’s primary Z-type receiver. He will be in a good spot to see his volume return when the Broncos face the Cover-3-heavy Raiders in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d85f-d82c-a79a-fbdf9c0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 3-of-7 targets for 42 yards in the Broncos’ Week 13 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d863-d90e-a9da-df6fb28f0000</link>
      <description>Bryant’s seven targets ranked second on the team behind veteran tight end Evan Engram, likely bolstered by the zone-heavy nature of Dan Quinn’s Washington defense. That also limited Bryant’s ability to break free downfield, which has been his calling card since earning more work in Week 5. Most notable was the fact that he continued to play well ahead of Marvin Mims, which appears likely to continue as we head down the back stretch of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d863-d90e-a9da-df6fb28f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota completed 28-of-50 passes for 294 yards, two touchdowns, and one interception in the Commanders’ 27-26, Week 13 loss to the Broncos, adding 55 yards on 10 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d866-d82c-a79a-fbf6f7da0000</link>
      <description>The 50 pass attempts were easily the most Mariota has attempted in a game in his career and marked the first time he has thrown the football more than 40 times since 2018, largely due to the team’s general inability to run the football effectively against the stout Denver defensive front. And while the team didn’t hold a lead for very long in this one, they also never trailed by more than six points in regulation as Mariota continually kept them within striking distance. He led a fourth quarter drive to tie the game as time expired to send it into overtime, only to immediately be forced to replicate the magic after Bo Nix’s Broncos scored in just over three minutes in the additional frame. He would cash in after converting twice on fourth down, narrowly missing ending the team’s six-game skid as his pass attempt on a two-point try was batted down. It appears this could be his final start of the 2025 season with Jayden Daniels inching closer to a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d866-d82c-a79a-fbf6f7da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed 11 times for 41 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d86f-db57-afda-de7f3dbc0000</link>
      <description>31 of his 41 yards came before the half as the Commanders were forced to air it out after the break, including on their overtime possession. Still, he saw one more carry than Jacory Croskey-Merritt and Jeremy McNichols did combined as the primary early-down bruiser, a role that could yield more fantasy value with the expected return of quarterback Jayden Daniels in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d86f-db57-afda-de7f3dbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 10-of-13 targets for 106 yards in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d872-d82c-a79a-fbf64f0f0000</link>
      <description>Ertz was one of the primary beneficiaries of a career-high 50 pass attempts from veteran backup Marcus Mariota, reeling in a season-high 10 balls in the process. His fantasy night could have been even bigger had he corralled a four-yard pass on third-and-goal in overtime, which nearly cost the team a chance at completing the comeback. Mariota would find Terry McLaurin on a pick-slant on the next play but a failed fourth down attempt sent the Commanders to their seventh consecutive loss. Ertz remains a steady, yet unspectacular, contributor in Washington’s offense and fantasy managers can continue starting him in PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d872-d82c-a79a-fbf64f0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 7-of-14 targets for 96 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d876-db57-afda-de7666b40000</link>
      <description>McLaurin was largely confined to key downs in the first half in his first full game since Week 2, but had his number called at greater frequency after the break as the Commanders went into desperation mode in an attempt to end their six-game skid. He would score from 30 yards out in overtime only to see it called by for offensive holding, but made good on the touchdown later on the drive on fourth down from three yards out. McLaurin reminded fantasy managers of his weekly upside ahead of a potential Jayden Daniels return in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d876-db57-afda-de7666b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 5-of-7 targets for 64 yards in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos, losing three yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87a-d6c4-abfb-de7b63590000</link>
      <description>Samuel took a backseat to tight end Zach Ertz and alpha wide receiver Terry McLaurin in what was the first full game from McLaurin since Week 2, seeing just seven looks to the 14 of McLaurin and the 13 of Ertz. That gives fantasy managers reason for concern considering quarterback Marcus Mariota set a career high with 50 pass attempts i the overtime affair, particularly with Jayden Daniels appearing ready to return to the active roster in Week 14. Samuel’s days of consistent fantasy production could be behind him in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87a-d6c4-abfb-de7b63590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treylon Burks caught 1-of-4 targets for a five-yard touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87c-db57-afda-de7ece7a0000</link>
      <description>Burks showed a glimpse at what made him a first-round pick for the Titans in the 2022 draft as he elevated over a defender for a one-handed touchdown in the third quarter. Unfortunately for him, that would go down as his only reception of the evening with the return of Terry McLaurin. He does not hold any fantasy value while playing behind McLaurin, Deebo Samuel, and Jaylin Lane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87c-db57-afda-de7ece7a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
