<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed DT Shy Tuttle to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bdb730000</link>
      <description>Tuttle will be a rotational interior piece behind T’Vondre Sweat and Jeffery Simmons. He was released by the Panthers at final cuts, but the Titans appear to value him more highly than Carolina did.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85b-dbe3-a9bb-f85bdb730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said Michael Burton (hamstring) will have surgery and be out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85e-de13-afdc-eedf961d0000</link>
      <description>In other words, he was placed on the season-ending version of injured reserve. The Broncos don’t currently have a fullback after cutting Adam Prentice earlier today, so they’ll likely either add there or use one of their tight ends in the backfield this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e85e-de13-afdc-eedf961d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived RB Israel Abanikanda.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e859-dbe3-a9bb-f85b2bcb0000</link>
      <description>In three preseason games, Abanikanda rushed 24 times for 71 yards, one touchdown and one fumble and caught 2-of-4 targets for 14 yards. He could return to the Packers via the practice squad. The Packers released DL Deslin Alexandre, DB Johnathan Baldwin, T Brant Banks, LB Jared Bartlett, G Tyler Cooper, RB Tyrion Davis-Price, DL James Ester, CB Tyron Herring, WR Julian Hicks, C Trey Hill, RB Amar Johnson, WR Cornelius Johnson, LB Jamon Johnson, CB Kalen King, G JJ Lippe, TE Johnny Lumpkin, K Mark McNamee, DL Arron Mosby, WR Isaiah Neyor, DL Devonte O’Malley, WR Will Sheppard, DB Jaylin Simpson, G/C Lecitus Smith, TE Messiah Swinson, T Kadeem Telfort and LB Kristian Welch. The Packers placed C/G Jacob Monk placed on injured reserve with a designation to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e859-dbe3-a9bb-f85b2bcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks placed G Christian Haynes on injured reserve and designated him for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e870-de13-afdc-eefb7fd60000</link>
      <description>Haynes, a third-round pick from 2024, was unable to play in the last two preseason games due to an elbow injury. The 25-year-old projects as a backup at this stage, and won’t be able to return until October at the earliest. The Seahawks also placed WR/KR Stephen Sims on IR while placing DE Rylie Mills and NT Jonathan Hankins on NFI (non-football injury list).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e870-de13-afdc-eefb7fd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed WR Christian Watson (knee) on the reserve/physically unable to perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e845-db7b-a5dd-e8458f310000</link>
      <description>Watson must now sit out at least four games before he is eligible to return. The field-stretching wide receiver is rehabbing from a torn ACL from suffered last year. The Packers also placed DL Collin Oliver and G John Williams on the reserve/physically unable to perform list, and S Omar Brown was placed on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e845-db7b-a5dd-e8458f310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released TE Harrison Bryant.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-de13-afdc-eeff0f8e0000</link>
      <description>The Texans traded for Bryant just nine days ago, so this could be some sort of procedural move. It would be unsurprising to see them sign him again shortly. He caught 2-of-2 targets for 13 yards in the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-de13-afdc-eeff0f8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders waived QB Cam Miller.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-db7b-a5dd-e8762f1a0000</link>
      <description>Miller was the Raiders’ sixth-round pick, and it seems very likely that the signal-caller will be back with Las Vegas on their practice squad. Tommy Mellott — a former college quarterback who is making the move to wide receiver — was also part of the cuts for the Raiders. The full list of players who won’t make the 53-man roster: aived DT Zach Carter, RB Chris Collier, DE Jahfari Harvey, WR Shedrick Jackson, LB Matt Jones, DT Treven Ma’ae, G Atonio Mafi, RB Sincere McCormick, DE Ovie Oghoufo, TE Carter Runyon, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, S Trey Taylor, CB Greedy Vance, T Dalton Wagner and S JT Woods, WR Alex Bachman, S Terrell Edmunds and TE Albert Okwuegbunam while Lonnie Johnson Jr. was placed on the injured list and designated for return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-db7b-a5dd-e8762f1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed CB Maxwell Hairston on injured reserve and designated him for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88b-d332-a1fd-febfed500000</link>
      <description>Hairston suffered a sprained knee at the end of July, and the 22-year-old will need to miss the first four games —at minimum — before having a chance to join the Bills. Once healthy, the 2025 first-round picks should be a cog in the secondary, but he may need to wait until 2026 until he’s ready to make a significant impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88b-d332-a1fd-febfed500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans placed DE Denico Autry on the reserve/physically unable to perform list with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88a-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbe7e00000</link>
      <description>Autry will now miss at least four games. The Texans’ talented pass rush can survive without their veteran rotational player but he will be welcomed upon his return. The Texans face the Ravens in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88a-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbe7e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released WR Robbie Chosen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e878-db7b-a5dd-e87cd8290000</link>
      <description>Chosen caught 9-of-12 targets for 117 yards this preseason, but he did not crack the roster in a banged-up 49ers wide receiver room. He appeared in just two games for the Dolphins last year and could catch on as practice squad depth. The 49ers also released OL Michael Dunn, WR Russell Gage Jr., DL Jonathan Garvin, DL Trevis Gipson, DL Bruce Hector, WR Isaiah Hodgins, CB Fabian Moreau, P Thomas Morstead, LB Curtis Robinson, LB Chazz Surratt, and WR Malik Turner. They waived WR Junior Bergen, LB Stone Blanton, DL William Bradley-King, DB Derrick Canteen, CB Dallis Flowers, LB Jalen Graham, S Jaylen Mahoney, OL Drake Nugent, WR Terique Owens, DL Sebastian Valdez, TE Brayden Willis and OL Nick Zakelj.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e878-db7b-a5dd-e87cd8290000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
