<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:21:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud said he’s “still getting adjusted to” the team’s offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</link>
      <description>Stroud said after the Texans’ Divisional Round loss to the Patriots that “there are no excuses” for throwing four interceptions on 47 attempts against New England, but that he was still getting comfortable in an offensive scheme installed by first-year offensive coordinator Nick Caley. Stroud in 2025 completed 64.5 percent of his passes for 3,041 yards and 19 touchdowns with eight interceptions, improving in most categories after a letdown of a 2024 season following his outstanding 2023 rookie campaign. The Texans will have to make a decision on Stroud’s fifth-year contract option by May 1, and head coach DeMeco Ryans said after the team’s postseason loss that he would not discuss the team’s plans for Stroud, who turns 25 in October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc5d-d56e-afff-fefd68530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the probable cause trespassing charges against Vikings WR Jordan Addison won’t be filed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</link>
      <description>Addison, who was arrested last week, “will prepare for the filing of a civil claim arising from the alleged wrongful arrest,” according to Garafolo. “As Mr. Addison’s agent has advised, from the very outset of this incident and arrest, Mr. Addison committed no legal wrong doing,” Addison’s attorney said in a statement. “We are thrilled that the truth was finally revealed and this poor man’s name was not besmirched any longer. I am thankful we were able to bring this to light as quickly as possible.” Addison has had other run-ins with the law, including a DUI, which led to a suspension. The Vikings will have to decide this offseason on extending a fifth-year option or beginning contract talks with Addison, entering his fourth season in the league in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dc77-d56e-afff-feff96a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired former Titans offensive line coach Bill Callahan as their offensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfecc80000</link>
      <description>It was a rumored move, and we’re a bit surprised because we expected Callahan to rejoin his son Brian in whatever offensive role the younger Callahan landed. The Falcons will let Dwayne Ledford, a well-respected offensive line coach, hit free agency. Ledford should be on several teams radars. There’s no disputing that Callahan is one of the best offensive line coaches in the business despite his relative struggles to fix the Titans’ woes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfecc80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals are interviewing Bills offensive coordinator Joe Brady regarding their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</link>
      <description>Brady, who Mike Garafolo adds has a second interview scheduled with the Ravens, is now on the radars of Arizona, Las Vegas, and Baltimore. He had interviewed for the Miami and Tennessee jobs before they were filled yesterday, as well. Brady had seemed to have a down season on paper as Bills offensive coordinator. He struggled to create downfield pass plays with Josh Allen. But it doesn’t seem like the NFL as a whole has agreed that it was his fault.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcaf-dc7a-af9b-dfbf7b970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</link>
      <description>Baltimore’s process drags on. The Ravens had a 16-coach list (that we know of), and are beginning the second interview phase shortly. Of Baltimore’s interviews, Kevin Stefanski and Robert Saleh have come off the board already. It looks like Anthony Weaver, Jesse Minter, and Joe Brady are early finalists for the position. It’s Campanile’s second head coaching interview, and with the Dolphins job now secured, his only active lead towards being a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcb6-d35e-a1bf-ddf62a890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired former Steelers special teams coach Danny Smith as their special teams coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</link>
      <description>The 72-year-old had been with the Steelers for the past 13 years, but was allowed to walk after Mike Tomlin stepped down. He should bring some stability to one of the worst special-teams units in the NFL last year. Todd Bowles has at least gotten off to a good start on fixing some of the issues his team had in 2025 through staff changes here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dccb-d968-a19b-dcfb0d0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed S Julian Blackmon to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcd9-d35e-a1bf-dddbfb180000</link>
      <description>Terms weren’t announced by the team. Blackmon was set to start for the Saints last year before he suffered a season-ending labrum tear in the team’s opening game. Assuming rehab goes fine, he should be in line to start next to Justin Reid at safety next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcd9-d35e-a1bf-dddbfb180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens DC Jesse Minter is expected to get an in-person second interview with the Ravens this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce5-dc7a-af9b-dfff83ec0000</link>
      <description>That would make three second interviews for Minter, who has also met with the Browns twice and Raiders twice. He’s also still an active candidate with the Steelers. He interviewed for the Dolphins, Titans, and Falcons jobs before they hired Jeff Hafley, Robert Saleh, and Kevin Stefanski respectively. Minter to the Ravens has felt like a natural fit for a bit and he was mentioned as a favorite early in the process, so it’s not surprising to see him get a second interview.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce5-dc7a-af9b-dfff83ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner believes that if Bengals OC Dan Pitcher takes a new job, former Titans head coach Brian Callahan would “be the leader in the clubhouse for the [Bengals OC job] by a wide margin.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce9-d35e-a1bf-ddebb08a0000</link>
      <description>Pitcher had an interview for the Browns head-coaching position and was also allowed to interview for a lateral move with the Buccaneers, a place where he’d actually get to call plays. To say the Bengals winding back up with Callahan after his stint as Titans head coach would be predictable is an insult to the word predictable. It would practically be written in the stars. Well, assuming Pitcher gets a new gig, anyway. Callahan has also interviewed for the Chargers and Buccaneers offensive coordinator jobs this cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dce9-d35e-a1bf-ddebb08a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Herald’s Barry Jackson believes it’s “natural to keep several impending Packers free agents” in mind for the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcf7-d968-a19b-dcf760d30000</link>
      <description>Jackson starts with Malik Willis, who spent the last two years marinating in Packers culture. The Dolphins have a very clear need at the position after benching Tua Tagovailoa late last season. Money might be an issue with the Dolphins starting the offseason $30 million over the cap, but it’s easy to connect the dots here and see Willis in Miami. Quay Walker, Kingsley Enagbare, Romeo Doubs and Sean Rhyan are also potential fits per Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dcf7-d968-a19b-dcf760d30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
