<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Thielen failed to catch his only target in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</link>
      <description>Thielen saw a reduced snap rate in a game the Vikings preferred to operate from heavy personnel after continued shortcomings, eventually breaking through with three fourth quarter touchdowns to steal the win from the Bears. Thielen would make his mark felt on the field by catching a two-point conversion on the team’s penultimate score for his only counting stats of the game. Thielen remains an iffy fantasy bet ahead of a Week 2 meeting with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports 49ers WR Jauan Jennings seems to have avoided a serious shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2edc-de13-afdd-6edfd7720000</link>
      <description>The Niners finally get a little bit of good news after a Week 1 win in which they may have lost both George Kittle (hamstring) and Brock Purdy (toe/shoulder). An MRI on Jennings’ shoulder injury did not show extensive damage. We could see him suit up for the team’s Week 2 game against the Saints if he’s able to practice in a limited fashion late in the week. Jennings and Ricky Pearsall are set to dominate wideout targets in the Niners offense for as long as Kittle is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2edc-de13-afdd-6edfd7720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed S Jabrill Peppers, formerly of the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ee6-d332-a1fd-bef669450000</link>
      <description>Peppers, released by the Pats in August, will join a Steelers secondary that was ripped by Justin Fields in Week 1. They’ll be without S DeShon Elliott for at least a couple weeks after Elliott injured his knee against the Jets. The 29-year-old safety started 26 games over the last three seasons with the Patriots. In 2024, Peppers had 20 solo tackles and two tackles for a loss. He has seven interceptions over eight NFL seasons. Peppers will likely be a rotational player for the Steelers if he suits up in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ee6-d332-a1fd-bef669450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports S DeShon Elliott (knee) will miss “a couple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ef7-db7b-a5dd-aef7d0f20000</link>
      <description>The team hopes to have Elliott back for their Week 4 game against the Vikings in Ireland, according to Schultz. Elliott will be replaced by some combination of Jalen Ramsey and Jabrill Peppers, who signed with the Steelers on Tuesday. The loss of Elliott is a blow for a Pittsburgh defense that allowed the fourth highest drop back success rate in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ef7-db7b-a5dd-aef7d0f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed K John Parker Romo, formerly of the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f2b-db7b-a5dd-af2fa50a0000</link>
      <description>Parker Romo, who lost the Week 1 starting competition in New England this summer, was inked to the Atlanta practice squad two days after Younghoe Koo whiffed on a game-tying fourth quarter kick. Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Koo would face competition ahead of the team’s Week 2 matchup with the Vikings. Koo, who made two of his three attempts against the Bucs in Week 1, converted a dismal 73 percent of his field goal tries in 2024. He reportedly struggled in training camp and could be out of a job with a rough Week 2 outing. Parker Romo made 11 of his 12 field goal tries last season with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f2b-db7b-a5dd-af2fa50a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers waived K Jake Moody.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f6d-db7b-a5dd-af6d55780000</link>
      <description>Greg Joseph was in camp for the 49ers and is a logical solution for them if they don’t opt to hold tryouts. Moody missed two field goals against the Seahawks in Week 1 after a horrendous 2024 season. He’ll join the tryout circuit if no immediate interest materializes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f6d-db7b-a5dd-af6d55780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed George Kittle (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f72-db7b-a5dd-af76b87a0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the next four games and be eligible to return in Week 6 against the Buccaneers. Kittle is a tough hold in shallow leagues without an injured reserve spot, but given the state of the 49ers offense he probably remains a hold. If Brock Purdy starts this week — that also seems to be in some question — it sounds like Christian McCaffrey will get all the workload he can handle against the Saints. Jauan Jennings feels like a question mark as well but would step in to a major role against the Saints if he can play, along with Ricky Pearsall. Jake Tonges will replace Kittle in the 49ers lineup and isn’t a recommended streamer at this point, though he did catch a touchdown against the Seahawks in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f72-db7b-a5dd-af76b87a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed RB Cody Schrader off the Rams practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f91-db7b-a5dd-af9567830000</link>
      <description>It’s hard to believe that Schrader could be a major part of the mix behind Travis Etienne and Bhayshul Tuten right away in the same way that Tank Bigsby hypothetically could, but it’s a great landing spot overall for the former Ram. Schrader was active in Week 1 ahead of Jarquez Hunter, though he played no offensive snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f91-db7b-a5dd-af9567830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed G Cole Strange off the Browns practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f96-db7b-a5dd-af96665b0000</link>
      <description>Strange will join the Miami interior competition in the absence of James Daniels, though it’s possible he just winds up as a pure backup. There’s got to be someone out there with a #RevengeGame narrative for Strange playing against the Patriots — who drafted him in the first round in 2022 — in Week 2, but we’d be surprised if he got many snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f96-db7b-a5dd-af96665b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala believes the Commanders may push the ball downfield more often to Deebo Samuel this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f9c-dbe3-a9bb-3fdf6e560000</link>
      <description>“With the 49ers, Samuel was a deep target roughly eight times a season, per TruMedia,” Jhabvala writes. She notes that the Commanders targeted Samuel on deeper routes “regularly” during training camp, and that Samuel had two deep targets in Week 1 against the Giants. It’s probably not a major step for Samuel’s fantasy value, which has always been more about PPR and explosive plays, but mixing in more deep routes could keep the 29-year-old receiver’s fantasy floor more stable. He handily out-targeted Terry McLaurin in Week 1 and has the look of a draft day bargain at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f9c-dbe3-a9bb-3fdf6e560000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
