<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 02:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports Chargers DC Jesse Minter and Packers DC Jeff Hafley could be head coaching candidates in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f820-db7b-a5dd-f82448570000</link>
      <description>Not all ownership groups are sold on the idea of hiring an offensive-minded head coach, though the approach certainly reduces the expected turnover rate when fielding a successful offense. For those interested in an old school approach, Howe believes teams in search of a “defense-minded approach” will be doing their homework on Minter and Hafley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f820-db7b-a5dd-f82448570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe believes that it “might not be all that shocking” if rookie WR Matthew Golden “quickly” becomes Jordan Love’s “go-to wide receiver.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f840-db7b-a5dd-f84426610000</link>
      <description>Golden punctuated his “tremendous camp” by starting alongside Romeo Doubs in the Packers’ third preseason game. With Christian Watson (knee) out for at least four games on the reserve/physically unable to perform list and Jayden Reed (foot) rehabbing a Jones fracture, Golden’s path to No. 1 pass-catcher duties is clear. Rookies sometimes develop slowly but Golden might be able to hit the ground running as a WR4 with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f840-db7b-a5dd-f84426610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that Kyle Pitts could be a trade candidate “if the Falcons stumble before the Nov. 5 deadline.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f858-db7b-a5dd-f85c1e030000</link>
      <description>Per Howe, “teams have been under the impression Pitts could have been available in a trade in the past.” He enters the fifth and final year of his rookie contract and is set to earn a $10.878 million salary. Howe believes that the financial aspect would be “the obstacle” in a potential trade, but teams are sometimes willing to eat a portion of a player’s salary if they are simply seeking future draft capital. If Pitts and Michael Penix Jr. form a strong bond, and that bond yields wins, this could all be moot. He’s a back-end TE1 with upside, entering 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f858-db7b-a5dd-f85c1e030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micah Parsons (back tightness) said he’s feeling “great” and that he won’t be sitting “on the sideline” for the Packers’ Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f844-dbe3-a9bb-f857ef820000</link>
      <description>Parsons assured Packers fans that he will be available for Week 1, saying he knows that the team “didn’t give up what they gave up for me to sit on the sideline.” It’s good to know his rehab program has cured him of that dreaded ailment. The Packers’ D/ST looks like one of fantasy football’s best, but they face stiff tests against the Lions and Commanders to open the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f844-dbe3-a9bb-f857ef820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe believes Seahawks S “Nick Emmanwori should be considered a dark-horse candidate to win NFL Defensive Rookie of the Year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f861-db7b-a5dd-f865fa790000</link>
      <description>Emmanwori “has been a playmaking force in practice,” and will “eventually” take on a similar role as the one Ravens S Kyle Hamilton played in head coach Mike Macdonald’s scheme when he served as the defensive coordinator in Baltimore. Howe believes “Macdonald’s defense should be even better in his second season.” It’s squarely on the D/ST1 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f861-db7b-a5dd-f865fa790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that the Seahawks’ offense “seems to be quickly coming together with a more unified vision” under new OC Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f86a-d332-a1fd-fe7eca850000</link>
      <description>Kubiak is expected to feature a zone rushing attack while confusing defenses with motion and attacking downfield via play-action. No. 2 RB Zach Charbonnet had a great training camp while starting RB Kenneth Walker III nursed a sore foot, though Walker is now back in action. Should Charbonnet force a timeshare, or even take over the starting job, both he and Walker should produce fruitful weeks regularly. Jaxon Smith-Njigba is in line for a large workload, operating as Seattle’s inside-outside No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f86a-d332-a1fd-fe7eca850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bengals believe Joe Burrow “enjoyed the best training camp of his career,” according to The Athletic’s Jeff Howe.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f877-de13-afdc-feff40d90000</link>
      <description>Burrow is fully healthy and the Bengals believe “he might have actually improved his accuracy and decision-making” this summer. Though Burrow lacks the rushing upside that the other elite QB1s possess, his exceptional passing talents and top-tier receiving weapons keep him firmly in the top-five conversation. The Bengals also reportedly believe Ja’Marr Chase looks “like he could still be ascending after leading the NFL with 127 catches, 1,708 yards and 17 touchdowns.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f877-de13-afdc-feff40d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed WR Jalen Coker (quad) on injured reserve with a designation to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbae-de13-afdc-ffef1bc40000</link>
      <description>According to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter, Coker will miss at least the first four games of the season with a quad injury. He was looking like a great late-round receiver option with the Panthers trading Adam Thielen and recent reports that Coker would primarily work out of the slot. While the Panthers have signed Hunter Renfrow to the active roster, Xavier Legette is the most likely to benefit from Coker’s absence as the Panthers’ WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbae-de13-afdc-ffef1bc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed WR Hunter Renfrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is back with the Panthers mere days after being cut, according to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter. The Panthers can better use Renfrow’s services now after they traded Adam Thielen to the Vikings and Jalen Coker (quad) went down with an injury. Renfrow could see a good amount of work from the slot in at least the first four games of the season as that’s where the team planned on using Coker. Can a Hunter Renfrow PPR scam work in 2025? I guess we’re going to find out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL fined former Buccaneers S Shilo Sanders $4,669 for unnecessary roughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</link>
      <description>Sanders threw a punch towards Bills tight end Zach Davidson in the team’s third preseason contest and was eventually waived by the franchise. Coming after his release, the fine represents more than three times Sanders’ guaranteed money this season. Sanders remained unsigned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
