<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports CeeDee Lamb is in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef47-d77b-adfa-efc7c8c80000</link>
      <description>This was expected after Lamb exited Week 14’s game against the Lions with a concussion. Lamb came down hard on his head in the second quarter of Thursday’s game and was ruled out shortly after being evaluated on the sideline. With the injury occurring on a Thursday, Lamb will have some additional time to clear protocol before playing next Sunday night against the Vikings. If he’s unable to go, Ryan Flournoy, who went for 9-115-1 against the Lions, would have some viability as a FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef47-d77b-adfa-efc7c8c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dion Dawkins cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef4d-d77b-adfa-efcf015e0000</link>
      <description>Dawkins was out of the non-contact jersey on Thursday and is now on track to play on Sunday against the Bengals. While Dawkins will be back in action after one game away, head coach Sean McDermott said EDGE Joey Bosa and LB Terrel Bernard would be out in Week 14, while WR Joshua Palmer will be listed as doubtful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef4d-d77b-adfa-efcf015e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Dalton Kincaid (knee/hamstring) will be questionable for Week 14 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6a-d8cf-affb-ff6a08430000</link>
      <description>McDermott said he would need to see Kincaid look “functional” to play. It’s hard to know what that means, given Kincaid’s limited status in practice over the last two weeks, but it sounds like the third-year tight end will be truly questionable ahead of Week 14’s game against the Bengals. If he’s not ruled out before Sunday, fantasy managers will want to check Kincaid’s status when inactives are released 90 minutes before kickoff. Dawson Knox would again see the majority of snaps if Kincaid is unable to go, but he shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a boom-or-bust TE2. In addition to Kincaid, McDermott also said RT Spencer Brown (shoulder) would be listed as questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6a-d8cf-affb-ff6a08430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Justin Fields (knee) will be out for Week 14 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6e-d005-a9bf-ff7ef4bb0000</link>
      <description>According to Glenn, the Jets’ backup QB reported knee soreness on Wednesday and will now be ruled out. Rookie UDFA Brady Cook will be elevated from the practice squad this weekend and serve as Tyrod Taylor’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef6e-d005-a9bf-ff7ef4bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray (foot) is not expected</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef77-d77b-adfa-eff740310000</link>
      <description>Gannon said on Monday that the team would not open Murray’s 21-day return window this week, but now the Cardinals’ head coach has ruled out any possibility of a return this season. According to Gannon, Murray’s recovery from a foot injury he suffered in Week 5 has not gone as hoped, leading to the belief that he will not return in 2025. Murray threw for 962-6-3 in the five games he appeared in this season, while leading the Cardinals to a 2-3 record. His last game came in a 22-21 loss to the one-win Titans. The former no. 1 overall pick signed a five-year, $230.5 million contract extension with the Cardinals in 2022 and remains under contract with the team through 2028. Whether or not the team sticks with him next season is to be determined, but Murray’s contract carries a dead cap hit just north of $57.5 million if he’s released next season. Since signing his new deal in the summer of 2022, Murray has gone 16-25 as a starter, with his best season coming in 2024 when he threw for 3851-21-11 while going 8-9. The losses don’t fall solely on Murray, but record aside, his performances have underwhelmed despite the team using multiple high draft picks to give him additional weapons in the passing game. With a new regime likely set to takeover in 2026, a decision will have to be made on Murray’s future with the team and whether or not it’s best to continue forward with him as the franchise QB.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef77-d77b-adfa-eff740310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) will not play in Week 14 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef7a-d77b-adfa-effb511e0000</link>
      <description>Harrison was a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday and has now been ruled out ahead of Sunday’s game. The second-year receiver returned in Week 13 after missing two games due to appendicitis, but was knocked from the game in the fourth quarter due to his heel injury. It’s been a challenging year for Harrison, whose receiving line through 10 games sits at 40-594-4. His absence should create another high-volume week for Michael Wilson, who saw 33 targets in the two games MHJ missed earlier this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef7a-d77b-adfa-effb511e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 14 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef87-da9b-a9bf-ff8fbbeb0000</link>
      <description>Higgins missed Week 13’s win over the Ravens due to a concussion he suffered in Week 12 against the Patriots. Now, Higgins will return to pair up with Joe Burrow and Ja’Marr Chase as the Bengals hope to keep their slim playoff chances alive with a much-needed win over the Bills. Higgins had been running hot prior to his injury, totaling 22 receptions for 355 yards and five touchdowns in his previous five games before going down, and will profile as a high-end WR2 in a game that should feature plenty of scoring this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef87-da9b-a9bf-ff8fbbeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (elbow) will start in Week 14 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef88-da9b-a9bf-ff8d7f880000</link>
      <description>Sunday will mark Daniels’ first game since a brutal elbow injury sidelined him in Week 9 against the Seahawks. The Commanders’ QB1 has appeared in just six games this season due to a series of injuries and will now hope to stay healthy through the final five games of what has become a lost season for the Commanders. Daniels returns just in time to play with his top two targets in Terry McLaurin and Deebo Samuel, something we haven’t seen since Week 2 against the Packers. Daniels logged back-to-back full practices to close out the week and will profile as a fringe QB1/QB2 in fantasy in his return against a stout Vikings defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef88-da9b-a9bf-ff8d7f880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Mike Evans (collarbone) will not play in Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef8d-d005-a9bf-ffbd2dc90000</link>
      <description>Simply put, Evans isn’t ready to return from the injury that sidelined him in Week 7. The veteran receiver saw his 21-day return window open this weekend and was able to log a limited week of practice, but he’ll need at least one more week before returning to the field. That said, with a short turnaround to prepare for a Thursday night game against the Falcons, it’s possible Evans could miss Week 15’s matchup as well. The Buccaneers’ passing game has struggled without Evans, as Baker Mayfield has thrown for 200-plus yards just once in his last five games while managing only five touchdown passes to two interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef8d-d005-a9bf-ffbd2dc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Jalen McMillan (neck) will not play in Week 14 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef8d-d77b-adfa-ef8fdc0a0000</link>
      <description>McMillan was limited in practice this week but will need at least one more week to recover from the neck injury he suffered in the Buccaneers’ second preseason game. McMillan is eligible to return at any time now that the Buccaneers have opened his 21-day return window. It’s possible he’ll be activated in time for Week 15’s Thursday night matchup against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ef8d-d77b-adfa-ef8fdc0a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
