<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 20-of-47 passes for 212 yards, one touchdown and four interceptions in the Texans’ 28-16, Divisional Round loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d36d-d35e-a1bf-d7efd57c0000</link>
      <description>About the only good news was that Stroud managed to avoid any fumbles in one of the worst fiasco performances in recent playoff memory. Missing Nico Collins (concussion) and without Dalton Schultz after a first quarter calf injury, Stroud seemed incapable of delivering a clean ball in adverse New England weather conditions. Almost literally every attempt was inaccurate, with Stroud’s picks being of the “hard-earned” variety rather than hard luck. It was a confidence- and potentially franchise-shaking performance as the Texans mull Stroud’s fifth-year team option for 2027. It will undoubtedly be exercised, but an extension is probably out of the question at this point after Stroud closed the book on his postseason with seven turnovers in eight quarters. Stroud is capable of deep touchdown strikes, but too often loses his mechanics and looks as if he is throwing literal darts over the middle of the field. Heading into his age-25 campaign, Stroud is a player more on the spot than ever.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d36d-d35e-a1bf-d7efd57c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 16-of-27 passes for three touchdowns and an interception in the Patriots’ 28-16, Divisional Round win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d36f-dc7a-af9b-dfff07e30000</link>
      <description>Unfathomably, Maye also fumbled four times, losing two, but that ended up “just” half C.J. Stroud’s disastrous turnover count. Unlike Stroud, Maye complemented his miscues with enough big plays — especially his 28- and 32-yard touchdown strikes — to help will the Pats to victory in terrible Boston weather conditions. Maye has not covered himself in glory through the Pats’ first two postseason games, but he’s done just enough to help cash in elite defensive performances. That wouldn’t normally be a recommended formula, but it will remain viable for an AFC Championship Game showdown with a Broncos team suddenly on backup quarterback Jarrett Stidham. Be that as it may, Maye needs to be better if the Patriots are to secure their spot in yet another 21st century Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d36f-dc7a-af9b-dfff07e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Chargers requested an interview with Arthur Smith for their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d378-d56e-afff-f7f869310000</link>
      <description>Smith remains one of the hottest candidates on the market, with multiple teams expressing interest in his services as their offensive coordinator or next head coach. Smith led the Steelers’ to a 15th ranked finish in points scored this season, but they averaged the eighth-fewest yards per game. Unless he returns as the next head coach of the Steelers, his time in the Steel City will likely come to an end in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d378-d56e-afff-f7f869310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37b-d968-a19b-dbfb4f500000</link>
      <description>One of the most requested head coaching candidates this coaching cycle, Saleh now adds the Ravens to the list of teams he has officially spoken with regarding their head coaching vacancies. He will follow up his interview with the Ravens with a trip to Tennessee to speak with the Titans about their opening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37b-d968-a19b-dbfb4f500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson rushed 16 times for 70 yards in the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans, adding four receptions for 11 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37d-d968-a19b-dbfda8de0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson’s 20 touches came despite what seemed to be a fairly significant eye injury. Stevenson looked like he was having an extremely difficult time getting comfortable, but he returned to help close out a wild, turnover-marred affair. Once again the Pats’ unquestioned lead back, Stevenson has an AFC Championship Game matchup with an elite Broncos run defense. Perhaps that will have the Pats looking to get TreVeyon Henderson more involved on the perimeter/in space than he has been the past few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37d-d968-a19b-dbfda8de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed an interview with Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37e-d56e-afff-f7fea37d0000</link>
      <description>Brady spoke with both the Raiders and the Dolphins about their head coaching vacancies a day after the Bills’ divisional round loss to the Broncos. The 36-year-old offensive coordinator has spent the last three seaons’ as the Bills’ OC after taking over for Ken Dorsey during the 2023 season, and helped coach Josh Allen to an MVP during his first full season as the helm in 2024. Brady has been viewed as a potential head coaching candidate dating back to 2019 when he helped lead LSU to a national championship. We’ll soon see if his number finally gets called by one of the seven teams still in search of their next head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d37e-d56e-afff-f7fea37d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 12 times for 25 yards in the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans, adding a -2 yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d382-d35e-a1bf-d7c27cb10000</link>
      <description>It was a disappointing performance, especially in light of what seemed to be a significant Rhamondre Stevenson eye injury. Stevenson did return to close out the game, out-touching Henderson 20-13 and out-gaining him 81-23. The Pats’ backfield duo has a rough AFC Championship Game matchup in the Broncos’ elite run defense. In theory, that could lead to OC Josh McDaniels looking to get Henderson more involved on the perimeter/out in space than he has been of late. It is nevertheless safe to assume Stevenson will remain the 1A ball-carrier as the Pats look to get back to the Super Bowl for the first time since the Tom Brady era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d382-d35e-a1bf-d7c27cb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 4-of-6 targets for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Divisional Round win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d385-d56e-afff-f7ed86e60000</link>
      <description>Diggs’ score was his first of the postseason and just his second since Nov. 9. Blanketed in the end zone, he made a tough catch then held on for dear life as he was ripped to the ground. Harassed all afternoon by physical coverage, Diggs helped move the chains just enough times as the Pats outlasted a turnover-destroyed Texans offense. Diggs now has another difficult defensive assignment for the AFC Championship Game in Patrick Surtain’s Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d385-d56e-afff-f7ed86e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught 3-of-5 targets for 75 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Divisional Round victory over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d389-d56e-afff-f7e9af350000</link>
      <description>Boutte’s score was an amazing, one-handed grab in Derek Stingley’s stingy coverage in the fourth quarter. Boutte caught the ball sliding in the end zone. It was an elite play on an afternoon where pass catchers weren’t exactly feeding the highlight reel. Once again stepping up as the Patriots’ primary deep threat with Mack Hollins (abdomen) sidelined, Boutte is a potential AFC Championship Game X-factor for the Pats’ westward trip to Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d389-d56e-afff-f7e9af350000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
