<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 3-of-4 targets for 36 yards in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43f8-d968-a19b-5bf91db90000</link>
      <description>Washington notably coughed up a fumble just before halftime. Washington was pushing toward the end zone but lost control of the ball. The Lions ultimately recovered it, costing the Steelers at least three points. Mike Tomlin wasn’t afraid to go back to his massive tight end and Washington came up with a big first down late in the fourth quarter, nearly icing the game for Pittsburgh. Washington is still splitting reps with Jonnu Smith and Pat Freiermuth, capping him at TE2 numbers. In a game versus Cleveland that will likely skew run-heavy next week, Washington will shuffle to the back of the TE2 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43f8-d968-a19b-5bf91db90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Carter rushed 11 times for 65 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43eb-d56e-afff-e7ebef380000</link>
      <description>Carter failed to catch either of his two targets. The shifty rusher looked great on runs up the middle, twisting and grinding through contact right out of the gate. His 22-yard run on the Cardinals’ second drive helped set up the offense’s lone touchdown. Carter is a high-end RB3 against the Bengals in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43eb-d56e-afff-e7ebef380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots ruled out RB TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) for the remainder of Week 16 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43ed-d35e-a1bf-47efdce50000</link>
      <description>Henderson had his head hit the turf hard on a routine tackle in the second quarter and was evaluated for a concussion. The team initially failed to provide an update after the half but the rookie back was ruled out half way through the third quarter. Henderson managed three yards on five carries and nine yards on one reception prior to departing. Rhamondre Stevenson figures to factor heavily into the second half game plan in a tight game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43ed-d35e-a1bf-47efdce50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught all four of his targets for 20 yards in the Steelers’ Week 16 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43fe-dc7a-af9b-cfffa1400000</link>
      <description>Muth led Pittsburgh’s tight ends in catches and tied for second among all the team’s pass-catchers in receptions. He was, however, held under 50 receiving yards for the eighth-straight game. Muth has only hit that mark once this year. He is stuck in the TE3 ranks for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43fe-dc7a-af9b-cfffa1400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 4-of-8 targets for 45 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 16 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4402-d56e-afff-e6ead3190000</link>
      <description>Meyers had a somewhat quiet game after five straight fantasy-viable outings as the Jaguars’ No. 1 receiver. He again served as Trevor Lawrence’s main intermediate target while Parker Washington dominated air yards and led the Jags with 145 yards and a touchdown. Meyers’ eight targets was second to Washington’s 10 targets; Brian Thomas Jr. had just two looks on the day. Meyers, who had been targeted on 25 percent of his routes going into Week 16, should be a playable WR2/3 option in Week 17 against the Colts thanks in part to the pass-first nature of the Jacksonville offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4402-d56e-afff-e6ead3190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs caught 10-of-13 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 16 win over the Steelers, adding two yards on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4402-dc7a-af9b-cfbfdae20000</link>
      <description>It’s rare that we feel the need to lead with a running back’s receiving line, but Gibbs truly got nothing going on the ground. His best carry of the day went for six yards and he was routinely hit well behind the line of scrimmage. Gibbs, of course, is one of the league’s best pass-catchers out of the backfield and had no issues making up for his lack of rushing with an elite receiving line. Playing from behind in the second half, Jared Goff peppered him with check-downs, including a four-yard walk into the end zone late in the fourth quarter. Gibbs is impervious to negative game script and thrives when the Lions get going downhill. He will continue to contend for the RB1 overall crown in Week 17 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4402-dc7a-af9b-cfbfdae20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed four times for 14 yards in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-440a-d968-a19b-5cfb14b10000</link>
      <description>Montgomery was not targeted once. He hasn’t touched the ball more than 10 times in a game since Week 10, Dan Campbell’s first as the team’s play-caller. Montgomery entered this contest riding a three-game touchdown streak, but the lack of volume was always going to catch up to him at some point. A loss to the Steelers did the trick. The Lions should find more success on the ground versus Minnesota next week, but Montgomery is close to falling out of the RB3 ranks entirely after this dud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-440a-d968-a19b-5cfb14b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado rushed five times for 30 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 16 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43f4-d35e-a1bf-47f69da80000</link>
      <description>Demercado went 0-of-1 as a receiver and he was out-touched 6-to-5 by fellow backup RB Corey Kiner. Cardinals RB Michael Carter is the clear-cut backup and Kiner’s presence reduces Demercado’s bench-stash value. This looks like a three-player committee with one FLEX-viable player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-43f4-d35e-a1bf-47f69da80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 4-of-9 targets for 54 yards in the Lions’ Week 16 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4410-d35e-a1bf-45d2007a0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown nearly saved the Lions’ season on the final play. ARSB was stopped at the one-yard line with time winding down. As he was pushed back, St. Brown flipped the ball to Jared Goff, who somersaulted into the end zone for a game-winning touchdown. St. Brown was flagged for offensive pass interference amidst the chaos and the game ended, giving Pittsburgh the win. The Lions are nearly out of the playoff hunt, but they can’t be eliminated entirely before their Christmas showdown with the Vikings. St. Brown will project for low-end WR1 numbers in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4410-d35e-a1bf-45d2007a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
