<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:11:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White rushed seven times for 38 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 12 loss to the Rams, adding four yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b42d-d90e-a9da-bf2f5cca0000</link>
      <description>White played well behind Sean Tucker for the second consecutive game, out-touched 13 to eight as the Buccaneers played from behind throughout. It remains to be seen how the backfield usage will shake out moving forward with Bucky Irving expected back in Week 13, leaving fantasy managers rolling the dice in the Tampa backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b42d-d90e-a9da-bf2f5cca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 3-of-8 targets for 32 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 12 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b42f-db57-afda-f63f7b8d0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka caught two passes for zero yards from starter Baker Mayfield, who did not return for the second half following an injury to his non-throwing shoulder in the second quarter. The electric rookie then managed only one additional reception from backup quarterback Teddy Bridgewater as the veteran was under constant duress from an aggressive Los Angeles defense. Egbuka’s fantasy value is likely tied to Mayfield’s health and would take a substantial hit moving forward if he’s forced to catch passes from Bridgewater.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b42f-db57-afda-f63f7b8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 4-of-7 targets for 21 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 12 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b432-d413-ad9f-b5ffc6240000</link>
      <description>Otton’s surface stats look similar to the rest of the team considering the Buccaneers managed only 193 yards of total offense, but it was the mistakes that proved most costly. One of Baker Mayfield’s two interceptions was a ball juggled by Otton that was then ripped away by the defender, resulting in a pick-six in what was then a 7-0 game. The Rams would pile it on from there before taking a 31-7 lead into the break, made worse by a second quarter injury to Mayfield that held him out for the second half. The up-and-down season for the veteran tight end continues with uncertainty at the quarterback position, pending testing on Mayfield’s non-throwing shoulder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b432-d413-ad9f-b5ffc6240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin caught 2-of-4 targets for nine yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 12 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b435-d90e-a9da-bf3ff06a0000</link>
      <description>Godwin was confined to key downs in his return to the lineup, marking just his third appearance of the 2025 season. The veteran wide receiver made his first start since Week 5 after suffering a hairline fracture to his fibula. There is now added uncertainty in his fantasy value moving forward after quarterback Baker Mayfield suffered an apparent shoulder injury to his non-throwing shoulder in the second quarter. Godwin can’t be trusted as more than a deep stash at present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b435-d90e-a9da-bf3ff06a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 25-of-35 passes for 273 yards and three touchdowns in the Rams’ 34-7, Week 12 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b438-d90e-a9da-bf3f6af40000</link>
      <description>Stafford and the Rams came out with guns blazing while finding the end zone on each of their first three possessions, a lead that would be padded by a pick-six in the first quarter. The veteran signal caller came one completion shy of matching a career best for consecutive completions to start the game while finding Davante Adams twice in the end zone on fades from the red zone, extending his lead in passing touchdowns in the process. The win pushes the Rams to 9-2, who now find themselves alone atop the NFC heading into Thanksgiving week. It has also now been nine games since Stafford’s last interception, passing for 25 touchdowns in that span since his last pick. Winners of six in a row, the Rams await the surging Panthers in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b438-d90e-a9da-bf3f6af40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams rushed 12 times for 46 yards in the Rams’ Week 12 win over the Buccaneers, adding two yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b43f-d413-ad9f-b5ff7de10000</link>
      <description>The Rams jumped out to an early 21-0 lead and still attempted 35 passes against just 19 team carries, which paints a clear picture of the plan of attack against Vita Vea and the vaunted Tampa run defense. He’ll look to return to RB1 status when the Rams travel to face the Panthers in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b43f-d413-ad9f-b5ff7de10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 7-of-11 targets for 97 yards in the Rams’ Week 12 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b450-d90e-a9da-bf5f27920000</link>
      <description>Nacua ranks behind only Ja’Marr Chase and Drake London in targets per game in 2025 as he continues to churn out consistent production as the focal point of one of the most potent pass offenses in the league. The only thing typically missing, as it was against the Buccaneers, is a robust red zone role, which manifested again in Week 12 as Davante Adams scored twice from inside the red zone. Up next for Nacua and the Rams is the Cover-3-heavy Carolina defense, against whom he should once again serve as Stafford’s top option through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b450-d90e-a9da-bf5f27920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 5-of-8 targets for 62 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ Week 12 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b45e-d90e-a9da-bf5fb3f10000</link>
      <description>Adams now has 12 touchdowns in 11 games for the Rams after joining them this offseason, notching two additional scores against the Buccaneers from inside the red zone. Both came on fades against man coverage from Zyon McCollum. The veteran wide receiver also narrowly missed tacking on a third on a back shoulder fade that fell incomplete. Adams continues to cede the bulk of the usage between the 20s to Puka Nacua but maintains one of the most robust red zone roles in the league, propelling his weekly fantasy value into the WR1 range consistently. That remains the case ahead of a Week 13 matchup with the Cover-3-heavy Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b45e-d90e-a9da-bf5fb3f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught all four targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 12 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b462-d413-ad9f-b5fffab90000</link>
      <description>It was the first game after fellow tight end Tyler Higbee was placed on injured reserve with an ankle injury, making the standout performance from Parkinson notable. He’ll continue to cede primary aerial usage to Puka Nacua and Davante Adams but brings a history of successes in the red zone to an offense leading the league in passing touchdown in 2025. Fantasy managers in a bind at the position could do worse than taking a flier on that profile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b462-d413-ad9f-b5fffab90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles told reporters that QB Baker Mayfield “sprained his left shoulder and will undergo an MRI on Monday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3e7-d90e-a9da-bfef38fa0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield injured his left, non-throwing shoulder in the second quarter on Sunday night. The 30-year-old quarterback finished the first half but was visibly in pain between plays. The team briefly listed him as doubtful to return at halftime before ruling him out shortly thereafter. He stood on the sideline with his left arm in a sling during the second half. In January 2022, Mayfield underwent surgery on the same shoulder to repair a torn labrum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b3e7-d90e-a9da-bfef38fa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
