<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB James Cook (ankle/foot) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-566b-d1e7-a1fa-5eebf9670000</link>
      <description>We expect Cook to be listed as a limited participant today, but his return puts him on track to play in Week 10 against the Dolphins, whose run defense is among the league’s worst. Backup RBs Ray Davis and Ty Johnson are still worth stashing on benches, just in case Cook’s injury flares up, but at this time, neither one appears to be a locked-in FLEX-worthy starter this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-566b-d1e7-a1fa-5eebf9670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a5d-d673-a39e-fedd7dac0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Last week, Bills slot CB Taron Johnson was sidelined by a groin injury of his own. Benford nursed a groin injury earlier this season, but has not missed any games. Bills EDGE Joey Bosa is playing through a wrist issue and is visibly bothered by it in-game. He should be on the field in Week 10, unless he is downgraded tomorrow, though. The Bills face the Dolphins this weekend. Bills DT DaQuan Jones (calf) also resumed practicing today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a5d-d673-a39e-fedd7dac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman Jr. (glute) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a6f-d45b-affe-5fff8fc00000</link>
      <description>The Colts sometimes give injured players a full day off rather than allowing them to practice in a limited capacity, with the goal of practicing in full soon thereafter. We do not yet know Pittman’s practice participation level, but it would be unsurprising to see him labeled as a full-go today. Pittman is no stranger to playing through injury. His return to practice today puts him on track to play in Week 10 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a6f-d45b-affe-5fff8fc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin Jr. (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a82-d45b-affe-5f9694b00000</link>
      <description>The practice report should clarify the situation, but unexpected Thursday absences are concerning. Hopefully, this is simply an excused absence of some sort. Browns WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) is practicing in full this week, which is a positive. Rookie WR Isaiah Bond (foot) remains sidelined. Veteran TE David Njoku would climb up the TE1 ranks if Fannin were to sit out in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a82-d45b-affe-5f9694b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said Parker Washington will continue to be the team’s primary F (slot) receiver.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aa8-d1e7-a1fa-5aeaba200000</link>
      <description>This is good news for his fantasy viability for Week 10, as is the news that Jalen Pitre (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday. We’ll see how that situation unfolds this week, but the idea of Washington being the only reliable wideout Trevor Lawrence has actually played with and facing a backup slot corner makes his matchup against the Texans a little less forgiving. Coen also said Jakobi Meyers will learn the outside positions first on a short week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aa8-d1e7-a1fa-5aeaba200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans named Davis Mills their starting quarterback for Week 10’s game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aab-d1e7-a1fa-5aeb62680000</link>
      <description>With Houston playing on Thursday night next week, it’s possible that Mills parlays C.J. Stroud’s concussion into a few starts here. Mills is a bottom-rung superflex streamer with this offensive infrastructure, but he’s probably preferable to quarterbacks at the true bottom like Tyler Shough and Cam Ward against the Jaguars in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aab-d1e7-a1fa-5aeb62680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Devaughn Vele will “have a healthy role” and “be very involved” the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aae-d673-a39e-febfa2f40000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t necessarily mean that Vele is going to have a fantasy-worthy role, but with Rashid Shaheed in Seattle, Vele should at least see a majority of the snaps for a team that projects to throw a lot the rest of the season. He’s a worthwhile pickup in deeper leagues. Shallow- and mid-sized leagues can monitor him from the waiver wire and see what comes of his new role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5aae-d673-a39e-febfa2f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Garrett Wilson (knee) said he feels “great” and will play in Week 10 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a8c-d45b-affe-5f9efb940000</link>
      <description>Wilson practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday, putting him on track to play this weekend. Given his comments, it seems likely he upgraded to full on Thursday. Wilson sat out in Weeks 7-8, and the Jets were on bye in Week 9, helpfully giving him a no-cost week off to heal. Wilson should return to the borderline WR1/2 ranks against the Browns this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5a8c-d45b-affe-5f9efb940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions OC John Morton said they’re planning to get WR Isaac TeSlaa “more involved this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ab2-d713-ad9e-7ef679d20000</link>
      <description>Well, the Lions have now threatened this a second time this season. TeSlaa actually has played only 12 snaps in his previous two games. The rookie has some dynasty upside, but doesn’t need to be on re-draft rosters barring a much larger share of the offensive involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ab2-d713-ad9e-7ef679d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) is not practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ab6-d1e7-a1fa-5afe6ee30000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t seem like Thomas is going to be active this weekend at this point. If he is, we’re going to need to see a major turnaround on Friday, probably with a coach quote attached, for it to be more than a pessimistic-side-of-questionable situation. Thomas has not practiced either day this week after incurring the lowest high-ankle sprain of all-time against the Raiders on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ab6-d1e7-a1fa-5afe6ee30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
