<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Jermaine Johnson (calf) could be a game-time decision for Week 5 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aab9-dca3-a9fb-bfb92a020000</link>
      <description>Johnson hasn’t played since Week 2 and was listed as a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday, so he’s likely on the wrong side of playing this week. The fourth-year pass rusher has totaled seven tackles this season and is still waiting to secure his first sack of 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aab9-dca3-a9fb-bfb92a020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said he is “hopeful” that Jack Conklin (elbow) will play in Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aac8-dca3-a9fb-bfd9306e0000</link>
      <description>Conklin was upgraded to a full participant in Friday’s practice, suggesting he’ll have a good chance to play despite his questionable tag. The veteran tackle hasn’t played since Week 1 and, if active, will be tasked with protecting the blindside of lefty QB Dillon Gabriel, who is slated to make his first career start against the Vikings in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aac8-dca3-a9fb-bfd9306e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aacc-d95b-addb-eace37220000</link>
      <description>The Ravens will pass on the official word soon, but Jackson is a near lock to miss Week 5’s game against the Texans after being a DNP all week. The Ravens will start veteran backup Cooper Rush in his place in hopes of ending a two-game losing streak that’s been amplified by poor defensive play and untimely turnovers on offense. Rush threw for 52 yards on 9-of-13 passing in relief of Jackson last week. All Ravens pass-catchers will receive a downgrade with Rush under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aacc-d95b-addb-eace37220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out Bucky Irving (foot) for Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae0-d6e9-af9d-aaf0c1df0000</link>
      <description>It was reported earlier in the day that Irving was expected to miss Week 5’s contest, but the team has made it official. Irving could be looking at a multi-week absence thanks to the foot sprain that landed him in a walking boot and crutches after last week’s loss to the Eagles, although, if he avoids injured reserve, it’s possible he’ll miss less than four games. We’ll see if anything changes ahead of Week 6’s game against the 49ers, but the Buccaneers will roll with Rachaad White and Sean Tucker as their top two options this weekend, with White looking like the safer bet as far as fantasy is concerned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae0-d6e9-af9d-aaf0c1df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out Mike Evans (hamstring) for Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae1-d95b-addb-eae7d9fc0000</link>
      <description>The Bucs ruling Evans out for the week is more so a formality than anything unexpected. It was reported after Evans’ injury that the veteran receiver was expected to miss between 3-4 weeks, and Week 5’s absence will mark his second missed game of the season. It’s possible he surprises us and suits up for Week 6 against the Niners, but a Week 7 or 8 return date seems more realistic based on the timeline we were provided.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae1-d95b-addb-eae7d9fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills ruled out LB Dorian Williams (knee) for Week 5 vs. Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aadd-d95b-addb-eadf5e240000</link>
      <description>The Bills also ruled out CB Dorian Strong (neck), who was added to the injury report on Thursday. Williams suffered his knee injury in last week’s win over the Saints, putting the Bills down a key defender. Williams has totaled 18 tackles and one pass breakup in four starts for the Bills this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aadd-d95b-addb-eadf5e240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out Jamel Dean (hip) for Week 5 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae7-d6e9-af9d-aaf70e430000</link>
      <description>In addition to Dean, the Buccaneers also ruled out CB Benjamin Morrison (hamstring) and S Christian Izien (quad). Dean is the most notable absence here. Having appeared on 175 defensive snaps this season, per PFF, Dean has been stingy in coverage thus far, allowing just six receptions on 16 targets to go with 43 scoreless yards. Backup corners Jacob Parrish and Kindle Vildor figure to see some extended work with Dean now out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aae7-d6e9-af9d-aaf70e430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said “they’ll all have their roles” when asked about his RB splits for Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaf1-d6e9-af9d-aaf1b20d0000</link>
      <description>Super. Thanks. Gannon is choosing to play this one close to the vest two days after Michael Carter proclaimed himself as the starting RB for the next several weeks. There’s truly no way to know how this will play out, but we would expect Emari Demercado to have a role after opening the season as the team’s RB3 and posting season highs in offensive snaps (26) and routes run (17) in last week’s loss to the Seahawks. Carter makes for an interesting stash and shouldn’t be relied on as a fantasy starter in Week 5 outside of the most desperate situations. The same can be said of Zonovan “Bam” Knight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaf1-d6e9-af9d-aaf1b20d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers ruled out Chuba Hubbard (calf) for Week 5 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaf8-dca3-a9fb-bff96f8f0000</link>
      <description>Just hours after it was reported that Hubbard was expected to miss Week 5, the Panthers have confirmed their RB1 will miss Sunday’s game against the Dolphins. Hubbard’s injury isn’t expected to be something that sidelines him long-term, but the Panthers will give him the week off and turnover duties to Rico Dowdle and Trevor Etienne. Dowdle profiles as a solid RB2 with RB1 upside, while Etienne should be viewed as a stash until we see how he’s utilized sans Hubbard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaf8-dca3-a9fb-bff96f8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce (concussion) will not play in Week 5 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaff-d6e9-af9d-aaff00240000</link>
      <description>This one comes as a bit of a surprise after Pierce was a full participant on both Wednesday and Thursday. Despite the optimistic practice outlook, it would appear the speedster was unable to clear concussion protocol in time to play in Sunday’s game. Adonai Mitchell will take Pierce’s place against a Raiders defense that enters the weekend ranked 22nd in points allowed and 21st in yards allowed through the first four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aaff-d6e9-af9d-aaff00240000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
