<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 22:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed told reporters that he views Seattle as his “long-term home,” saying he is “here to stay.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55cf-d673-a39e-f5dff06d0000</link>
      <description>Shaheed is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of this season, so if Seahawks general manager John Schneider wants to keep him here long-term, a contract extension will soon be needed. Shaheed’s comments are easy for one to make before negotiations have begun, at which point, his advanced age (27) for a player coming off a rookie contract could be held against him. Regardless, the Seahawks acquired Shaheed with a vision in mind, reuniting him with his former OC, Klint Kubiak. Questions remain as to how Shaheed fits in with intriguing rookie WR Tory Horton and injured veteran WR Cooper Kupp (heel/hamstring), but Shaheed winning the No. 2 wide receiver role, while Horton attempts to overtake Kupp, is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55cf-d673-a39e-f5dff06d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55e6-d45b-affe-55f680d20000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been playing through the ankle issue for a few weeks. A limited session on Wednesday is standard fare for him. He should be good to go for Week 10’s game against the Panthers. With his efficiency on the decline and his pass-catching role falling off the map, Kamara is barely an RB3 versus Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55e6-d45b-affe-55f680d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55e8-d1e7-a1fa-5fea895e0000</link>
      <description>Tillman is now on track to play this weekend. Projecting the Browns’ impending target shares is challenging. TEs David Njoku and Harold Fannin Jr. should continue operating as a featured duo, while WR Jerry Jeudy gator-arms targets on the perimeter. Tillman has a chance to overtake the latter player in the pecking order, who has caught just 42.3 percent of his team-high 52 targets. Whether overtaking Jeudy earns Tillman FLEX consideration is a separate issue. He can be stashed in deep leagues, but cannot yet be counted on to produce down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55e8-d1e7-a1fa-5fea895e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond (foot) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ef-d713-ad9e-7dffd3870000</link>
      <description>Bond has not caught a pass since Week 6 despite briefly being talked up by the coaching staff. The rookie wide receiver does not need to be rostered in 12-team re-draft leagues, particularly with WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) expectedly returning from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ef-d713-ad9e-7dffd3870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ed-d45b-affe-55ff52140000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez left Week 9’s game against the Falcons for a concussion check. A full practice means he will be good to go for Week 10 against the Bucs. Gonzalez will likely be tasked with covering Emeka Egbuka this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55ed-d45b-affe-55ff52140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Jets and is not listed on the team’s injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f0-d713-ad9e-7df4c2b90000</link>
      <description>Reports rightly indicated that Judkins had decent odds of returning to action following the Browns’ Week 9 bye after suffering an AC joint sprain in Week 8 against the Patriots. The Browns’ featured rusher will be on the field this weekend and can be started as a borderline RB1/2 against a Jets defense that recently traded away game-wrecking DT Quinnen Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f0-d713-ad9e-7df4c2b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports free agent CB Asante Samuel Jr. will visit the Panthers, Packers, Vikings, 49ers, Bears, and Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f7-d713-ad9e-7df7872d0000</link>
      <description>Samuel Jr.'s Carolina visit was reported this morning. He is now up to six visits lined up for the next week, all with teams above .500 in the win-loss column. Samuel Jr. was recently medically cleared after undergoing spinal fusion surgery in the offseason. He is now free to sign with any team and should be back on the field after he gets up to speed with his new squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f7-d713-ad9e-7df7872d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55fe-d713-ad9e-7dfecf4d0000</link>
      <description>This is just what Purdy does these days. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reporters last week that Purdy had a chance to be active as a backup in Week 9 against the Giants. He was instead declared inactive before kickoff. It remains to be seen when he will return, though he will likely need to practice in full, repeatedly, before doing so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55fe-d713-ad9e-7dfecf4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon (ankle) was limited in Wednedsay’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5600-d1e7-a1fa-5eeac7f70000</link>
      <description>Gordon tweaked his ankle in Week 9 against the Ravens. The good news is that the game took place on Thursday night, giving Gordon the mini-bye to recover. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport called him “day to day” after the game. All signs point to Gordon suiting up on Sunday, including his limited practice for the first session of Week 10. Gordon is purely a two-down backup, and the Dolphins have rarely gotten the chance to establish the run this year. That won’t change versus the Bills, making Gordon a touchdown-or-bust RB5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5600-d1e7-a1fa-5eeac7f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f8-d673-a39e-f5f9ff270000</link>
      <description>Pearsall’s PCL sprain continues to be a problem. The 49ers’ early-season star has not practiced since suffering the injury in Week 4, and yet, the team has chosen not to place him on injured reserve. Pearsall technically has a chance to play if he can practice later this week, but it seems likely we will revisit his availability on Wednesday, next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-55f8-d673-a39e-f5f9ff270000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
