<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets downgraded RB Breece Hall (knee) to out for Week 18 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8565-dc7a-af9b-cfffa6e10000</link>
      <description>Hall’s season ends with 1,065 yards on the ground on 243 carries, good for a respectable 4.4 yards per carry mark. He added 350 yards and a touchdown on 36 receptions, bringing his season total to five scores. Hall played the 2025 season on the final year of his initial four-year rookie contract and is expected to draw significant interest in the offseason market, meaning he could have played his final snap as a member of the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8565-dc7a-af9b-cfffa6e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers T Tristan Wirfs (toe) and WR Chris Godwin (illness) are active for Week 18 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8571-d35e-a1bf-c5f32e4e0000</link>
      <description>Wirfs has been battling a turf toe injury but makes his return to the active roster just in time for a must-win game against the divisional rival Panthers with a potential playoff spot on the line. The Buccaneers need to beat the Panthers and have the Saints beat the Falcons to back their way into the postseason. Also active is Godwin after the veteran receiver was added to the injury report earlier Saturday with an illness. Inactive for the Buccaneers are QB Connor Bazelak, CB Jamel Dean, G Elijah Klein, OLB Anthony Nelson, WR Sterling Shepard, and DL Elijah Simmons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8571-d35e-a1bf-c5f32e4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Hunter Renfrow, CB Robert Rochell, S D’Anthony Bell, S Demani Richardson, LB Claudin Cherelus, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, and DT Tershawn Wharton inactive for Week 18 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8577-d968-a19b-ddf770f70000</link>
      <description>The Panthers remains mostly healthy as they prepare to face the Buccaneers on the road with the divisional title on the line. The path to the postseason is simple for the Panthers - win and in. A win would mark the team’s first NFC South title since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8577-d968-a19b-ddf770f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers elevated OT Brandon Parker and LB Eric Kendricks from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cd-d56e-afff-e7ed89e60000</link>
      <description>Parker’s elevation seems to suggest that Trent Williams will not be able to play Saturday against the Seahawks in Week 18. Kendricks will provide special teams depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cd-d56e-afff-e7ed89e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (illness) has been ruled out for Week 18 agaisnt the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cf-d968-a19b-ddff9f040000</link>
      <description>Bateman didn’t practice all week, and the 26-year-old wideout will miss the winner-take-division matchup against the Steelers. He should be available if Baltimore advances to the Wild Card round with a win over Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85cf-d968-a19b-ddff9f040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed WR Savion Williams on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85d2-d35e-a1bf-c5d23a820000</link>
      <description>Williams, 24, was a non-factor for Green Bay in 2025 with 10 catches for 78 yards; although he did a solid job as a kick returner with 717 yards on his 28 attempts. The 2025 third-round pick has the athleticism to be a helper in 2026, but fantasy managers in redraft leagues shouldn’t count on it .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85d2-d35e-a1bf-c5d23a820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills elevated EDGE Matthew Judon from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85de-d35e-a1bf-c5de67db0000</link>
      <description>Judon was signed by the Bills in the middle of December after being released by the Dolphins, and he’ll have a chance to show he could be a helper as a pass-rusher in the playoffs in Week 18 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85de-d35e-a1bf-c5de67db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers elevated QB DJ Uiagalelei from the pracice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85f9-d56e-afff-e7f9321d0000</link>
      <description>It will be Uiagalelei who backs up Trey Lance for the Week 18 finale against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-85f9-d56e-afff-e7f9321d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks elevated RB Cam Akers and CB Tyler Hall for Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8601-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7f180000</link>
      <description>Akers will be the third running back for the season finale versus San Francisco behind Kenneth Walker and Zack Charbonnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8601-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7f180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens elevated WR Keith Kirkwood from the practice squad for Week 18 agaisnt the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8608-d35e-a1bf-c7ca64900000</link>
      <description>Kirkwood will essentially take the roster spot of Rashod Bateman, with Bateman ruled out due to illness. The 32-year-old won’t likely do much outside of special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8608-d35e-a1bf-c7ca64900000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
