<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LB Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) won’t play in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86b4-deb6-a7fd-d7ffd0ec0000</link>
      <description>Van Ginkel was a DNP all week. The veteran linebacker suffered a neck injury in Week 2 against the Bengals and will now miss a second-straight game with the injury. The Vikings also ruled out J.J. McCarthy (ankle) ahead of the weekend, but the second-year quarterback isn’t expected to return until close to Week 7, so this was always expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86b4-deb6-a7fd-d7ffd0ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Anthony Belton hurt his knee in practice and won’t play in Week 4 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86c3-d6e9-af9d-8ed38f720000</link>
      <description>Belton started Week 2 for the injured Zach Tom (oblique), and took over for Tom in Week 3 after Tom logged one offensive snap. Tom is on the wrong side of playing after being a DNP all week, so Belton’s absence could force the Packers to roll with a third-string right tackle on Sunday. LaFleur said he doesn’t believe Belton’s injury is long-term, but if he and Tom are both unable to go, backup Darian Kinnard appears in line to draw the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86c3-d6e9-af9d-8ed38f720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said he expects Andrew Thomas (foot) to see an increased workload in Week 4 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86d3-d6e9-af9d-8ed3d9b00000</link>
      <description>Thomas made his return from a Lisfranc injury in Week 3 against the Chiefs, playing on 28 of the team’s 66 offensive snaps. Thomas played well in his return, allowing no sacks or pressures, per PFF, while earning a pass blocking grade of 84.4. Daboll didn’t indicate how much more work Thomas could see in Week 4, but it’s clear he’s trending to a complete return in the next week or so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86d3-d6e9-af9d-8ed3d9b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced it will play a regular season game in Rio de Janeiro in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86d8-d6e9-af9d-8ed80aee0000</link>
      <description>This will be the first of three regular-season games the league will play in Rio de Janeiro over the next five years. Next year will mark the third-straight season the league has played in Brazil, after the Chargers and Chiefs faced off in São Paul, Brazil, to kick off this season, and the Packers and Eagles met in Week 1 of 2024. Next season’s game will mark the first time an NFL regular-season game has been played in Rio at Maracanã Stadium. The league has not announced which two teams will play in Brazil next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86d8-d6e9-af9d-8ed80aee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) will not play in Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86dd-d6e9-af9d-8edda1b80000</link>
      <description>This was the most likely outcome after McLaurin missed all three days of practice during the week. The veteran receiver is reportedly dealing with an injury to his quad/hip/groin area, but isn’t expected to need surgery to correct the issue at this time. That said, McLaurin met with a core muscle specialist earlier in the week to get a second opinion on the injury, leading us to believe this could be more than a one-week absence. With McLaurin sidelined, Deebo Samuel becomes the default WR1 for the Commanders in Week 4, with veteran Chris Moore and second-year receiver Luke McCaffrey potentially in line to see bigger roles. In addition to McLaurin, the Commanders also ruled out WR Noah Brown (groin/knee) and TE John Bates (calf/groin) for Sunday’s contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86dd-d6e9-af9d-8edda1b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) will not play in Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86df-d95b-addb-eedff62b0000</link>
      <description>Despite being a limited participant in two practices this week, Daniels was a DNP on Friday and will now miss a second consecutive game with a knee injury. According to NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Daniels “was pushing to play,” however, doctors did not clear him to take the field. The Commanders will enter the week down two key starters in Daniels and Terry McLaurin (quad) in what could be a tough road matchup against a Falcons team looking to rebound from an embarrassing Week 3 loss to the Panthers. Marcus Mariota will again make the start in Daniels’ absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86df-d95b-addb-eedff62b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette (hamstring) won’t play in Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86e7-dca3-a9fb-bfff39080000</link>
      <description>Legette will miss his second-straight game with a hamstring injury he suffered in Week 2. The Panthers will likely deploy David Moore in his absence after Moore played on a season-high 56 offensive snaps in last week’s win over the Panthers while running 26 routes, per PFF. Moore saw only one target in that game and can be let on fantasy waivers this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86e7-dca3-a9fb-bfff39080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard (calf) is questionable for Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ea-d6e9-af9d-8efac9b80000</link>
      <description>Hubbard popped up on Thursday’s injury report with a calf injury and was officially limited as a limited participant. He was again listed as limited on Friday, which is a relatively good sign for his Week 4 availability, but his name will be one to watch when inactives are announced 90 minutes before kickoff. In the event he can’t go, backup Rico Dowdle would be the favorite to handle the majority of backfield duties with rookie Trevor Etienne also being in the mix for touches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ea-d6e9-af9d-8efac9b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren (knee) was added to Friday’s injury report and is questionable for Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ea-d6e9-af9d-8efac1390000</link>
      <description>This is a new one. Warren was listed as a limited participant in Wednesday and Thursday’s practices as a “resting vet,” but now the team has added a knee injury to the veteran back’s stauts. Hopefully, this is just a minor issue the Steelers are trying to manage throughout the week, but Warren’s status will be worth monitoring for fantasy managers. With the Steelers playing Week 4 in Ireland, fantasy managers will need to remember to check the Steelers’ inactives early in the morning. If Warren can’t go, Kenneth Gainwell would most likely handle lead duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ea-d6e9-af9d-8efac1390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith (hip) is questionable for Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ed-d95b-addb-eeefc07c0000</link>
      <description>Smith was a DNP on Wednesday but logged limited practices on back-to-back days to close out the week. The veteran tight end has been unreliable for fantasy managers in each of his last two games, totaling seven catches for 50 scoreless yards over that span. Even if he’s active, there’s little reason to start him in your lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86ed-d95b-addb-eeefc07c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
