<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 22:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 18 times for 80 yards in the Bills’ Week 14 win over the Bengals, adding 31 yards receiving on two targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac7-da9b-a9bf-fecf7b980000</link>
      <description>Coming off a historic performance against the Steelers, this was not quite the rushing performance many expected against the Bengals. Cook looked good, but found running room hard to come by throughout the day. He had a tough sequence in the third quarter where he ripped off a great run down the sideline, but had the ball knocked loose as he stretched for a touchdown at the 1-yard line. That run was called back for holding, and then two plays later, Cook lost a fumble for real that the Bengals recovered in the end zone. That seemed to seal a loss for the Bills before they pulled off a miraculous comeback. Cook remains an RB1 for fantasy, but he has struggled to find the end zone over the last few months, scoring four touchdowns in seven games since the team’s bye. Things won’t get easier next week against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac7-da9b-a9bf-fecf7b980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirk Cousins completed 15-of-30 passes for 162 yards and two interceptions in the Falcons’ 37-9, Week 14 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac2-d77b-adfa-fac3a1280000</link>
      <description>Cousins stuck to dink-and-dunk football versus the Seahawks’ elite defense. Even that couldn’t protect him from turnovers, of which he had two. Both were on short targets into traffic. The first was a tight-window pass to Kyle Pitts that deflected into the hands of a defender. The second was on a screen to David Sills. Seattle sniffed the play out instantly and hit Sills as the ball touched his hands. The shot popped the ball into the air and Devon Witherspoon eventually fielded the pass. Cousins has three touchdowns and three interceptions in four starts this year. Needless to say, he is not on the fantasy radar, even in 2QB leagues, heading into Week 15 versus the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac2-d77b-adfa-fac3a1280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught 3-of-6 targets for 87 yards in Jacksonville’s Week 14 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-faca-d77b-adfa-facb10220000</link>
      <description>The good news is that BTJ’s performance almost felt normal. He had a sensational one-handed catch down the sideline, and added a second long catch that wasn’t overturned despite being close on review. The bad news is that Trevor Lawrence threw 30 times and Thomas was only “in the picture” compared to Jakobi Meyers. He’s probably closer to the WR3 ranks than the WR2 ranks against the Jets in Week 15, and hasn’t scored a touchdown since October 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-faca-d77b-adfa-facb10220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed seven times for 92 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 14 win over the Jets, adding one reception for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac6-d8cf-affb-feee4e560000</link>
      <description>Achane got off to a fast start with the Dolphins offense. He ripped off a 39-yard rush on the first possession and was tackled at the three-yard line. Achane was able to punch in a score on the Dolphins’ second possession with a 13-yard run and continues to be a shifty playmaker in space. However, fantasy managers got a scare with Achane leaving the game in the second quarter with a rib injury. He was initially questionable to return and did return to stand on the sidelines, though he did not play a snap afterwards. It’s possible the Dolphins held him out with a large lead out of caution, but the rib injury is one to monitor with the fantasy playoffs on the horizon. Achane is a fantasy RB1 if he plays in Week 15 against the Steelers, otherwise Jaylen Wright and Ollie Gordon will carry the load.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac6-d8cf-affb-feee4e560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders ruled out CB Kyu Blu Kelly in Week 14 against the Broncos after suffering a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f097-d8cf-affb-fcbf37400000</link>
      <description>Kelly was injured on the Broncos’ second drive and remained down after the play with what the broadcast described as a “serious” leg injury. Trainers applied an air cast while teammates offered consolation before Kelly was taken to the locker room on the cart. Kelly leads the Raiders with three interceptions this season. His loss is consequential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f097-d8cf-affb-fcbf37400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 4-of-10 targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in Jacksonville’s Week 14 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-facd-d8cf-affb-feefb57a0000</link>
      <description>Meyers was being used as an almost ever-present part of this offense, even taking three carries for nine yards as an end around threat on key downs. He’s got low-end WR2 vibes heading into Week 15’s game against the Jets and has now gone over six targets and scored in each of his last three games. It’s clear he’s become Jacksonville’s No. 1 receiver and is now fully integrated into the offense after coming over at the trade deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-facd-d8cf-affb-feefb57a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught 6-of-7 targets for 93 yards in the Bills’ Week 14 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-facc-da9b-a9bf-fecd4a5d0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals came into the day as the worst defense in the NFL at defending tight ends. That proved true in Week 14 as the Bills’ three tight ends combined for 11 catches, 137 yards, and two touchdowns. Knox was the surprising leader of the group this week, but we wouldn’t expect that to continue in the weeks ahead. This was mainly about the matchup and the snowy conditions, so don’t go chasing this on the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-facc-da9b-a9bf-fecd4a5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 4-of-7 targets for 62 yards in the Vikings’ Week 14 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac7-da9b-a9bf-fecf632a0000</link>
      <description>Despite a decent day through the air for J.J. McCarthy, the Vikings’ pass-catchers remained mostly silent. Addison led the team with 62 yards on a team-high seven targets, with two of his receptions going for 20-plus yards. This week marked the first time in seven games that Addison went for 50 or more yards. Fantasy managers should keep expectations low in Week 15’s game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fac7-da9b-a9bf-fecf632a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 14 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fad0-da9b-a9bf-fedde9720000</link>
      <description>Kincaid returned for the first time since injuring his hamstring in Week 10 and made an immediate impact. The Bills featured their tight ends heavily this weekend against the Bengals, so Kincaid didn’t see a full complement of snaps, but he looked healthy and should be right back on the TE1 radar for the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fad0-da9b-a9bf-fedde9720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Patrick caught 5-of-6 targets for 78 yards and a touchdown in Jacksonville’s Week 14 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fad0-d8cf-affb-fefaf0880000</link>
      <description>...What? Patrick had been threatening some high target counts (nine in the last three games) and playing more snaps of late, but he managed a season-high 42 snaps and scored in Parker Washington’s absence. In fairness — his touchdown catch wasn’t exactly impressive as Trevor Lawrence broke the pocket and Patrick simply sat down on a route wide open in the end zone. He also had dropped a touchdown the play before. It’s possible he goes back into the pocket with Parker Washington back next week, but if Washington is absent again, it sounds like Patrick has some desperation FLEX appeal against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fad0-d8cf-affb-fefaf0880000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
