<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson caught 6-of-8 targets for 82 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 4 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9874-d95b-addb-f8765f5c0000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s touchdown came with under two minutes to play from 23 yards out, aided by Miami defensive coordinator Anthony Weaver’s questionable decision to send extra men on a blitz and leave Rasul Douglas isolated against the elite receiver on two consecutive plays while up by 14. The solid fantasy outing goes down as his third in four tries after notching three scores and 82 yards or more in those contests. Wilson has crept into fantasy WR1 territory in spite of the low volume exhibited by the New York pass offense through four games. Next up is a sparkling matchup against the injury ravaged Cowboys in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9874-d95b-addb-f8765f5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 5-of-7 targets for 65 yards in the Jets’ Week 4 loss to the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9888-d6e9-af9d-9a9870e60000</link>
      <description>Taylor finished second on the team in targets and yardage as the Jets were forced to work the intermediate areas of the field in the second half against soft shells from the Dolphins. He combined with alpha wide receiver Garrett Wilson and running back Breece Hall to account for 21 targets on 27 Justin Fields pass attempts, something fantasy managers are thrilled to see considering the general lack of pass-catching depth behind the top two options in the offense. Perhaps Taylor can keep the momentum going into a matchup with the Cowboys in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9888-d6e9-af9d-9a9870e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 17-of-25 passes for 177 yards and two touchdowns in the Dolphins’ 27-21, Week 4 win over the Jets, adding six yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988b-d95b-addb-f8cf35a70000</link>
      <description>Both of Tua’s passing scores went to newcomer tight end Darren Waller, emphasizing this team’s need for a legitimate red zone threat. In what seems like a constant drill for this Dolphins team in recent history, head coach Mike McDaniel will have to overcome more setbacks after star wide receiver Tyreek Hill saw his season end with a dislocated knee, something that could influence the team’s ability to attack downfield moving forward. Tagovailoa and McDaniel were able to overcome Hill’s injury in this one via cleverly designed short area passing build off play action, something that is only effective behind a threatening run game. Their offensive success in the near future likely depends on that ability. Lucky for them they get a reeling Panthers team in Week 5 before matchups against the Chargers, Browns, Falcons, and Ravens. Tagovailoa falls to a low-end QB2 with the injury to Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988b-d95b-addb-f8cf35a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 20 times for 99 yards and a touchdown in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets, adding two yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9890-dca3-a9fb-bd99a59f0000</link>
      <description>Achane was the spark for the offense, behind which they were able to find success on short and intermediate passing via play action. That became a pressing need for the offense following the departure of Tyreek Hill, who suffered a dislocated knee early in the third quarter. Achane’s pass game involvement should return in Week 5 when the Dolphins take on the Panthers considering Hill’s absence, and he remains an elite RB1 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9890-dca3-a9fb-bd99a59f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle caught 3-of-6 targets for 48 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9895-d6e9-af9d-9a9584710000</link>
      <description>Waddle’s volume was heavily influenced by positive game script as the Jets seemingly beat themselves with mistakes and penalties. That said, he could be counted on for a featured role moving forward after Tyreek Hill was lost for the season with a dislocated knee. Waddle has struggled to function as the primary target in previous seasons but will be tasked with that burden for the remainder of the 2025 season. Fantasy managers are hoping he can rise to the occasion and return WR2 numbers as the focal point of the offense through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9895-d6e9-af9d-9a9584710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller caught 3-of-4 targets for 27 yards and two touchdowns in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9898-deb6-a7fd-dbdfc2160000</link>
      <description>Waller was the recipient of both Tua Tagovailoa touchdown passes and even recovered the New York onside kick attempt to end the game, making his mark felt from the beginning. He played sparingly in his first appearance with the Dolphins, primarily held to third downs and red zone snaps, but still managed to give this team a spark in the red zone they have sorely lacked the previous two seasons. His first score came on a slant off a clean release on fourth down to give the team their first touchdown of the game and he added a second in the third quarter on a crosser off a rub. Waller’s size and athleticism make him an interesting fantasy bet as the team could be forced into more short area passing after they lost wide receiver Tyreek Hill for the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9898-deb6-a7fd-dbdfc2160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 2-of-3 targets for 13 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 4 win over the Jets, adding eight yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-989d-deb6-a7fd-dbdf9be10000</link>
      <description>Washington could be tasked with an increased role moving forward after star wide receiver Tyreek Hill was lost for the season with a dislocated knee. His current role as a gadget, short-area receiver could also be forced to change in the absence of Hill, which could give him paths to fantasy utility the rest of the season. Treat Washington as an upside FLEX until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-989d-deb6-a7fd-dbdf9be10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 29-of-42 passes for 326 yards, two touchdowns and one interception in the Broncos’ 28-3, Week 4 win over the Bengals, adding six rushes for seven yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988f-d95b-addb-f8cfd89e0000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ pass catchers hurt Nix with a few costly drops, but his interception was largely on him. The play occurred inside the Bengals’ five-yard line. Nix rolled out to the right and fired a pass to the right side of the end zone, straight into LB Demetrius Knight’s hands. It is unclear whether Nix intended to hit RB RJ Harvey or WR Troy Franklin running behind him, but it was an errant pass nonetheless. Aside from that error, Nix looked sharp throwing on the move. He is a low-end QB1 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-988f-d95b-addb-f8cfd89e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 5-of-6 targets for 81 yards and one touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 4 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98a9-dca3-a9fb-bdb9197a0000</link>
      <description>Sutton’s early-game successes allowed the Broncos to cruise to an easy victory in the second half. The Broncos’ No. 1 wide receiver caught 5-of-5 targets for 81 yards and a touchdown in the first half. He bullied Bengals’ would-be tacklers from the jump, looking fluid and assertive with the ball in his hands. His 8.8 yards after the catch average is a season-high. On his 20-yard score, he got open on a post route in the Bengals’ red zone, leaping to catch the pass from the four-yard line and coming down in the end zone. Sutton is a WR2 against the Eagles in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98a9-dca3-a9fb-bdb9197a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 6-of-6 targets for 69 yards in the Broncos’ Week 4 win over the Bengals, adding one rush for 16 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98ba-dca3-a9fb-bdbb92250000</link>
      <description>Mims racked up explosive gains, both through the air and on the ground, against the Bengals. He delivered a critical reception on the Broncos’ final drive before halftime by beating his cornerback one-on-one and securing the target for a 28-yard gain before the safety could get to him. Mims found the end zone earlier, on the Broncos’ third drive, via a 16-yard end-around thanks to a big block by WR Pat Bryant. Mims was later seemingly saved from an embarrassing fumble on a punt return when the referees called the recovering defender for a fair catch interference penalty after snatching the ball from Mims’ juggling hands when he bobbled it. Mims remains a volatile FLEX against the Eagles in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98ba-dca3-a9fb-bdbb92250000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
