<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings EDGE Andrew Van Ginkel (neck) will not play in Minnesota’s Week 7 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39d-d651-a9df-fb9d68fc0000</link>
      <description>Van Ginkel was able to generate a little positive progress off the bye, getting in some limited practice sessions after missing Week 4 and Week 5. It’s one step closer to a return, perhaps in Week 8. Dallas Turner figures to remain more involved with Van Ginkel out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39d-d651-a9df-fb9d68fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Abdul Carter (hamstring) is questionable for New York’s Week 7 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39f-d99b-a1dd-fb9f73920000</link>
      <description>He was a surprise limited participant in Friday’s practice, indicating he hurt it mid-session. Carter did talk to the media on Friday, which is usually a good sign, but he’s probably a true question mark heading into Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39f-d99b-a1dd-fb9f73920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 7 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39f-df81-ab9b-ffdf80a30000</link>
      <description>McCarthy is listed as questionable to play, though ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports that the young quarterback will serve as the Vikings’ emergency No. 3 QB. Quarterbacks in that role are typically listed on the official game-day inactive list, with the NFL allowing them to take the field if the Nos. 1 and 2 quarterbacks, in this case Carson Wentz and Max Brosmer, get hurt. McCarthy can be stashed in superflex leagues at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f39f-df81-ab9b-ffdf80a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RT Brian O’Neill (knee) is questionable for Minnesota’s Week 7 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3a3-d651-a9df-fbb716090000</link>
      <description>O’Neill missed Minnesota’s final game in England after spraining his MCL in Ireland during Week 4’s loss to the Steelers. O’Neill did practice thrice this week and it would be a big help for Minnesota’s offensive line, which is getting healthier, if he were able to go against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3a3-d651-a9df-fbb716090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) and WR Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) are practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3aa-d651-a9df-fbbffb190000</link>
      <description>Neither player would seem especially likely to play — particularly Bowers after Pete Carroll said earlier this week that it might be best for the long haul if he sits — but they’re both giving it a go to see where they’re at in Friday’s practice. The injury status report will drop soon and be the main indicator for how far this goes. We’re still expecting Bowers to be ruled out, but perhaps Meyers has a chance to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3aa-d651-a9df-fbbffb190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs ruled out OT Josh Simmons (personal) for Week 7 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ac-d651-a9df-fbbdfc9f0000</link>
      <description>Chiefs OT Jaylon Moore will start in Simmons’ stead, as the rookie deals with a personal matter. Moore is a downgrade on Patrick Mahomes’ blindside, unfortunately, but the Chiefs’ offense should move the ball efficiently, regardless. Chiefs RB Brashard Smith (illness) is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ac-d651-a9df-fbbdfc9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Josh Reynolds (hip) is not on New York’s final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3b4-d651-a9df-fbb56c3e0000</link>
      <description>With Garrett Wilson officially doubtful, Reynolds has a chance to step in as the Jets No. 1 receiver. We’re sure there’s a league deep enough for that to matter, but we can’t endorse Reynolds as a what-the-heck FLEX in most standard-sized leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3b4-d651-a9df-fbb56c3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (groin) is questionable for Indianapolis’ Week 7 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3b9-d99b-a1dd-fbbd4ca90000</link>
      <description>Goodson has been healthy enough to suit up for two weeks this season and recorded four offensive snaps in each game. Even if he does finally shake off this groin injury, you can do better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3b9-d99b-a1dd-fbbd4ca90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles CB Quinyon Mitchell (hamstring) is not on Philadelphia’s final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3bb-d651-a9df-fbbfa92d0000</link>
      <description>Quinyanamo Bay is accepting Justin Jefferson applications for Week 7. We don’t think Jefferson is in any danger of getting shut out, but expectations should be somewhat tempered for the sure-fire WR1 against Philadelphia’s best cover corner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3bb-d651-a9df-fbbfa92d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OL Landon Dickerson (ankle) is questionable for Philadelphia’s Week 7 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3bd-da18-a39b-fbbf22530000</link>
      <description>Dickerson got in a full practice and seems like he’s on the optimistic side of questionable after missing Week 6’s TNF game against the Giants. Jalen Carter (heel) could only go for a limited session after missing last week’s game and is probably closer to a true question mark heading into 48 hours before game time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3bd-da18-a39b-fbbf22530000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
