<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip/groin) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eea6-da18-a39b-feb7af1d0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade over Wednesday’s DNP for the 28-year-old receiver. It sounds like there’s a real chance he’s able to go for Week 7, but we wouldn’t be surprised if he wound up on the questionable line. We’ve still seen nothing about the extent of the injury that hospitalized Moore unexpectedly after Monday night’s win over the Commanders. Friday’s status update will be revealing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eea6-da18-a39b-feb7af1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee8f-da18-a39b-fe9f48330000</link>
      <description>Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) and DB Avonte Maddox (hamstring) remain sidelined. Joseph has been playing through the knee injury as best he can, but misses snaps in-game from time to time. The Lions will be without S Brian Branch (suspension) against the Buccaneers on Monday night. The Buccaneers’ offense is also short-staffed, but QB Baker Mayfield will do what he can to exploit the Lions’ beleaguered unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ee8f-da18-a39b-fe9f48330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Wilson (knee) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeab-da18-a39b-febb1ae90000</link>
      <description>He almost certainly will be ruled out on Friday given the fact that he’s expected to miss a couple of weeks with this knee injury. Week 10, after the Jets Week 9 bye, feels like the most likely spot for Wilson to make his return from the sidelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeab-da18-a39b-febb1ae90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Van Jefferson (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eea6-d651-a9df-efb75eb90000</link>
      <description>Jefferson remains limited through two practices, which puts him on track to play. The journeyman wide receiver earned six targets last week, trailing only TE Chig Okonkwo (seven). Jefferson can only be viewed as a dart-throw FLEX option, though, given his streaky play and difficult matchup against the Patriots, if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eea6-d651-a9df-efb75eb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Reynolds (hip) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeae-da18-a39b-febf4cfc0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from a DNP on Wednesday. Reynolds is looking like the Jets No. 1 receiver by default against the Panthers. Were it for not for the overall instability of the Jets passing attack, Reynolds would look like a lot more interesting of a play. Carolina has been something of a pass funnel of late. Still, it’s possible that there’s desperation FLEX value to be mined here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeae-da18-a39b-febf4cfc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez (calf) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb0-df81-ab9b-fef7349a0000</link>
      <description>That makes back-to-back DNPs for Rodriguez, who has not practiced since Washington’s win over the Chargers. He did actually suit up for Week 6 despite the lack of practice time, but had just one offensive snap and looked to be an emergency-only option as “Bill” took the reins. The continued missed practice time will make it hard for him to do more than be an emergency option again in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb0-df81-ab9b-fef7349a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb2-d651-a9df-efb7b64d0000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be fine, but Ertz missed Wednesday’s practice with the ailment. Given how things are trending for the Commanders main passing weapons, Ertz could be in for a throwback game against a weak Cowboys pass defense in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb2-d651-a9df-efb7b64d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (hip) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeaa-df81-ab9b-feef98d70000</link>
      <description>Outstanding news. Olave appeared on Wednesday’s injury report as a limited participant but he is now firmly on track to play in Week 7 against the Bears. The two struggling defenses should facilitate a fantasy-friendly environment for both teams’ offensive stars. Olave’s 61 targets are second only to Puka Nacua’s 64. Olave is a locked-in WR2 with upside this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeaa-df81-ab9b-feef98d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb5-d651-a9df-efb5f2760000</link>
      <description>We expect Pearsall to officially be listed as a non-participant once again when the 49ers’ injury report comes out later today. The 49ers’ wide receiver has neither practiced nor played since spraining his PCL in Week 4, and appears to be heading toward another missed game this weekend. Kendrick Bourne could again operate as the 49ers’ No. 1 wide receiver when they face the Falcons on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eeb5-d651-a9df-efb5f2760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR CeeDee Lamb (ankle) said he will play in Week 7 against the Commanders “without limitations.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eecb-d651-a9df-efdf38400000</link>
      <description>Lamb told reporters that he could have played in Week 6 against the Panthers, but sat out an extra week so he could be “fully healthy” upon his return. Lamb remains sidelined through two Week 7 practices, but we assume this is simply a precautionary measure as the star wide receiver eases back into action following a high-ankle sprain suffered in Week 3. He can immediately be started as a high-end WR1. Fellow WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) also remained limited on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-eecb-d651-a9df-efdf38400000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
