<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Breece Hall (knee) is questionable to play in Week 18 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-805b-d35e-a1bf-c5dbc2cb0000</link>
      <description>When asked if Hall will play, Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said, “we’ll see.” Glenn has played coy with most start-sit decisions in the Jets’ 3-13 season. No reason to stop now. Hall logged just two limited sessions to close the week. He is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the season. Preserving his health for free agency could be the smart move. He may wish to put his stamp on the season with a strong showing, though. It would be difficult to project his playing time if he is active. Treat him as a volatile RB2 if he suits up. His backup, RB Isaiah Davis (concussion), has been ruled out, leaving Kene Nwangwu (quad) and Khalil Herbert behind Hall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-805b-d35e-a1bf-c5dbc2cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) is not on Dallas’ final Week 18 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8063-dc7a-af9b-cffff5b20000</link>
      <description>He’ll get some work in with Dak Prescott in the finale. Flournoy has showcased some big play ability and nearly had a two-touchdown game against the Chargers in December before leaving with an injury. He’s a potential WR4/WR5 play this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8063-dc7a-af9b-cffff5b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) is not on Dallas’ final Week 18 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8066-d968-a19b-d8f7442c0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson probably isn’t in line for major work in the finale as he has just 10 targets in his last three games, but the calf injury he tweaked in Week 17 won’t hold him out here. Ferguson would be a low-end TE1 if we could count on four quarters of Dak Prescott. Since we can’t, he’s probably in the TE2 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8066-d968-a19b-d8f7442c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) is questionable to play in Week 18 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8051-d968-a19b-d8f1b5210000</link>
      <description>Taylor has dealt with knee injuries intermittently this season. If he is unable to suit up as Brady Cook’s backup, the Jets will call up QB Hendon Hooker from the practice squad, who the Jets added in-season..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8051-d968-a19b-d8f1b5210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Isiah Pacheco (NIR/rest) is questionable for Kansas City’s Week 18 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8076-d968-a19b-d8f7214f0000</link>
      <description>Uh, okay, why not. Kareem Hunt carries no designation and looks to be the main bludgeoning back against a Raiders team that has given up in Week 18 if Pacheco can’t shake his dreaded case of NIR/rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8076-d968-a19b-d8f7214f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions T Penei Sewell (ankle) won’t play in Detroit’s Week 18 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8078-d35e-a1bf-c5fac3360000</link>
      <description>He’s out, and the Lions made Giovanni Manu (knee), Christian Mahogany (illness), Kayode Awosika (illness) and Taylor Decker (shoulder/illness rest) questionable as well. Keeping Jared Goff upright could be a challenge for the Lions in Week 18 with that much of their offensive line on the injury report, even if the questionable tags play. Sewell ends his age-25 season with a career-high 95.0 PFF offensive grade in 998 offensive snaps. He will be desperately missed in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8078-d35e-a1bf-c5fac3360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) is not on the injury report for Week 18 against Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-806a-dc7a-af9b-cfff57480000</link>
      <description>Jacobs will be available if the Packers need him. Yesterday, Packers RB coach Ben Sirmans indicated Jacobs won’t play much, if at all, though. Either No. 2 Emanuel Wilson or No. 3 RB Chris Brooks will lead the backfield in touches. Wilson has played a key role in the Packers’ offense this season. He could join Jacobs in the proverbial bubble wrap on the sideline this week. If so, Brooks warrants RB2/3 consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-806a-dc7a-af9b-cfff57480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (knee/ankle) is questionable for Detroit’s Week 18 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-807b-d35e-a1bf-c5fbfafe0000</link>
      <description>Dan Campbell said that St. Brown is trending towards playing earlier today. He should be considered on the optimistic side of questionable. He’s on the WR1 line in fantasy leagues that are still going in Week 18, but could be at risk of sitting later in the game if things get out of hand in one way or the other as the Lions have nothing to play for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-807b-d35e-a1bf-c5fbfafe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (hamstring) is not on Pittsburgh’s final Week 18 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-807f-d56e-afff-e6ff6a350000</link>
      <description>He’s a fringe WR4/WR5 without D.K. Metcalf as the Steelers try to find some semblance of seam-stretching power against the Ravens in a must-win AFC North divisional title game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-807f-d56e-afff-e6ff6a350000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
