<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Alvin Kamara (ankle) is expected to play in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44ca-d45b-affe-55de31050000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been dealing with the ankle issue for a few weeks. He appeared to aggravate the injury in Week 8’s loss to the Bucs but managed three limited practices during the week. Head coach Kellen Moore was optimistic about him suiting up as of Friday. Kamara has been losing work to his backups more often this year and his efficiency has fallen off the map. As a massive underdog to the Rams this week, he barely registers as an RB3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44ca-d45b-affe-55de31050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rashid Shaheed (hip) is expected to play in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44cc-d45b-affe-55de0d440000</link>
      <description>Shaheed injured his hip late in the Saints’ Week 8 loss to the Bucs. He was limited in practice throughout the week before being given a questionable designation. With Tyler Shough making his first start this week, Shaheed has no floor to offer fantasy managers, despite the Saints likely needing to pass early and often to hang with the Rams. He remains a boom/bust WR4 for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44cc-d45b-affe-55de0d440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Dalton Schultz (knee/shoulder) is expected to play in Week 9 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44d2-d673-a39e-e4d36eab0000</link>
      <description>Schultz looked truly questionable for Week 9 after missing practice on Wednesday and Thursday. He returned for a full practice on Friday, putting him in line to play despite the questionable tag. Schultz managed just two catches for 24 yards with Nico Collins out last week. Collins and Christian Kirk are back in the lineup, meaning Schultz’s target share will likely take a hit versus Denver. He is a low-ceiling TE2 for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44d2-d673-a39e-e4d36eab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes “a potential benching is not off the table at some point this season” for Tua Tagovailoa.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44d6-d713-ad9e-6cd64ba30000</link>
      <description>Rapoport doesn’t cite any sources, but it’s hard to argue with his speculation. Tagovailoa leads the league with 11 interceptions and the Dolphins are all but out of the playoff hunt with a 2-7 record. The team has Zach Wilson as his backup and rookie Quinn Ewers waiting in the wings. As Rapoport points out, the Dolphins would take on a record-setting cap hit of $114.2 million if they cut Tua next offseason. They could spread it out between 2026 and 2027 via a post-June 1st designation, but it will be painful no matter how the accounting is done. Miami could also trade Tagovailoa, though they would still need to eat a large portion of his contract before any team considers buying the damaged goods. Either way, all signs point to a split between Tua and Miami sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44d6-d713-ad9e-6cd64ba30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel “is staying for the foreseeable future, with the hope that he continues to coach through 2025 and beyond.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44dc-d713-ad9e-6cdc1ed60000</link>
      <description>Rapoport almost immediately followed up with, “If the on-field product really suffers, however, and the players essentially stop playing for him, changes could be made prior to the end of the season.” At 2-7 with no hope in sight, it’s safe to say the on-field product is already suffering. The Dolphins let go of GM Chris Grier and Tua Tagovailoa could be benched at any point. There are only so many heads that can roll in Miami, and McDaniel is on the shortlist. The Dolphins appear destined for a full reset in 2026, even if they are put on a brave face and stick with McDaniel through the end of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44dc-d713-ad9e-6cdc1ed60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Calvin Ridley “has emerged as a potential trade target.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eebc1950000</link>
      <description>Ridley has been out since Week 6 with a hamstring injury, making a trade for the age-30 wideout a risky proposition for any team. On the other hand, the Titans are going full youth movement, having already traded cornerback Roger McCreary and released wideout Tyler Lockett. Moving on from Ridley would allow the team to keep evaluating rookie wide receivers Elic Ayomanor and Chimere Dike. Ridley still has two years left on his current deal, though he will likely be a cap casualty in the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eebc1950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports a trade for Jaylen Waddle is considered “highly unlikely.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44f1-d1e7-a1fa-5efb98130000</link>
      <description>As much sense as a Waddle trade makes, teams rarely commit to the most obvious of moves. Having already fired GM Chris Grier, the Dolphins are all but throwing in the towel in the 2025 season. With a dead cap hit of over $100 million potentially on the horizon via Tua Tagovailoa’s release, the Dolphins could be staring down the barrel of a multi-year rebuild. Schefter notes that the Dolphins are looking for “a 1 plus” as compensation in a Waddle trade. We doubt any team is willing to spend that much, meaning Waddle will remain a Dolphin for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-44f1-d1e7-a1fa-5efb98130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver reports the Jaguars “are confident” that Travis Hunter “did not sustain any long-term damage to his knee.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4500-d45b-affe-559647ef0000</link>
      <description>Hunter suffered a non-contact knee injury in practice on Thursday. The good news is that both Silver and ESPN’s Adam Schefter have made optimistic reports on Hunter’s outlook. Per Schefter, Hunter’s ACL is intact. The bad news, on the other hand, is that the Jags immediately placed the No. 2 overall pick on injured reserve and we still don’t have concrete details on the nature of the injury. Hunter will miss at least four games while on IR, though we suspect he will be out much longer than a month. As Silver notes, the Jags will not rush him back, meaning Brian Thomas Jr. will continue to operate as the team’s No. 1 wideout for a while, possibly the remainder of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4500-d45b-affe-559647ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Vikings “could make a move for a quarterback by Tuesday’s deadline.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4520-d1e7-a1fa-5feae6040000</link>
      <description>As Schefter notes, the Vikings always wanted to have an experienced backup behind J.J. McCarthy. They signed Carson Wentz in the offseason, but his year is now over because of a shoulder injury. That leaves them with only UDFA rookie Max Brosmer to back up McCarthy. Schefter mentioned the usual suspects as trade candidates: Kirk Cousins, Russell Wilson, and Jameis Winston. The Falcons have shown little interest in trading Cousins, and his $180 million contract makes a deal hard to swing for both sides. The Giants, on the other hand, don’t need two veteran backups for Jaxson Dart. McCarthy’s performance against Detroit today will play a major role in how important the QB2 position in Minnesota is going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4520-d1e7-a1fa-5feae6040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Tracy Wolfson reports Isiah Pacheco (knee) is expected to return after the Chiefs’ Week 10 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4533-d673-a39e-e5b36bb50000</link>
      <description>Pacheco has already been ruled out for Week 9. He went down with an MCL sprain versus the Commanders and did not practice once this week. An extra week of rest between now and Kansas City’s next game should be enough to get him back on the field. Kareem Hunt and Brashard Smith with handle the backfield versus Buffalo. Hunt should see the majority of the carries while Smith will get a mix of rushes and targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4533-d673-a39e-e5b36bb50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
