<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Kenny Pickett is likely to start in Week 15 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b1-d8cf-affb-bdbb21740000</link>
      <description>Pickett faces one of his former teams this weekend. The 27-year-old quarterback appeared in seven games for the Eagles during their Super Bowl-winning season last year, averaging 6.8 yards per attempt on 43 attempts from Week 1-Super Bowl LIX. Pickett is now working with far less talent-wise, and can only be viewed as a shaky QB2 if he indeed gets the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b1-d8cf-affb-bdbb21740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b1-da9b-a9bf-dfbdb92e0000</link>
      <description>In a stunning turn of events, St. Brown played on Thursday last week despite being held out of all three practices leading up to the game. He played a relatively normal role, catching six passes for 96 yards. Even a limited practice today is a good sign that his ankle issue is getting better. He will hold a spot at the back of the WR1 ranks for his Week 15 date with the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b1-da9b-a9bf-dfbdb92e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions TE Shane Zylstra (knee) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b8-d8cf-affb-bdba3cca0000</link>
      <description>The Lions were without their top three tight ends last week. Sam LaPorta and Brock Wright were—and remain—on injured reserve while Zylstra missed the game with a knee issue. His return to practice today puts him on track to start for Detroit in Week 15. In a potential shootout with the Rams, Zylstra will be a touchdown-or-bust TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09b8-d8cf-affb-bdba3cca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said CeeDee Lamb has two more hurdles to clear in the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09bc-d8cf-affb-bdbe44cb0000</link>
      <description>Lamb was spotted at practice today. He suffered the brain injury on Thursday versus the Lions. Lamb was ruled out shortly after exiting the game and immediately entered the league’s protocol. It sounds like he is trending toward playing in Week 15, but there are certain benchmarks he has to clear before being given the green light. If he does sit, Ryan Flournoy, who went for 115 yards and a touchdown versus the Lions, would be the next man up in Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09bc-d8cf-affb-bdbe44cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ad-d8cf-affb-bdaf67e50000</link>
      <description>Jacobs worked with Packers trainers on Wednesday, as he continues to work through the bone bruise he suffered in Week 11 against the Giants. We expect Jacobs to resume practicing tomorrow. He should handle his typical high-volume workload, but he faces the Broncos’ elite defense, potentially pushing him into the high-end RB2 tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ad-d8cf-affb-bdaf67e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans (collarbone) is questionable for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c4-d77b-adfb-cbc7f8220000</link>
      <description>Evans was limited in practice throughout the week. Head coach Todd Bowles told reporters this morning that Evans “has shown everything he needed to show” to play in Week 15. It sounds like fantasy managers can plan on having him back in the fold this week. In his first game back, Evans should be treated as a high-variance WR3, though he could be back in the WR2 ranks as soon as Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c4-d77b-adfb-cbc7f8220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LT Tristan Wirfs (oblique) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c8-d77b-adfb-cbcb30bf0000</link>
      <description>The Bucs are getting healthy just in time for a playoff push. Wirfs practiced in full today and is good to go. Mike Evans appears to be on the right side of his questionable tag as well. Baker Mayfield and the Bucs’ offense have repeatedly flopped over the past month. If they are ever going to turn things around, tomorrow’s game against Atlanta would be the time to do it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c8-d77b-adfb-cbcb30bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton (knee) is doubtful for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09cb-da9b-a9bf-dfcfdde90000</link>
      <description>Otton failed to practice on Monday or Tuesday. He managed a limited session today, but the doubtful tag makes it highly unlikely that he suits up versus Atlatna. Payne Durham will see an uptick in routes with Otton out, though there won’t be many targets for him to handle with Mike Evans expected to make his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09cb-da9b-a9bf-dfcfdde90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen McMillan (neck) is questionable for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ce-d77b-adfb-cbcf53080000</link>
      <description>McMillan suffered a neck injury during the preseason and hasn’t played this year. He remains on injured reserve, meaning the team will have to officially activate him if he is going to suit up. With Mike Evans also expected to return, McMillan won’t have much of a role in his first game of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ce-d77b-adfb-cbcf53080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d1-d8cf-affb-bdfbe50c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ role has declined in recent weeks with Rhamondre Stevenson healthy once again. Jennings did not touch the ball before the Pats’ bye in Week 14. His likely absence this week will keep New England’s backfield at a two-man committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d1-d8cf-affb-bdfbe50c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
