<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:06:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Vikings have had trade talks with teams regarding DT Javon Hargrave.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f3-d629-a1bc-b0ff548b0000</link>
      <description>This is usually the first step towards a release, and The Athletic’s Alec Lewis called Hargrave’s release “a predictable offseason move” in December. Hargrave simply didn’t live up to expectations last year. Entering his age-33 season, we’d be surprised if the Vikings got anything more than a late-round swap for Hargrave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f3-d629-a1bc-b0ff548b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions GM Brad Holmes said the team has had conversations with David Montgomery and his agent and the situation is “fluid.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f5-d042-afbc-fdf73d960000</link>
      <description>It sure sounds like the Lions could move on from Montgomery in a trade. Entering his age-29 season, Montgomery could emerge as a solid fantasy RB2 in the right situation this offseason. This Lions enter the offseason roughly $10 million over the cap, releasing Montgomery would free up $3.5 million. It is also possible that Montgomery simply wants a bigger role than he had down the stretch during Jahmyr Gibbs’ takeover. Montgomery had 10 or more carries just once after Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f5-d042-afbc-fdf73d960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said he’s “not overly optimistic” about Jeremiah Owusu-Koramoah (neck) playing in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f9-d042-afbc-fdfbb35c0000</link>
      <description>A recent report from Mary Kay Cabot said Owusu-Koramoah is “doubtful to ever return to the field,” so missing just the 2026 season would be a mild upgrade. It’s clear that Owusu-Koramoah is not returning any time soon, but we’ll continue to monitor the situation in case the tone around that changes at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f9-d042-afbc-fdfbb35c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he’ll call plays on defense in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90fc-d89c-a1be-bfff40120000</link>
      <description>It confirms one of the worst-kept secrets in the league after the Jets passed up on numerous other coordinator options to land on unheralded Brian Duker as their defensive coordinator. Glenn said “play calling is my superpower, really.” Well, it’s good to have one of those. We’ll see how it lasts with this Jets roster. It certainly can’t be worse than it was last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90fc-d89c-a1be-bfff40120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said RB Quinshon Judkins (leg/ankle) is out of his boot and will be good to go for training camp.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9109-d629-a1bc-b11db03e0000</link>
      <description>It’s expected news, but good to hear it from a team source. Judkins was expected to miss about 4-5 months after fracturing his fibula and dislocating his ankle in late December. It’s possible that Judkins could show up for some later parts of minicamp/OTAs based on that schedule, but even if he doesn’t, he should be ready to be Cleveland’s bellcow back in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9109-d629-a1bc-b11db03e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said it’s “too early to say” if Deshaun Watson or Shedeur Sanders will be their Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</link>
      <description>Between the smoke on Ty Simpson and Malik Willis and Berry refusing to really stamp a player as “in the lead” here, it sure feels like this situation is unsettled heading into free agency. Sanders probably enters training camp as the main favorite for the job if the Browns don’t sign Willis, but anything could happen there. Up to and including a drafted quarterback winning the organization over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said OC Brad Idzik will call offensive plays for the Panthers in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910f-d629-a1bc-b11f731e0000</link>
      <description>We’re interested in seeing if Idzik will bring more of a deep-shot focused approach to the table, it’s an area where the Panthers have sporadically been good with Bryce Young, but one they seemingly can’t access every game. Otherwise we’d generally call moving to an unknown playcaller a theoretical downgrade for the Panthers, but it’s hard to get too caught up in it given Canales wasn’t exactly blowing anyone away in the coach tape community.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910f-d629-a1bc-b11f731e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks GM John Schneider said “obviously we’d love” to have Kenneth Walker back, but didn’t comment on the idea of franchise-tagging Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9117-d57c-a1dd-951f66260000</link>
      <description>Walker has been bandied about as a possible target for the tag, though Adam Schefter reported it was unlikely last week. This could perhaps be another space for the transition tag, as Breece Hall is learning. That tag would simply allow the Seahawks to match any offer Walker signs in free agency. Regardless of what they do, with Zach Charbonnet likely out well into the season, the Seahawks are heavily incentivized to keep Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9117-d57c-a1dd-951f66260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Kevin Stefanski said “i’m not big on giving out positions in February” when asked if Michael Penix is the team’s starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9122-d57c-a1dd-952abc890000</link>
      <description>“I think you guys know how I feel about Michael and I’m excited about his trajectory. I also know he’s focused on his rehab, which is the right thing to do,” Stefanski continued. Penix certainly appears to be the starting quarterback on the roster by default, but it’s possible that the Falcons could get involved in free agency to find a bridge quarterback — or perhaps more — to upgrade the room. It’s not as if Penix’s first two years of action were unimpeachable proof he has to start in 2026. It’s a situation to watch as free agency unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9122-d57c-a1dd-952abc890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper believes G Mekhi Becton could be a cap casualty.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9137-d57c-a1dd-953fed6d0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers would save $10 million by moving on from Becton, who openly seemed to not jive with former OC Greg Roman’s preferred blocking structures. Chargers GM Joe Hortiz said “I’m not going to talk about that right now” when asked about a Becton release at the NFL Combine. Becton, entering just his age-27 season, would be an interesting rebound candidate on the open market after a woeful year in Los Angeles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9137-d57c-a1dd-953fed6d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
