<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said LT Broderick Jones (neck) won’t play in Pittsburgh’s Week 13 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc2d-d413-ad9f-bdfd8b960000</link>
      <description>Jones played 49 snaps in Week 12 before giving way to Calvin Anderson at left tackle. Anderson is the likely replacement in Week 13. Tomlin also said that rookie DT Derrick Harmon (knee) will miss this game as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc2d-d413-ad9f-bdfd8b960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said DK Metcalf (ankle) will be limited early in the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc31-d82c-a79a-bfb50feb0000</link>
      <description>Metcalf played a season-high 61 snaps against the Bears last week, so he didn’t appear to be especially limited by the ankle in-game. This will likely just be an injury the Steelers manage through his practice schedule with rather than something that threatens his Week 13 status, but we’ll keep an eye on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc31-d82c-a79a-bfb50feb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said he has “great optimism” that Aaron Rodgers (wrist) will play in Pittsburgh’s Week 13 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc33-d90e-a9da-bf3f28490000</link>
      <description>Rodgers will reportedly be limited early in the week, and Tomlin added that his practice participation will “dictate the quarterback’s availability” for Sunday. Certainly we aren’t getting set up for another Mason Rudolph rug pull on Sunday morning, no, no, why would you suggest that? If Rodgers plays against the Bills he’ll merely be a QB2 option in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc33-d90e-a9da-bf3f28490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Isiah Pacheco (knee) will play in Kansas City’s Week 13 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc35-d90e-a9da-bf3ffc5c0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys defense has been revitalized of late with their midseason acquisition of Quinnen Williams and did a great job handling Philadelphia’s run game, so it remains to be seen if this is the smash spot it looked a week ago. Still, Pacheco is an RB3/FLEX option this week and his return likely pushes Kareem Hunt into the same tier as the two have roughly split snaps when healthy this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc35-d90e-a9da-bf3ffc5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Rashee Rice (hamstring) is expected to practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc38-db57-afda-fe3aab6c0000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be headed for a limited session, but this should quell the panic that he might miss the game against the Cowboys on Thanksgiving. Rice is coming off a 8/141 game on 12 targets against the Colts and should be a set-it, forget-it WR1 in Week 13 as long as he plays and no dire reporting emerges about the hamstring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc38-db57-afda-fe3aab6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes the 49ers could get “a Day 2 pick in 2026 and maybe a conditional Day 3 pick in 2027" for Mac Jones this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc47-d90e-a9da-bf4fb2d70000</link>
      <description>The rub is that Jones is under contract for just $4.66 million in 2026, so a team trading for him at that number can afford to do quite a bit of maneuvering with the cap. Breer lists the Vikings, Dolphins, and Cardinals as teams that could potentially look at Jones this offseason. The Vikings scenario makes all the sense in the world considering Jones would be able to send McCarthy to the bench barring drastic offseason improvement from the second-year signal caller. Jones has thrown for 2151 yards with 13 touchdowns and six interceptions while winning 5-of-8 starts with Brock Purdy sidelined this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc47-d90e-a9da-bf4fb2d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (toe) practiced on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc50-d82c-a79a-bfd401110000</link>
      <description>This is the norm for Jackson now, he misses the first session of the week and practices in the second. While both Jackson and John Harbaugh have insisted he’s fine physically, it’s hard to see him looking a step slow and actually believe that. Regardless, Jackson-reliant managers are absolutely using Jackson in Week 13 against the league’s worst defense, Cincinnati. Even if he’s thrown for just one touchdown in the last three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc50-d82c-a79a-bfd401110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys coach Brian Schottenheimer said George Pickens (knee/calf) will practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc60-d82c-a79a-bff473930000</link>
      <description>Numerous beats have mentioned that they didn’t seem to think Pickens was laboring in the locker room after the game on Sunday, as he apparently played through this leg injury in the second half. This will probably be a limited session, but it sounds like Pickens is just getting some extra rest ahead of the Thanksgiving showdown with the Chiefs on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc60-d82c-a79a-bff473930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals OC Drew Petzing said that he’ll “continue to put [Michael Wilson] higher in the progression” even when Marvin Harrison Jr. returns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc6b-d90e-a9da-bf6f69320000</link>
      <description>“When you produce in this league, we’re gonna give you more opportunities to continue to do that,” Petzing added. Wilson could cut into Harrison’s sure-fire role and create a triumvirate of playable pass-catchers in Arizona down the stretch between Trey McBride, Harrison, and Wilson. Don’t necessarily assume you need to drop Wilson once it’s confirmed Harrison is coming back — he could still be a viable WR3/FLEX going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc6b-d90e-a9da-bf6f69320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said the Michael Penix (knee) injury could force the Falcons to “make some different plans” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc74-d6c4-abfb-fe77580e0000</link>
      <description>With how late in the year Penix’s ACL injury happened, there’s not a guarantee that he’ll be ready for the start of the 2026 season. Of course, there’s also not a guarantee that Morris or GM Terry Fontenot survive what has been a calamitous season despite the fact that the Rams own their 2026 first-round pick. Releasing Kirk Cousins could free up $32.5 million in cap space. The Falcons don’t have much in the way of avenues out of Penix given the lack of a first-round pick and a lack of options beyond cutting Cousins to free up cap space, but they could prioritize a veteran backup if the current braintrust stays in place. If Morris and Fontenot are fired, Penix will not be the new regime’s hand-picked quarterback. The dynasty value of Penix is in a dicey situation as he tries to rehab his partial ACL tear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bc74-d6c4-abfb-fe77580e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
