<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:29:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed five times for 20 yards in the Steelers’ Week 13 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d761-d82c-a79a-f7f593350000</link>
      <description>Gainwell also added 25 receiving yards on two catches, including a ridiculous one-handed catch on a poor throw from Aaron Rodgers that Gainwell had to nearly scrape off the turf. Gainwell looked explosive as a receiver, but was unable to get much going as a runner and was also stuffed on a crucial fourth-and-two that helped seal the win for the Bills. If the Steelers are playing from behind in Week 14 against the Ravens, which is possible, Gainwell could be a decent deep-league FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d761-d82c-a79a-f7f593350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers HC Jim Harbaugh said Justin Herbert will have surgery on his left hand on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d762-db57-afda-d772d36e0000</link>
      <description>The injury is a break in Herbert’s non-throwing hand. The Chargers’ QB1 played through the injury in Week 13’s win over the Raiders, but Harbaugh was unsure whether Herbert would miss time after the procedure, saying the team will see how the week goes for his star QB. He did enough to pull out the win on Sunday, throwing for 151-2-1 on 20 passes, but Herbert will face a tougher challenge in Week 14 against the Eagles if active. In the event he can’t go, former No. 3 overall pick Trey Lance would draw the start, which would massively downgrade the fantasy stocks of all Chargers offensive players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d762-db57-afda-d772d36e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 4-of-6 targets for 39 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d73d-db57-afda-d73f1e380000</link>
      <description>McConkey delivers solid results, though he nearly scored a touchdown on the Chargers’ second drive, when Raiders CB Kye Blue Kelly perfectly jumped McConkey’s route in the end zone. Chargers QB Justin Herbert linked up with McConkey for six on the Chargers’ seventh drive, though. The Chargers’ No. 1 wide receiver motioned into the slot on the left side of the field, just before the snap. Herbert evaded pressure by rolling out of the pocket, kept his eyes on McConkey and let the pass rip once McConkey got open. McConkey is a WR2 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d73d-db57-afda-d73f1e380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-5 targets for 32 yards in the Steelers’ Week 13 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d763-d82c-a79a-f7f7c6020000</link>
      <description>The winds were gusting up to 30 mph in this one, but Metcalf never really threatened to make a big play. His longest catch was on a 14-yard slant, and he was also the target of an overthrown pass that led to an interception. On the surface, Metcalf has a good matchup next week against the Ravens, but he has not topped 55 receiving yards in a game since Week 6 against the Browns, and has topped 40 receiving yards only once in the last five games. He’s a TD-dependent FLEX option at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d763-d82c-a79a-f7f7c6020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 2-of-4 targets for 45 yards in the Steelers’ Week 13 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d767-d82c-a79a-f7f763e70000</link>
      <description>The Steelers’ offense couldn’t get much going, but Washington did lead the team in receiving and finish second in targets. Over half of his yardage came on one play where the Bills somehow had small cornerback Tre’Davious White trying to cover and tackle Washington, which was never going to end well. Apart from that, the big tight end wasn’t able to get much going, and we’d prefer not to rely on him in fantasy, but he could be a TE2 in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d767-d82c-a79a-f7f763e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d766-db57-afda-d77622500000</link>
      <description>Allen was seemingly headed toward a big day. Instead, he delivers a classic, scoreless bummer. All five of his targets were earned on the Chargers’ first three drives. He was seemingly getting open at will. Heartbreak struck on the Chargers’ third drive when Allen had a seemingly winnable one-on-one situation, running down the right sideline from the Raiders’ 23-yard line. QB Justin Herbert targeted him just outside the goal line but the two were unable to connect. Allen is a FLEX option against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d766-db57-afda-d77622500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden II caught 1-of-2 targets for 27 yards in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d762-db57-afda-d772f2e70000</link>
      <description>Chargers QB Justin Herbert missed a portion of the team’s second drive after injuring his left ring finger late in the first drive. He returned partway through the second drive. On 1st-and-10, from the Raiders’ 29-yard line, Herbert found Gadsden wide open on a seam route and let it rip. The agile tight end went up, secured the pass and was immediately brought down at the Raiders’ two-yard line. So close. Herbert went back to him on the Chargers’ fourth drive, 10 yards down the field on 2nd-and-16. Gadsden had the pass in his hands, but Raiders LB Devin White laid a hard hit, making Gadsden unable to secure it, resulting in an incompletion. Gadsden is once again a TE1 against the Eagles in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d762-db57-afda-d772f2e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert (hand) said he’s “treating it as if I’m playing on Monday,” after breaking a bone in his hand in Week 13’s win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d77a-db57-afda-d77a4a260000</link>
      <description>Herbert played through a broken bone in his non-throwing hand in Sunday’s win over the Raiders and will undergo a surgical procedure on Monday. He’s clearly taking a more optimistic approach to the possibility of playing in Week 14 than head coach Jim Harbaugh did after the game, but whether or not Herbert suits up will likely come down to the opinions of doctors first and foremost. We’ll get an update on his availability later in the week, but with the Chargers’ first practice not being until Thursday, it could be a few days before we get a good idea of where things stand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d77a-db57-afda-d77a4a260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 3-of-4 targets for 30 yards in the Chargers’ Week 13 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d770-d6c4-abfb-d773e7d80000</link>
      <description>Harris has a ways to go before he can be treated as re-draft-relevant, but his four targets rank third on the team today. Harris’ longest play was a 16-yard reception on the Chargers’ seventh drive, though he ironically benefitted from being ragdolled forward by a Raiders defender, picking up at least two extra yards as a result. He does not need to be in starting lineups in Week 14 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d770-d6c4-abfb-d773e7d80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
