<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB Tyler Badie (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9e2-d94a-a79d-c9efdeae0000</link>
      <description>Badie was banged up in Week 5 against the Eagles but should be OK for Week 6 after being upgraded to a full practice on Thursday. Badie hasn’t seen a carry since Week 2 but has worked in as a pass catcher out of the Denver backfield alongside JK Dobbins and RJ Harvey. Badie has four targets over the past two games. He won’t be fantasy viable unless Dobbins or Harvey miss time this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9e2-d94a-a79d-c9efdeae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f0-db72-a199-fbfbe5c90000</link>
      <description>This is Johnson’s first practice since injuring his ankle in Week 2. Earlier this week, ESPN’s Rich Cimini reported that Johnson will travel with the team to London ahead of their Week 6 game against the Broncos, which suggests the Jets believe he has a chance to suit up. Today’s limited session is another step in the right direction, though his availability on Sunday is not yet guaranteed. The Jets’ 6.5 NFL sacks tie for the sixth-fewest in the league. They need him back badly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9f0-db72-a199-fbfbe5c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Terry McLaurin (quad) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9fd-db72-a199-fbffc4310000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported McLaurin is “not looking good” for Week 6 against the Bears. His continued inability to practice furthers that notion. McLaurin could be seen working off to the side, without a jersey, while the rest of the team practiced in pads. Fantasy managers should expect McLaurin to miss his third straight game this weekend, unless something drastically changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c9fd-db72-a199-fbffc4310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Steelers reportedly inquired about Saints WR Rashid Shaheed’s availability during Pittsburgh’s Week 5 bye.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca02-dd4c-afb9-efc3971b0000</link>
      <description>No word yet on whether the Saints seriously entertained the inquiry. The former undrafted free agent is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill opines that a potential trade “would be a complicated deal” because the acquiring team “would have to be willing to trade for him and pay a new contract.” Shaheed was a small-school prospect who earned five college accolades as a returner and one as a wide receiver. He earned Pro Bowl and first-team All-Pro honors as a returner in 2023. Were the Steelers to acquire him, his FLEX appeal would likely take a hit. The Saints’ voluminous passing offense provides him and Chris Olave with enough opportunities for both players to remain fantasy-relevant. The Steelers’ run-oriented playcalling would likely reduce his weekly target count while reducing DK Metcalf’s reliability as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca02-dd4c-afb9-efc3971b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-db72-a199-fa5b6ca90000</link>
      <description>Jackson was labeled week-to-week after straining his hamstring in Week 4. Nearly two weeks later, he has not yet returned to practice, which makes sense. The Ravens are on bye in Week 7. If he can play in Week 6, he surely will, but at this point, it seems likely that the team holds him out until Week 8. Ideally, the extended absence allows his injured muscle to fully heal, which should set him up for immediate fantasy success upon his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-db72-a199-fa5b6ca90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals QB Kyler Murray (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-def2-abdb-df71698a0000</link>
      <description>The mobile Murray has stalled out through two Week 6 practices. If he can log a limited session on Friday, he will have a chance to suit up, but he is at his best when his footwork is unimpeded. Fantasy managers should make backup plans at this time. Journeyman QB Jacoby Brissett replaced him in the lineup last week, though he is not a recommended starter in single-quarterback leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca11-def2-abdb-df71698a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) was not seen participating in team drills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca2a-d94a-a79d-cb2f9fd50000</link>
      <description>Hubbard was instead observed running routes, shirtless, on a side field. This all but guarantees he will be listed as a non-participant on the official injury report released later in the day. Hubbard is on track to miss his second consecutive game this weekend, clearing the way for another high-volume workload for backup RB Rico Dowdle, who finished as the overall RB1 last week. While another chart-topping performance should not be expected, Dowdle belongs firmly locked into fantasy lineups against the Cowboys in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca2a-d94a-a79d-cb2f9fd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Velus Jones Jr. to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca1f-dd4c-afb9-efdfa0670000</link>
      <description>The Saints released Jones just two days ago. His presence on the practice squad gives them an emergency option for backup running back and kick return duties. He is not fantasy-relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca1f-dd4c-afb9-efdfa0670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) will not practice today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca35-def2-abdb-df7565000000</link>
      <description>Worthy practiced in full on Wednesday. This is likely just a rest day for Worthy, but his Friday participation level is obviously worth following. Worthy has logged WR2 and WR4 finishes since fully tearing his labrum during a shoulder dislocation in Week 1. If active, he will be a WR2 with upside in what should be a high-scoring game against the Lions on Sunday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca35-def2-abdb-df7565000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca3c-d94a-a79d-cb3d91650000</link>
      <description>The Falcons face the Bills on Monday night, so Thursday is the team’s first Week 6 practice. Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Mooney is still day-to-day despite having more than a full week to rehab the muscle strain. The Falcons were on bye in Week 5. Mooney injured his hamstring on September 28th, and initial reports suggested he is not expected to miss any time. He should be considered questionable to play at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ca3c-d94a-a79d-cb3d91650000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
