<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 5-of-6 targets for 46 yards in the Bears’ Week 2 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a5d-da67-a99f-cefd161a0000</link>
      <description>Moore was once again out-targeted and out-produced by second-year pro Rome Odunze. Moore now owns an 8/114/0 line on 11 targets through two games to Odunze’s 13/165/3 on 20 looks. The Bears are undoubtedly going to need Moore’s underneath and manufactured looks as they try to dig out of their 0-2 hole, but this could be a real changing of the guard in the No. 1 spot. Moore is going to need to show something against the Cowboys’ struggling defense in Week 3. For now, he’s a lower-end WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a5d-da67-a99f-cefd161a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow is “believed to have turf toe with torn ligaments” and could miss “several weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a5f-dc44-a9d9-4f7feaaf0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’sIan Rapoportwas able to confirm the turf toe aspect, specifically. Fantasy managers should immediately begin combing the free agent pool to see if there are any decent quarterbacks available who can be added before the three Sunday and Monday games kick off. Burrow is likely due for a multi-game absence. He was seen using crutches in the locker room post-game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a5f-dc44-a9d9-4f7feaaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cole Kmet caught 2-of-2 targets for 29 yards in the Bears’ Week 2 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a66-da67-a99f-cef7140f0000</link>
      <description>Kmet now has three catches for 60 yards through two games compared to just 2/12 for first-round TE Colston Loveland. Kmet obviously isn’t producing his own fantasy value, but he’s also currently making it impossible for Loveland to carve out any of his own. It’s just a real mess in Chicago right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a66-da67-a99f-cef7140f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo caught 2-of-3 targets for 31 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 2 win against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a59-dc44-a9d9-4f7f5efe0000</link>
      <description>Arroyo and fellow TE AJ Barner were far more involved in Week 2 than they were last week against the 49ers, with Barner catching two of his three targets for 26 yards and a score. Barner ran 24 routes to 19 routes for Arroyo. Neither guy will be fantasy viable in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a59-dc44-a9d9-4f7f5efe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 1-of-2 targets for two yards in the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots, adding three carries for 23 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a51-da67-a99f-cef5af600000</link>
      <description>Washington was involved in the Dolphins’ screen and motion game, taking three carries from the backfield and catching one pass. The 24-year-old also took a punt 74 yards to the house in the fourth quarter, though it was quickly countered by an Antonio Gibson kick return touchdown on the ensuing kickoff. Meanwhile, Nick Westbrook-Ikhine caught 2-of-3 targets for 18 yards. Neither Washington or Westbrook-Ikhine is fantasy relevant behind Tyreek Hill and Jaylen Waddle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a51-da67-a99f-cef5af600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley caught 3-of-6 targets for 57 yards in the Titans’ Week 2 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a60-d86f-abdd-4ffd8e0e0000</link>
      <description>Ridley only caught half of his targets for the second week in a row, but a 26-yard grab in the first quarter nearly equaled his receiving total of 27 from the entirety of Week 1. Despite upping his yardage total, Ridley’s role seemingly declined in his second game of the year. Rookie wideout Elic Ayomanor was targeted six times as well and caught Cam Ward’s only touchdown pass of the day. Ridley and Ayomanor tied for a team-high in targets. With Ward still taking his lumps as he adjusts to the speed of the pro game, Ridley’s role as a co-WR1 on the Titans might not be enough to save him from a downgrade to the WR3 ranks for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a60-d86f-abdd-4ffd8e0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught a 29-yard pass in the Lions’ Week 2 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a68-da67-a99f-cefdf7f50000</link>
      <description>For the second week in a row, TeSlaa made a circus, one-handed grab. For the second week in a row, it was his only target. This one came late in the second quarter. Coach Dan Campbell has said he wants to get the third-round rookie more involved on offense, but one target in a 52-point Lions outburst is proof that will be easier said than done behind Amon-Ra St. Brown, Jameson Williams and Sam LaPorta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a68-da67-a99f-cefdf7f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London is active for Week 2 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a6a-d294-a19b-eefa1b6e0000</link>
      <description>London was injured late in the team’s Week 1 loss to the Buccaneers, failing to finish the game after a missed connection in the end zone. He was limited in practice throughout the week and will play against the Vikings. Fellow wide receiver Darnell Mooney is also active after missing the team’s first game. Inactive for the Falcons are K Younghoe Koo, WR Jamal Agnew, CB Clark Phillips III, OL Jack Nelson, WR Casey Washington, and DL Sam Roberts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a6a-d294-a19b-eefa1b6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Lions’ Week 2 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a6f-da67-a99f-ceff9b720000</link>
      <description>3/26 on four looks probably isn’t what fantasy managers had in mind when they saw 52 Lions points. LaPorta simply couldn’t compete with Amon-Ra St. Brown’s all-around dominance and Jameson Williams’ big-play prowess. LaPorta is continuing to default into higher-end TE1 status, but that says more about the lack of depth in that range than it does anything else. The Lions are visiting Baltimore for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a6f-da67-a99f-ceff9b720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared S Harrison Smith, CB Jeff Okudah, LB Andrew Van Ginkel, LB Austin Keys, G Joe Huber, and LT Christian Darrisaw inactive for Week 2 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a71-dc44-a9d9-4f7735bb0000</link>
      <description>Smith was listed on the injury report with an illness, ultimately ruled inactive with a personal designation. Darrisaw will have to wait another week before he makes his season debut. The Vikings will look to continue their late successes against the Bears from their opener into their second game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a71-dc44-a9d9-4f7735bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
