<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor reports the Chiefs are “optimistic” that Xavier Worthy (shoulder) “will be able to play a limited role for the offense while wearing a small harness” in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-779e-d1b3-a5dd-77ff2d260000</link>
      <description>Does that sound like a role that elevates beyond decoy? Not to us. Even if Worthy is active for Week 4 after missing the last two weeks following a Week 1 dislocated shoulder, this indicates he could be eased back into the offense slowly. This line comes from a piece about Tyquan Thornton, who deservedly is getting major waiver wire love this week. We might rather start Thornton than Worthy this week even if both of them are active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-779e-d1b3-a5dd-77ff2d260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants signed K Younghoe Koo to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77bf-dfde-a1bd-7fbff36f0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like a vote of confidence for the health of incumbent Graham Gano (groin), who kicked through injury on Sunday night. Koo could be the Giants kicker this week against the Chargers in what some are calling “not exactly a smash spot for a kicker” in Jaxson Dart’s season debut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77bf-dfde-a1bd-7fbff36f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released S C.J. Gardner-Johnson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77c2-d6a5-adff-f7c717d60000</link>
      <description>What was your favorite moment of the Gardner-Johnson era in Houston? He did play 96 percent of the snaps for the Texans in three weeks, so it’s a loss. NBC’s Aaron Wilson reports there was “friction behind the scenes” behind the release, with Gardner-Johnson “complaining about his role, wanting to blitz more, per league sources, and even communicating that he wanted to be traded.” M.J. Stewart will take over at safety for the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77c2-d6a5-adff-f7c717d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed LB Quincy Williams (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77d0-d1b3-a5dd-77f12b180000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least four weeks and NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said he’d be “down for a while.” The Jets signed Mark Robinson off New England’s practice squad to take his roster spot. Marcelino McCrary-Ball replaced Williams in the lineup if you’re looking for an IDP waiver pickup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-77d0-d1b3-a5dd-77f12b180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired CB Jarvis Brownlee and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Titans for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7811-d6a5-adff-fed5a4960000</link>
      <description>Brownlee, who had started 16 games while being active for 18 games for the Titans in his rookie season and this year, was a surprise inactive in Week 3 and was spotted in a walking boot pre-game. It appears the Titans tired of how grabby he was being on the outside. The Jets will try to channel his outside coverage ability and take a cheap chance on a good tackler with mediocre PFF coverage grades (61 this year, 55.9 in 2024) on the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7811-d6a5-adff-fed5a4960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Shilo Sanders visited the 49ers on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7872-d93f-ad9d-7af7a3c00000</link>
      <description>Deion’s other son played for the Buccaneers in training camp and was waived well ahead of final cuts. This is the first time we’ve seen him on the league’s transaction wire since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7872-d93f-ad9d-7af7a3c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) was an estimated full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78e8-d6a5-adff-feeddbed0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks held a walk-through practice, but Charbonnet was estimated as a full participant for the second straight day. He missed the Seahawks’ Week 3 win over the Saints, but is now back on track to play Thursday against the Cardinals. Kenneth Walker scored twice but averaged an inefficient 2.4 yards per carry on Sunday without Charbonnet. Look for Charbonnet to be involved again in Week 4. The other backfield injury concern is fullback Robbie Ouzts (ankle), who was an estimated non-participant on back-to-back days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78e8-d6a5-adff-feeddbed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE Elijah Arroyo (groin) was an estimated limited participant in Tuesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78f1-dfde-a1bd-7efd34910000</link>
      <description>Arroyo was an estimated limited participant in both Monday and Tuesday’s practice reports. The rookie has four receptions so far this season, splitting tight end looks with AJ Barner. There is no indication this is an injury that will cost Arroyo time, but Barner will get a slight boost in opportunity should Arroyo miss Thursday’s Week 4 game against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78f1-dfde-a1bd-7efd34910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) was an estimated limited participant in Tuesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78ff-d1b3-a5dd-79ffa9500000</link>
      <description>Rookie safety Nick Emmanwori (ankle) and DB Julian Love (hamstring) were also listed as limited. None of the trio practiced last week, so it is notable that they were estimated limited participants both Monday and Tuesday. The boost to the secondary was not needed in a blowout victory against the Saints in Week 3, but Witherspoon, Emmanwori, and Love returning for Week 4 against the Cardinals will help the defense in a rivalry game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-78ff-d1b3-a5dd-79ffa9500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) did not participate in Tuesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-790a-d1b3-a5dd-797b58570000</link>
      <description>Johnson did not practice last week and missed the Cardinals’ Week 3 game against the 49ers. The rookie got off to a good start the first two weeks of the season, but a groin injury is now causing him to miss time. He was estimated as a non-participant for both Monday and Tuesday, so it is unlikely we see him on Thursday against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-790a-d1b3-a5dd-797b58570000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
