<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) will not play in Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ea-dfde-a1bd-5eef0f650000</link>
      <description>Waller was limited in all three practices this week, suggesting he is making progress with the hip issue. He has yet to play in 2025 after coming out of retirement during the summer to backfill Jonnu Smith’s role. Even if he does return next week, fantasy managers can ignore the age-33 tight end for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ea-dfde-a1bd-5eef0f650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ec-d93f-ad9d-5aef1aee0000</link>
      <description>Wright missed the first two games of the year with a knee issue he suffered just before the start of the season. He was limited in the first two practices of the week but managed a full session today. Ollie Gordon failed to carve out a meaningful role in Miami while Wright was sidelined. Neither back has much fantasy value going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ec-d93f-ad9d-5aef1aee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert (knee) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5904-d1b3-a5dd-5975359b0000</link>
      <description>Goedert didn’t practice at all last week before being ruled out on Friday. A return to practice for the first session of the week puts him on track to face the Rams, though fantasy managers will still want to keep tabs on Philly’s injury report throughout the week. Goerdert led the Eagles with seven catches and seven targets in Week 1. A similar role would have him back in the TE1 ranks for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5904-d1b3-a5dd-5975359b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell expressed “confidence” in Jordan Mason as a “potential bellcow.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58da-d6a5-adff-fedffcd30000</link>
      <description>We expect Mason to handle a significant rushing workload with Aaron Jones (hamstring) sidelined, and he could play on passing downs as well. O’Connell sang praises for Mason’s multi-faceted skillset, specifically mentioning his pass-protection chops and ability to catch the football. Mason’s in-game passing game performances have left a lot to be desired, but if he’s earning O’Connell’s trust in practice, that’s a plus. At worst, he’s a high-end RB2 against the Bengals. Mason is backed up by 2023 undrafted free agent RB Zavier Scott and the recently signed RB Cam Akers. O’Connell complimented Scott’s preseason play in the press conference but Akers is familiar with the system and could rotate in ahead of him. Neither player offers standalone value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58da-d6a5-adff-fedffcd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed LB Khalil Mack on injured reserve with an elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58f9-d1b3-a5dd-59f9569f0000</link>
      <description>Per Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh, the injury is not considered season-ending, so Mack’s will miss at least the next four games before being eligible to return. Mack suffered a dislocated elbow in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders. The veteran pass rusher has totaled one tackle, four quarterback pressures and one sack this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58f9-d1b3-a5dd-59f9569f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5915-dfde-a1bd-5f9d14020000</link>
      <description>Tracy was limited to five carries in Week 2, ceding 11 totes to rookie runner Cam Skattebo. The calf issue was likely part of the reason the Giants eased up on his workload, but Tracy has been dreadfully inefficient through two weeks. He also publicly criticized the team’s play-calling near the goal line after Week 1. Even a minor calf injury should ensure the continued decline of his role heading into Week 3. Tracy is nothing more than a low-ceiling RB4 at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5915-dfde-a1bd-5f9d14020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5931-dfde-a1bd-5fbde82f0000</link>
      <description>The Giants are doing their due diligence on the injury report by listing Skattebo. A full practice suggests the injury is a non-factor for Week 3. Tyrone Tracy, on the other hand, was limited with a calf injury. Though he should also be good to go for Sunday’s game, the issue will give Brian Daboll another reason to keep his touch total low. Skattebo out-carried Tracy 11-5 last week and ran for 45 yards plus a touchdown in the process. The rookie has fully taken over the backfield, putting him in line for an RB3 ranking heading into Sunday’s slate of games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5931-dfde-a1bd-5fbde82f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5913-d93f-ad9d-5bd7e86e0000</link>
      <description>This relevant for the handful of fantasy managers who have not yet dropped Legette. The second-year wide receiver has caught 4-of-12 targets for eight yards through two games this season. Regardless of his Week 3 availability, Legette does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5913-d93f-ad9d-5bd7e86e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (calf/groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5936-d6a5-adff-fff70ca00000</link>
      <description>Slayton played through the groin injury last week, but the calf issue is a new addition to the injury report. He saw just three targets despite Russell Wilson attempting 41 passes in the Giants’ overtime loss to the Cowboys. With two catches through two games this year, Slayton is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5936-d6a5-adff-fff70ca00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson (foot) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5940-d6a5-adff-ffc540d40000</link>
      <description>Robinson played through an ankle issue last week and will likely push through his foot issue this time around. The fourth-year wideout erupted in Week 2 with 10 catches for 142 yards and a score versus the Cowboys. It was just the second 100-yard outing of his career. Robinson is pushing beyond his usual low-aDOT role this year, giving him a far higher fantasy ceiling on a weekly basis. As long as this foot injury doesn’t get worse, he has worked himself into the WR3 ranks for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5940-d6a5-adff-ffc540d40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
