<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f01e-d005-a9bf-f83e41730000</link>
      <description>This game determines which team takes over first place in the AFC North. Both squads are 6-6. Rodgers practiced fully on Thursday and Friday, which is positive. He does not need to be in single-quarterback lineups, though, profiling as a low-end superflex QB2 at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f01e-d005-a9bf-f83e41730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f019-d005-a9bf-f83d01cd0000</link>
      <description>Steelers LB Patrick Queen (glute) will also play. Watt took the day off on Wednesday before practicing fully thereafter. Queen did the same to begin the week but only managed limited sessions on Thursday and Friday. Watt has generated 39 quarterback pressures and eight sacks, while Queen has racked up 58 tackles. Having both players active is helpful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f019-d005-a9bf-f83d01cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Chimere Dike (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f026-d77b-adfa-faa72ba80000</link>
      <description>Dike has been quite the volatile scorer as of late. In his late six games, he has finished as the half-PPR WR15-18 three times. In his other three showings, he finished as the WR75 or worse. Facing the Browns’ elite defense, he makes for a very risky FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f026-d77b-adfa-faa72ba80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f014-d77b-adfa-fa97e4c80000</link>
      <description>He has one game over four targets or 60 yards this year — Week 3’s loss against the Ravens — and Baltimore’s passing offense can’t support many fantasy mouths with how Lamar Jackson is currently playing. Even healthy and with a good matchup, you’d have to really contort things to see a reason to play Bateman in fantasy this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f014-d77b-adfa-fa97e4c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins OL Aaron Brewer (ankle/neck/knee) is questionable for Miami’s Week 14 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f040-d8cf-affb-fc6aef270000</link>
      <description>We’ve crossed the Terron Armstead threshold with three injury designations, good work by Brewer. The knee is the newest injury he’s dealing with, but Brewer is expected to play after being limited in a few sessions this week. The center has taken a major step forward this year with a 80.2 PFF grade, the highest in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f040-d8cf-affb-fc6aef270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RT Jawaan Taylor (triceps/knee) is doubtful to play in Week 14 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f040-d005-a9bf-f87405c80000</link>
      <description>Chiefs RG Trey Smith (ankle) is also doubtful, and Chiefs LT Josh Simmons (wrist) was recently placed on injured reserve. The Texans’ pass rush generates pressure at the NFL’s second-highest rate (42.4 percent). This is a tough break for QB Patrick Mahomes. Expect him to funnel targets to WR Rashee Rice and TE Travis Kelce on short routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f040-d005-a9bf-f87405c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) is not on Houston’s final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f044-d8cf-affb-fc6e5e5e0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday for the first time this week. The rookie back can be started as a low-end RB2 — he has a good role, but the Chiefs are a good enough run defense that they create a pass funnel, and the Texans have struggled to give him any touchdown equity with a rough red zone offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f044-d8cf-affb-fc6e5e5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Anderson (chest/shoulder) is not on Houston’s final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f045-d77b-adfa-fac7b5620000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday and should be fine. In IDP leagues, it would be a disappointment if Anderson did not provide at least a half-sack or so against a Chiefs offensive line that looks likely to be down several starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f045-d77b-adfa-fac7b5620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Kamari Lassiter (foot) is questionable for Houston’s Week 14 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f046-da9b-a9bf-fe4fe3680000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session on Friday after two DNPs, and the Texans were reportedly (per Aaron Wilson) optimistic that he’ll play on Sunday. It would be good news for Rashee Rice and Xavier Worthy if Lassiter sat, as he’s complied a 73.9 PFF coverage grade in 721 snaps this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f046-da9b-a9bf-fe4fe3680000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
