<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dion Dawkins (concussion) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3f-da9b-a9bf-ff3f061e0000</link>
      <description>He did, however, shed his non-contact jersey, so he may be closer to clearing concussion protocol. Dawkins and Spencer Brown (shoulder, limited for the second day in a row) are both trending towards playing on Sunday, or at least hitting the questionable line on Friday. It would do wonders for Buffalo’s offense to have their bookend tackles back on Sunday against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3f-da9b-a9bf-ff3f061e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (hamstring/knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb40-da9b-a9bf-ff4ded0f0000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign for Kincaid that he was able to string a pair of practices in a row together. And play he will for fantasy managers if he’s healthy, because the Bengals defense was designed in a lab to increase tight end production for their opponents. Kincaid seems likely to at least hit the questionable line on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb40-da9b-a9bf-ff4ded0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3c-dce4-a1da-fb3e67be0000</link>
      <description>Golden is seemingly on track to play, although he was limited throughout Week 13 before being declared inactive pre-game. If he can return, his presence is more helpful to QB Jordan Love than it is to fantasy managers. The rookie wide receiver has not finished as a WR4 or better since Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3c-dce4-a1da-fb3e67be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Tee Higgins (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb43-d005-a9bf-fb77941d0000</link>
      <description>He’s not completely out of concussion protocol yet, but this is a great sign about his chances of playing on Sunday against the Bills. It’s an upgrade from a limited session on Wednesday. Higgins would be an easy WR2 despite how the Bills invite the running game with Joe Burrow back feeding Higgins the rock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb43-d005-a9bf-fb77941d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB MarShawn Lloyd (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3e-d77b-adfa-ebbf77db0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd was placed on injured reserve due to a hamstring injury. He is, almost unbelievably, now rehabbing a calf injury. Lloyd is a very capable player, but he is tough to trust as a bench stash at this point. Fellow backup RB Emanuel Wilson has proven himself as a reliable backup, and he would likely be in line to start if Josh Jacobs were to miss time. Stashing Lloyd is a bet on talent, not health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3e-d77b-adfa-ebbf77db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb44-dce4-a1da-fb56084e0000</link>
      <description>We were hoping to see Reed upgrade to full participation. He still has a chance to play, but one imagines the Packers will ask him to practice fully before allowing him to retake the field after a prolonged absence. It all comes down to Friday’s official injury report. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb44-dce4-a1da-fb56084e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-dce4-a1da-fb5e7ade0000</link>
      <description>The Packers continue to limit Wicks’ practice reps after a busy Week 13 showing against the Lions, in which Wicks caught 6-of-7 targets for 94 yards and two touchdowns. He seemingly injured his left ankle on one of his touchdown grabs, but it did not slow him down. We expect Wicks to play in Week 14 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-dce4-a1da-fb5e7ade0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb51-d77b-adfa-ebd303a40000</link>
      <description>Bateman was already off the FLEX radar, given his recent play and the Ravens’ struggles. His downgrading only furthers that notion. Bateman still has a chance to play, but he is clearly still rehabbing his high-ankle sprain. Having him on the field would at least be helpful for QB Lamar Jackson (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb51-d77b-adfa-ebd303a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb56-d005-a9bf-fb7672150000</link>
      <description>Sampson appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 14 against the Titans, elevating RB Jerome Ford to the No. 2 role. Ford does not need to be in fantasy lineups, having lost his job to Sampson earlier this year with ineffectual play. Expect Quinshon Judkins to handle a sizable workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb56-d005-a9bf-fb7672150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb5c-d77b-adfa-ebdfbcaf0000</link>
      <description>Njoku continues to play through his knee injury as rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr.'s fantasy-unfriendly backup. Njoku does not need to be rostered in re-draft formats, though he technically could be considered one of the rare tight end stash options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb5c-d77b-adfa-ebdfbcaf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
