<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Andrei Iosivas caught 3-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</link>
      <description>Iosivas’ missed connection was a bad drop. Iosivas posted his second best overall statline of the season as Joe Flacco dropped back 49 times and attempted 47 passes, but he was out-targeted 33-4 by Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins’ combined efforts. It would take injury to one of the elite wideouts ahead of him for Iosivas to become fantasy relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 3-of-6 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</link>
      <description>Both the six-target effort and score were Smith’s first since Week 1, while he was the No. 2 producing tight end behind Pat Freiermuth, who turned his six looks into 5/111/2. Improbably, Darnell Washington also found the end zone. That’s the long way of saying no Steelers tight end is producing consistently enough to merit a real TE2 look ahead of Week 8 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 3-of-5 targets for two yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career-high 62-yard effort, Washington posted one of the more bizarre box scores you will ever see. He does now have 10 targets over the past two weeks after that number was four across his first four appearances. Perhaps his usage really is changing, but there has been little indication Washington is about to make a legitimate push for TE2 value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f271-d651-a9df-fb75fc670000</link>
      <description>Meyers has not practiced this week ahead of the Raiders’ Week 7 game against the Chiefs. Unless you gets in at least a limited practice on Friday, he’ll likely be sidelined against KC. The Raiders, according to ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler, might be looking to trade Meyers before the league’s trade deadline after Meyers formally requested a trade just before the regular season. Meyers’ absence could be a boost for Tre Tucker and Michael Mayer in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f271-d651-a9df-fb75fc670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports Garrett Wilson (knee) will be a DNP on Friday and miss Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</link>
      <description>This is according to a source who spoke with Zenitz, but we assume the team’s official injury report, which will come later Friday, will have Wilson ruled out. The star receiver was expected to miss multiple weeks with the knee injury he picked up in Week 6, so the idea of him missing Week 7 doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Jets will hope the duo of Josh Reynolds and Allen Lazard can step up in Wilson’s absence as they look to pick up their first win of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said there is “real uncertainty” about Terry McLaurin (quad) playing in Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</link>
      <description>Pelissero also said the same of Deebo Samuel (heel). It sounds a bit redundant given that Pelissero said on Thursday night there was “real concern” about both receivers’ Week 7 availability, but the fact the tone hasn’t changed over the last 12-plus hours suggests both receivers are trending in the wrong direction for a pivotal NFC East matchup. The Commanders will take the practice field in a few hours, so we should know more about both receivers’ availability soon. That said, a DNP for either player likely means them being ruled out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Garrett Wilson (knee) will be doubtful for Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2b6-df81-ab9b-fef747fa0000</link>
      <description>It’s a slight contradiction from an earlier report that said Garrett Wilson will miss Week 7’s game against the Panthers, but players listed as doubtful are often near locks to be ruled out come game day — if not sooner. Fantasy managers will still want to watch for any surprise announcements regarding Wilson, but it’s safe to assume he will miss Sunday’s game against the Panthers. Fantasy managers should plan accordingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2b6-df81-ab9b-fef747fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua (ankle) will not play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c2-d651-a9df-fbd7a8a80000</link>
      <description>With Nacua officially ruled out, Tutu Atwell and Jordan Whittington will be the favorites to handle receiving duties opposite Davante Adams. The Rams have a Week 8 bye before returning in Week 9 to face the Saints. Hopefully two weeks of rest will be enough for Nacua to return in a timely manner for the Rams and his fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c2-d651-a9df-fbd7a8a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) will not play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c7-df81-ab9b-fec7c6130000</link>
      <description>Sunday will mark the third-straight missed game for Havenstein, who will hopefully have a chance to return after the Rams’ Week 8 bye. Backup tackle Warren McClendon has started the last two games for the Rams in Havenstein’s absence and will again draw the start over seas against the Jaguars in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2c7-df81-ab9b-fec7c6130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutu Atwell (hamstring) will play in Week 7 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2cb-d651-a9df-fbdff8340000</link>
      <description>Atwell is dealing with a hamstring injury, but was upgraded to a full participant for Thursday’s practice. The mid-week upgrade was a good sign that he was trending in the right direction, and could come at a good time for the Rams and fantasy managers who will be without Puka Nacua (ankle) this week. Since 2023, Atwell has averaged seven targets per game in games Nacua missed, which could signal a decent floor for his fantasy outlook. While the potential for a big week is there, we’ll conservatively project Atwell as a WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2cb-d651-a9df-fbdff8340000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
