<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:04:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired Vikings assistant wide receivers coach Tony Sorrentino as their wide receivers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fcb-d89c-a1be-efdfe1840000</link>
      <description>Sorrentino spent the past four seasons with the Vikings, spending four seasons as the assistant wide receivers coach to a group consisting of Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison. New Cardinals head coach Mike LaFleur is building out his offensive staff and now adds Sorrentino to coach a wide receivers group hoping to get more out of Marvin Harrison Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fcb-d89c-a1be-efdfe1840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs hired former NFL RB DeMarco Murray as their running backs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fd2-d629-a1bc-ffdfadb90000</link>
      <description>Murray is known for his prolific seven-year NFL career, lasting from 2011-2017. He won NFL Offensive Player of the Year in 2014 with the Cowboys, also playing for the Eagles and Titans throughout his career. Murray has been a running backs coach at the college level, first for Arizona in 2019, and next for Oklahoma since 2020. The Chiefs will give him his first shot at coaching in the NFL. Murray will be the team’s new running backs coach under offensive coordinator Eric Bieniemy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4fd2-d629-a1bc-ffdfadb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Boykin retired from the NFL after seven seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ee3-d629-a1bc-feffcc620000</link>
      <description>The former Notre Dame wideout entered the NFL as a third-round pick in 2019. He spent three years in Baltimore before joining the Steelers. He played primarily special teams in Pittsburgh. Boykin has bounced around various practice squads over the past two years. His career comes to a close with 38 catches for 498 yards and seven scores.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4ee3-d629-a1bc-feffcc620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Texans defensive pass game coordinator Cory Undlin for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-52ad-d042-afbc-7fffb2e20000</link>
      <description>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot notes that the Browns also interviewed Falcons defensive pass game coordinator Mike Rutenberg for the job. The Browns were initially expected to keep DC Jim Schwartz in the fold. After being passed over for their head coaching opening, Schwartz chose to resign from his position, meaning he will take the year off from coaching. Though the Browns are far from a functional franchise, the opportunity to coach Myles Garrett is one most young defensive coaches will pounce on. Undlin has been in the NFL for over two decades. He has one year of defensive coordinator experience and even coached in Cleveland for a few seasons early in his NFL days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-52ad-d042-afbc-7fffb2e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars head coach Liam Coen said Travis Hunter (knee) “looks great right now.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-532d-d629-a1bc-f33dcda40000</link>
      <description>Coen adds that Hunter was “bouncing around” the weight room the other day, celebrating the young player’s mental resilience as he recovers from a torn LCL. Coen also echoed general manager James Gladstone’s recent messaging regarding Hunter’s 2026 usage, indicating that the team’s positional needs will, at least partially, influence their decision-making regarding Hunter’s deployment. The coaching staff will remain “fluid” in assessing his offensive and defensive practice schedule this offseason. Whether Hunter takes on a fantasy-relevant role next season is currently unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-532d-d629-a1bc-f33dcda40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders are interviewing Seahawks WR coach Frisman Jackson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-535c-d355-a5bd-df5c4cb60000</link>
      <description>It sounds like the interview is happening today, though NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero did not specify when he broke the news. Jackson has coached wide receivers with six college teams and four NFL teams since entering the coaching ranks in 2008 after a short playing career with the Browns (2002-2006). He spent one season on the Jets’ practice squad. Jackson has served in his current role with the Seahawks since 2024, signing on in Seattle one year before former Seahawks OC and new Raiders head coach Klint Kubiak arrived. He evidently made a good impression if Kubiak is already considering him for the Raiders’ offensive coordinator vacancy. Kubiak publicly confirmed that he accepted his new role on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-535c-d355-a5bd-df5c4cb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Mike McCoy as their new assistant head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-536a-d629-a1bc-f37fdac30000</link>
      <description>This hiring makes sense for all involved. McCoy, 53, concluded his 2013-2016 run as the Chargers’ head coach with a 27-37 record. He then served as the Broncos’ (2017) and Cardinals’ (2018) offensive coordinators in one-off campaigns before spending three seasons as the Jaguars’ quarterbacks coach. The Titans hired him as a senior offensive assistant last year and promoted him to interim head coach in-season. The Raiders’ first-time head coach, Klint Kubiak, will call plays offensively while learning how to handle his other, newfound responsibilities. McCoy can help teach Kubiak team management basics, among other things.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-536a-d629-a1bc-f37fdac30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that there is still “a lot to repair” between the Raiders and EDGE Maxx Crosby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5396-d89c-a1be-ffdf55070000</link>
      <description>Raiders head coach Klint Kubiak recently said he wants Crosby “to be a part of our success going forward,” though Pelissero believes that the team is still determining whether it makes sense to keep Crosby or trade him. From Crosby’s side of things, he remains undecided as to whether he will ask to be traded. Crosby, 28, has regularly played through injuries in lost seasons with the Raiders since entering the NFL in 2019. The team’s decision to shut him down with two games to go in 2025 remains a sore spot for him. For now, the veteran pass rusher will continue dutifully rehabbing at the Raiders’ team facility after undergoing a meniscus repair in early January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5396-d89c-a1be-ffdf55070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers hired Robert Kugler as their new tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5364-d042-afbc-7ff678f20000</link>
      <description>Kugler spent the last two seasons serving as an assistant offensive line coach with the Patriots. He held the same role with the Panthers in the two prior seasons. The Pat McAfee Show’s Steelers correspondent, Mark Kaboly, notes that Krugler is a former Steelers training camp “ball boy” and son of former Steelers OL coach Sean Kugler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5364-d042-afbc-7ff678f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers hired Ken Zampese as their new senior offensive assistant and pass game specialist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers also hired T.J. Yates as pass game coordinator, Andrew Mitchell as assistant offensive line coach and Todd Bowles Jr. as a defensive assistant. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport previously reported both Zampese and Yates’s expected hirings. Bowles joins his father’s coaching staff after playing most recently at Long Island University in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-53ce-d042-afbc-7fde33ae0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
