<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 22:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed EDGE Trevis Gipson off the 49ers’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</link>
      <description>Gipson had actually been one of San Francisco’s main outside players last week while they dealt with injuries, but figures to play a backup role in Carolina. It’s another blow for a 49ers defensive line group that struggled to rush the passer against the Texans last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Isiah Pacheco (knee) is “week-to-week” with an MCL sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</link>
      <description>Kareem Hunt and Brashad Smith could find themselves in bigger roles in Week 9 against the Bills, but with the Chiefs holding a Week 10 bye, this feels like something that may only cost Pacheco a week of action. We’d be extremely surprised if Pacheco made a real attempt to play on a short week after suffering the injury with the bye as extra incentive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Michael Carter to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2be7-d245-adfb-bfff9bce0000</link>
      <description>He’s bumped D’Ernest Johnson (released from squad) from the Cardinals Backs Who Will Annoy You wiki listing. Carter was released yesterday, but it appears that was just roster manipulation. He probably isn’t set for a major role even if elevated, but check back on Monday evening when it leaks that the plan is actually to use Michael Wilson as the starting running back instead of Carter or Bam Knight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2be7-d245-adfb-bfff9bce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes “at least one” of the Saints wide receivers will be dealt, and added that “if I had to bet, I’d say Rashid Shaheed is the guy who interests most teams.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c01-deb1-a39b-2d0f4b0c0000</link>
      <description>Schefter listed the Bills, Steelers, and Broncos as main suitors looking for a wideout, and added that the Saints would be open to this if “the compensation was fair and right.” We’d bet the remaining 10 weeks of Shaheed’s contract could fetch at least a swap up to a fourth-rounder, maybe more. Schefter noted that he thinks there will be a flurry of moves at the actual deadline, after Week 9’s games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c01-deb1-a39b-2d0f4b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Werder reports the Cowboys and George Pickens have not engaged in contract extension talks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</link>
      <description>Well, yeah, that’s how the Cowboys do things. We have read a few columns out of Dallas arguing for a Pickens trade, but there seems to be no legitimate smoke on that. We’re anticipating a Pickens franchise tag or tag-and-trade in the offseason. Certainly nothing about the fit has been bad thus far with Pickens on pace for a little under 1,300 yards and 13 touchdowns through eight games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) said “I’m ready to go now” when asked about playing in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</link>
      <description>Things were trending the right way before this, but Jackson actually meeting the media all but confirms he’ll be back for Thursday night’s game against the Dolphins. He raises all boats on the Baltimore offense and is an easy QB1, even against a Dolphins defense coming off a surprising Week 8 win over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (hamstring) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</link>
      <description>It looks like Marcus Mariota’s latest stint as a stopgap superflex quarterback is done. The reporting on Daniels returning for Week 9 has been encouraging so far. We expect to do plenty of Daniels blurbs leading up to Seahawks-Commanders on Sunday night, and it wouldn’t be surprising if Daniels is limited in practice at times this week. But the Commanders need this game badly to avoid falling in a 3-6 hole and it would be surprising if it weren’t all hands on deck to take it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released K Matthew Wright.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c7f-dab4-a3fb-bf7fa3680000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign for Matt Gay’s availability for Week 9. Wright did not attempt a field goal against the Chiefs on Monday night as the Commanders scored seven points and went for two fourth downs with Marcus Mariota under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c7f-dab4-a3fb-bf7fa3680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent TE Marcedes Lewis visited with the Broncos on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cad-d245-adfb-bdff23d80000</link>
      <description>Denver is reportedly bracing to be without No. 2 tight end Nate Adkins for a bit, though nothing has officially been said on his status. They attempted to claim a pair of tight ends on waivers Monday and lost out on them due to priority. Lewis has been looking for One Last Job since the offseason started and could be an interesting fit in Denver as a blocker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cad-d245-adfb-bdff23d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Diontae Johnson visited the Giants on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</link>
      <description>Desperation will drive one to that. Darius Slayton was active again in Week 8 and Wan’Dale Robinson has been performing up to par, but sans Malik Nabers the Giants have had trouble finding another wideout they can count on. Johnson makes some sense given that idea — the baggage is there, but he can certainly earn some targets in a way that Jalin Hyatt has not yet proven he can.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
