<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ec-dc7a-af9b-dfff8abd0000</link>
      <description>Darn. Per Shanahan, Pearsall aggravated the PCL sprain in his knee during the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears. He was unable to play in Week 18 against the Seahawks, though “he did participate in the 49ers’ 3 light practice sessions last week.” Hopefully, Pearsall resumes practicing tomorrow. Pearsall was recently listed with an ankle injury as well. The 49ers have not yet released the official injury report, so we do not know whether that is also an issue this week. 49ers beat reports on the matter vary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ec-dc7a-af9b-dfff8abd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said LT Trent Williams (hamstring) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99f6-d968-a19b-d9f7fd210000</link>
      <description>Williams still has a chance to play this week, but we were hoping to see him resume practicing today. Williams is dealing with his first recorded hamstring injury, suffered as he clocked 17.6 miles per hour on his team’s first play from scrimmage in Week 17. The 49ers face the Eagles this weekend. Getting Williams back would be a great development for QB Brock Purdy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99f6-d968-a19b-d9f7fd210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (ankle) will be limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</link>
      <description>While we would prefer to see Kittle begin the week with a full practice, we cannot complain about this outcome. Kittle made it through Week 18 without suffering any reported setbacks. His early-week participation puts him on track to play in the 49ers’ Wild Card Weekend game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99e6-d968-a19b-d9f75efd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks designated TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</link>
      <description>Arroyo missed the last four games after suffering a knee injury. The 22-year-old notably fell in the 2025 NFL Draft due to concerns over knee-related issues, but Arroyo is not yet being relied upon as a featured pass catcher. The Seahawks should be able to bring him along slowly, given starting TE AJ Barner’s presence and their first-round playoff bye. Thus far, Arroyo has caught 15-of-24 targets for 179 yards and one touchdown. The Seahawks have 21 days to evaluate him in practice before officially activating him from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99da-d56e-afff-fffacf990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles designated OLB Azeez Ojulari (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles have 21 days to observe Ojulari in practice before making a decision on whether they will officially activate him from injured reserve. They face the 49ers on Sunday, though. Ojulari would likely operate as an infrequently used situational pass rusher if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99fd-d56e-afff-fffdeffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a06-d56e-afff-feee8eb30000</link>
      <description>The shifty pass catcher and change-of-pace player has been a valuable contributor this season. He still has a few days to get back on track for Sunday, but if Johnson were to sit out the Bills’ Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars, it would likely add passing down work to RB James Cook’s workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a06-d56e-afff-feee8eb30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh said that Hampton is “working through it” and “doing everything he can” to get the ankle better. Hampton neither practiced nor played last week, as the Chargers shut down multiple key starters, giving off the impression that Hampton’s absence was more of a precautionary move than anything else. Harbaugh’s comments, coupled with Hampton’s absence, suggest he is still working his way back from the ankle fracture he suffered in Week 5. Hampton’s per-game touch counts increased each week after the talented rookie resumed playing in Week 14, culminating in a 22-touch outing in Week 17. It was his second-largest workload of the year. We still think Hampton has strong odds of suiting up for the Chargers’ Wild Card Round game against the Patriots, though his practice participation should be followed closely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said he will remain the team’s head coach for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</link>
      <description>Per the Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Bowles “met with the Glazer family, which owns the team, Tuesday.” He met with his coaching staff on Wednesday and informed the Tampa Bay Times that “there will be some changes to his coaching staff.” The Glazer family reportedly took the offensive line’s myriad injuries into account before they made their decision. While no information was shared about the potential coaching staff changes, Stroud did note that “the offense did not produce under first-year coordinator Josh Grizzard.” Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
