<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Buccaneers believe Jalen McMillan (neck) “avoided anything major” after exiting Saturday’s game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd4c-d90d-a5bd-bf5f2cb00000</link>
      <description>McMillan suffered what appeared to be a nasty injury in Saturday’s outing against the Steelers, but was reportedly “in good spirits over the weekend and sore” the following day. The second-year receiver is battling for playing time behind vets Mike Evans and Chris Godwin, and is facing additional competition from rookie Emeka Egbuka, who hauled in an impressive five-yard score over the weekend. McMillan isn’t expected to have any fantasy value out of the gate, but could profile as a WR3/WR4 for fantasy should anybody miss time with injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd4c-d90d-a5bd-bf5f2cb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed WR Isaiah Bond to a three-year, $3.018 million contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd53-d45c-a7fc-bf5bf26b0000</link>
      <description>Bond’s contract is fully guaranteed, per Browns beat writer Mary Kay Cabot. The former Texas Longhorn went undrafted earlier this year after being accused of sexual assault in April, but now the explosive receiver will join the Browns’ receiving corps. Bond caught 34 passes for 540 yards and five touchdowns in 14 games with the Longhorns last season and topped out with a 48-668-4 line in 2023 with Alabama. Bond averaged 8.0 yards after catch per reception last season while playing 76.8 percent of his snaps out wide, per PFF. It seems unlikely he would make much, if any impact as a rookie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd53-d45c-a7fc-bf5bf26b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints head coach Kellen Moore said TE Taysom Hill (ACL) won’t be “ready to get on the field any time soon.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd7d-d05a-adda-bffffda50000</link>
      <description>Hill, who was seen in late July working with trainers, is expected to begin the regular season on the PUP list, meaning he will miss at least the season’s first four weeks. His 2024 season ended with a devastating ACL injury that was thought to imperil his NFL career. It seems for now that Hill, 34, is intent on a return to action at some point in 2025. That might not happen until well into the regular season. Hill in 2024 ran for 277 yards and six touchdowns over eight games while catching 23 passes for 187 yards. He leads the NFL in EPA per rush since the start of the 2023 season. Juwan Johnson is expected to operate as the Saints’ No. 1 tight end, with Jack Stoll as the TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd7d-d05a-adda-bffffda50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed CB Xavien Howard to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd58-df63-a199-fd7b14c60000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero, Howard can earn up to $5 million on his deal. Howard has spent the entirety of his eight-year career with the Dolphins, but was released in March 2024. He remained unsigned throughout the year despite having interest in joining both the Texans and Bengals. The veteran corner will be 32 at the start of this season and earned a PFF coverage grade of 51.9 in his last season of action, allowing opposing receivers to go for 44-502-2 on 71 targets while playing on 475 coverage snaps. It’s hard to imagine this is anything more than a depth signing at this time, but Howard brings a wealth of experience to the Colts’ secondary and spent two years playing under defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bd58-df63-a199-fd7b14c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots Executive VP of Player Personnel Eliot Wolf said the team would be willing to trade away a first or second round pick if it was “best for the team.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bda7-d90d-a5bd-bfff36030000</link>
      <description>Interestingly, a high draft pick is part of what would be required to facilitate a trade with the Bengals to land star pass rusher Trey Hendrickson. Wolf also said the team would “absolutely” be open to making a big trade before the start of the season. Who Wolf could have in mind while making these statements is anybody’s guess, but these quotes come less than 24 hours after we learned the Bengals are open to talking to teams about a potential trade for Hendrickson. The Patriots are one of a handful of teams that could have the cap space to get a deal done with Hendrickson. They $59.798 million in available cap space, which leads the league by a wide margin. They would need to figure out a player or two to give back to the Bengals in a deal, but the Patriots are officially a team to watch in the coming days as a suitor for Hendrickson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bda7-d90d-a5bd-bfff36030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons released WR DJ Chark.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdb0-df63-a199-fdbbdd750000</link>
      <description>The Falcons signed Chark in late July and are now parting ways with him after nearly a month. The veteran receiver totaled 31 receiving yards and one touchdown last season with the Chargers and has struggled to replicate the success he enjoyed in 2019 when he broke out for 73-1008-8. Now an official journeyman of the league, Chark will be looking for his fifth team in four seasons. In addition to releasing Chark, the Falcons also waived/injured QB Emory Jones (concussion) and signed QB Ben DiNucci.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdb0-df63-a199-fdbbdd750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots Executive VP of Player Personnel Eliot Wolf said Stefon Diggs is “ahead of schedule injury wise.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdb8-d90d-a5bd-bffb96520000</link>
      <description>Wolf isn’t exactly breaking news here. Diggs was cleared for full participation to start training camp and hasn’t suffered any reported setbacks. The veteran receiver is making his way back from a torn ACL he suffered in Week 8 of last season, and is presumably on track to be ready for Week 1. Wolf said last month that Diggs does not look limited in practice, which is another encouraging sign for his return. We’ll get a better sense of Diggs’ availability once final roster cutdowns take place next week, but he’s been trending in the right direction for months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdb8-d90d-a5bd-bffb96520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (thumb) returned to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdcf-d45c-a7fc-bfdfb52f0000</link>
      <description>Love underwent surgery to correct a ligament issue on his non-throwing hand, but was away for less than a week. The Packers’ QB1 was sporting a glove on his hand, but appears to be on track to be ready for Week 1 when the Packers play host to the Lions. Love finished as the QB20 in fantasy points per game last season and had only six top-12 weeks. He’ll profile most weeks as a mid QB2 in an offense that’s expected to feature plenty of Josh Jacobs after leading the league with a 53 percent neutral rush rate last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdcf-d45c-a7fc-bfdfb52f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be01-d45c-a7fc-be1b98ce0000</link>
      <description>Our national nightmare is over. After refusing on Saturday to say if Stafford worked out as planned, the Rams’ QB1 took to the field in full pads and jersey on Monday, looking ready for his first taste of training camp practice. Stafford has been dealing with a back injury for weeks and, at one point, had an epidural to help with the pain. Stafford has endured numerous injuries throughout his 16-year career, including multiple back injuries. Head coach Sean McVay said last week that part of Stafford’s absence last week was due to function and pain tolerance, which doesn’t seem great. The Rams are going to do what they can to have Stafford ready for the season, but we wouldn’t assume he’s a lock to start Week 1 until we see how he progresses in the coming weeks. If he’s unable to go at any point in the season, Jimmy Garoppolo would take the reins at QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be01-d45c-a7fc-be1b98ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (undisclosed) was spotted in a non-contact jersey on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be13-df63-a199-ff3bf58d0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from last week, when Stevenson was completely sidelined in practice. Stevenson is dealing with an undisclosed injury that was first announced last Tuesday, but could be trending toward a full return by the end of the week. The fifth-year back could be on the wrong side of a split backfield after rookie TreVeyon Henderson has impressed through two preseason games, rushing for 5-38-1 while also returning a kick return for a 100-yard score. We’ll be sure to provide any updates on Stevenson’s availability as they are announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be13-df63-a199-ff3bf58d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
