<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC Jesse Minter declined to discuss Nnamdi Madubuike’s (neck) future with the team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ea-d57c-a1dd-94eacd2c0000</link>
      <description>“That will be up to him when the time is right,” Minter said. Madubuike missed almost the entire season with the neck injury and there have been rumors here and there about it being career-threatening. The Ravens badly missed Madubuike as an interior force last year and, if they can’t bring him back, will likely seek to fortify their interior line in free agency and the draft this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ea-d57c-a1dd-94eacd2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers GM Jason Licht said Mike Evans “knows we’d love to have him back.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ec-d629-a1bc-b0fdfd880000</link>
      <description>Evans only recently told the Buccaneers he’d play in 2026 and that he intends to test free agency. We’d be surprised to see Evans leave in free agency without some kind of desperate, monster offer from a receiver-needy team. We’d also be surprised to see Evans get that kind of offer after missing most of last year with a broken collarbone. But we can’t exactly rule it out given how weak the wideout market looks in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ec-d629-a1bc-b0fdfd880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders GM Adam Peters said the team has had “good talks” with LT Laremy Tunsil on an extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ee-d89c-a1be-bffff97c0000</link>
      <description>There’s no deadline and Peters “feels good about the direction.” It was an open secret that Tunsil wanting a new extension helped guide him to Washington in trade last offseason, and he enters 2026 on the final year of his contract. With as great a year as Tunsil had for the Commanders last year — a career-best 84.7 PFF grade — we’d be surprised if this wasn’t eventually done. That said, the Commanders haven’t exactly worked fast to extend their own players, as the Terry McLaurin saga taught us in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90ee-d89c-a1be-bffff97c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Vikings have had trade talks with teams regarding DT Javon Hargrave.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f3-d629-a1bc-b0ff548b0000</link>
      <description>This is usually the first step towards a release, and The Athletic’s Alec Lewis called Hargrave’s release “a predictable offseason move” in December. Hargrave simply didn’t live up to expectations last year. Entering his age-33 season, we’d be surprised if the Vikings got anything more than a late-round swap for Hargrave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f3-d629-a1bc-b0ff548b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions GM Brad Holmes said the team has had conversations with David Montgomery and his agent and the situation is “fluid.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f5-d042-afbc-fdf73d960000</link>
      <description>It sure sounds like the Lions could move on from Montgomery in a trade. Entering his age-29 season, Montgomery could emerge as a solid fantasy RB2 in the right situation this offseason. This Lions enter the offseason roughly $10 million over the cap, releasing Montgomery would free up $3.5 million. It is also possible that Montgomery simply wants a bigger role than he had down the stretch during Jahmyr Gibbs’ takeover. Montgomery had 10 or more carries just once after Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f5-d042-afbc-fdf73d960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said he’s “not overly optimistic” about Jeremiah Owusu-Koramoah (neck) playing in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f9-d042-afbc-fdfbb35c0000</link>
      <description>A recent report from Mary Kay Cabot said Owusu-Koramoah is “doubtful to ever return to the field,” so missing just the 2026 season would be a mild upgrade. It’s clear that Owusu-Koramoah is not returning any time soon, but we’ll continue to monitor the situation in case the tone around that changes at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90f9-d042-afbc-fdfbb35c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he’ll call plays on defense in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90fc-d89c-a1be-bfff40120000</link>
      <description>It confirms one of the worst-kept secrets in the league after the Jets passed up on numerous other coordinator options to land on unheralded Brian Duker as their defensive coordinator. Glenn said “play calling is my superpower, really.” Well, it’s good to have one of those. We’ll see how it lasts with this Jets roster. It certainly can’t be worse than it was last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-90fc-d89c-a1be-bfff40120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said RB Quinshon Judkins (leg/ankle) is out of his boot and will be good to go for training camp.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9109-d629-a1bc-b11db03e0000</link>
      <description>It’s expected news, but good to hear it from a team source. Judkins was expected to miss about 4-5 months after fracturing his fibula and dislocating his ankle in late December. It’s possible that Judkins could show up for some later parts of minicamp/OTAs based on that schedule, but even if he doesn’t, he should be ready to be Cleveland’s bellcow back in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9109-d629-a1bc-b11db03e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said it’s “too early to say” if Deshaun Watson or Shedeur Sanders will be their Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</link>
      <description>Between the smoke on Ty Simpson and Malik Willis and Berry refusing to really stamp a player as “in the lead” here, it sure feels like this situation is unsettled heading into free agency. Sanders probably enters training camp as the main favorite for the job if the Browns don’t sign Willis, but anything could happen there. Up to and including a drafted quarterback winning the organization over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-910c-d89c-a1be-bfdfb6b90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
