<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys ruled out WR CeeDee Lamb (ankle) for Week 6 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfcb-def2-abdb-dfebb6c50000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys will be without Lamb and fellow WR KaVontae Turpin (foot), giving WR Ryan Flournoy a chance to prove that last week’s outing (6/114) was no fluke, though a repeat showing is far from guaranteed. Flournoy can be treated as a FLEX with upside this week. Yesterday, ESPN’s Todd Archer indicated Lamb could return next week against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfcb-def2-abdb-dfebb6c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Zay Flowers (shoulder) is questionable for Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd1-db72-a199-ffdbacfd0000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited sessions and is probably on the optimistic side of questionable. But between the shoulder injury, Cooper Rush at quarterback, and a looming bye week, we probably should err on the side of WR2/WR3 status for Flowers in Week 6. It’s entirely possible that if the Rams start beating up on Baltimore’s defense, Flowers will get some rest in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd1-db72-a199-ffdbacfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed RB Miles Sanders (knee/ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd3-db72-a199-ffdbcf210000</link>
      <description>It’s a season-ending injured reserve stint for Sanders per Cowboys.com’s Patrik Walker. That puts Jaydon Blue into a firm backup role ahead of Week 6’s game against the Panthers and makes him at least an interesting bench spot behind Javonte Williams, even if Week 5 showed the Cowboys aren’t ready to give Blue a real role yet. It’s big news for both Williams and Blue in a positive sense — at least for Week 6. Dallas will probably elevate a third back from the practice squad and perhaps sign someone ahead of Week 7. Sanders was playing on a one-year contract and figures to be a fixture in that market again next season. He showed enough with the Cowboys to perhaps be given an invitation back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd3-db72-a199-ffdbcf210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens LB Roquan Smith (hamstring) won’t play in Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfda-d94a-a79d-cfdfc3f10000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice at all this week. Neither did fellow ruled-out defender Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring) — both players probably have a chance to come back after Baltimore’s Week 7 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfda-d94a-a79d-cfdfc3f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfb5-dd4c-afb9-eff5146a0000</link>
      <description>Cowboys LG Tyler Smith (knee) is questionable and RG Tyler Booker (ankle) is out. The Cowboys’ offensive line health is beginning to improve, which bodes positively for both Dak Prescott and Javonte Williams. The Panthers’ defensive line is among the league’s weaker units, but the Cowboys face a tougher Commanders squad in Week 7. The Cowboys also ruled out LB Jack Sanborn (concussion). CBs DaRon Bland (shoulder) and Trevon Diggs (knee) are questionable, though both players remained limited in practice all week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfb5-dd4c-afb9-eff5146a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens S Kyle Hamilton (groin) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 6 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfdd-dd4c-afb9-efddb9950000</link>
      <description>Neither are T Ronnie Stanley (ankle) or CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) — Baltimore’s defense should at least feel a little more NFL-quality than they were last week against the Texans. The Roquan Smith-shaped hole at linebacker will be a challenge to overcome. Hamilton, Humphrey, and Stanley each wound up missing just one game with their respective injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfdd-dd4c-afb9-efddb9950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe2-def2-abdb-dfe31fa60000</link>
      <description>He did, however, return to practice this week, getting in two limited sessions after being sidelined for most of the last month-and-a-half. It seems likely that Ricard will be back for Baltimore in Week 8 after their bye, and perhaps that can help get their running game back on track.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe2-def2-abdb-dfe31fa60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Devontez Walker (oblique) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 6 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe3-db72-a199-ffebe63d0000</link>
      <description>He got in a DNP on Friday after two limited sessions, perhaps signaling a setback or the Ravens understanding that they can’t push him right now. Walker heads into Baltimore’s bye as a promising player ready for a bigger role in an offense, but also someone who simply can’t do more than limited snaps on a deep Baltimore wideout depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe3-db72-a199-ffebe63d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd8-dd4c-afb9-efd9b2f00000</link>
      <description>Higbee has just one finish in the TE2 ranks this season, and is largely an afterthought in the Rams’ offense. Against the Ravens’ injury-depleted defense, he is on the touchdown-dependent TE2 radar, which is hardly a ringing endorsement. He is likely available in most leagues, if need be, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfd8-dd4c-afb9-efd9b2f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (concussion) is not on Las Vegas’ final injury report for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</link>
      <description>With Brock Bowers out, Mayer will serve as the clear No. 1 tight end against Tennessee. It’s not exactly a smash spot, but Mayer went 4/38 against the Patriots in the opener and has had some TE1-worthy games in the past. Mayer probably is more of a TE2 until we see a ceiling game again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cfe6-db72-a199-ffef95eb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
