<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (eye) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2566-dbe3-a9bb-35773d580000</link>
      <description>Conklin left late in the first half with the eye issue before being listed as questionable to return. He didn’t return for the start of the second half, suggesting his day is done. Cornelius Lucas is in at right tackle for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2566-dbe3-a9bb-35773d580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) is active for Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2586-dbe3-a9bb-35d7782d0000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation for Parsons, though NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported this morning that he will likely be on a pitch count. Parsons is a game-changer even on limited snaps, so that shouldn’t be much of a concern for Packers fans. Inactive for the Packers are CB Nate Hobbs, S Zayne Anderson, OL Donovan Jennings, TE Ben Sims, DL Warren Brinson, and DL Barryn Sorrell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2586-dbe3-a9bb-35d7782d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared OL Ed Ingram (abdomen) inactive for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258b-db7b-a5dd-a58f835c0000</link>
      <description>Ingram popped up on the injury report on Thursday and was on a questionable tag. His absence will lead to an OL shuffle that would seem likely to put Tytus Howard at guard, Aireonate Ersery at right tackle, and Cam Robinson at left tackle. So, in other words, a normal Texans game. Also inactive for the Texans are: WR Christian Kirk (hamstring), WR Braxton Berrios (hamstring), DT Tommy Togiai, QB Graham Mertz (third QB) , and RB British Brooks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258b-db7b-a5dd-a58f835c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers S DeShon Elliott (knee) left Pittsburgh’s Week 1 game against the Jets and was ruled out.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258f-dbe3-a9bb-35df8a150000</link>
      <description>He walked off the field on his own, though he was surrounded by trainers, and went directly to the blue medical tent. Elliott had five solo tackles before leaving. Jalen Ramsey has been playing more safety with Elliott sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258f-dbe3-a9bb-35df8a150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared RB Sione Vaki, S Thomas Harper, LB Trevor Nowaske, DL Chris Smith, DL Mekhi Wingo, and DL Tyrus Wheat inactive for Week 1 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258f-db7b-a5dd-a58f9d020000</link>
      <description>Vaki is dealing with a hamstring issue and was ruled out on the final injury report. The Lions are fairly healthy heading into Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258f-db7b-a5dd-a58f9d020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (foot) is active for Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258b-dbe3-a9bb-35db36b40000</link>
      <description>Reed has been dealing with the foot issue for weeks and even missed the first practice of Week 1. He returned for two limited sessions before being listed as questionable and is now good to go. The injury all but guarantees Reed is stuck in a part-time role to start the year. Even without a full route tree, the explosive young wideout should stay in the WR4 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-258b-dbe3-a9bb-35db36b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared Jarquez Hunter inactive for Los Angeles’ Week 1 game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2591-d332-a1fd-b7b762950000</link>
      <description>They elevated Cody Schrader from the practice squad to play over Hunter, though neither should have much a role behind Kyren Williams and Blake Corum. Non-dynasty leagues don’t need to hold Hunter at this point. Also inactive for the Rams are: QB Stetson Bennett (third quarterback), DL Ty Hamilton, OL Justin Dedich, OL David Quessenberry, and DL Desjuan Johnson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2591-d332-a1fd-b7b762950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee) is questionable to return Week 1 against the Cardinals</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-259f-dbe3-a9bb-35dff5210000</link>
      <description>Fuaga left the Saints’ Week 1 game against the Cardinals with an apparent knee injury. The 23-year-old did not head to the locker room, instead sitting on the Saints’ bench while Asim Richards replaced him at right tackle. Fuaga is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-259f-dbe3-a9bb-35dff5210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave exited Week 1 against the Cardinals with an apparent chest injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25a9-dbe3-a9bb-35fbaf930000</link>
      <description>Olave was rocked on a fourth quarter hit from Cardinals CB Will Johnson. With his concussion history, the Saints immediately took Olave off the field and into the blue medical tent. He played just eight games due to concussions last season and was briefly in the medical tent to get his ankle checked out earlier in this game. Olave is listed as questionable to return with a chest injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25a9-dbe3-a9bb-35fbaf930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones completed 22-of-29 passes for 272 yards and a touchdown in a 33-8, Week 1 win over the Dolphins, adding 26 yards rushing and two rushing touchdowns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ba-d332-a1fd-b7beeb380000</link>
      <description>Jones didn’t hit many big gainers, except for a 27-yard touchdown pass to Michael Pittman Jr., but he consistently went through his progressions and gained chunk yards against this beat-up Dolphin secondary. The threat of a running game and a strong offensive line helped Jones, but he also found Tyler Warren over the middle a bunch and looked poised all game long. We wouldn’t expect this kind of production against a much healthier and stingier Broncos defense next week, which means Jones remains just an option in two-quarterback leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-25ba-d332-a1fd-b7beeb380000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
