<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 01:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught 5-of-5 targets for 53 yards in the Lions’ Week 10 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b48-d45b-affe-7fde9d120000</link>
      <description>LaPorta was left out in the cold on the first drive, but Lions head coach and new play caller, Dan Campbell, corrected the issue on the second drive. LaPorta’s first reception went for 14 yards, aided by pre-snap motion and play action, and the Lions quickly went back to him three plays later, picking up eight yards on a quick-hitting slant. LaPorta later helped RB Jahmyr Gibbs score his second touchdown of the day by driving the Lions’ running back forward through multiple Commanders defenders, two of whom ended up injured, from 13 yards out. LaPorta is a TE1 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b48-d45b-affe-7fde9d120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 12 times for 30 yards in San Francisco’s Week 10 loss to the Rams, adding eight catches for 66 yards on 10 targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b48-d673-a39e-efd9b8c90000</link>
      <description>The 49ers’ star running back feasted against a weak Giants run defense last week, but this is more his speed this season, as he was held under 70 rushing yards for the eighth time this season in 10 tries. Nobody who started McCaffrey is upset — well, maybe a little upset that Brian Robinson vultured a touchdown from McCaffrey on the goal line — because the PPR side of this is what makes the whole scheme work. McCaffrey will remain on the RB1 line against the Cardinals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b48-d673-a39e-efd9b8c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions HC Dan Campbell confirmed he took over as the team’s offensive play-caller in Week 10’s win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b46-d1e7-a1fa-7bee19730000</link>
      <description>Playing against one of the worst defenses in the league, Campbell showcased his offensive play-calling skills against the Commanders, which was an easy first test that he passed with flying colors. The Lions scored their second-most points of the season in Sunday’s win while averaging an impressive eight yards per play in the drubbing. Under Campbell’s play-calling, wide receiver Jameson Williams also tied a season-high with seven targets in the win and had his most productive game of the season after struggling to get much going over the past month. It was an impressive first showing from Campbell, who will get a tougher test in Week 11 against the Eagles if he continues to call in the plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b46-d1e7-a1fa-7bee19730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson rushed eight times for 41 yards and a touchdown in San Francisco’s Week 10 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b4c-d1e7-a1fa-7beee88f0000</link>
      <description>Mostly an afterthought after a pair of zero-carry games in October, Robinson has now reeled off back-to-back games of 40 or more yards and a score. The role is still pretty tiny — he had just 14 snaps here and nine last week — and it keeps him from being more than a what-the-heck FLEX against the Cardinals in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b4c-d1e7-a1fa-7beee88f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams (oblique) caught 6-of-8 targets for 77 yards and a touchdown in Los Angeles’ Week 10 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b51-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb378b0000</link>
      <description>Everyone got fed today, as Adams managedjustone touchdown after five in his last two games. It was an end zone quick out, professionally done. Adams did miss some time with what Sean McVay said was an oblique issue after the game, he was seen on the broadcast holding his back gingerly after a snap. McVay said that Adams could have come back in had the game been close. We’ll see what that means for his practice status this week, but that’s an encouraging exit quote. Adams is on the WR2 line next week against a tough Seahawks defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b51-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb378b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 15 times for 142 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 10 win over the Commanders, adding three receptions for 30 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b42-d45b-affe-7fd6d2220000</link>
      <description>Gibbs dominated the Commanders’ defense from start to finish, averaging 9.5 yards per carry and 10.0 yards per reception. He was featured on the Lions’ opening drive, touching the ball on 6-of-10 plays, which culminated in a 14-yard catch-and-run touchdown on an angle route. The Lions’ electric running back was untouchable at times, racking up multiple explosive gains on outside runs and tosses by patiently waiting for holes in the second level to appear before knifing through them. He remains a weekly candidate to finish as the overall RB1 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b42-d45b-affe-7fd6d2220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 5-of-6 targets for 64 yards and a touchdown in Los Angeles’ Week 10 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b54-d1e7-a1fa-7bfed8080000</link>
      <description>He played on just 35 of the Rams’ 68 snaps, but he took a screen pass from Matthew Stafford on a blitz to make it 14-0 early. We’re guessing the Rams were just playing cautiously with Nacua after he left last week’s game with a chest injury, and that he probably could have played more had the team not established a big lead. Nacua will remain a must-start regardless — look at what he did despite this snap count — but there is a little more floor potential than usual next week against the Seahawks’ defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b54-d1e7-a1fa-7bfed8080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in Los Angeles’ Week 10 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b59-d45b-affe-7fdf03de0000</link>
      <description>The Rams have created an incredible situation where none of their tight ends are actually fantasy-reliable, but all of them are threats to score off play-action in jumbo packages. Parkinson (39 snaps), Tyler Higbee (3/33, 36 snaps), Davis Allen (2/8/1, 35 snaps) and Terrance Ferguson (1/32, 22 snaps) are all potential TE2 plays right now given the situation. It’s impossible to figure out which of them will blow up every week given the playing time split.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b59-d45b-affe-7fdf03de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed 15 times for 71 yards in the Lions’ Week 10 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b55-d713-ad9e-6f5504610000</link>
      <description>Montgomery functioned as a rumbling breather back in between RB Jahmyr Gibbs’s explosive gains. Lions head coach Dan Campbell technically attempted to get Montgomery into the end zone on a two-point conversion attempt following Gibbs’ second touchdown, but the play was unfortunately unsuccessful. Montgomery remains a borderline RB2/3 against the Eagles next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b55-d713-ad9e-6f5504610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Smith caught his only target for 14 yards in Los Angeles’ Week 10 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b5d-d45b-affe-7fdf3ccf0000</link>
      <description>He and Konata Mumpfield (33 snaps, zero catches) led the Rams’ WR3 platoon with Jordan Whittington only playing seven snaps. None of these players are worthwhile roster spots in this current incarnation of the Rams’ offense, though perhaps if a team thoroughly game-scripted the Rams they’d pop up. Nobody has really stepped up to fill the Tutu Atwell role to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b5d-d45b-affe-7fdf3ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
