<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 22-of-38 passes for 309 yards, two touchdowns, and two interceptions in the 49ers’ 26-21, Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a5-dca3-a9fb-bfbde89e0000</link>
      <description>Purdy was running out of receivers in this game, but he kept threatening to put more in there with a few hospital balls as he sent Jauan Jennings into the tent on a two-point attempt. He didn’t have the best zip on his throws today, and the two touchdowns were a shovel pass to Christian McCaffrey and a screen to Jake Tonges. The 49ers will have a short week ahead as they take on the Rams on Thursday night — Purdy is probably best approached as a high-end QB2 for that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a5-dca3-a9fb-bfbde89e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 4-of-6 passes for 56 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 4 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a8-d6e9-af9d-9ab832cd0000</link>
      <description>Adams was clearly limited by the hamstring issue, but it didn’t prevent him from coming down with a touchdown catch for the second-straight game, and he also had a key 25-yard connection with Matthew Stafford late in the contest. The 32-year-old is clearly second-fiddle to Puka Nacua in this offense, but there’s still a chance to put up good numbers in this offense. He’ll be on the WR1 cusp against the Ravens in Week 6 after the Rams’ bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a8-d6e9-af9d-9ab832cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutu Atwell caught 1-of-2 targets for 88 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 4 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a9-dca3-a9fb-bfb90d480000</link>
      <description>If you’re only going to catch one pass, make it an 88-yard touchdown. Atwell took advantage of a blown coverage by the Colts and sprinted into the end zone to give the Rams a 27-20 lead and ultimately the victory. A moment he’ll remember forever, but not one that leads to fantasy relevancy in Week 6 against the Ravens after the Rams’ bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a9-dca3-a9fb-bfb90d480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry had eight rushes for 42 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs, adding two catches for 16 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9298-d95b-addb-fade36340000</link>
      <description>Henry hardly played in the fourth quarter after Lamar Jackson exited the game with a hamstring injury. Henry didn’t play much in Week 4 due to negative game script for Baltimore, which usually plays Justice Hill when facing a big deficit. Henry now has 23, 50, and 42 rushing yards over the Ravens’ past three games. That’s partly due to poor offensive line play and partly due to a Baltimore defense that can’t keep game script in check. If Jackson misses time with his hamstring issue, Henry’s fantasy prospects will take a major blow, starting in Week 5 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9298-d95b-addb-fade36340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 7-of-8 targets for 74 yards in the Ravens’ Week 4 loss against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92b4-d6e9-af9d-9ab4426e0000</link>
      <description>Flowers led the Ravens in targets, receptions, and receiving yards in a disastrous day for the Baltimore offense. Lamar Jackson left the game in the second half with a hamstring injury that could keep him out in the coming weeks. It was a nice bounce back for Flowers after his 13-yard outing in Week 3 against the Lions. Flowers should continue running as the team’s WR1 no matter who is under center for the Ravens in Week 5 against the Texans. Cooper Rush under center could mean more drop backs and targets for Flowers and the rest of the Baltimore wideouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92b4-d6e9-af9d-9ab4426e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 5-of-8 targets for 83 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92b7-deb6-a7fd-d3ffdcd00000</link>
      <description>Worthy returned from his Week 1 shoulder injury and instantly reasserted himself as Kansas City’s No. 1 wideout, leading the Chiefs in targets and receiving yards. Worthy’s big play of the day came on a 37-yard grab in the second quarter after separating from the injury-ravaged Ravens coverage unit. Worthy dominated air yards in the KC offense, narrowly missing on a couple downfield shots from Patrick Mahomes. Worthy will be a top-24 fantasy play next week against a surprisingly solid Jacksonville defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92b7-deb6-a7fd-d3ffdcd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh declined to comment on whether or not Lamar Jackson (hamstring) could have returned to Sunday’s Week 4 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-929b-d95b-addb-fadfd1530000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are 1-3 and just saw their roster get decimated by injuries in real time in Sunday’s loss to the Chiefs. As we noted during the game, Jackson did not appear to receive any medical attention while on the bench, and the Chiefs were holding a solid lead at the time of his injury. Hopefully, this is a minor issue that Jackson can work through in time to face the Texans in Week 5, but we may not know more about his availability until later. If he’s unable to go, Cooper Rush would draw his first start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-929b-d95b-addb-fadfd1530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Williams completed 22-of-37 passes for 212 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Bears’ 25-24, Week 4 win over the Raiders, rushing eight times for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91c4-d6e9-af9d-9bd44b090000</link>
      <description>Williams’ pass protection was poor, and the coaching staff rotated offensive tackles intermittently throughout the game, on both the left and right sides of the line. Williams was constantly throwing on the run as a result, and had just 98 passing yards, one interception and minus-six rushing yards at halftime. Credit to him for making a few tough, low-probability completions. Both RB D’Andre Swift and TE Cole Kmet let pinpoint on-the-run passes hit them in the facemask. Kmet’s was particularly costly; he was just six yards from the Raiders’ end zone. Kmet’s unreliable hands struck again as he was unable to secure a 23-yard toe-tapper that Williams threw on a dead sprint, running toward the sideline. Williams’ interception occurred on a bat-and-catch play made by Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby, who notched three passes defended, five tackles and one quarterback hit on the day. Williams gets a chance to rest his weary legs during next week’s bye. He will be back on the QB1 radar against the Commanders in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91c4-d6e9-af9d-9bd44b090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 4-of-8 targets for 69 yards and one touchdown in the Bears’ Week 4 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a1-dca3-a9fb-bfb922e50000</link>
      <description>Odunze was nigh unstoppable on five- and 10-yard out routes, picking up chunk gains whenever Caleb Williams had enough time to look for him. Odunze’s 27-yard touchdown occurred on a post route. It was one of the (seemingly) rare occurrences where Williams was able to stand tall and throw from the pocket. The two had a chance to connect for a score on the Bears’ third drive but Williams overthrew him in the end zone. Odunze is on bye next week but he will be a high-end WR2 at worst against the Commanders in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92a1-dca3-a9fb-bfb922e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus caught 5-of-6 targets for 41 yards in the Bears’ Week 4 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92c2-d95b-addb-fac663100000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus is still serving as a safety blanket option for Caleb Williams, who was regularly playing under pressure against the Raiders. His most notable play occurred on the Bears’ third drive, when he helped Williams successfully convert on third down. Zaccheaus does not need to be in starting rosters in 12-team leagues but it is possible he emerges from his team’s Week 5 bye with a larger role, on the off chance that WR DJ Moore gets traded away. The Bears face the Commanders in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92c2-d95b-addb-fac663100000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
