<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed RB Patrick Taylor (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c38d-de13-afdc-c7cff57e0000</link>
      <description>That will end Taylor’s season before it begins — he suffered the shoulder injury in the second week of the preseason. Taylor has been a deep depth piece for the 49ers, drawing 39 carries for 183 yards and a score last year, and San Francisco’s injury woes at the position will continue. This slides Jeff Wilson into a stronger position at the start of the year, perhaps as high as Christian McCaffrey’s backup if Isaac Guerrendo and Jordan James aren’t able to recover from their injuries ahead of Week 1. The 49ers signed Nate Sudfeld to take Taylor’s place on the roster and absorb some punishment in Week 3 of the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c38d-de13-afdc-c7cff57e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indianapolis Star’s Joel A. Erickson reports Tyler Goodson (shoulder) avoided a major injury on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c394-dbe3-a9bb-f3d766440000</link>
      <description>Goodson injured his elbow in Indianapolis’ second preseason game on Saturday, but it appears the door will not be cracked for DJ Giddens just yet. At least not via injury, anyway. Goodson hasn’t returned to practice yet but it sounds like he has a decent shot at being available for the opener based on this report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c394-dbe3-a9bb-f3d766440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner believes WR Mitchell Tinsley is making the Bengals 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c397-db7b-a5dd-e3977ff30000</link>
      <description>Other than the Bengals sad first-team defense, Tinsley was the talk of last night’s preseason game between the Bengals and the Commanders with a 5/73/2 display on six targets, including two extremely nice end zone catches, one from Joe Burrow. Dehner adds that Tinsley’s performance “had him running with the first team during certain practices.” Do we need to scrap the entire depth chart and worry about Ja’Marr Chase’s target share? No. But Tinsley could potentially push Andrei Iosivas for some time in the third receiver role, and perhaps scoot ahead of Jermaine Burton at last cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c397-db7b-a5dd-e3977ff30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Gabe Davis will visit the Bills “this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3b3-d332-a1fd-d7b7c0a20000</link>
      <description>Davis has been this offseason’s most-courted visit, appearing for the Steelers twice, the Giants, the 49ers, and now his old stomping grounds in Buffalo. There’s little to suggest that Davis is going to be a fantasy factor regardless of where he signs this offseason, but at least in Buffalo he’d be able to slide right back into a familiar role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3b3-d332-a1fd-d7b7c0a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jon Machota believe the Cowboys “still need to see more” from DT Mazi Smith for him to make the 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3b6-db7b-a5dd-e3b683300000</link>
      <description>Smith has played in both preseason games — the Cowboys have sat most of their starters — and he was still on the field in the second half against the Ravens on Saturday. The former first-round pick’s 2024 PFF grade was 208th among 220 interior defensive linemen and it sure doesn’t seem like the Cowboys feel he’s played any better in training camp. “For a defense that badly needs to improve at stopping the run, an outside addition might be a requirement before Week 1,” Machota adds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3b6-db7b-a5dd-e3b683300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes Diontae Johnson “has been outplayed at camp” and may be on the wrong side of the roster bubble.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3d6-dbe3-a9bb-f3d7ed6b0000</link>
      <description>“Even though his role would be different than [new signing Isaiah] Bond’s, that addition doesn’t help his chances, either,” Jackson added. Johnson has been listed behind Jamari Thrash on the depth chart for a bit, and the Browns may be choosing between Johnson and special teams helpers for their end-of-roster spots. Even if he does make the roster, Johnson’s role is so unsettled that he’s hard to trust in fantasy drafts at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3d6-dbe3-a9bb-f3d7ed6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Mac Jones (knee) sustained a sprain against the Raiders, but will be available in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3de-db7b-a5dd-e3deb4570000</link>
      <description>That further explains the Nate Sudfeld signing. Jones has by all accounts been a fine backup for the 49ers in training camp and shouldn’t see his 53-man spot at any risk assuming Shanahan’s forecast of his injury is correct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3de-db7b-a5dd-e3deb4570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB isaac Guerendo (shoulder) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3ff-db7b-a5dd-e3ff36910000</link>
      <description>He missed just over two weeks with a shoulder injury. Guerendo should slot right back in as Christian McCaffrey’s main backup over Jeff Wilson going forward. It’s possible Guerendo gets a little run in the final preseason game to make sure he’s fully ready for the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c3ff-db7b-a5dd-e3ff36910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Neal (hamstring) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c410-db7b-a5dd-e4143f7d0000</link>
      <description>It’s worth noting that Saints media only gets access to positional drills now that they’re in “regular season mode,” so we’re not entirely sure if Neal is going to get eased in or if he’s practicing with full contact just yet. If healthy, Neal is a candidate to get some run in the third preseason game for New Orleans. He missed roughly two weeks with the hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c410-db7b-a5dd-e4143f7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints head coach Kellen Moore said he is “really, really close” on deciding the team’s starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c466-de13-afdc-c6efc06a0000</link>
      <description>Moore and the Saints have yet to decide on a starting quarterback for Week 1 and the preseason finale against the Broncos will be the last chance for Tyler Shough and Spencer Rattler to make their cases. Both have had perfectly fine outings so far, with Rattler starting the first preseason game and Shough the second. Rattler had subpar performances starting last season, while Shough is the oldest rookie quarterback with a shot to start. Neither will be an appealing fantasy option for the redraft format.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c466-de13-afdc-c6efc06a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
