<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 04:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbe0bf0000</link>
      <description>Now healthy, Meyers gets one last chance to strut his stuff for any team that might be interested in trading for him before the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline. The Raiders’ No. 1 wide receiver has finished as a half-PPR WR4 three times this season, with his season-best performance (WR16) occurring in Week 1. He can generously be treated as a WR3 with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbe0bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbdace0000</link>
      <description>Bowers last played in Week 4 and is now ready to retake the field following the Raiders’ Week 8 bye. Only time will tell if his PCL sprain and bone bruise have fully healed, but fantasy managers do not want to be late to the punch on this one. Bowers belongs in season-long lineups as an elite TE1 against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3c4a-d673-a39e-bcdbdace0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RB Tyler Allgeier (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3d24-d1e7-a1fa-7fee707f0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier briefly caused a scare when he reappeared on the Falcons’ injury report on Thursday as a limited participant. He was upgraded to full on Friday and carries no game-day designation. Allgeier can be started as an RB3/FLEX option, if need be, though he is fairly touchdown-dependent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3d24-d1e7-a1fa-7fee707f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bengals QB Joe Flacco (shoulder) is planning to start against the Bears in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3dd1-d713-ad9e-7dd542540000</link>
      <description>Flacco is still officially questionable with an AC joint sprain in his right shoulder. There was optimism that the 40-year-old signal caller will be healthy enough to play following Thursday’s practice and that optimism has continued this weekend. Rapoport cautions that Flacco is planning to start barring a setback and that no one knows how his shoulder will ultimately react. Jake Browning would likely start if Flacco is ruled out, but it seems everyone is doing their best to avoid that scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3dd1-d713-ad9e-7dd542540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals QB Jacoby Brissett will start in Week 9 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4030-d713-ad9e-6c74c00e0000</link>
      <description>No big surprise here as the Cardinals tipped their hand earlier this week by canceling Kyler Murray’s media availability and giving Brissett the majority of the first-team reps in practice. Murray was expected to return after the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye, but he’ll take at least another week to recover from a foot injury. While Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon previously stated that Murray would be the starting quarterback when healthy, GM Monti Ossenfort was noncommittal when asked about the situation last month. Brissett is a QB2 option in superflex formats and fantasy managers can start Trey McBride and Marvin Harrison Jr. with confidence as both have increased their production with Brissett under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4030-d713-ad9e-6c74c00e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon told reporters Bam Knight will be the first running back out there against the Cowboys in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-404d-d673-a39e-e4ddff900000</link>
      <description>Gannon went on to say that all three running backs will have a role and that the Cardinals will use whichever back is most effective. Emari Demercado is the only other running back on the active roster, though Michael Carter is expected to be elevated from the practice squad once again. Carter was the first running back working with the starters in practice on Thursday and Friday, but he’s been outplayed by Knight during games. Knight isn’t necessarily a safe play this week, but he’s certainly the only Cardinals running back fantasy managers can even consider starting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-404d-d673-a39e-e4ddff900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed RB Hassan Haskins (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4068-d1e7-a1fa-5aeab0150000</link>
      <description>The hamstring injury suffered by Haskins in Week 7 will now cost him the next four games, and five in total. Haskins will be eligible to return following the team’s Week 13 game against the Raiders, by which time it is likely Omarion Hampton is back and healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4068-d1e7-a1fa-5aeab0150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals listed QB Kyler Murray (foot) as questionable for Week 9 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4106-d673-a39e-e59765ec0000</link>
      <description>The team has already announced Jacoby Brissett as the starter but said that Murray “could have a role.” There has been a lot of speculation surrounding Murray’s status as the franchise quarterback in the desert, and the media games played this week do little to quell those concerns. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4106-d673-a39e-e59765ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos elevated TE Marcedes Lewis from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-411d-d673-a39e-e59d94f70000</link>
      <description>Lewis needs four appearances to get credit for his 20th season in the NFL, meaning he would need to be signed to the active roster at some point considering teams are allowed to elevate a player only three times from the practice squad. He starts that journey in Week 9 after his first of three standard elevations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-411d-d673-a39e-e59d94f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens traded CB Jaire Alexander to the Eagles in pick swap.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-411f-d45b-affe-559feaf10000</link>
      <description>Alexander heads to his third team in a calendar year as the Eagles continue hoarding talent, with the team sending a 2026 sixth-round pick to the Ravens for Alexander and a seventh. Howie Roseman is no stranger to taking a cheap gamble on underperforming talent, which appears to be the case yet again with the recent addition. Alexander could compete with backup corner Kelee Ringo immedaitely considering the absence of Adoree’ Jackson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-411f-d45b-affe-559feaf10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
