<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Will Shipley rushed three times for 26 yards in the Eagles’ Week 1 win over the Cowboys before departing with a rib injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-184a-dbe3-a9bb-385bf5e20000</link>
      <description>Mixing in as a change-of-pace back behind Saquon Barkley, Shipley was the only Eagle to notch a 20-yard run before going down. He was announced as “questionable” but never returned following halftime or a lengthy third quarter weather delay. Not great, though he does have 10 days to get healthy for the Eagles’ Week 2 Super Bowl rematch with the Chiefs. Shipley has at least confirmed he’s the unquestioned No. 2 and in line to see a few weekly breather touches when healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-184a-dbe3-a9bb-385bf5e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the league is “reviewing last night’s spitting incident for potential additional discipline against Eagles DT Jalen Carter.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19d6-d332-a1fd-9ff60e1f0000</link>
      <description>This was expected. Carter’s decision to spit on Dak Prescott in last night’s season-opener led to an immediate ejection of the third-year lineman. Carter didn’t log a snap in Thursday’s contest, which could mean the league will effectively view his ejection as a one-game suspension, but we’ll know where things officially stand once the review concludes. Prescott, who was also seen spitting in Carter’s direction beforehand, is “unlikely to face any (discipline) for his role,” per Pelissero. He also notes that historically, the league has dealt more fines than suspensions toward players who were ejected for spitting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19d6-d332-a1fd-9ff60e1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said “I do not get the sense, based on the conversations I have had so far, that there are alarm bells going off about Christian McCaffrey (calf).”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19dd-db7b-a5dd-b9ddf4cf0000</link>
      <description>Pelissero noted that he is making these comments “cautiously” before pointing out that McCaffrey is a player with whom a team will exercise extreme precautions due to his value to the team and the nature of the injuries he dealt with last season. McCaffrey has had a healthy camp after dealing with multiple calf and Achilles injuries last season. After being activated from injured reserve in Week 10, McCaffrey landed on season-ending IR following a Week 13 game against the Bills in which he suffered a PCL injury that would sideline him for over a month. Fantasy managers are understandably panicking over McCaffrey popping up on Thursday’s injury report, but those concerns could be diffused before the weekend if he’s able to log a full practice on Friday. In the event McCaffrey is unable to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks, Brian Robinson would become a volume-based play with top-24 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-19dd-db7b-a5dd-b9ddf4cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed C Ted Karras to a one-year, $5 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a0c-d332-a1fd-9e3ed4dc0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals did something similar with Karras last offseason when they signed him to a one-year extension in June. The veteran lineman was set to enter the final year of his deal with the Bengals before this extension, but now will be under contract through the 2026 season. Karras earned a PFF grade of 64.1 last while playing on over 1,100 offensive snaps. A pillar of health for most of his career, Karras has missed just one game since joining the Bengals in 2022 while starting in every game he’s appeared in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a0c-d332-a1fd-9e3ed4dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Justin Shorter to active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a64-d332-a1fd-9e76103b0000</link>
      <description>Shorter was added to the Raiders’ practice squad last week after being waived during final roster cutdowns. A former fifth-round pick of the Bills back in 2023, Shorter appeared in six games for the Raiders last season while playing primarily on special teams. The decision to sign him to the active roster comes a day after Amari Cooper abruptly announced his retirement. Shorter doesn’t have any fantasy value at this time and is far from a lock to stick on the roster throughout the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a64-d332-a1fd-9e76103b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vita Vea (foot) returned to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a71-d332-a1fd-9e77299b0000</link>
      <description>It’s potentially good news for the Bucs as Vea appears set to log at least one practice before the end of the week. The veteran lineman was a DNP during the team’s first two practices to open the week, but even a limited practice would bode well for his Week 1 outlook against the Falcons. The team will release their final injury report later in the day, which should give us a good sense of whether or not Vea has a chance to suit up for the season opener.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a71-d332-a1fd-9e77299b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he expects Sauce Gardner (fibula) to play in Week 1 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a77-d332-a1fd-9e77de560000</link>
      <description>Glenn said he expects every player to be available on Sunday, with the exception of Alijah Vera-Tucker, who has been ruled out for the season due to a triceps injury suffered earlier in the week. After being a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice, Gardner was upgraded to a full participant on Thursday and will likely be removed from the team’s injury report by the end of Friday. Gardner should see plenty of DK Metcalf in Week 1, which could severely cap the already limited upside Metcalf is expected to have in the Steelers’ run-heavy attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a77-d332-a1fd-9e77de560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said Darren Waller (hip) is doubtful for Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a86-d332-a1fd-9eb658350000</link>
      <description>Waller’s return to the league continues to go horribly. After missing nearly all of training camp to get into football shape, the veteran tight end has gone from being on track to return in Week 1 at the start of the week to being a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday. McDaniel reports Waller suffered a setback ahead of Thursday’s practice, giving us little reason to believe he’ll be on the field on Friday. It wouldn’t be surprising if he is officially ruled out before the weekend, paving the way for Julian Hill to draw the start. It should go without saying, but there’s no reason to jam Hill into a fantasy lineup this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a86-d332-a1fd-9eb658350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said Malik Nabers’ back is a “little tight” but that he will be okay for Week 1 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a92-d332-a1fd-9eb679470000</link>
      <description>Daboll said the team will “back down on Malik” in Friday’s practice after the star receiver returned to the field earlier in the week. Nabers has not been listed on the team’s injury report this week, but it sounds like he could receive a limited designation for Friday based on Daboll’s quotes. Regardless of how the team lists him for Friday’s practice, Daboll seems confident that his WR1 will be ready to roll on Sunday against the Commanders. He’s a must-start in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a92-d332-a1fd-9eb679470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said Andrew Thomas (foot) will practice on Friday and “do some team stuff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a96-d332-a1fd-9eb66b190000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Thomas will be in a good position to play in Week 1 against the Commanders after being a DNP on Thursday. Thomas was limited in Wednesday’s practice, so it’s possible Thursday’s absence was due more to rest than further injury. We’ll have a better sense of his availability when the team releases its final injury report on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a96-d332-a1fd-9eb66b190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
