<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is doubtful for New York’s Week 5 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab55-dca3-a9fb-bfddd52e0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade after he saw some limited work, but this seems to point more towards a Week 6 return for Tracy. Tracy was already appearing to lose his starting gig to Cam Skattebo before he picked up this shoulder injury. When he does come back, he’ll likely be on a low enough snap count to not be worthwhile for most fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab55-dca3-a9fb-bfddd52e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) is not practicing Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab58-deb6-a7fd-fbdf7a770000</link>
      <description>Not good. Bowers was a surprise downgrade on Thursday and it seems likely we’ll be dropping a questionable tag at best on him later today. This hasn’t been the season you hoped for when you spent a first or second-round pick on the star sophomore tight end — now fantasy managers should probably be making plans to replace him in their Week 5 lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab58-deb6-a7fd-fbdf7a770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) will not play in Week 5’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab68-deb6-a7fd-fbff00c90000</link>
      <description>He’s now missed three games in a row and hasn’t practiced since getting hurt in Week 2. Stewart had two tackles in 66 defensive snaps in his two active weeks earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab68-deb6-a7fd-fbff00c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (hamstring) will “miss some time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab76-deb6-a7fd-fbff16c10000</link>
      <description>DT Alfred Collins (sprained knee) also was hurt in Thursday’s latest injury game for the 49ers, though it’s not known if he’ll miss time. The 49ers have been as banged up as any team in the league besides the Ravens the last four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab76-deb6-a7fd-fbff16c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (IR/hamstring) is a “long shot” to have his practice window opened before Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab7b-deb6-a7fd-fbff04e80000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Week 7 is a more realistic target for the soon-to-be 32-year-old veteran. Kittle has missed the required four games after suffering the injury in Week 1’s win over the Seahawks, so the 49ers opting to not open his practice window ahead of Week 6 is purely them reading where Kittle is at. Kittle will be an easy TE1 when he does return — especially in this environment — the question is simply: When?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab7b-deb6-a7fd-fbff04e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said the team would open Jalen Coker’s (IR/quad) window to return ahead of Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab7e-d95b-addb-eb7ed3100000</link>
      <description>Once he’s designated to return, Coker would have 21 days to recover enough to be officially activated to the roster. Coker thus is not guaranteed to be ready to play in Week 7, but it is the starting point of when he could be ready. The Panthers would surely like to see what they have in him if he’s healthy. We’ll give practice reports next week, but it looks like Coker has a chance to be a WR4/WR5 option starting in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab7e-d95b-addb-eb7ed3100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions DL Alim McNeill (PUP/knee) will not play in Week 5’s game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab8a-deb6-a7fd-fbdff97b0000</link>
      <description>It’ll be at least one more week for McNeill after he had his 21-day return window opened this week. Kerby Joseph got in a practice on Friday to get to the questionable line for the Lions defense, which seems to be in a prime spot this week despite cornerback depth concerns against Jake Browning’s Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab8a-deb6-a7fd-fbdff97b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pectoral) is questionable for Buffalo’s Week 5 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab91-d6e9-af9d-ab910f250000</link>
      <description>Ditto DL Ed Oliver (ankle) and OL Spencer Brown (calf) — all three of these players got in limited practices on Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday ahead of Sunday night football. We’d tentatively expect them all to play given the fact there were no setbacks. Milano and Oliver have not played since Week 2, while Brown missed Week 4 despite practicing on Friday ahead of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab91-d6e9-af9d-ab910f250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Michael Pittman (hamstring) is not on Indianapolis’ final Week 5 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab99-d95b-addb-ebdfcd7b0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on Friday and the hamstring injury looks to instead just be a small blip, great news for the Colts offense. Pittman will be a WR3 against a dismal Raiders defense in Week 5 as a high-floor option despite the threat that Indy may be able to run all over Vegas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ab99-d95b-addb-ebdfcd7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) is not on Philadelphia’s final Week 5 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aba1-d95b-addb-ebe710cd0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full today. Goedert will be a low-end TE1 against the Broncos mainly based on his touchdown upside. The tight end has three scores in three starts thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aba1-d95b-addb-ebe710cd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
