<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e05-deb1-a39b-2f0fb09d0000</link>
      <description>Brown lands on the Eagles’ injury report as a non-participant due to a hamstring injury to open the week. The 28-year-old has had an up-and-down role to start the season in the low-volume Philly offense, but remains the team’s top wideout. This could be the same hamstring issue Brown dealt with before the season though the severity is unclear. Fantasy managers should stay tuned for the rest of the week; if Brown can squeeze in a limited practice, his chances to play Week 8 against the Giants will increase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e05-deb1-a39b-2f0fb09d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e09-deb1-a39b-2f0fcfc00000</link>
      <description>Goedert was listed as a limited participant to open the week, dealing with a calf issue. He dealt with a knee issue earlier in the season, though he scored a touchdown in four straight games after returning from the injury. Goedert was at least able to practice which makes us believe this is not a serious issue. He is in the low-end TE1 mix for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e09-deb1-a39b-2f0fcfc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LB Jeremiah Trotter Jr. (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e10-deb1-a39b-2f1e00590000</link>
      <description>Trotter left the Eagles’ Week 7 game against the Vikings with the injury. EDGE Azeez Ojulari (hamstring), C Cam Jurgens (knee), and CB Adoree’ Jackson (concussion) also all left in Week 7 and did not participate in Wednesday’s practice. The Eagles defense and offensive line turn to depth options with all four players question marks for Week 8 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e10-deb1-a39b-2f1e00590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Daniel Bellinger (neck) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e18-d5d8-a3ff-ff799fe60000</link>
      <description>Bellinger was listed as a limited participant to open the week with a neck issue. The 25-year-old has become a viable target in the Giants offense with Malik Nabers out, catching a 44-yard touchdown in Week 7 against the Broncos. He is still trending to play Week 8 against the Eagles, but Theo Johnson enters the TE1 ranks if Bellinger misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e18-d5d8-a3ff-ff799fe60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e1e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e252d0000</link>
      <description>Diggs suffered the concussion in Week 7 and is still in protocol as practices for Week 8 start. S Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder) also did not participate, leaving the Cowboys secondary without a pair of starters. Both are in jeopardy of missing Week 8 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e1e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e252d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e2b-d5d8-a3ff-ff6bc0a50000</link>
      <description>Ehlinger has bounced between the active roster and practice squad for the Broncos to start the season. He was briefly released and brought back to the practice squad last week and is now back on the active roster. Ehlinger will continue to sit behind Bo Nix and Jarrett Stidham amidst the Broncos’ roster management ping-ponging his roster status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e2b-d5d8-a3ff-ff6bc0a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (back/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e32-d5d8-a3ff-ff73536c0000</link>
      <description>Schultz lands on the injury report with back and shoulder issues to begin the week. The 29-year-old caught nine of his 10 targets as one of C.J. Stroud’s top pass-catchers in Week 7. With a limited practice, he is still trending to play in Week 8 against the 49ers and should get a boost with Nico Collins (concussion) and Christian Kirk (hamstring) dealing with injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e32-d5d8-a3ff-ff73536c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson said, “my plan is to play” in Week 8 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e44-dab4-a3fb-9f7496710000</link>
      <description>Watson is ramping up from a torn ACL 10 months ago and this is his final week to be activated from his 21-day activation window. The 26-year-old is confident he will play against the Steelers, adding another wrinkle to the Packers offense. Doubs is Jordan Love’s current No. 1, but Watson is in line to take some of those deep targets away from Doubs and rookie Matthew Golden. He is worth a stash on fantasy benches as his production ramps up moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e44-dab4-a3fb-9f7496710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants designated K Graham Gano (groin) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e77-d5d8-a3ff-ff77a0630000</link>
      <description>Gano initially went on injured reserve last month with a groin issue. Jude McAtamney took over for him, but was waived this week after multiple missed extra points in Week 7. Gano is nearing a return to kick for the Giants, but Younghoe Koo awaits on the practice squad if he is not ready for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e77-d5d8-a3ff-ff77a0630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) said he plans to play in Week 8 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-111d-d5d8-a3ff-f97d4cdc0000</link>
      <description>Alt is listed as questionable and could still be held out of tonight’s game, but it looks like he is back after missing under a month with a high-ankle sprain. Alt went down with the injury in Week 4. Fellow LA offensive Trey Pipkins is also listed as questionable. Getting both blockers back would be a huge boost to a Chargers squad that is 1-4 over its past five games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-111d-d5d8-a3ff-f97d4cdc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
