<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 20:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad73-d35e-a1bf-edf380400000</link>
      <description>The coaching pool isn’t as deep this year as it was in 2025 when Ben Johnson and Liam Coen were both on the market. That, in turn, has teams like the Browns digging deeper into the McVay tree. Scheelhaase joined LA last year as an assistant and passing game specialist. He was promoted to passing game coordinator ahead of the 2025 season. Matthew Stafford went on to post career numbers this year, leading the league with 4,707 passing yards and 46 touchdowns. Scheelhaase is an under-the-radar name to watch for Cleveland. He will likely be in consideration for offensive coordinator gigs around the league as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad73-d35e-a1bf-edf380400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “a lot of people around the league have been wondering” if the Packers would be at the top of John Harbaugh’s list of head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad9c-dc7a-af9b-efbfae280000</link>
      <description>The Packers haven’t decided on Matt LaFleur’s future yet, but another early playoff exit has many speculating that they will move on from him in the coming days. As Schefter notes, Harbaugh is from the Midwest and his agent, Bryan Harlan, is the son of a former Packers president. It’s admittedly a tenuous link, but the dots are there for someone to connect. More importantly, the Packers would, in this scenario, be the only playoff team with a head coaching vacancy. Harbaugh wouldn’t need to spend any time rebuilding a defunct roster and could instead focus on getting Green Bay out of the Wild Card Round. They already have an answer at quarterback with Jordan Love and just spent big on defensive superstar Micah Parsons. We would expect Harbaugh to prefer Green Bay to any other landing spot if the team fires LaFleur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad9c-dc7a-af9b-efbfae280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports teams “still believe there is a chance” Notre Dame head coach Marcus Freeman comes to the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adc0-d968-a19b-fdf12e0a0000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Freeman recently had his contract adjusted by Notre Dame to stay with the team. He also posted on social media late last year that he would be returning to the Fighting Irish. Still, a massive raise and a chance to coach in the pros could lure him away from college football. We suspect multiple teams will reach out to him just to be sure, though all signs point to him staying in the college ranks for another year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adc0-d968-a19b-fdf12e0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared RB Ty Johnson, LB Terrel Bernard, CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle), DT Larry Ogunjobi, S Darnell Savage, OL Tylan Grable, TE Keleki Latu inactive for the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adcf-d35e-a1bf-edcf93820000</link>
      <description>Johnson suffered the ankle injury in the Bills’ final game of the regular season. He only practiced once this week before being listed as questionable. Ray Davis will see more work in his absence. James Cook could also be used more on passing plays, upping his fantasy value for Sunday’s DFS slate. Kicker Matt Prater is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adcf-d35e-a1bf-edcf93820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Dyami Brown, RB DeeJay Dallas, OL Cole Van Lanen, TE Hunter Long, DL Emmanuel Ogbah, and DT Maason Smith inactive for the Wild Card Round against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ade0-d35e-a1bf-ede276a80000</link>
      <description>Van Lanen has played all over the formation this year, filling in wherever needed. The team recently rewarded his versatility with a three-year extension. He has been starting at left tackle as of late. Walker Little will likely slide back to left tackle for this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ade0-d35e-a1bf-ede276a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington left the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round game against the Bills to be evaluated for a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae39-dc7a-af9b-efbf7e230000</link>
      <description>Washington left the game in the first quarter for the concussion evaluation. He was quickly taken to the locker room after getting shaken up. Jakobi Meyers and Brian Thomas Jr. would be asked to step up if Washington cannot return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae39-dc7a-af9b-efbf7e230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (concussion) has returned to the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae79-d968-a19b-fef9f4e60000</link>
      <description>Washington left for the locker room in the first quarter to be evaluated for a concussion. He missed time spanning multiple drives but did eventually return. Brian Thomas Jr. caught a short touchdown pass in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae79-d968-a19b-fef9f4e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Tyrell Shavers (knee) is questionable to return in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae7d-d56e-afff-eefde4f70000</link>
      <description>Shavers injured his left knee while on punt coverage in the second quarter. He quickly left for the locker room and was listed as questionable to return. With Josh Palmer now on IR, the Bills would be forced to lean on Keon Coleman, Gabe Davis, and Brandin Cooks for wide receiver snaps if Shavers is done for the day. Bills S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) is also questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae7d-d56e-afff-eefde4f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu suffered a ruptured patellar tendon in the Wild Card Round against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae89-dc7a-af9b-efbf47840000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, Ekwonu will undergo surgery and his availability for Week 1 of the 2026 season is in doubt. It’s a brutal end to the season for him and the Panthers. Now Carolina will likely have to spend a bit more on a backup tackle in the offseason. Pro Football Focus has Ekwonu graded as a top-40 tackle this year. He had just one year left on his contract and was likely eying an extension in the spring. Ekwonu might be forced to wait until next year to ink a new deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae89-dc7a-af9b-efbf47840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrell Shavers (knee) returned to the Bills’ Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae98-d968-a19b-fef9d8b60000</link>
      <description>Shavers left in the second quarter with the knee issue. He went to the locker room and the team listed him as questionable to return. Shavers was back on the field coming out of halftime, giving the Bills some extra receiver depth for the final two quarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae98-d968-a19b-fef9d8b60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
