<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 4-of-7 targets for 23 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c5-deb6-a7fd-f7df4f710000</link>
      <description>Coleman routinely matched up against the top coverage corner from the Patriots in Christian Gonzalez, whose coverage all but eliminated Coleman from the game plan. A second-half touchdown brought the Bills within three points and he narrowly missed adding a second on the following possession, with Gonzalez able to leverage the back of the end zone to ensure Coleman didn’t get both feet down in the field of play. The modest fantasy outing now marks four consecutive games with four or fewer receptions after his Week 1 eruption, making Coleman nothing more than a touchdown-dependent FLEX option moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c5-deb6-a7fd-f7df4f710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer caught both targets for 36 yards in the Bills’ Week 5 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c9-d95b-addb-ffcf47ea0000</link>
      <description>Palmer ranked behind Keon Coleman, Khalil Shakir, Dalton Kincaid, and Dawson Knox in offensive snaps played this season and has now gone four straight games with two or fewer receptions after his five-catch outing in Week 1. That leaves him unworthy of weekly fantasy consideration, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b7c9-d95b-addb-ffcf47ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Xavier Worthy (shoulder/ankle) “is expected to go” for Week 5 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b97c-de31-a999-bdfe32150000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, the Chiefs’ decision to place Worthy on their injury report was more out of precaution. He then added that the second-year receiver “is fine” and should be good to go for Monday night’s game against the Jaguars. Despite the optimism to start the morning, fantasy managers will still want to check the Chiefs inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to ensure Worthy is officially in the clear for tonight’s tilt with the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b97c-de31-a999-bdfe32150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said “it’s a very fair question after the turnovers that we had” when asked if he still believes in Jake Browning as the QB1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9a1-db72-a199-fbeb23610000</link>
      <description>The question about Taylor’s belief in Browning came following Taylor’s postgame remarks in which he said the team will “look at all personnel to make sure we’re doing the right thing.” Browning hasn’t been great in place of Joe Burrow. The backup has done most of his stat padding in meaningless garbage time, but the options behind him, which include journeymen Brett Rypien and Mike White, are unlikely to be much better. This felt like an inevitable problem the Bengals would face the moment Burrow (toe) went down in Week 2, but the Bengals’ offense has imploded in quick fashion. Since Week 3, the Bengals rank last in EPA per play, 31st in dropback success rate, and 29th in offensive success rate. It’s not good, folks. We’ll see if a change comes down the line, but as far as fantasy is concerned, Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins will be more inconsistent than usual no matter who is starting next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9a1-db72-a199-fbeb23610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports Jets LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) will travel with the team to London for Week 6 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9b1-db72-a199-fbfb802b0000</link>
      <description>Johnson isn’t a lock to play in Week 6, but the Jets will give him a chance to suit up by letting him travel to London. Johnson hasn’t played since Week 2 and was a DNP all week ahead of Week 5’s game against the Cowboys. Johnson should still be considered a long shot to play until we see how he fares this week in practice. In addition to Johnson, the Jets will also have RB/KR Kene Nwangwu (hamstring) travel to London in hopes of suiting up next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9b1-db72-a199-fbfb802b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Omarion Hampton (ankle) will undergo more testing to determine the severity of his injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9ea-dd4c-afb9-ffebb5200000</link>
      <description>Hampton is at risk of missing some time after being spotted in a walking boot following Week 5’s loss to the Commanders, but we could have a better sense of his return timeline once we know more about the severity of his injury. Any length of absence would be tough for a Chargers team that has been dealt long-term injuries to several key offensive players already, including Najee Harris, whose season ended in Week 3 due to a torn Achilles. We’ll hopefully have more information on Hampton soon, but if he were to miss any time, the Chargers would be looking at Kimani Vidal and Hassan Haskins as their top two backs heading into Week 6 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b9ea-dd4c-afb9-ffebb5200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports it’s “more likely than not” that Travon Walker (wrist) will miss Week 5 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba22-d94a-a79d-bb2fe8920000</link>
      <description>Walker underwent surgery on his wrist last week. While the star pass rusher is not expected to be out long-term, a one-game absence was always the most likely outcome. According to Rapoport, the Jaguars will allow Walker to decide how he feels before game time, but added that Walker seems like a “long shot” to play at this point. Walker has totaled 12 tackles, two TFLs, and two sacks in four games this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba22-d94a-a79d-bb2fe8920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers designated WR Christian Watson (knee) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba2d-def2-abdb-bf6d4c980000</link>
      <description>Watson was on the practice field Monday, marking his first practice since tearing his ACL in Week 18 of last season. The Packers now have 21 days to activate Watson from injured reserve, and given the nature of his injury and his extended time away, it wouldn’t be surprising if they used every day available to them to ramp Watson up before his return. The fourth-year receiver caught 29 passes for 620 yards and two touchdowns in 15 games last season while seeing just 53 targets. He’ll help add another deep element to Green Bay’s passing attack, but Watson has been very boom-or-bust for fantasy managers for much of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba2d-def2-abdb-bf6d4c980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Tom (oblique) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba40-def2-abdb-bf6154ea0000</link>
      <description>We don’t know the capacity in which Tom practiced, but after two weeks off, it’s possible Tom could be in line to return for Week 6 against the Bengals. The Packers don’t need to release an official injury report until Wednesday, but his return following a Week 5 bye is a good sign to start the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba40-def2-abdb-bf6154ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts K Spencer Shrader (knee) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba5d-db72-a199-fa5f5e4d0000</link>
      <description>The first report of Shrader’s season-ending injury came from The Pat McAfee Show. Shrader, who has made 13-of-14 field goals for the Colts this season, exited Week 5’s game against the Raiders after a defender collided with his knee. It didn’t look good the moment it happened, so the season-ending report doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Colts will bring in a new kicker later this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ba5d-db72-a199-fa5f5e4d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
