<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 24 times for 89 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 12 win over the Panthers, adding 53 yards on seven receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b95c-db57-afda-ff7efc4b0000</link>
      <description>In atypical fashion, the 49ers continue to be the least efficient run offense in the league, a trend McCaffrey failed to buck while averaging just 3.7 yards per carry. His elite pass game involvement remained high as head coach Kyle Shanahan fed him touches on the first six plays run from scrimmage, helping to march down the field to score on their opening possession and seize control of the game. That is particularly notable considering the offense is now back to full strength, minus Brandon Aiyuk. Fantasy managers that invested a first-round pick in the veteran back must be pleased with the returns thus far. McCaffrey gets a more difficult matchup on the ground against the stout Cleveland front in Week 13, but his work through the air keeps him a top tier RB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b95c-db57-afda-ff7efc4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle caught 6-of-10 targets for 78 yards in the 49ers’ Week 12 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b961-d90e-a9da-bf6f5ca30000</link>
      <description>Kittle was the primary beneficiary of the play action exploits of Kyle Shanahan’s offense in this one, with Christian McCaffrey setting the tone and keeping the Carolina defense on heir heels. He was held out of the end zone for only the second time in his last five games, but remains one of the highest-upside tight ends in the league in an offense now back to full heath. That doesn’t change ahead of a Week 13 matchup against the Browns, regardless of the effects on his floor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b961-d90e-a9da-bf6f5ca30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 5-of-7 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 12 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b964-d82c-a79a-bbf44bb10000</link>
      <description>Jennings got the party started on the team’s opening possession, finding paint from 12 yards out to get the team on the board. His follow-on exploits were mostly confined to the short areas of the field, tacking on an additional four catches for 29 yards. In typical Jennings fashion, he continued to play hard throughout the game, most notably throwing blocks for McCaffrey. It was on one such play that he appeared to be upper-cutted by Panthers safety Tre’Von Moehrig in a sensitive area, something Jennings would not forget as he waiting until after the game to take exception. Expect a fine to be levied by the league in short order. Jennings continues to return viable WR2 counting stats as one of the primary cogs of the San Francisco aerial game, and he’ll look to further that streak against the Browns in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b964-d82c-a79a-bbf44bb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall caught 2-of-4 targets for six yards in the 49ers’ Week 12 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b96a-db57-afda-ff7af6ff0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall’s mundane fantasy outing could have been saved on an end zone target in the second quarter, but Panthers cornerback Mike Jackson undercut the route and picked Brock Purdy off to flip the script. Kyle Shanahan was able to institute a play action-heavy game plan that fed targets to George Kittle, Christian McCaffrey, and Jauan Jennings for much of the game, resulting in the poor fantasy outing for the talented second-year receiver. Pearsall’s primary function as the downfield receiver is likely to continue to lead to a wide range of outcomes, something fantasy managers will be forced to live through as the fantasy regular season comes to a close.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b96a-db57-afda-ff7af6ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor reports Isiah Pacheco (knee) could return in Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb07-d90e-a9da-bf0fb2f10000</link>
      <description>Pacheco logged some limited practice time last week but was inactive for the Chiefs’ Week 12 win over the Colts. Kareem Hunt took over the KC backfield with 33 touches for 130 yards and a touchdown. That workload would be trimmed back to somewhere around a dozen touches if Pacheco is able to return for the team’s Thanksgiving Day matchup against Dallas. Hunt would become a 12-team flex option and Pacheco would be unplayable in all but the deepest fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb07-d90e-a9da-bf0fb2f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs head coach Todd Bowles said the team would have to change the offense for QB Teddy Bridgewater.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb0f-d82c-a79a-bb9fa4500000</link>
      <description>Bridgewater played the entire second half in the team’s Week 12 blowout loss to the Rams after Baker Mayfield went down with a shoulder injury that was deemed a “low-grade” shoulder sprain — one that could cost him at least one week. Bridgewater on Sunday completed eight of 15 attempts for 62 scoreless yards, with an average depth of target of 6.4, well short of Mayfield’s aDOT of 8.5. “He’s a different quarterback, so schematically, we’ll have to do some different things for him to make him feel comfortable within the offense and do a lot of things he likes to do,” Bowles said of Bridgewater. “There are some similar things, but there are also some differences that way to make him more comfortable. He’s been here long enough to where if he had to go, we can tweak it the right way for him to be successful.” Short-area Bucs pass catchers like Cade Otton and Rachaad White might benefit if Bridgewater draws the start in Week 13 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb0f-d82c-a79a-bb9fa4500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed EDGE Shaq Lawson, formerly of the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb6f-d413-ad9f-bfffc8ed0000</link>
      <description>This will be Lawson’s third stint with the Bills. He was drafted by Buffalo and played for the Bills from 2016 to 2019, and again from 2022 to 2023. He last played for the Panthers in 2024. Lawson will start on the Bills’ practice squad but could see game action shortly as the Bills defense struggles to stop opposing rushing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb6f-d413-ad9f-bfffc8ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports up to three NFL teams are interested in pursuing North Carolina head coach Bill Belichick this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb8e-d90e-a9da-bf8f7e900000</link>
      <description>Anderson’s somewhat vague report suggests the 73-year-old Belichick could be in the running for another NFL job even after failing as UNC’s head coach in 2025. The Tarheels are 4-7 after losing two straight games; they have just two wins in the ACC. “There’s more to the story of why Belichick did not end up head coaching another NFL team a couple seasons ago--with his own desires and preferences regarding workplace dynamics playing more into a part of it, than I think has been discussed, publicly known, or given real credence,” Anderson said. Belichick has said he won’t pursue another NFL head coaching job after being passed over by the Falcons two years ago. The presence of Belichick’s social media influencer girlfriend, Jordon Hudson, could complicate things for Belichick if he goes after an NFL gig in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb8e-d90e-a9da-bf8f7e900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports Colts defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo “is expected to receive strong consideration” for the Giants head coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb95-d82c-a79a-bb9504b20000</link>
      <description>Anarumo’s role in improving the Colts defense this season could leave him with his choice of head coaching jobs in the offseason, assuming a handful of head coaches will get the axe in January and February. The Colts are allowing the tenth lowest EPA per play this season. They’ve been particularly tough against opposing passing offenses. The Giants, meanwhile, sport one of the league’s most putrid defenses in need of a total overhaul. Anarumo, 59, served as the Giants’ defensive backs coach in 2018 before landing the Bengals’ defensive coordinator job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bb95-d82c-a79a-bb9504b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans interim head coach Mike McCoy said Cam Ward’s rushing in Week 12 was “the next part of his growth” as an NFL quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bba3-d82c-a79a-bbb758aa0000</link>
      <description>“I think yesterday he took that next step and made plays with his feet,” McCoy said Monday, a day after Ward logged six rushes for 37 yards and a touchdown on a broken play near the goal line. “He was not only taking what they gave him, but he was taking off and running. That was the next part of his growth.” Coming into Week 12 against the Seahawks, Ward had just 79 rushing yards on the season. His 37-yard rushing effort against Seattle came after a 33-yard rushing total against Houston in Week 11. McCoy said Ward’s running was part of a renewed effort for the QB to be more decisive in the pocket. A little more rushing could make Ward a superflex-viable fantasy option in the final month of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-bba3-d82c-a79a-bbb758aa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
