<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 01:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f14-d6a5-adff-ffd5d22a0000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet is now firmly on the wrong side of questionable. The Seahawks will likely be without their No. 2 running back, setting up Kenneth Walker III for a large workload against the Saints in Week 3. The Seahawks list RB George Holani in the No. 3 role, behind Charbonnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f14-d6a5-adff-ffd5d22a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5edc-d1b3-a5dd-5ffda7960000</link>
      <description>Horton is on track to play, though returning to full participation today would have been nice to see. The Seahawks’ rookie speedster had a productive outing on four targets last week, though that sum is likely his projectable ceiling, at least in the short term. He could play efficiently against the Saints’ defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5edc-d1b3-a5dd-5ffda7960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f19-dfde-a1bd-5f9dce010000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon is rehabbing an MCL contusion, and was unable to play in Week 2. Rookie S Nick Emmanwori remains sidelined by a high-ankle sprain and fellow S Julian Love is sidelined by a hamstring injury. The Saints’ speedy wide receivers could have a productive day against the Seahawks’ banged up secondary in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f19-dfde-a1bd-5f9dce010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f24-d93f-ad9d-5fe718400000</link>
      <description>Purdy was asked if he could end up playing this weekend, and he responded by saying that the decision will come down to how he is feeling come “game time.” That’s a bit surprising, but it sounds as though Purdy may actually suit up this weekend. His continued limited participation only furthers the notion. His mobility may be impeded if he is active, however, and he is also still nursing a left shoulder injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f24-d93f-ad9d-5fe718400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f08-d1b3-a5dd-5f79c5290000</link>
      <description>Last week, when Jennings was only dealing with a shoulder injury, he sat out practice on Wednesday and Thursday before practicing in a limited capacity on Friday. He then improbably caught 5-of-10 targets for 89 yards and one touchdown. Jennings is tough to trust, given the new injury, but we expect a similar practice participation situation to unfold tomorrow. He is a boom-bust WR3 for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f08-d1b3-a5dd-5f79c5290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jordan Watkins (calf) was added to the injury report on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f2f-d1b3-a5dd-5f7f002d0000</link>
      <description>Watkins is listed as a limited participant, which suggests the once-hyped rookie wide receiver strained his calf in practice. It’s a brutal development for a young player who just rehabbed an ankle injury. Watkins is seemingly unlikely to suit up in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f2f-d1b3-a5dd-5f7f002d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (back) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f32-d1b3-a5dd-5f737bbc0000</link>
      <description>The good news is that the 31-year-old tight end is no longer listed with a calf injury. It ends there. Engram has caught 4-of-6 targets for 33 yards through two games, making him difficult to roster given the injury concerns and questionable upside. Should Engram get right in a week or two, it is possible for him to return TE1 value. Fantasy managers are encouraged to explore the waiver wire for superior bench stashes though. Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) notably has a chance to return this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f32-d1b3-a5dd-5f737bbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) was limited again on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f37-d93f-ad9d-5ff726c10000</link>
      <description>Bowers is up to two limited sessions this week, which is twice as many as he logged before suiting up last week. The second-year tight end is clearly limited by the injury, given the sizable brace he’s currently sporting on his left leg, but few tight ends can earn seven targets in a game while they’re playing through injury. He remains a high-end TE1 in Week 3 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f37-d93f-ad9d-5ff726c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe said that the Dolphins are not considering trading Tyreek Hill “at this stage” and hope to increase Hill’s downfield opportunities.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f45-d1b3-a5dd-5f75b5460000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said Tua Tagovailoa has focused on getting the ball out quickly in an effort to keep from getting hit too often, but that tactic has resulted in fewer downfield opportunities for Hill. The Dolphins are reportedly hoping to get the downfield passing game back on track against the Bills this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f45-d1b3-a5dd-5f75b5460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Dolphins owner Stephen Ross “does not want to fire” head coach Mike McDaniel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f4d-dfde-a1bd-5fcd33a50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport then added that Ross’ view could change if “fans suddenly stop showing up to the stadium,” or “if players stop playing” for McDaniel. While the initial report is positive, the latter almost reads like Ross is laying out a road map for McDaniel’s firing. McDaniel wields a creative playbook and employs star-focused game plans, which bode positively for fantasy productivity. For a multitude of reasons, it would be nice for him to stick around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f4d-dfde-a1bd-5fcd33a50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
