<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:02:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Commanders believe Marshon Lattimore suffered a torn ACL in Week 9’s loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a20-d673-a39e-eeb116820000</link>
      <description>The hits keep coming. After possibly losing Jayden Daniels (elbow) and Luke McCaffrey (collarbone) for the season, the Commanders may now be looking at another season-ending injury. Lattimore will undergo an MRI to confirm, but it sounds like the veteran corner is shaping up to miss the remainder of the season with his injury. Lattimore has struggled since arriving in Washington, consistently getting beaten in coverage while also being among the most penalized cornerbacks in the league. The Commanders traded a third-round pick to the Saints last season to acquire him ahead of the deadline. He remains under contract through 2026 butcan be cut for a cap savings of $18.5 million, per OverTheCap.com.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a20-d673-a39e-eeb116820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Bengals are still seeking a first-round pick for Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a93-d1e7-a1fa-5afbd5360000</link>
      <description>The asking price remains high for Hendrickson, who did not play in Week 9 due to a hip injury and has managed just four sacks in the seven games he has appeared in this season. Hendrickson is still on an expiring contract and has reportedly generated interest from multiple teams, per a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter over the weekend. With the trade deadline set for Tuesday, there is still time for the Bengals to lower the asking price if they hope to move Hendrickson for some assets, but for now, the price remains high for one of the league’s premiere pass rushers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a93-d1e7-a1fa-5afbd5360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns designated WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a95-d45b-affe-5f9760190000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin Stefanski said last week that the team hopes to have Tillman back after their Week 9 bye, so it’s possible we see Tillman as early as Week 10 against the Jets. Given the release of S Damontae Kazee, it sounds like the team is already clearing room for a return. Tillman enjoyed a five-game stretch last season where he totaled 26 receptions for 330 yards and three touchdowns before a concussion ended his season. In four games this season — all with Joe Flacco, he went for 11-106-2 while averaging five targets per game. While he’s shown an ability to make plays down field, Tillman is now playing with one of the most conservative passers in the league in Dillon Gabriel. It’s hard to imagine him having anything more than WR4 upside in a passing offense that has lived primarily in the short areas of the field since Gabriel took the reins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4a95-d45b-affe-5f9760190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers TE Tucker Kraft suffered a torn ACL in Week 9’s loss to the Panthers, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aa9-d673-a39e-eeb900780000</link>
      <description>The worst was confirmed on Monday, as Kraft’s season now comes to an end. The third-year tight end will now land on IR with his injury. Kraft was on pace for the best season of his career, and already had two 100-yard games on his resume through the first nine weeks of the season. Kraft was on a 17-game pace for his first 1,000-yard season and will now set his sights toward another high-end season in 2026. Backup tight end Luke Musgrave is now expected to step up in Kraft’s absence, and has caught just nine passes for 88 yards this season on 10 targets. He won’t replicate the production we saw from Kraft, but Musgrave could prove to be sneaky waiver wire add in fantasy for managers still looking for a dependable option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aa9-d673-a39e-eeb900780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said S Andre Cisco (pectoral) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4abf-d45b-affe-5fbfa8db0000</link>
      <description>Cisco suffered a torn pectoral in Week 8’s win over the Bengals. Returning from the team’s Week 9 bye, Glenn confirmed that the fifth-year safety will now miss the remainder of the season. Cisco signed a one-year deal with the Jets this offseason and started all eight games he appeared in while totaling 41 tackles, one TFL, and one pass breakup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4abf-d45b-affe-5fbfa8db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Garrett Wilson (knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac2-d713-ad9e-6ed671a20000</link>
      <description>Glenn didn’t say how much he expected Wilson to practice this week, but his return to the field is a good sign for his Week 10 availability against the Browns. Wilson missed the last two games after suffering a knee injury in Week 6, but avoided a stint on injured reserve. Assuming he’s able to get on the field every day this week, Wilson should have a chance to suit up for the Jets coming off their bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac2-d713-ad9e-6ed671a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn declined to name a starting QB for Week 10’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac3-d45b-affe-5fd721f90000</link>
      <description>With such a big game on tap, we can’t blame for Glenn wanting to keep his decision on QB close to the vest against **checks notes** the 2-6 Browns. Even after a Week 9 bye to further evaluate Justin Fields’ performance against the Bengals, Glenn on Monday refused to say who he would roll with in Week 10. Glenn has thoroughly enjoyed leaving the media in the dark when asked about his QB room, but it would be surprising to see him move off Fields following a solid Week 8 performance against the Bengals in which he threw for 244-1-0 on the way to getting the Jets their first win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ac3-d45b-affe-5fd721f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said OC Tommy Rees will take over offensive play-calling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ad4-d713-ad9e-6ed4750c0000</link>
      <description>It’s the second time in as many years that Stefanski has turned over the team’s offensive play-calling. Rees was promoted from pass game specialist to offensive coordinator this offseason and also served as offensive coordinator for Notre Dame (2020-2022) and Alabama (2023). Rees will look to improve an offense that currently ranks 30th in scoring and 31st in yards. It’s also looked far more conservative under QB Dillon Gabriel than it did under Joe Flacco, who wasn’t shy about airing it out in his four starts this season. Rees will get his first crack at play-calling in Week 10 when the Browns take on the one-win Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4ad4-d713-ad9e-6ed4750c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) was seen practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adb-d1e7-a1fa-5afb56ed0000</link>
      <description>Judkins was seen participating at the start of practice following the team’s Week 9 bye. Head coach Kevin Stefanski said Judkins would be considered “day-to-day” following his Week 8 shoulder injury, so a return to the field on Monday is a good sign for his Week 10 availability. The Browns won’t release their first injury report until Wednesday, but it sounds like Judkins has a legitimate chance to play after this promising start to the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adb-d1e7-a1fa-5afb56ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Simmons (personal) hs returned to the Chiefs after four weeks away.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</link>
      <description>Simmons was away from the Chiefs for four weeks to tend to a family issue. We don’t know the specifics beyond that, but the rookie tackle who started the first five games of the season is now set to return following his absence, and should immediately slot in as the team’s left tackle when the team returns from its Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
