<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears hosted RB Raheem Blackshear for a tryout on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-511d-d673-a39e-f59d48cb0000</link>
      <description>In addition to Blackshear, the Bears also hosted Israel Abanikanda, Montrell Johnson, and ShunDerrick Powell. Starting running back D’Andre Swift did not play in Week 9 due to a groin injury, leading to Kyle Monangai having a monstrous 29-touch workload in a win over the Bengals. The Bears may be evaluating their options should Swift miss more time, looking to add depth. None of the four backs were signed, but a situation to watch as the week of practices unfolds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-511d-d673-a39e-f59d48cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans K Ka’imi Fairbairn is dealing with a lower body injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5136-d673-a39e-f5b702780000</link>
      <description>Wilson adds that Fairbairn’s status for Week 10 is “still being determined” and the 31-year-old is receiving treatment for a lower body injury. He knocked down five kicks in the Texans’ Week 9 loss to the Broncos and is averaging 11.5 fantasy points per game this season, best among kickers. If Fairbairn misses times, fantasy managers will have a legitimate hole in their roster with his production matching that of a low-end RB2. The Texans signed Matthew Wright to the practice squad; Wright is likely to kick in place of Fairbairn if he is out Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5136-d673-a39e-f5b702780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos K Wil Lutz (illness) did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5141-d1e7-a1fa-5bebfee90000</link>
      <description>Lutz was a new addition to the practice report with an illness Tuesday. The Broncos play on a short week with a Thursday game against the Raiders, so Lutz’ addition is notable as he has two days to get ready. We often see players not miss time with an illness, so expect Lutz to play barring any setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5141-d1e7-a1fa-5bebfee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys waived RB Malik Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5169-d45b-affe-55ff0ae00000</link>
      <description>Davis was active as the backup to Javonte Williams in Week 9 over rookie Jaydon Blue and saw just one carry for three yards. He has played in three games this season, totaling three carries for six yards. The Cowboys jettisoning Davis either indicates rookie seventh-rounder Phil Mafah (shoulder) is nearing a return from injured reserve or a renewed confidence in Blue. Either way, Williams will continues to dominate backfield touches for the Cowboys. Davis is also a candidate to return via practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5169-d45b-affe-55ff0ae00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Derrick Brooks reduced Commanders LB Frankie Luvu’s one-game suspension to a $100,000 fine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5206-d45b-affe-5796e4060000</link>
      <description>Brooks, jointly appointed by the NFL and the NFLPA, reduced Luvu’s one-game suspension to a $100,000 fine. Luvu was initially suspended for “repeated violations of playing rules” after committing his third hip-drop tackle of the season in Week 9. The 29-year-old has now been fined for all three tackles, but will no longer serve a suspension. Luvu is eligible to play Week 10 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5206-d45b-affe-5796e4060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Florida Times-Union’s Ryan O’Halloran believes WR Jakobi Meyers is “not just a rental” player for the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5469-d673-a39e-f4f9bd670000</link>
      <description>The team gave up a fourth and a sixth round pick for Meyers in their trade with the Raiders Tuesday, shoring up an injury-marred receiver room ahead of their Week 10 matchup against the Texans. “They feel like they’re going to keep Jakobi Meyers here after this season, probably not even let him hit the market,” O’Halloran said, adding Meyers becomes the team’s No. 1 receiver ahead of Parker Washington with both Travis Hunter and Brian Thomas dealing with injuries. O’Halloran expects Meyers to have a “package of plays” for the Jaguars’ Week 10 game. Washington could still function as the team’s top wideout until Meyers is up to speed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5469-d673-a39e-f4f9bd670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns QB Shedeur Sanders practiced Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54b9-d1e7-a1fa-5efbdfa10000</link>
      <description>Sanders did not practice ahead of the Browns’ Week 8 loss to the Patriots and exits the team’s Week 9 bye in better health with a return to practice. Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski has made every effort to dodge questions about whether Sanders will get a shot to start this season. Stefanski said after the loss to New England that the starting QB situation was “not my focus.” Dillon Gabriel has been one of the league’s worst passers since landing the starting job. It would hardly be shocking if Sanders eventually got a start in another lost season for Cleveland. He can be rostered in deep superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54b9-d1e7-a1fa-5efbdfa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner remains in the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54d1-d673-a39e-f4d1bc2a0000</link>
      <description>Gardner, according to head coach Shane Steichen, will practice Wednesday despite being in the protocol. He hasn’t played since Week 7 and seems iffy to suit up in Week 10 against the Falcons after being traded to the Colts on Tuesday. Steichen said Gardner would likely suit up against Atlanta if he clears concussion protocol. While Gardner’s early-career play has fallen off a bit over the past couple years, he’ll be a marked upgrade for an injury-riddled Colts secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54d1-d673-a39e-f4d1bc2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a great development as the Bucs come out of their bye week. There was hope Irving would be back at practice ahead of Tampa’s Week 10 game against the Patriots after being sidelined more more than a month with foot and shoulder injuries. If Irving can’t get in a limited practice Thursday or Friday, he’ll likely miss Week 10, leaving Rachaad White as the team’s lead back. White, who has 67 touches over his four games as the Bucs’ starter, would be a top-20 fantasy option against New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54e3-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb6a0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</link>
      <description>Godwin continues to sit with a lingering fibula injury, even coming out of Tampa’s Week 9 bye. He would appear to be a long shot to suit up for Week 10 against New England unless he can practice tomorrow or Friday. Godwin hasn’t played since early October. Returning from a major 2024 ankle injury, he has six catches on 14 targets this season. Sterling Shepard and Tez Johnson could continue as Tampa starters this week if Godwin remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-54ed-d673-a39e-f4fde0a10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
