<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall (knee) is active for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2125-dab4-a3fb-bb75207c0000</link>
      <description>Tight end Mason Taylor is also active, as expected. Expect both players to be heavily involved this week with Garrett Wilson and Josh Reynolds out. Hall remains in the RB1 ranks while Taylor is a high-risk TE1. Inactive for the Jets are CB Sauce Gardner, QB Tyrod Taylor, WR Garrett Wilson, KR Kene Nwangwu, DT Jay Tufel,e TE Stone Smartt and LB Kobe King.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2125-dab4-a3fb-bb75207c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared QB Bryce Young, WR Hunter Renfrow, RB DeeJay Dallas, OL Nick Samac, TE James Mitchell, DT Cam Jackson, and DT Jaden Crumedy inactive for Week 8 against the Bills</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212a-dab4-a3fb-bb7a66ea0000</link>
      <description>This is the second week in a row that the Panthers have made Renfrow a healthy inactive with Jalen Coker back from the IR. Coker will continue to see essentially all the slot snaps, but he has a really tough matchup against Taron Johnson, who is one of the best slot corners in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212a-dab4-a3fb-bb7a66ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared QB Lamar Jackson, SS Sanoussi Kane, CB Jaire Alexander, OG Emery Jones, OT Carson Vinson, WR Devontez Walker, and DT Aeneas Peebles inactive for Week 9 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-deb1-a39b-212fe5ae0000</link>
      <description>The big name here is Jackson, who will now miss a third-straight game with the hamstring injury he suffered in Week 4 against the Chiefs. The league is investigating the team’s handling of Jackson on last week’s injury report after he was listed as a full participant on Friday despite only taking reps with the scout team. The 1-5 Ravens are in true must-win territory on Sunday and will look to veteran Tyler Huntley to lead them to victory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-deb1-a39b-212fe5ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared QB Michael Penix, WR Drake London, EDGE Jalon Walker, CB Billy Bowman, OL Michael Jerrell, DL LaCale London, and DL Zach Harrison inactive for Week 8 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b8c460000</link>
      <description>Penix was reported to be out multiple times over the weekend, so the news doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Kirk Cousins will make his first start of the year. He will do so without his top receiver. Drake London was a late addition to the injury report this week and will now miss today’s game because of a hip issue. Cousins is a low-end QB2 for Superflex purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b8c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared WR A.J. Brown, OLB Azeez Ojulari, CB Adoree’ Jackson, C Cam Jurgens, and QB Sam Howell inactive for Week 8 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2119-d5d8-a3ff-f9798ee70000</link>
      <description>Brown is expected to return after the team’s Week 9 bye. DeVonta Smith becomes an elite fantasy play with Brown sidelined, going against a middling New York coverage unit. Dallas Goedert profiles as a top-five tight end play with Brown out. Philly’s secondary could continue to struggle with Jackson sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2119-d5d8-a3ff-f9798ee70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared DE Keion White, S Kyle Dugger, LB Caleb Murphy, DT Eric Gregory, OL Caedan Wallace, WR Efton Chism, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 8 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-d5d8-a3ff-f969e6580000</link>
      <description>Dugger is set to miss Week 8 with a knee issue that kept him limited in practice and landed him with a questionable tag heading into Sunday. Meanwhile, White is a surprise healthy scratch. Both White and Dugger could be on the trade block ahead of the November 4th trade deadline, but for now the Pats make both inactive against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2129-d5d8-a3ff-f969e6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is active for Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212f-deb1-a39b-212fc4380000</link>
      <description>Njoku was listed as questionable after a week’s worth of limited practices due to a knee injury he suffered in Week 6. He missed Week 7 against the Dolphins, but is now back for Week 8 against the Patriots. Rookie Harold Fannin’s presence makes the waters murky for Njoku’s fantasy value, but he is a solid low-end fantasy TE1 for this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212f-deb1-a39b-212fc4380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared QB Quinn Ewers, DB Elijah Campbell, CB Juju Brents, S Jordan Colbert, WR Tahj Washington, DT Zeek Biggers, and TE Julian Hill inactive for Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b42170000</link>
      <description>Ewers is back to QB3 duties this week after getting a few reps in garbage time against the Browns in Week 7. Zach Wilson will back up Tua Tagovailoa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-212b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b42170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) is active for Week 8 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2131-d245-adfb-b57f85430000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson missed last week’s game against the Steelers, but a Thursday showdown was always going to be a hard turnaround for him to make. The mini-bye was more than enough to get him back on the field for Week 8, just in time to terrorize Justin Fields. Inactive for the Bengals are CB Marco Wilson, OL Matt Lee, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DT McKinnley Jackson, and DE Cam Sample.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2131-d245-adfb-b57f85430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared S Jevón Holland, WR Jalin Hyatt, CB Paulson Adebo, T James Hudson III, DL Chauncey Golston, OL Evan Neal, and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2134-dab4-a3fb-bb74105e0000</link>
      <description>Holland continues to deal with a lingering knee injury. The absence of Holland and Adebo could make for a good matchup for Jalen Hurts and the Philly pass catchers. The Eagles have been far more pass heavy than usual in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2134-dab4-a3fb-bb74105e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
