<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 04:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a745-deb6-a7fd-f7df1e180000</link>
      <description>It is time to make backup plans. Bowers practiced in full last week. He worryingly kicked off Week 5 with a limited session and was unable to practice at all today. No setbacks have been reported. One wonders if he indeed suffered one, though technically this could be precautionary. Raiders backup TE Michael Mayer (concussion) remains limited. Both players are on the wrong side of questionable for Week 5 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a745-deb6-a7fd-f7df1e180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a717-deb6-a7fd-f7df5c6c0000</link>
      <description>This is, unfortunately, a new injury for the Raiders’ stalwart pass rusher and he appears to have suffered it in practice. He should be considered questionable to play in Week 5 against the Colts. It would be impossible for the Raiders to replace his productivity if he is ruled out. Crosby ranks and/or ties for first on the team in quarterback pressures (16), sacks (two) and tackles (eight).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a717-deb6-a7fd-f7df5c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that “there is a real chance” TE George Kittle (hamstring) returns for the 49ers’ game against the Buccaneers in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a74c-dca3-a9fb-bfdd0bfb0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that Kittle “has had no setbacks” in his recovery from the hamstring strain he suffered early in September. This would be a hugely positive development for a 49ers squad jockeying for first place in the NFC West despite experiencing myriad star-play injuries. Kittle would immediately vault back into the elite TE1 tier if active next week, likely catching passes from capable fill-in starter Mac Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a74c-dca3-a9fb-bfdd0bfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that 49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) is considered “week-to-week” after suffering a setback in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a754-d6e9-af9d-afd4d20f0000</link>
      <description>Last week, Purdy reportedly “got hit the same way” that he did when he initially suffered the injury. He reported soreness the next day and underwent an MRI to confirm that a re-injury had occurred. On the plus side, it is not considered a “major, major” re-injury, and the 49ers likely would have placed Purdy on injured reserve before Thursday Night Football kicks off if they expected him to miss more than three games, though Rapoport adds that Purdy’s Week 6 availability is already in question. Mac Jones should be added by quarterback-needy squads in all formats, though he will likely remain in the QB2 rankings tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a754-d6e9-af9d-afd4d20f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) “could be back” for the 49ers’ Week 6 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a75d-d95b-addb-ef5f2dc70000</link>
      <description>49ers TE George Kittle (hamstring) and WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) could also return, which is good news for a team that is expected to be without Brock Purdy in the short term after the starting quarterback aggravated his turf toe injury in Week 4. Pearsall’s 327 receiving yards rank fourth among NFL wide receivers, though he has not yet scored a touchdown, which could afford savvy fantasy managers a one-week buy-low opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a75d-d95b-addb-ef5f2dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) “could be back” for the 49ers’ Week 6 game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a760-deb6-a7fd-f7ff51840000</link>
      <description>The 49ers are expected to be without Brock Purdy (toe) for one or more games after the starting quarterback suffered a re-injury in Week 4. Potentially getting Jennings, TE George Kittle (hamstring) and WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) would significantly stabilize the 49ers’ turbulent situation. Continue stashing Jennings on benches. He should return to his typical WR4/FLEX status soon enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a760-deb6-a7fd-f7ff51840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that 49ers WR Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is “still weeks away” from returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a768-d6e9-af9d-aff8eba30000</link>
      <description>Aiyuk’s recovery from ACL and MCL tears suffered in Week 7, 2024, continues. The remaining 49ers pass catchers are only in moderately better health, with TE George Kittle (hamstring), WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) and WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) currently rehabbing injuries of their own. Hopefully, Aiyuk can return before too long. Until then, he remains stashed on injured reserve roster spots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a768-d6e9-af9d-aff8eba30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones completed 33-of-49 passes for 342 yards and two touchdowns in the 49ers’ 26-23, Week 5 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a7ea-dca3-a9fb-bffb746d0000</link>
      <description>Playing on one leg on a short week as he filled in for even more injured starter Brock Purdy, Jones ended up throwing for the second most yards of his career. Battling through cramps and a busted plant leg — Jones’ left foot was coming down like it was landing in a bed of nails — Jones relentlessly targeted emergency No. 1 wideout Kendrick Bourne, fighting the veteran warhorse for 10/142. He also directed the ball Christian McCaffrey’s way eight times for 82 yards and a score. In other words, he understood the assignment with George Kittle, Ricky Pearsall and Jauan Jennings all sidelined. Frankly heroic stuff, both from Jones and coach Kyle Shanahan. Shanny comes with his annoying habits and contrivances, but it was quite the feat to pull out a road win this short-handed on three days rest. The Niners now get a hard-earned 10-day break to heal up for a Tampa road trip. Your guess is as good as ours whether it will be Purdy or Jones under center. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a7ea-dca3-a9fb-bffb746d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford completed 30-of-47 passes for 389 yards and three touchdowns in the Rams’ 26-23, Week 5 overtime loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a82f-dca3-a9fb-bdbf8f1e0000</link>
      <description>Making his 227th start, Stafford’s 389 yards ended up being the 13th most of his career. The fact that those numbers came in a loss was the result of two back-breaking fumbles by the Rams’ running backs, and Stafford’s own slow start. Inaccurate in the first half, he entered the break with only 109 yards. He obviously made up for it and then some in the final two-plus quarters, but the Rams couldn’t get over the hump vs. a 49ers team starting second and third-stringers at seemingly every other position. Extremely frustrating, though Stafford continues to be largely dazzling after missing the majority of training camp with a back injury. He now gets his first extended break of the season, rejoining the fray in 10 days for a Ravens road trip where he may or may not be trading blows with Lamar Jackson (hamstring).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a82f-dca3-a9fb-bdbf8f1e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
