<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RG Mekhi Becton (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b62-d1e7-a1fa-5bea55ce0000</link>
      <description>Becton’s continued participation is a positive, but it would be great to see him upgrade to full participation on Friday. Chargers backup OT Bobby Hart (knee/ankle) remains sidelined, unfortunately. That Chargers’ offensive line is in rough shape, though the team has effectively navigated offensive tackle issues in the past. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b62-d1e7-a1fa-5bea55ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b65-d45b-affe-5ff72a0f0000</link>
      <description>Brown told reporters earlier today that he will play on Monday night. His full practice participation supports that. Brown has been a volatile producer this season, but he is seemingly healthy, coming off the team’s Week 9 bye. He finished as a WR1 in Week 8 and can be started as a WR2 with WR1 upside this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b65-d45b-affe-5ff72a0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (groin) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b37-d713-ad9e-7f7720840000</link>
      <description>Barkley’s pre-bye groin injury in Week 8 caused a scare, thrusting backup RB Tank Bigsby to the top of many waiver wire bids. It appears as though Bigsby has been reduced to a high-value bench stash, though, with Barkley practicing in full to begin the week. The Eagles’ No. 1 running back can be started as a borderline RB1/2 on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b37-d713-ad9e-7f7720840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (ribs) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b72-d1e7-a1fa-5bfae6dc0000</link>
      <description>Ever willing to play through injury, even reportedly injured ribs, Nacua is firmly on track to play in Week 10 against the 49ers, whose injury-depleted pass rush should struggle to pressure QB Matthew Stafford. Expect Nacua to perform as an elite WR1, per usual, while Stafford slings it from cozy pockets on Sunday. Hopefully, we see Nacua once again practice in full on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b72-d1e7-a1fa-5bfae6dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport that the Colts believe Daniel Jones is their “franchise” quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b77-d45b-affe-5ff753bc0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport made the comments in a segment explaining the Colts’ thought process behind shipping two first-round picks out to acquire CB Sauce Gardner. Jones’ starting job is evidently secure, regardless of QB Anthony Richardson’s health down the road. That said, Jones is only under contract through the end of this season. If Rapoport’s report is true, we should expect to see the front office sign him to a long-term deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b77-d45b-affe-5ff753bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles OLB Nolan Smith (triceps) is practicing in full for Week 10 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b7d-d673-a39e-fffd6f1b0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles activated Smith’s 21-day practice window on Tuesday, and he appears to be on track to retake the field on Monday night. In late September, Smith re-injured the same triceps muscle he tore in Super Bowl LIX. Fortunately, he rehab plan has evidently gone according to plan, as a return “around” the Eagles’ Week 9 bye was the goal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b7d-d673-a39e-fffd6f1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said that the team will “make a decision tomorrow afternoon” regarding whether QB Brock Purdy (toe) “will suit up” in Week 10 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b85-d45b-affe-5f97fe310000</link>
      <description>Per Shanahan, Purdy is “getting closer to returning.” Just last week, the 49ers decided not to have Purdy active, even for backup duties, after practicing in a limited capacity all week. He remains limited through two Week 10 practices. While Shanahan’s words are encouraging, caution is advised. Stay tuned, tomorrow afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b85-d45b-affe-5f97fe310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Buccaneers are “thinking” WR Chris Godwin (fibula) could return in late November or in December.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b76-d713-ad9e-7f7649940000</link>
      <description>Godwin has not yet returned to practice, so missing Week 10 against the Patriots makes sense. Fowler adds that RB Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) could sit out in Week 10 as well. The Buccaneers face the Saints on December 7th, at which point, Godwin should apparently be back. Unfortunately, that is five games away, which could prove costly for fantasy managers who continue to stash him. He does not need to be rostered at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b76-d713-ad9e-7f7649940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared WR Marvin Mims Jr., CB Pat Surtain II, TE Nate Adkins, RB Jaleel McLaughlin, OLB Que Robinson, DL Sav’ion Jones and DL Jordan Jackson inactive for Week 10 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5bef6ad40000</link>
      <description>Mims (concussion) and Surtain (pectoral) both missed the Broncos’ Week 9 game against the Texans as well. The Broncos’ top-tier defense should be okay in this one, but it is an unfortunate missed opportunity for Mims’ fantasy managers. The speedy wide receiver would have had decent odds of producing an explosive gain or two against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5bef6ad40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Zamir White, TE Carter Runyon, G Caleb Rogers, DT JJ Pegues and DL Leki Fotu inactive in Week 10 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b94-d45b-affe-5f96eca90000</link>
      <description>The Raiders get back S Lonnie Johnson, who broke his leg in training camp. Rookies, DT Tonka Hemingway and WR D’Onte Thornton, are active tonight as well. The Raiders will ostensibly use the next few weeks to see if one or more of their rookie wide receivers, including Jack Bech, can unseat one of head coach Pete Carroll’s favorites, WR Tyler Lockett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b94-d45b-affe-5f96eca90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
