<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:04:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>JK Dobbins had 11 rushes for 83 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 3 loss against the Chargers, adding one catch for one yard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eac-d6a5-adff-feedac700000</link>
      <description>Dobbins once again functioned as the Broncos’ lead back over rookie RB RJ Harvey. Dobbins handled 11 of the team’s 12 running back rushes, including red zone work. Dobbins had a 41-yard rush in the second half and crept into the end zone for a short score in a sudden offensive burst from the mostly lifeless Denver offense. Though Harvey continues as the team’s preferred pass-catching back, Dobbins is usable as a top-24 weekly option who should continue seeing goal line looks. Dobbins has a prime Week 4 matchup against a soft Bengals front seven.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eac-d6a5-adff-feedac700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said initial tests did indicate Nick Bosa suffered an ACL injury in Week 3’s win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ead-d93f-ad9d-7eefc4100000</link>
      <description>Shanahan won’t fully rule out an ACL injury, saying that there “is concern because of how he feels,” but noted that tests don’t indicate an ACL injury. The veteran pass rusher exited in the first half of Sunday’s win over the Cardinals to be evaluated and didn’t return to the field. Shanahan said the team is hoping for “good news tomorrow,” which is when we would expect to learn more about where things stand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ead-d93f-ad9d-7eefc4100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker III rushed 16 times for 38 yards and two touchdowns in the Seahawks’ Week 3 win over the Saints, adding one reception for 12 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e9e-d93f-ad9d-7edf02040000</link>
      <description>In three games this season, the Seahawks have had four instances where a running back totals double-digit carry counts while averaging less than 3.0 yards per carry. Walker accounts for two such instances. To be fair to him, Walker had a 20-yard run called back due to holding today and he averaged 8.1 yards per carry just last week, but Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak must identify and correct his ground game’s consistency issues. Walker remains RB2-viable against the Cardinals next week. Zach Charbonnet (foot) missed practice all week, but was able to participate in an extensive pre-game warmup today. He faces a short turnaround in Week 4, with the NFC West showdown taking place on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e9e-d93f-ad9d-7edf02040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb said he “absolutely” feels he can play in Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eaf-d6a5-adff-feeff71e0000</link>
      <description>FOX Sports’ Jay Glazer reported that Lamb suffered a high-ankle sprain, but he will undergo further testing to confirm the severity of his injury. Lamb exited Week 3’s game against the Bears in the first quarter after having his ankle rolled up on. He briefly returned to the field only to leave and remain permanently sidelined in the 31-14 defeat. Lamb’s early optimism is a good sign for his Week 4 availability, but the real indicator will be his practice status for the week. If Lamb can play, we would expect him to take it easy in the week and possible be a game-time decision, which would be inconvenient timing for fantasy managers given that the Cowboys and Packers play on Sunday Night Football on NBC in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eaf-d6a5-adff-feeff71e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Ferguson caught 13-of-14 targets for 82 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 3 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eab-d93f-ad9d-7eefe3170000</link>
      <description>It all came together for Ferguson, who caught short passes, and more short passes, and a few more short passes as the Cowboys dinked and dunked together this obscene box score line. CeeDee Lamb (13/98/2 in Week 18 of 2023) and Alvin Kamara (13/33/0 in Week 4 of 2023) are the only players this decade to go over 13 catches without reaching 100 yards. So you can definitely say that Jake Ferguson is one of the three best players mentioned in that stat. This is a legendary heist of a PPR scam, something that would make 2024 Wan’Dale Robinson blush, and it figures to continue against the Packers next week if Lamb misses more time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eab-d93f-ad9d-7eefe3170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught 4-of-6 targets for 38 yards in the 49ers’ Week 3 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eaf-d6a5-adff-feeff7c30000</link>
      <description>Bourne stepped in as the 49ers’ No. 2 receiver with Jauan Jennings inactive for this game. He was the only wide receiver other than Ricky Pearsall to see more than one target. Bourne is a better real-life player than a fantasy asset. Even if Jennings remains out for Week 4, Bourne will top out at a WR5 ranking versus Jacksonville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eaf-d6a5-adff-feeff7c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens caught 5-of-9 targets for 68 yards and a touchdown in the Cowboys’ Week 3 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb2-dfde-a1bd-7ebf698a0000</link>
      <description>It wasn’t quite the Week 2 performance as far as yards left on the table, but Pickens again had three red zone targets and remains a good bet to keep finding the paint. If CeeDee Lamb is ready for Week 4, Pickens will remain a WR3 candidate in a tough matchup against the Packers. If Lamb is out, Pickens might find himself on the WR2 line just for the sake of added volume.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb2-dfde-a1bd-7ebf698a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 2-of-3 targets for 21 yards in the 49ers’ Week 3 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb3-d1b3-a5dd-6ff32b910000</link>
      <description>Tonges is the 49ers’ top tight end with George Kittle on injured reserve, but there isn’t much fantasy value to be had in Kittle’s wake. Tonges was the only San Francisco tight end to earn a target in this game and still managed a measly eight percent target share. Tonges is not on the fantasy radar heading into Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb3-d1b3-a5dd-6ff32b910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KaVontae Turpin caught 2-of-3 targets for 64 yards in the Cowboys’ Week 3 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb6-dfde-a1bd-7ebf0c860000</link>
      <description>Turpin remains explosive, he hauled in a 27-yard sideline ball from Dak Prescott despite getting his bell rung in the third quarter, then found the rest of it on Prescott’s last drive, a 37-yard catch. It sure seems like the Cowboys can create some fun and interesting things with Turpin, which is why it’s very frustrating that he was limited to 49 snaps after CeeDee Lamb went down, with Jalen Tolbert getting 65 snaps to go 3/24 on six targets. Turpin should be on the monitor list, but isn’t an urgent pick up or start at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb6-dfde-a1bd-7ebf0c860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 28-of-39 passes for 218 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Saints’ 44-13, Week 4 loss to the Seahawks, adding two rushes for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb2-d1b3-a5dd-6ff3d6cf0000</link>
      <description>Rattler deserves credit for playing fearlessly. He was pressured on a season-high 17 dropbacks and admirably completed 10-of-13 qualifying passes for 94 yards, one touchdown and one interception. He was throwing on the run constantly. Unfortunately, the Seahawks jumped out to a 21-0 lead in the first quarter, which allowed Seattle’s defense to largely disregard the run game. Rattler should have a similarly difficult game script on his hands when the Saints travel to Buffalo for a bout with the Bills in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6eb2-d1b3-a5dd-6ff3d6cf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
