<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brenton Strange caught 6-of-7 targets for 61 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 3 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e38-dfde-a1bd-7ebd40190000</link>
      <description>He broke tackles when he got the ball, he was a key target for Trevor Lawrence ... at some point with how bad everyone else looks on offense, it becomes strange that Strange is not really a focal point. He’ll be a viable TE1 streamer in Week 4 against the 49ers, but hasn’t been much of a red-zone threat to date and fantasy managers would be hoping for that to change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e38-dfde-a1bd-7ebd40190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 13 times for 72 yards in the Falcons’ Week 3 loss to the Panthers, adding five catches for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e31-d1b3-a5dd-6f71ec140000</link>
      <description>Robinson was once again the Falcons’ best offensive weapon, accounting for a third of the team’s total yards. He was the target of several Michael Penix checkdowns while he also tore through several tacklers in space to average 5.5 yards per carry. Robinson dominated running back snaps on a day where the Falcons had to play catch-up the entire game. The offense never really came close to scoring, but Robinson is the RB1 and will be the go-to in passing-down situations. He is a fantasy RB1 heading into Week 4 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e31-d1b3-a5dd-6f71ec140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins caught 1-of-2 targets for 15 yards in the Bengals’ Week 3 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3e-d1b3-a5dd-6f7fcee90000</link>
      <description>Already off to a slow start, Higgins’ slump deepened considerably without Joe Burrow under center this afternoon. Aside from the catch, Higgins’ only other play of note was taking a helmet-to-helmet shot in the second quarter to draw a Vikings penalty. Higgins was not one of the three Bengals pass catchers to lose a fumble, but he got out-targeted 6-2 by Ja’Marr Chase, who was also featured the last time Jake Browning filled in for Burrow. This is going to be a rocky road, especially with the Bengals headed back on the road to face another elite defense in Week 4 in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3e-d1b3-a5dd-6f7fcee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku caught 5-of-7 targets for 40 yards in the Browns’ Week 3 win against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e41-d6a5-adff-fec501af0000</link>
      <description>Njoku led the Browns in targets while running a pass route on 34 of the team’s 46 drop backs. Harold Fannin, meanwhile, had a quiet day with three grabs for 25 yards on five targets from Joe Flacco. Njoku now has a dozen catches over the season’s first three games — not exactly the kind of production fantasy managers banked on when they took him in drafts last month. Even so, Njoku should be a top-15 weekly tight end play and has a nice Week 4 matchup against the pass-funnel Detroit defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e41-d6a5-adff-fec501af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed one time for four yards in the Falcons’ Week 3 loss to the Panthers, adding one catch for zero yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3e-d93f-ad9d-7eff29b50000</link>
      <description>Allgeier saw just two touches for four total yards in the Falcons’ blowout loss to the Panthers. As the team’s grinder back, he saw little run as the offense played from behind the entire game. The Falcons pulled their starters late and rookie Nathan Carter got all the touches on the final Atlanta possession. Allgeier saw just six snaps on the day and although better days are ahead, he is far behind Robinson in terms of fantasy utility. He is a handcuff value for fantasy purposes moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3e-d93f-ad9d-7eff29b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) left Chicago’s Week 3 game against the Cowboys and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e44-d93f-ad9d-7ec7e8360000</link>
      <description>He had a 31-yard catch on three targets before leaving, ceding a touchdown to Cole Kmet in an ideal game script. It’s been a disappointing first month for Loveland so far, as preseason concerns that he’d be splitting time have mostly been validated and the Bears have not fed tight ends as often as they could have.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e44-d93f-ad9d-7ec7e8360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerome Ford caught 4-of-4 targets for ten yards in the Browns’ Week 3 win against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e45-d93f-ad9d-7ec7c1ac0000</link>
      <description>Ford did not log a carry as Quinshon Judkins had 18 of the team’s 19 rushing attempts on the day. Ford led the Cleveland backfield with both routes and targets and appears to be the preferred pass-catching option, for now. Ford won’t have much fantasy value as long as Judkins is healthy and functioning as the team’s lead back. He should be monitored on the waiver wire for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e45-d93f-ad9d-7ec7c1ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase Brown rushed 10 times for three yards in the Bengals’ Week 3 loss to the Vikings, adding four receptions for 17 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e46-dfde-a1bd-7ecf3c9f0000</link>
      <description>Alrighty then. Brown at least wasn’t one of four Bengals to turn the ball over, though he did fumble. His team just recovered it. Brown has been stupendously awful through three games thus far, taking the rock 47 times for 93 yards (1.97 YPC). Things, obviously, were even worse this afternoon with Jake Browning under center instead of Joe Burrow. Brown can’t afford to be a focus on the opposing defense. Now he is. We would say Cincy needs to get another back involved, but there’s no viable alternatives, especially since Samaje Perine injured his wrist in Minnesota. Brown will be a lower-end RB2 for Week 4 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e46-dfde-a1bd-7ecf3c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-4 targets for 32 yards in the Steelers’ Week 3 win over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d200d0000</link>
      <description>It was another quiet showing for the former Seahawks, but, just as he did last week, Metcalf did good by his fantasy managers with a receiving score. Metcalf connected with Aaron Rodgers on a jump-ball in the end zone, a play Rodgers has hit Davante Adams on countless times. Metcalf has topped out at four catches in a game this season, but he can get by on low volume with chunk plays and receiving scores. He remains on the WR2/3 border for his week 4 matchup with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e3c-d1b3-a5dd-6f7d200d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Carter rushed seven times for 46 yards and a fumble in the Falcons’ Week 3 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e46-d1b3-a5dd-6f7729820000</link>
      <description>Carter came into the game late with the Falcons already down big towards the end of the fourth quarter. He handled seven carries for 46 yards, but fumbled on his final touch of the game. It was the undrafted rookie’s first NFL action on offense, and though the fumble was not a great way to end the day, he was efficient on the ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6e46-d1b3-a5dd-6f7729820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
