<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapaport reports Steelers OL Max Scharping (knee) tore his ACL and will miss the remainder of the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e29-d1b3-a5dd-5f79bb100000</link>
      <description>Scharping has bounced around as veteran depth since playing out his four-year rookie deal with the Texans and, later, Bengals. He’s played just 20 snaps the last two years. He’ll likely be on the practice squad/end-of-roster shuttle again in 2026 if his knee cooperates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e29-d1b3-a5dd-5f79bb100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB TJ Edwards (hamstring) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e2c-d6a5-adff-feed814b0000</link>
      <description>He’s been listed with this hamstring since the very start of the season and left Week 2’s game against the Lions with the listing — it’s possible he re-aggravated it. Ruben Hyppolite II would be in line for extra work if Edwards can’t play, with Noah Sewell likely becoming the other main linebacker. Kyler Gordon (hamstring) also remained out of practice on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e2c-d6a5-adff-feed814b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (quad) was limited during practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e2b-dfde-a1bd-5eaf65b60000</link>
      <description>Swift was limited in Wednesday’s session as well. The continued participation puts him on track to play, but the fact that he remains limited indicates the injury is not a complete non-issue. Bears backup RB Kyle Monangai could handle a few extra touches against the Cowboys in Week 3 if Swift remains limited tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e2b-dfde-a1bd-5eaf65b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said he “would like” to get Ashton Jeanty around 20 carries per game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e48-d1b3-a5dd-5f7921210000</link>
      <description>“We want more of him,” Carroll said after Week 2. Jeanty saw 19 carries in Week 1, but was at 11 in Week 2 as the Raiders trailed and the team relied on other backs in catch up mode. Chip Kelly and Geno Smith, per the Las Vegas Review-Journal’s Vincent Bonsignore, wanted to get other players “more involved.” We don’t necessarily think Jeanty is a lock to get 20 touches a game, but it does make some sense to rest him in the second half of a blowout. His snap share isn’t worth worrying about. Jeanty remains on the RB2 line until we see the Las Vegas offensive line deliver him to fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e48-d1b3-a5dd-5f7921210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan Alexander believes the Texans will “likely go more to playing two running backs instead of three.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e53-d1b3-a5dd-5f730e350000</link>
      <description>There wasn’t much separation between Dare Ogunbowale and Woody Marks in training camp, but Marks had a 37-yard reception last week and played a bigger role than he had in the past. Ogunbowale has also fumbled in Week 1 and looked bad in pass protection in Week 2. Marks isn’t a FLEX play yet — he’ll probably have to outplay Chubb to get more than a third-down share — but he’s at least put himself into position to do that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e53-d1b3-a5dd-5f730e350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dfa-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb337f0000</link>
      <description>Legette experienced hamstring “soreness” after going through individual drills yesterday, so the team sidelined him for the remainder of practice. He was once again limited today, and fantasy managers can expect excessively limited production from the second-year wide receiver unless he turns things around with an unprecedented, Herculean effort moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5dfa-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb337f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts EDGE Laiatu Latu (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e63-dfde-a1bd-5eef82fa0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from Wednesday’s limited session and Latu would seem likely to play against the Titans in Week 3. Every Colts EDGE player will want a chance at Cam Ward, who has been sacked 11 times in two starts so far. CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) also practiced in full. Both players have a chance at not being on the team’s final injury report at this rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e63-dfde-a1bd-5eef82fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e53-dfde-a1bd-5edf7a2a0000</link>
      <description>Harmon could still suit up on Sunday, even if he remains limited tomorrow, but we would expect him to be on a snap count if that is the case. The Steelers need their rookie defensive tackle back badly. Porter remains sidelined by his hamstring injury and does not appear to be close to returning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e53-dfde-a1bd-5edf7a2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (foot) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e66-d6a5-adff-fee7478c0000</link>
      <description>He was limited all of last week as well with the same injury before dusting Dallas’ secondary. Don’t expect miracles in Week 3 against a more game Chiefs defense, but Robinson is firmly on the WR3/FLEX radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e66-d6a5-adff-fee7478c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (calf/groin) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e67-d6a5-adff-fee7eabd0000</link>
      <description>It looks like Slayton has a good chance to suit up after back-to-back limited practices on Wednesday and Thursday. He isn’t much of a fantasy option at this point — Russell Wilson simply hasn’t targeted him much — but having Slayton on the field will keep defenses honest in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e67-d6a5-adff-fee7eabd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
