<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders released LB Germaine Pratt.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bab3-def2-abdb-bff347bf0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Pete Carroll said during the Raiders’ Monday presser that Pratt has been let go. The veteran linebacker joined the Raiders on a one-year deal this offseason after spending the first six years of his career with the Bengals. Pratt totaled 25 tackles and one TFL in four starts with the Raiders this season, but didn’t join the team in Indy for Week 5 due to non-injury reasons. Carroll declined to get into why the Raiders released Pratt, opting to leave it at the team deciding to go in another direction. Pratt is 29 and has 92 career starts under his belt. He will likely catch on with another team in the coming days/weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bab3-def2-abdb-bff347bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Antonio Gibson suffered a torn ACL in Week 5’s win over the Bills, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bacf-db72-a199-facfefae0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots wasted little time ruling Gibson out for the remainder of Sunday’s game after he exited in the second quarter following a hard hit to his legs. Gibson is in the second year of a three-year contract he signed with the Patriots last offseason. Serving as the Patriots’ primary kick returner, the sixth-year back also rushed 25 times for 106 yards and a touchdown this season, and will hopefully be back in time for training camp next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bacf-db72-a199-facfefae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said the Ravens will “consider everything” when asked if Tyler Huntley could get snaps if Lamar Jackson (hamstring) can’t go in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae2-d94a-a79d-bbefc0960000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly a glowing endorsement of Cooper Rush after one week. Huntley was rumored to be in some goal-line packages for his ability to be a run threat, but never actually took a snap in the game. If Rush and Huntley split the load in any way in Week 6, it would be hard to recommend either of them in even the deepest fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae2-d94a-a79d-bbefc0960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants listed QB Jaxson Dart (hamstring) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae3-d94a-a79d-bbefebde0000</link>
      <description>There was no injury reported for Dart during Sunday’s loss to the Saints, so we’ll assume this is something minor unless we hear otherwise. Dart is one of two Giants starters dealing with a hamstring injury, as Darius Slayton (hamstring) was listed as a DNP on Monday. Dart and the Giants have a short week to get right ahead of Thursday night’s game with the Eagles. Even if he’s limited throughout the week, we’ll assume Dart will be good to go for Thursday’s divisional tilt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae3-d94a-a79d-bbefebde0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae5-def2-abdb-bfe5abe60000</link>
      <description>These are all projections, standard Monday-ahead-of-Thursday caveat. But this isn’t a surprising bit of news after Slayton missed the end of Week 5’s game against the Saints with a hamstring injury. He seems likely to miss Thursday night’s game against the Eagles at this point. Jaxson Dart is running out of receivers, leaving Wan’Dale Robinson a near-lock for eight or more PPR scam targets. Perhaps there would be more stream appeal for the New York tight ends as well, with neither Beaux Collins nor Jalin Hyatt offering much in limited samples on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae5-def2-abdb-bfe5abe60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants listed RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae8-d94a-a79d-bbedac740000</link>
      <description>Tracy was a DNP in two of three practices last week but managed to log a limited session on Friday. Monday isn’t an official practice day, but a limited designation on Monday is still an encouraging sign. The Giants face the Eagles on a short week as they draw the Thursday night matchup in Week 6. If Tracy does return, we would expect him to eat into Cam Skattebo’s workload, which could make both backs difficult to trust against a stout Eagles defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bae8-d94a-a79d-bbedac740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said “like all personnel decisions, we have to evaluate it” when asked about Jake Browning starting in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baec-d94a-a79d-bbedc7e80000</link>
      <description>The “evaluate it” bit is often the first step before a quarterback gets relieved of their duties. Browning’s confidence sounded shot in interviews after the game, and it would be surprising if the Bengals didn’t have a new quarterback at some point in the near future. The problem is that the only other one on their roster is Brett Rypien, and the Bengals are not often a team that has made win-now trades in search of better options. Still, throwing the “evaluate” quote out there shows that Browning won’t hold this job much longer without an immediate turnaround — if he’s given the chance — in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baec-d94a-a79d-bbedc7e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Terrion Arnold (shoulder) is going to be out for “a long time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baf3-d94a-a79d-bbff2cda0000</link>
      <description>So probably an IR stint ahead for Arnold. The Lions are down their top three cornerbacks entering the season and that should help them be more of a get-right spot for receivers going forward — as they were for Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins last week — as they flail around with Amik Robertson and depth pieces in front of Brian Branch and Kerby Joseph.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baf3-d94a-a79d-bbff2cda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Treylon Burks (collarbone) has been cleared to return to football activities.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baee-dd4c-afb9-ffef10b30000</link>
      <description>Burks was placed on the waived/injured list by the Titans following his injury in training camp. After going unclaimed, Burks is now free to sign with any team. The former first-round pick has struggled to live up to the expectations that made him the No. 18 overall pick in the 2022 NFL Draft, posting a career receiving line of 53-699-1 in 27 career games while battling multiple injuries along the way. Still only 25 years old, Burks is an ideal practice squad candidate for any team looking to improve their wide receiver room, but it’s hard to imagine him making much of an impact wherever he may land this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-baee-dd4c-afb9-ffef10b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said he’s “optimistic” about Terry McLaurin (quad) for Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb13-d94a-a79d-bb1f446f0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders do have an extra day of rest ahead of Monday Night Football. It is worth pointing out that Quinn said McLaurin was “trending in the right direction” last week before a DNP-DNP-Ruleout, so the optimism doesn’t exactly mean much until we see McLaurin in practice. Still, it doesn’t sound like this will drag on too much longer based on reports from ESPN last week and we’d anticipate McLaurin showing up in Week 6 or Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bb13-d94a-a79d-bb1f446f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
