<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Ian O’Connor reports that John Harbaugh “needed it in writing that he would report to John Mara, and not to [GM Joe] Schoen.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7b0-d56e-afff-f7f8abdc0000</link>
      <description>“This wasn’t about Schoen; the coach definitely feels he can work with the GM. Harbaugh wanted the ability to impact the entire operation, from security to training to analytics to media relations to staff size to assistant salaries to relocation expenses to you name it. And yes, in the unlikely event there’s a stalemate on draft day between Harbaugh and Schoen, there’s no longer any question who will prevail,” O’Connor writes. Well then. Joe Schoen begins the Harbaugh Era as a convenient scapegoat the second it takes more than a year to get things going in the right direction. What could go wrong for him?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7b0-d56e-afff-f7f8abdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions hired former Cardinals OC Drew Petzing as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7c2-d35e-a1bf-d7c2ee0b0000</link>
      <description>It was truly a storied courtship as the Lions ... never were directly reported to have interviewed Petzing. We’re not sure who Petzing’s agent is, but he needs to put in some work with the #sources next go around. It’s possible that Kevin Stefanski’s elevation to Falcons head coach hurried this hire along, as Petzing coached under Stefanski in Cleveland and would have been a potential offensive coordinator candidate for the Falcons as well. Petzing did not exactly oversee a complex and exciting offense in Arizona as both Kyler Murray and Marvin Harrison Jr. flatlined, though he did oversee the renaissance of the Jacoby Brissett Pass Yards Machine as well. We’re surprised this is the direction the Lions went, but as long as Dan Campbell is overseeing things, it’s hard to drastically downgrade the Lions skill position players for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7c2-d35e-a1bf-d7c2ee0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Broncos are opening the practice window for J.K. Dobbins (foot) this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7c5-d35e-a1bf-d7c70f7b0000</link>
      <description>Dobbins will have a chance to practice and suit up for the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots, something head coach Sean Payton hinted at earlier this month. Dobbins suffered a Lisfranc injury in Week 10 and has been sidelined ever since. Dobbins has rushed 153 times for 772 yards and four touchdowns this season while averaging an impressive 5.0 YPC. How this week of practice goes will likely be the deciding factor in whether or not the Broncos choose to activate him from injured reserve, but with Bo Nix (ankle) already out for the remainder of the playoffs, they will take any help they can get from other playmakers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7c5-d35e-a1bf-d7c70f7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said he’ll “use this week to evaluate the coaching staff” when asked about the status of OC Nick Caley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d4-d56e-afff-f7fcb1e70000</link>
      <description>Caley’s Texans finished 19th in DVOA in the regular season, but actually picked things up fairly well after an uninspiring 3-5 start. It would be a little surprising to see the Texans move on from the 42-year-old in his first season as an offensive coordinator, but we would have called it a little surprising to see Bobby Slowik get canned after 2024 as well. This will be a situation to watch until we get better clarity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d4-d56e-afff-f7fcb1e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans HC DeMeco Ryans said “as of right now I don’t know that” when asked if he expected Joe Mixon to remain with the team in the future.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d5-d56e-afff-f7fd5f380000</link>
      <description>Ryans continues to downplay any conversation surrounding Mixon, who missed all of the 2025 season with a foot injury. It was reported in late December that some of Mixon’s issues stemmed from some procedures he got “on his own, away from the Texans,” which could complicate his future with the team and the contract he signed that will keep him with the team through 2026. It’s impossible to say where things truly stand with Mixon and the Texans right now after Ryans and the team spent a full season avoiding the topic, but it seems unlikely he would return to the team next season given how things have played out since Mixon was mysteriously injured last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d5-d56e-afff-f7fd5f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said “I’m not getting into that right now” when asked about an extension for QB C.J. Stroud.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d8-d968-a19b-dff9166c0000</link>
      <description>It is just a day after the Texans’ season ended, so it’s an unsurprising non-answer. It’s still noteworthy that the answer wasn’t exactly an affirmative, no-questions-asked, yes. “There is a lot of negative talk right now and he understands that,” Ryans said in an answer about how his message to Stroud is to block out the noise. Stroud’s catastrophic playoff performance will likely leave him getting his fifth-year option picked up this offseason, but neither Stroud nor the Texans should exactly be giddy about negotiating off his 2025 season. We’d be surprised if a long-term extension was coming before the conclusion of 2026 — if it comes at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7d8-d968-a19b-dff9166c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said he’s “excited to see [Tank Dell] back on the field next year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7dc-d35e-a1bf-d7deb5d10000</link>
      <description>Dell missed the entire season after tearing his ACL, MCL, and LCL against the Chiefs in Week 16 of the 2024 season. The fact that the head coach is still optimistic is noteworthy, and Dell probably will slot in as Houston’s No. 2 receiver in 2026 assuming he bounces back and is fully recovered from the surgeries. Dell’s return, should it come to pass, will be a development that will make it hard to see Jayden Higgins or Jaylin Noel boosting their fantasy stock in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7dc-d35e-a1bf-d7deb5d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said he’d “watch” Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb as a potential candidate for the Bills head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7eb-d35e-a1bf-d7ebd7070000</link>
      <description>“He’s really close to Josh Allen,” Pelissero says while noting the Bills are focusing on a more offensive-minded coach. Apparently multiple teams are waiting for the Broncos to be eliminated to get Webb in for a second interview per Pelissero’s reporting. Based on that, it sure seems likely that the 30-year-old former NFL quarterback stands a good chance of leaving the cycle with a head-coaching gig. The NFL Network reporter also says that Joe Brady is “a candidate, but I don’t know if he isthecandidate” in Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7eb-d35e-a1bf-d7ebd7070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero says “the teams to watch” for former Bills head coach Sean McDermott are Pittsburgh, Baltimore, and Tennessee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d804-d968-a19b-d8f52a8b0000</link>
      <description>“It doesn’t make a ton of sense for him to go into a total rebuild” per Pelissero, who rules out Arizona and Las Vegas as landing spots for McDermott. Pelissero mentions that McDermott would be outside of the normal bucket the Steelers hire from, and says Baltimore “makes a lot of sense” while the Titans brass has mutual ties to McDermott from his work with Andy Reid. Seeing McDermott coach Lamar Jackson might be the funniest idea we’ve ever heard of, so of course we’re for it. The Titans also seem like a reasonable landing spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d804-d968-a19b-d8f52a8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Vikings DC Brian Flores will interview with the Steelers on Tuesday for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d807-d35e-a1bf-ddc7d3780000</link>
      <description>Flores has long been considered a potential replacement for Mike Tomlin, and will now have a chance to meet with the team he spent the 2022 season with under Tomlin. The former Dolphins head coach has spent the last three seasons as the Vikings’ defensive coordinator, and over that span, elevated the defense from one of the worst in the league to being a top-10 unit. In addition to fielding head coaching requests from the Steelers and Ravens, Flores has also met with the Commanders to discuss their defensive coordinator vacancy. If he’s unable to land a head coaching job, the option to return to Minnesota remains on the table, but Flores is in high demand after turning in one of his strongest years as a coordinator to date.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d807-d35e-a1bf-ddc7d3780000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
