<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy completed 13-of-20 passes for 143 yards and two touchdowns in the Vikings’ 27-24, Week 1 win over the Bears, adding 25 yards and a touchdown on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9a-db7b-a5dd-ac9ec45b0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy and the Minnesota offense went three-and-out on four of their first five possessions in the first half, and started the third quarter with a pick-six to fall into a 17-6 deficit. They would then go three-and-out their next two possessions before finding the end zone on their first three possessions of the fourth quarter to steal victory from the clutches of defeat. McCarthy connected with Justin Jefferson for his first professional touchdown pass before hitting running back Aaron Jones down the sideline for his second score. He would take on a rushing score 14 yards out on the next possession after scoring just three times on the ground during his collegiate career. The Vikings would hold on to get to 1-0 ahead of their home opener against the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9a-db7b-a5dd-ac9ec45b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed 15 times for 68 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9f-d332-a1fd-bebf8b0b0000</link>
      <description>Mason out-carried veteran Aaron Jones 15 to eight and averaged a solid 4.5 yards per carry in the win, making good on offseason promises that he would be heavily involved in the offense in 2025. The fact that he managed 15 carries in a game in which the Vikings trailed until the fourth quarter speaks volumes to his presence as the primary rusher after being acquired by the Vikings this offseason, and he is likely to remain heavily involved when the Vikings host the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9f-d332-a1fd-bebf8b0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones rushed eight times for 23 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears, adding 44 yards and a touchdown on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca2-de13-afdd-6eeb3e430000</link>
      <description>Jones managed just eight carries to the 15 of Jordan Mason but cashed in on a 27-yard receiving touchdown in the fourth quarter in the comeback victory. His 44 yards tied with Justin Jefferson for the team lead on a night the Vikings failed to get much going until the final frame. Jones is likely to cede more work on the ground than he has in the past after the team acquired Mason this offseason, but he remains an integral piece of the offense via his dynamism through the air. Jones’ next chance to return viable fantasy counting stats comes in week 2 when the Vikings host the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca2-de13-afdd-6eeb3e430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 4-of-7 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca5-de13-afdd-6eef5e070000</link>
      <description>The Vikings went three-and-out on six of their first nine possessions, with the other three resulting in two field goals and a pick-six thrown by J.J. McCarthy. Jefferson understandably had little production through the team’s early struggles but ignited a ferocious comeback with a fourth quarter touchdown in tight coverage to the middle of the end zone. Fantasy managers were surely wishing for more from their first-round pick but the touchdown eased the pain slightly. Jefferson will look to return to dominance when the Vikings host the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca5-de13-afdd-6eef5e070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 3-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca8-de13-afdd-6eeb95fb0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson saw little fantasy success on a night the Minnesota offense went three-and-out on six of their first nine possessions, failing to find the end zone until the fourth quarter. They would score on three fourth quarter possessions to snatch the win from the Bears, but Hockenson was relegated to blocking duties as the Vikings looked to establish their ground game to open up play action late. That venture would be fruitful on the scoreboard but left Hockenson’s fantasy managers yearning for more from the veteran tight end. His next opportunity to return usable counting stats comes in Week 2 when the Vikings host the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca8-de13-afdd-6eeb95fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Thielen failed to catch his only target in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</link>
      <description>Thielen saw a reduced snap rate in a game the Vikings preferred to operate from heavy personnel after continued shortcomings, eventually breaking through with three fourth quarter touchdowns to steal the win from the Bears. Thielen would make his mark felt on the field by catching a two-point conversion on the team’s penultimate score for his only counting stats of the game. Thielen remains an iffy fantasy bet ahead of a Week 2 meeting with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports 49ers WR Jauan Jennings seems to have avoided a serious shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2edc-de13-afdd-6edfd7720000</link>
      <description>The Niners finally get a little bit of good news after a Week 1 win in which they may have lost both George Kittle (hamstring) and Brock Purdy (toe/shoulder). An MRI on Jennings’ shoulder injury did not show extensive damage. We could see him suit up for the team’s Week 2 game against the Saints if he’s able to practice in a limited fashion late in the week. Jennings and Ricky Pearsall are set to dominate wideout targets in the Niners offense for as long as Kittle is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2edc-de13-afdd-6edfd7720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed S Jabrill Peppers, formerly of the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ee6-d332-a1fd-bef669450000</link>
      <description>Peppers, released by the Pats in August, will join a Steelers secondary that was ripped by Justin Fields in Week 1. They’ll be without S DeShon Elliott for at least a couple weeks after Elliott injured his knee against the Jets. The 29-year-old safety started 26 games over the last three seasons with the Patriots. In 2024, Peppers had 20 solo tackles and two tackles for a loss. He has seven interceptions over eight NFL seasons. Peppers will likely be a rotational player for the Steelers if he suits up in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ee6-d332-a1fd-bef669450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports S DeShon Elliott (knee) will miss “a couple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ef7-db7b-a5dd-aef7d0f20000</link>
      <description>The team hopes to have Elliott back for their Week 4 game against the Vikings in Ireland, according to Schultz. Elliott will be replaced by some combination of Jalen Ramsey and Jabrill Peppers, who signed with the Steelers on Tuesday. The loss of Elliott is a blow for a Pittsburgh defense that allowed the fourth highest drop back success rate in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ef7-db7b-a5dd-aef7d0f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed K John Parker Romo, formerly of the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f2b-db7b-a5dd-af2fa50a0000</link>
      <description>Parker Romo, who lost the Week 1 starting competition in New England this summer, was inked to the Atlanta practice squad two days after Younghoe Koo whiffed on a game-tying fourth quarter kick. Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Koo would face competition ahead of the team’s Week 2 matchup with the Vikings. Koo, who made two of his three attempts against the Bucs in Week 1, converted a dismal 73 percent of his field goal tries in 2024. He reportedly struggled in training camp and could be out of a job with a rough Week 2 outing. Parker Romo made 11 of his 12 field goal tries last season with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2f2b-db7b-a5dd-af2fa50a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
