<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer said “there’s plenty of buzz that some level of change is coming” for the Atlanta Falcons after the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c19-d35e-a1bf-5ddba9920000</link>
      <description>Breer notes that the Falcons have brought in consulting firm Sportology to evaluate the in-house operations. We’re not getting many leaks on the ground out of Atlanta, but it’d be somewhat surprising if GM Terry Fontenot survived this latest failure after trading his 2026 first-round pick for rookie EDGE James Pearce, especially now that the team’s quarterback situation looks fully unsettled going forward after Michael Penix’s ACL tear. Raheem Morris is only in his second season on the job and may have more rope than Fontenot on account of that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c19-d35e-a1bf-5ddba9920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) is questionable for Buffalo’s Week 17 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c22-d35e-a1bf-5de230940000</link>
      <description>Kincaid finally got in a limited practice today after two DNPs — this has been his normal of late — and despite the high-scoring potential of a Bills-Eagles game it’s going to be hard to trust a clearly-playing-through-it Kincaid after a one-target bagel in Week 16. The tight end stream room is busy right now, especially after Brock Bowers went on IR, but you can probably do better than Kincaid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c22-d35e-a1bf-5de230940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RT Trent Brown (ankle/knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c1d-d968-a19b-5cfd09060000</link>
      <description>This is good news for the Texans’ offense. Brown’s 68.6 PFF offense grade ranks second among the Texans’ offensive line starters. Brown will help fend off the Chargers’ talented front-seven defenders as the Texans seek to secure a postseason appearance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c1d-d968-a19b-5cfd09060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (knee) is questionable for Buffalo’s Week 17 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c24-d968-a19b-5cf5f9fb0000</link>
      <description>Knox got two DNPs early in the week and came back with a limited session on Friday. It’s his first week with the injury so it’s hard to set expectations entirely, but this is typically the practice pattern of a player who would be on the pessimistic side of questionable in Week 17. It could be Jackson Hawes szn for Buffalo against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c24-d968-a19b-5cf5f9fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (oblique) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c24-d56e-afff-feec2e870000</link>
      <description>Stingley will be available for the Texans’ game against the Chargers on Saturday. The Texans (10-5) are in the playoff hunt, while the Chargers (11-4) have already secured a spot, though like the Texans, they sit in second place in their division. The Texans’ perimeter cornerback ties for eighth at the position in pass breakups (nine) and ties for third in interceptions (four).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c24-d56e-afff-feec2e870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out WR Rome Odunze (foot) for Week 17 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c1d-d35e-a1bf-5ddf0ab00000</link>
      <description>Bears head coach Ben Johnson told reporters earlier this week that Odunze is “going to be able to help us this year.” Unfortunately, that will not be the case this week. The 23-year-old wide receiver will now miss his fourth straight game, having aggravated the stress fracture in his foot during pre-game warmups in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c1d-d35e-a1bf-5ddf0ab00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c2c-d968-a19b-5cfd587b0000</link>
      <description>Burden was limited on Wednesday and Thursday, and encouragingly upgraded to full participation on Friday. The rookie wide receiver earned 6-7 targets in each of his last three games. He is a decent bet to stay in that range against the 49ers this week, putting him squarely on the FLEX radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c2c-d968-a19b-5cfd587b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Chris Olave (back) is questionable for New Orleans’ Week 17 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c37-d968-a19b-5cf7a6e40000</link>
      <description>He was limited in practice today, despite not being seen by reporters in the media access portion of the session. Olave has been listed with this back issue before and has said this week that he had “similar back issues dating back to high school.” We’d consider him on the optimistic side of questionable, but it’s never great to have a Friday downgrade on the injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c37-d968-a19b-5cf7a6e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants T Andrew Thomas (hamstring) will not play in New York’s Week 17 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c3a-d968-a19b-5cfb917e0000</link>
      <description>It’s a sneaky-big loss as Thomas is the Giants best offensive lineman by far. The Giants also have John Michael Schmitz (finger) listed as doubtful for the contest. It lowers the floor for Jaxson Dart in what should, in theory, be a smash start against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c3a-d968-a19b-5cfb917e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints ruled out RB Alvin Kamara (ankle/knee) for Week 17 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c38-d968-a19b-5cf938b70000</link>
      <description>This leaves RB Audric Estime as the nominal starter, though TE Taysom Hill logged 16 touches to Estime’s eight last week. The Saints apparently wanted to feature Hill in Week 16, in what could be his final home game as a Saint. Projecting each player’s Week 17 role is difficult. Neither one should be considered a confident play, though the Titans’ defense is unimposing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c38-d968-a19b-5cf938b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
