<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch told KNBR that he’d be “very surprised” if TE George Kittle didn’t play in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7533-d968-a19b-7df396d10000</link>
      <description>Kittle was a limited participant in 49ers practice Tuesday. Head coach Kyle Shanahan went as far as to say that Kittle had a chance to play this week. Lynch is more optimistic, essentially saying that a return from Kittle this week is more likely than not. If he has to sit out again, Jake Tonges is coming off a game with seven catches, 60 yards and a touchdown as Kittle’s replacement last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7533-d968-a19b-7df396d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts head coach Shane Steichen told reporters QB Riley Leonard will start in Week 18 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-753b-dc7a-af9b-ffbff8c10000</link>
      <description>Leonard, a sixth-round pick in the 2025 NFL Draft, threw for 145 yards and an interception in relief of Daniel Jones in Week 14 against the Jaguars. The Colts were so impressed with Leonard’s performance that they immediately signed 44-year-old Philip Rivers. While Rivers wasn’t able to keep the Colts in playoff contention, he proved that he gave the Colts a better chance to win than the Notre Dame rookie. Leonard was known for his rushing ability in college, which is the only aspect of his game that’s interesting for fantasy purposes. In what’s essentially a preseason game with the Colts already eliminated, Leonard draws a difficult matchup against the Texans vaunted pass rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-753b-dc7a-af9b-ffbff8c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch told reporters RB Christian McCaffrey (back) is trending towards playing in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7548-d56e-afff-f7e8cb020000</link>
      <description>The 49ers had a walkthrough Tuesday and McCaffrey was listed as out with a back injury. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reports the 29-year-old running back’s back is “a little stiff.” Trainers tended to CMC’s back in the fourth quarter of the win over the Bears in Week 17, with McCaffrey returning to finish the game. With Lynch saying that he’s trending towards playing, fantasy managers can expect McCaffrey to be available in Week 18. Brian Robinson is the clear handcuff to roster if anything changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7548-d56e-afff-f7e8cb020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) is out for Week 18 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-754f-d968-a19b-7dff7e170000</link>
      <description>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Harrison would continue to play through his heel injury this week if he was healthy enough. It turns out that the 23-year-old receiver isn’t healthy enough after hurting his other foot in the Week 17 loss to the Bengals. Harrison wasn’t having much of an impact with one catch in the last two games since returning to the lineup. With Harrison out, Michael Wilson is a must-start option for fantasy managers. Wilson is the WR3 over the last seven weeks behind only Puka Nacua and Jaxon Smith-Njigba. He needs 93 yards in Week 18 to have his first 1,000-yard season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-754f-d968-a19b-7dff7e170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott told reporters that while QB Josh Allen (foot) won’t practice Wednesday, he’s trending in the right direction ahead of Week 18’s matchup with the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7556-d56e-afff-f7fefbe40000</link>
      <description>The Bills will hold a walkthrough Wednesday, though their quarterback won’t participate. McDermott reiterated that Allen is moving in the right direction. It’s good news, though Buffalo can probably get by the Jets with Allen only playing some of the game. He’s certainly at risk to get benched late, which is worth considering for those still in active fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7556-d56e-afff-f7fefbe40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson told reporters he’s “hopeful” WR Luther Burden (quad) can play against the Lions in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7567-d968-a19b-7df765910000</link>
      <description>Burden was carted off the field after injuring his quad on the last play of the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported earlier this week that the injury isn’t thought to be serious. Johnson’s comments Wednesday seem to confirm that report. With the Bears hopeful Burden can play against the Lions this week, he’ll likely be available for the playoffs even if he’s ultimately held out this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7567-d968-a19b-7df765910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFluer told reporters QB Jordan Love (concussion) will practice on Wednesday, though he remains in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756b-dc7a-af9b-ffffce780000</link>
      <description>LaFluer also confirmed that the Packers plan on resting some of their starters in Week 18 against the Vikings. It makes plenty of sense with Green Bay already locked into the No. 7 seed in the NFC Playoffs. Love would seem to be a prime candidate to get the week off even if he clears concussion protocol in time this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756b-dc7a-af9b-ffffce780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFluer told reporters QB Malik Willis (shoulder) will be limited in practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756f-d56e-afff-f7efe1b90000</link>
      <description>Willis left Week 17’s loss with a shoulder injury, though he impressed with 288 yards passing, 60 yards rushing and three total touchdowns against the Ravens. Clayton Tune finished out the game with Willis and Jordan Love sidelined. With Love still in the NFL’s concussion protocol and the Packers locked into the No. 7 seed in the NFC Playoffs, Willis could start again in Week 18 against the Vikings if he’s healthy enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-756f-d56e-afff-f7efe1b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn told reporters QB Marcus Mariota (quad) is doubtful for Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7579-d968-a19b-7df949280000</link>
      <description>Not much has changed since Quinn met with reporters Monday. Mariota still isn’t practicing and his coach called him a long-shot to play and even added that he’s “likely doubtful.” Barring a miraculous recovery, Josh Johnson will be under center for Washington in Week 18 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7579-d968-a19b-7df949280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn told reporters QB Brady Cook will start against the Bills in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-757c-dc7a-af9b-ffff7bd10000</link>
      <description>Cook has done very little to elevate the Jets’ offense in his three starts so far. He’s had less than 200 passing yards in all three games and has one touchdown to seven interceptions. He’ll get one more chance to make a lasting impression on the new Jets’ regime in Week 18 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-757c-dc7a-af9b-ffff7bd10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
