<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 03:31:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brycen Tremayne caught 2-of-2 targets for 27 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8684-d35e-a1bf-c7c660560000</link>
      <description>One of the catches was a 20-yard connection. Tremayne finished with just 14 catches for 143 yards in his first season with the Panthers. It’s hard to see fantasy relevance going forward, but he might be an option for Carolina in the playoffs if the Falcons beat the Saints. If not, he’ll compete for a roster spot this summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8684-d35e-a1bf-c7c660560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette caught 3-of-4 targets for 22 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8685-d968-a19b-def504160000</link>
      <description>Legette did not build on a disappointing rookie season — at least statistically — as he finished with just 34 catches for 363 yards despite playing in 16 games. You can’t completely give up on him as a dynasty option, but there hasn’t been much to suggest he’s on the right track. There’s still a chance he could play in the postseason, however, if the Falcons beat the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8685-d968-a19b-def504160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Horn Jr. caught his only target for 15 yards in the Panthers’ Week 18 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8686-d35e-a1bf-c7c601c70000</link>
      <description>Horn was an undrafted free agent from Prime University aka Colorado, and the 23-year-old did see more involvement in the offense than anticipated. Not enough to make him relevant in fantasy formats, but enough to suggest he could be a part of the offense in 2026. Horn will compete for slot reps with the Panthers this summer, but will hope the Falcons beat the Saints so they can play at least one postseason game next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8686-d35e-a1bf-c7c601c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 7-of-9 targets for 94 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 win over Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8691-dc7a-af9b-cfbf73080000</link>
      <description>Calling Otton the top target for Tampa Bay in the passing game is quite the understatement; as no other receiver had 40 yards. The 26-year-old tight end not only had a touchdown, but picked up what was essentially a game-clinching first down late in the game on a connection with Baker Mayfield. Amazingly it was the first touchdown of the season for Otton, but outside of those lack of scores it was a solid season for the fourth-year player. Otton will head to free agency after the season. He could get a chance to find the end zone again in the playoffs, but they’ll need the Saints to upset the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8691-dc7a-af9b-cfbf73080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans caught both targets for 34 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8692-d968-a19b-def3c1440000</link>
      <description>Evans would have needed a little over 600 yards to keep his streak of thousand-yard seasons alive. He didn’t. The 32-year-old dealt with injuries, but even when on the field this was far from his best regular season with just one game over the century mark. Evans is a decent bounceback candidate for 2026 — even if he will be entering his age-33 season — but also could have a chance to do damage in the postseason if the Falcons lose to the Saints on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8692-d968-a19b-def3c1440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tez Johnson caught his only target for 17 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 win over the Panthers, adding a five-yard rush.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8693-d35e-a1bf-c7d3b6b80000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers didn’t throw the ball much due to Baker Mayfield’s shoulder issues on top of rainy conditions in Tampa Bay. But Johnson wasn’t likely to get many targets anyway. The rookie wideout showed some real promise at times while Tampa dealt with wideout injuries, and could be in line for more targets in 2026 depending on what the Bucs do with their crowded wideout room. He likely won’t be a factor in the playoffs if the Buccaneers are able to clinch the division with a Saints win over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8693-d35e-a1bf-c7d3b6b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen McMillan caught his only target for 11 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8695-dc7a-af9b-cfbf9b4e0000</link>
      <description>McMillan and the Bucs’ passing game was mostly an afterthought, outside of Cade Otton — a fellow former Washington standout — going for 94 yards. McMillan’s year was decimated by injuries, but fantasy players shouldn’t forget how impressive he looked in his rookie season before his neck ailments. He’s a sleeper play for 2026, but also could get a chance to play in the postseason if the Falcons lose to the Saints in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8695-dc7a-af9b-cfbf9b4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin Jr. caught his lone target for eight yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8697-dc7a-af9b-cfbf21620000</link>
      <description>Godwin was not a factor again in Week 18, and unfortunately for fantasy managers who took a “chance” on the 29-year-old, that’s becoming a recurring theme. Injuries played a major factor, but this is the fourth time in five games that he was held under 60 yards. That’s a far cry from what was once one of the most effective PPR receivers in the sport. Godwin and the Bucs finish the year 8-9, and they’ll need a Saints’ win over the Falcons to play in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8697-dc7a-af9b-cfbf21620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 1-of-3 targets for eight yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 18 win over the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8697-d968-a19b-def7c3830000</link>
      <description>It was another disappointing game for Egbuka, who just didn’t show the same production after getting off to such a sensational start to begin the season. He still finishes with 938 yards on his 63 catches with six touchdowns, and it’s hard to imagine he won’t be one of the top options in the Bucs’ passing attack in 2026. The 23-year-old could get a chance to show out in a playoff game, but in order for that to happen, the Saints will have to beat the Falcons in Week 18</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8697-d968-a19b-def7c3830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (ankle) left San Francisco’s Week 18 game against the Seahawks and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-86cd-dc7a-af9b-cfffb2440000</link>
      <description>He was stepped on by Seahawks OL Josh Jones. Winters had two tackles before leaving. He spent some time in the medical tent and walked to the locker room with trainers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-86cd-dc7a-af9b-cfffb2440000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
