<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (foot) returned to practice but said Week 1 “still feels uncertain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee36-dbe3-a9bb-fe77e1010000</link>
      <description>Reed apparently isn’t yet running routes without pain. We’ll be monitoring Reed’s practice status ahead of Week 1’s game against the Lions, but with both Reed himself and Matt LaFleur setting early expectations that Reed will miss the game, fantasy managers should be prepared to pivot away from Reed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee36-dbe3-a9bb-fe77e1010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Michael Carter to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee3d-dbe3-a9bb-fe7f4fe10000</link>
      <description>Carter surprisingly lost out to Zonovan Knight for the final roster spot at running back, but decided to remain with the Cardinals practice squad. Joining him so far are: WR Andre Baccellia, LB Elliott Brown, OL Jeremiah Byers, OL Jake Curhan, TE Josiah Deguara, WR Simi Fehoko, DL Anthony Goodlow, CB Darren Hall, OL Sincere Haynesworth, OL Nick Leverett, WR Tejhaun Palmer and DL Elijah Simmons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee3d-dbe3-a9bb-fe7f4fe10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans signed WR Xavier Restrepo to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee44-de13-afdc-eecff7ce0000</link>
      <description>The former Miami (FL) receiver stays with his quarterback, albeit a beat away from actual NFL playing time on the practice squad. The Titans also added WR Mason Kinsey, WR James Proche II, QB Trevor Siemian, OL Andrew Rupcich, DT Isaiah Raikes, DE Ali Gaye, RB Jordan Mims, DB Kendell Brooks, DT Cam Horsley, RB Jermar Jefferson, DB Amani Oruwariye, DE Carlos Watkins, TE Thomas Odukoya and C Corey Levin to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee44-de13-afdc-eecff7ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed QB Cam Miller to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee53-dbe3-a9bb-fe53f8b20000</link>
      <description>Miller finished with a 38.8 PFF offense grade for his 80 preseason snaps at quarterback. It would be surprising if the Raiders turned to him at any point this season, but perhaps he can take a step forward and show more next preseason. Also joining the Las Vegas practice squad are: WR Alex Bachman, RB Chris Collier, S Terrell Edmunds, DE Jahfari Harvey, WR Shedrick Jackson, LB Matt Jones, DT Treven Ma’ae, G Atonio Mafi, TE Albert Okwuegbunam Jr., TE Carter Runyon, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, S Trey Taylor, CB Greedy Vance, T Dalton Wagner and S JT Woods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee53-dbe3-a9bb-fe53f8b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed WR Mecole Hardman to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee58-dbe3-a9bb-fe5be04e0000</link>
      <description>Hardman was waived at last cuts but decided that staying with the Packers made sense. The 27-year-old will likely be elevated in Week 1 if Jayden Reed’s injury is as serious as it seems. Also joining the Packers practice squad are: QB Clayton Tune, RB Israel Abanikanda, DL Deslin Alexandre, DB Johnathan Baldwin, T Brant Banks, DL James Ester, LB Jamon Johnson, K Mark McNamee, DL Arron Mosby, WR Isaiah Neyor, WR Will Sheppard, DB Jaylin Simpson, and LB Kristian Welch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee58-dbe3-a9bb-fe5be04e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed RB Jeff Wilson to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee5f-dbe3-a9bb-fe5fbc2f0000</link>
      <description>With Brian Robinson now in San Francisco, Wilson probably felt better about his chances of being elevated off Miami’s practice squad. The Dolphins also signed TE Greg Dulcich, CB BJ Adams, CB Cornell Armstrong, LB Quinton Bell, OL Braeden Daniels, WR AJ Henning, DT Alex Huntley, LB Derrick McLendon, K Riley Patterson, OL Josh Priebe, TE Hayden Rucci, S John Saunders Jr., TE Theo Wease Jr., S Jordan Colbert to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee5f-dbe3-a9bb-fe5fbc2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed QB Will Grier to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee69-d332-a1fd-fe7f7a580000</link>
      <description>The usual. Grier spent all of 2022 and most of 2024 with the Cowboys practice squad. He’s back to ride again. Joining him on the Dallas practice squad are: LB Justin Barron, WR Jalen Brooks, DT Earnest Brown, G Saahdiq Charles, T Geron Christian, S Alijah Clark, WR Jalen Cropper, RB Malik Davis, TE Rivaldo Fairweather, TE Princeton Fant, CB Kemon Hall, WR Traeshon Holden, LB Buddy Johnson and CB Robert Rochell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ee69-d332-a1fd-fe7f7a580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed WR Tyler Scott to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0ae-dbe3-a9bb-f0ff3e660000</link>
      <description>The former Bears fourth-rounder will look to re-establish himself in what is a stacked Colts receiver room. Also joining the Colts practice squad are: LB Austin Ajiake, RB Ulysses Bentley IV, RB Khalil Herbert, T Marcellus Johnson, WR Tyler Kahmann, CB Chris Lammons, TE Maximilian Mang, DL Earnest Brown, TE Sean McKeon, DE Durrell Nchami, WR Coleman Owen, G Josh Sills, DT Josh Tupou, C Mose Vavao and S Trey Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0ae-dbe3-a9bb-f0ff3e660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said the “plan is to split those up a little bit and distribute” when asked about Kyren Williams’ workload on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0b6-d332-a1fd-f6b625b00000</link>
      <description>“He’s made of all the right stuff. He’s done everything we’ve asked of him, not that we even have to ask too much of him because he’s wired the right way. I thought he had a good preseason. Obviously, we left him out of that third game right there. He’s had a really good training camp. He’ll get his opportunities come Week 1,” LaFleur said about the second-year back from Michigan. Corum probably doesn’t have standalone value at the start of the season, and coaches talk about splitting reps more evenly all the time. But it’s worth monitoring Corum’s workload early in the season to see if he can make a real dent in Kyren Williams’ fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f0b6-d332-a1fd-f6b625b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel said Tyreek Hill (oblique) “looks great” for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f12b-dbe3-a9bb-f17bba950000</link>
      <description>Hill has missed quite a bit of training camp and, obviously, didn’t play in the preseason. The team has been cautious with him after he suffered an oblique injury and will “do some stuff” today. It sounds like he’ll be on the injury report ahead of Week 1, but that we shouldn’t expect him to have problems playing barring a setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f12b-dbe3-a9bb-f17bba950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
