<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said he wasn’t ready to name a starter for Week 7 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dead-def2-abdb-dfedb6580000</link>
      <description>Carson Wentz is apparently still recovering from his shoulder injury, though he will participate in practice this week. O’Connell added that J.J. McCarthy (ankle) would practice “in some capacity” this week. That’s a load-bearing “some capacity” in our opinion and we should probably have Wentz as the leader in the clubhouse for this role in Week 7. Neither player rates out as more than a QB2 against what has been a fierce Eagles defense this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dead-def2-abdb-dfedb6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Blake Corum (ankle) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb2-dd4c-afb9-fff31c460000</link>
      <description>Corum wouldn’t practice today if there were a practice, per McVay, but that’s standard for players and Corum did return and play in the second half of Week 6’s win over the Ravens. We might see the Rams hold back on Corum a bit in practice this week, but we’d be surprised if he was actually held out of Week 7’s Fourth Meal London game against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb2-dd4c-afb9-fff31c460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans fired head coach Brian Callahan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb3-dd4c-afb9-fff3ca3f0000</link>
      <description>Why now? Why not 10 months ago? Frankly, it was a bit of a miracle that the Titans actually won a game this season and it took one of the most bizarre interception fumble recovery touchdowns we’ve ever seen to make it possible. The Titans finished 4-19 under Callahan’s guidance, were outscored by 78 points in their six games this season, and by 149 points in 2024. Tennessee drafted Cam Ward No. 1 overall and has seen him play like one of the worst quarterbacks in the league to this point. It’s hard to say that Callahan’s offense was the main culprit as the team is entirely bereft of talent at wideout and on the offensive line, but he certainly hadn’t been elevating Ward to this point either. The Titans have not yet named an interim head coach, though we presume Bo Hardegree will continue calling offensive plays in what is officially another lost season for the franchise. Mike Vrabel’s Patriots are in town this week if Titans fans want to remember what a real head coach looks like.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb3-dd4c-afb9-fff3ca3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said “we’ll see” when asked if Rico Dowdle earned the right to be the team’s starting RB going forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb0-db72-a199-fefb925b0000</link>
      <description>Typically, when a player goes for 473 yards from scrimmage and two touchdowns in a two-week span, teams lean into that success. Dowdle’s success over these last two weeks stands out even more when you compare it to the four-game sample we have from Chuba Hubbard this season (53-217-0). Even if Dowdle doesn’t stay in the bell cow role we’ve seen sans Hubbard, it’s hard to imagine the Panthers relegating him to backup duties. Hubbard missed all of practice last week, so whether or not he returns in Week 7 is a question on its own. Sure, “we’ll see” what Canales and company decide, but there’s no doubt Dowdle has forced the Panthers’ hand a bit here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deb0-db72-a199-fefb925b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said Anthony Richardson (orbital fracture) will miss some time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dec4-db72-a199-fecf24790000</link>
      <description>The former first-rounder suffered a freak accident ahead of Week 6’s game against the Cardinals during an elastic band workout that landed him in the hospital. Richardson has been the QB2 behind Daniel Jones all season, but that job will now go to rookie Riley Leonard for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dec4-db72-a199-fecf24790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said it “might be best for the long haul” to keep Brock Bowers (knee) out for Week 7.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dedb-dd4c-afb9-ffdb2cf20000</link>
      <description>The Raiders have a Week 8 bye and this would give Bowers about a month of consecutive rest and rehab to see if he can get his knee injury into a spot where he can be 2024 Brock Bowers again. Carroll noted that he was “optimistic” — when isn’t he? — about Bowers returning but this felt like a telling comment with the bye week approaching. We wouldn’t be surprised if Bowers missed Week 7 and fantasy managers should probably walk into this week expecting that scenario to come to pass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dedb-dd4c-afb9-ffdb2cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Tavius Robinson (foot) is likely looking at a 6-8 week absence.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ded3-def2-abdb-dff3073a0000</link>
      <description>It’s a broken foot for Robinson, who will land on injured reserve due to his extended absence. The third-year linebacker has started all six games he’s appeared in for the Ravens this season, totaling nine tackles, two TFLs, and two sacks. If all goes well with his recovery, Robinson could be back on the field by late-November/early-December.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ded3-def2-abdb-dff3073a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings open Blake Cashman’s practice window.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deed-d94a-a79d-dfedd5b10000</link>
      <description>Cashman has been on injured reserve since suffered a hamstring injury in Week 1 against the Bears. Now the seventh-year linebacker will have his 21-day return window opened, allowing him a chance to ramp up before making his return to the field. Cashman totaled 69 tackles and 4.5 sacks with the Vikings last season and tallied three tackles in his limited action this season. He’s not a lock to return in Week 7, but the decision to designate him for return means the Vikings can activate him at any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-deed-d94a-a79d-dfedd5b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Lisa Salters reports Deebo Samuel (heel) is expected to play in Week 6 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df02-def2-abdb-df63e6740000</link>
      <description>Deebo entered the weekend as a game-time decision. While the team will still probably take a good look at him during warmups, but the early report seems like good news regarding his availability. Samuel played through the same heel injury last week and managed to log only one practice this week, so hopefully he isn’t too limited on Monday night. With Terry McLaurin (quad) still sidelined, the Commanders can ill-afford to be without Samuel, who has caught 14 passes for 168 yards and two touchdowns over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df02-def2-abdb-df63e6740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray (foot) is “the starting quarterback” when he’s healthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-dd4c-afb9-ffd9d5e20000</link>
      <description>Of course, it’s kind of telling that the question was even asked. Jacoby Brissett’s 320-yard game against a solid Colts defense — mostly without Marvin Harrison Jr. — certainly showcased the Cardinals offense in a different light than what we’ve seen from Murray up to this point. Murray is averaging just 6.0 yards per attempt in five starts, while Brissett hit 7.1 in turning Zay Jones and Michael Wilson into more involved players. Gannon complimented Brissett’s “poise and command” while Wilson tellingly complimented Brissett by noting: “His ability to stay in the pocket, deliver strikes, his vision of the game, throws a catchable ball.” We don’t quite see a change as imminent, but Brissett putting a strong foot forward on Sunday at least opens up the possibility of an in-season benching for Murray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df18-dd4c-afb9-ffd9d5e20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
