<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) is not on Los Angeles’ final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e1-d651-a9df-fbf583820000</link>
      <description>He’ll be returning after a one-week absence to a great situation against Indianapolis’ weakened cornerback corps. Johnston can be started as a WR3 in most leagues, even if the luster has come off of Los Angeles’ hot start with offensive line injuries severely impacting their ability to keep Justin Herbert upright over the last few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e1-d651-a9df-fbf583820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (knee) is questionable for Week 7 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3cf-da18-a39b-fbdf2cea0000</link>
      <description>Jones returned to practice in a limited capacity on Friday, making him truly questionable to play this weekend. With No. 1 WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (concussion) cleared to play, Jones would only be a dart-throw FLEX option, if he is also active. The Packers’ top-tier defense does not make for a matchup to target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3cf-da18-a39b-fbdf2cea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (illness) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 7 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e4-d651-a9df-fbf5fb760000</link>
      <description>It must be a pretty significant illness to keep Jacobs on the questionable line despite practicing in full on Friday. Since he missed no practices, this feels like a situation where Jacobs is on the optimistic side of questionable. Emanuel Wilson and Chris Brooks would be in line for committee work if Jacobs can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e4-d651-a9df-fbf5fb760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Zonovan Knight (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 7 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e4-d651-a9df-fbf5d9750000</link>
      <description>Knight practiced in full twice after a limited session on Wednesday, indicating his availability was never really in doubt this week. Knight took over as the Cardinals’ lead rusher last week and will likely handle the same role this time around. His lack of passing game involvement reduces his ceiling, making him a somewhat touchdown-dependent FLEX, though he should touch the ball 10-plus times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e4-d651-a9df-fbf5d9750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers K Brandon McManus (quad) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 7 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e6-d99b-a1dd-fbeecb5a0000</link>
      <description>It would seem extremely questionable to us from the outside as McManus has not practiced all week and Matt LaFleur has continued to be dour about his prospects of returning. Lucas Havrisik is in line to kick again for the Packers if McManus can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e6-d99b-a1dd-fbeecb5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 7 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e8-df81-ab9b-ffef683f0000</link>
      <description>OL Zach Tom joins him there. Wicks got in three limited sessions and seems likely to give it a go after being pulled from Week 6’s game against the Bengals with the injury. Tom went DNP-limited-limited and is probably more of a true question mark with an oblique injury that has sidelined him for most of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3e8-df81-ab9b-ffef683f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans K Joey Slye (calf) is not on Tennessee’s final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3eb-df81-ab9b-ffef4e520000</link>
      <description>This was telegraphed earlier when the Titans waived Matthew Wright. Those of you looking for a chance at a zero from your fantasy kicker can happily start Slye against the Patriots in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3eb-df81-ab9b-ffef4e520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (chest) is questionable for Week 7 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ed-da18-a39b-fbffa0e90000</link>
      <description>Haskins was curiously added to the Chargers’ injury report on Thursday, though he was listed as a full participant. He did not practice on Friday, indicating he is truly questionable to face the Colts on Sunday. Haskins was out-touched 21-7 by the hot-handed Kimani Vidal in Week 6. Even if Haskins is active, he is difficult to trust as a dart-throw FLEX given last week’s results and his new injury. Vidal is a locked-in RB2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ed-da18-a39b-fbffa0e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys G Tyler Booker (ankle) is not on Dallas’ final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ef-d651-a9df-fbff03fb0000</link>
      <description>Booker has been out since suffering a high-ankle sprain in Week 3. He avoided injured reserve, returning after missing just three weeks. It’ll be a small boost for Dallas’ run game against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3ef-d651-a9df-fbff03fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (foot) is not on Dallas’ final Week 7 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3f1-d651-a9df-fbf5ac960000</link>
      <description>Turpin’s return should leave your Ryan Flournoy shares in shambles. With CeeDee Lamb and Turpin back, Dallas will have its starting receivers from Week 1 healthy for the first time since Lamb left Week 3’s game against the Bears. Turpin should probably be approached cautiously in his first game since Week 4, but he does have real FLEX upside against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f3f1-d651-a9df-fbf5ac960000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
