<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:17:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Lockett did not catch his lone target in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2717-dbe3-a9bb-375786370000</link>
      <description>The grizzled veteran served as the Titans’ distant WR3 behind Calvin Ridley and Elic Ayomanor, who saw eight and even targets, respectively, against a tough Denver defense. Lockett logged a pass route on 27 of the team’s 38 drop backs but was an afterthought throughout. Ayomanor appears to be Cam Ward’s main downfield threat. Lockett should remain on waivers ahead of Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2717-dbe3-a9bb-375786370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught both of his targets for 16 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2713-d332-a1fd-b737f2c10000</link>
      <description>Golden was not overly involved in the Green Bay offense for his first game of the year. He earned a measly nine percent target share and only ran a route on 58 percent of the Packers’ dropbacks. The first-round rookie still has work to do before emerging as a true fantasy threat. His role should ramp up over time, but a short turnaround to a Thursday date with Washington won’t do him any favors. He is buried in the FLEX ranks for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2713-d332-a1fd-b737f2c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 3-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271d-dbe3-a9bb-375f630a0000</link>
      <description>Mims was bottled up on his three grabs and made some mental mistakes in the return game. The good news: Mims, a part-time gadget player last season, ran a pass route on 31 of Bo Nix’s 48 drop backs. Courtland Sutton and Troy Franklin had more routes than Mims on the day. Mims’ explosiveness on both short-area targets and downfield looks make him a high-variance weekly fantasy play. He gets the Colts in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271d-dbe3-a9bb-375f630a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 2-of-4 targets for 68 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Doubs was the Packers’ most trusted receiver, leading the team in routes. He ran a route on 18-of-24 Jordan Love dropbacks. He also finished second on the team in targets behind only Jayden Reed. Doubs isn’t the flashiest fantasy option, but his role is secure and he plays on an offense that won’t have any issues putting up points. He will stick in the WR4/5 range for Week 2 against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 3-of-4 targets for 19 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2723-de13-afdd-67eb1c570000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo’s usage was solid enough, as he ran a route on 31 of Cam Ward’s 36 drop backs. He was third in targets on a day when Ward threw for a meager 112 yards and had just 12 completions. Things will loosen up for Okonkwo and the other Tennessee pass catchers following their brutal Week 1 matchup against a stellar Denver defense. Okonkwo will be a legit streaming play in Week 2 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2723-de13-afdd-67eb1c570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught both of his targets for 30 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2725-dbe3-a9bb-3777a5430000</link>
      <description>Wicks entered Sunday listed as questionable with a calf issue but never appeared to be at risk of missing Week 1. He was good to go by kickoff and playing a surprisingly robust role. He ran 11 routes, all of which came from an outside alignment. Though that’s not enough to be a relevant fantasy player in his own right, it did kneecap the role of first-round rookie Matthew Golden. The Packers’ receiver room is once again a messy rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2725-dbe3-a9bb-3777a5430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White had two rushes for 14 yards in the Bucs’ Week 1 win against the Falcons, adding one catch for two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2729-d332-a1fd-b73fc93b0000</link>
      <description>The short of it: White was the team’s distant No. 2 back behind Bucky Irving, who handled 14 rushes and had four receptions, one for a touchdown. Irving dominated the pass-catching role out of the Tampa backfield; he ran 23 pass routes to just nine for White. For now, White profiles purely as a contingency option. If Irving were to miss time in 2025, White would suffice as a top-20 PPR option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2729-d332-a1fd-b73fc93b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (left shoulder) will undergo an MRI and “additional testing” to determine the severity of his injury in the next 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d3-de13-afdd-66db08bf0000</link>
      <description>Jennings injured his left shoulder in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks. Although he was initially deemed questionable to return, he spent the rest of the game on the sideline. The 49ers’ receiving corps is extremely thin, with Brandon Aiyuk (knee) still rehabbing and George Kittle (hamstring) also set to under an MRI and additional testing. Marquez Valdes-Scantling is the next man up. The error-prone speedster could catch one or two deep passes against his former team, the Saints, in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d3-de13-afdd-66db08bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 25-of-40 attempts for 176 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Broncos’ 20-12 Week 1 win against the Titans, adding eight rushes for 17 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-272f-db7b-a5dd-a72f599c0000</link>
      <description>Nix posted a hideous 4.3 yards per attempt, missing open pass catchers and making baffling decisions in critical moments against a poor Tennessee defense. Nix tried to get something going as a rusher to no avail. Nix connected with his WR1 Courtland Sutton for his lone touchdown on a nicely throw red zone jump ball, but couldn’t get anything going in a game that should not have been close. Nix should continue giving fantasy managers a handful of rushing attempts every week, giving him some fantasy juice that can compensate for poor passing performances. Nix will be a borderline starting option in 12-team formats next week against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-272f-db7b-a5dd-a72f599c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 4-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2735-dbe3-a9bb-377722e80000</link>
      <description>Franklin operates as Denver’s No. 2 receiver behind Courtland Sutton and ahead of Marvin Mims, who was held to 12 yards on three grabs. Franklin saw 23 percent of the Broncos’ air yards and was second in target share behind Sutton. He could pass for a usable fantasy option in deep leagues next week against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2735-dbe3-a9bb-377722e80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
