<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed EDGE Will McDonald IV (knee) on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c8a-d35e-a1bf-5dcaf9370000</link>
      <description>McDonald marked eight sacks in 15 games this year and continues to look like a solid building block pass rusher. The Jets will face a decision on whether they want to pick up his fifth-year option this offseason. With the season over in all but name, the Jets also sent LB Kiko Mauigoa (neck) and DL Jay Tufele (foot) to the injured reserve list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c8a-d35e-a1bf-5dcaf9370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks ruled out LT Charles Cross (hamstring) for Week 17 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c83-d968-a19b-5cf3ec960000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know Cross’ participation level on Friday, but he remained sidelined on Wednesday and Thursday after missing the team’s Week 16 game against the Rams. The Seahawks could be taking the long view with Cross. The lowly Panthers are unimposing and the 12-4 Seahawks currently own the NFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. Hopefully, they can secure a victory while also allowing their stud left tackle to successfully rehab his hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c83-d968-a19b-5cf3ec960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 17 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c99-d35e-a1bf-5ddb9aa40000</link>
      <description>The Panthers get their left tackle back after a one-game absence. The Panthers (8-7) astonishingly hold the NFC South’s top spot. Getting Ekwonu back in time to face the Seahawks’ top-tier defense is good news for QB Bryce Young, who has one year remaining on his contract and will continue to be evaluated closely by the coaching staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c99-d35e-a1bf-5ddb9aa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) is expected to be sidelined for three weeks, “through the first two rounds of the playoffs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</link>
      <description>Wattenberg grades well as both a pass protector and run blocker, earning a 70.9 PFF offense grade. With Wattenberg sidelined, the Broncos signed C Sam Mustipher off the Chargers’ practice squad. Broncos C Alex Forsyth will operate as the starter with Wattenberg sidelined. Mustipher is his backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) is questionable for Week 17 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cbc-d56e-afff-fefc26c80000</link>
      <description>The team put out an estimated practice report for Christmas Day, but gave players the day off. Vidal is surprisingly listed as a limited participant after sitting out the team’s first two practices. He would be a very risky FLEX option if active. We expect RB Omarion Hampton to hog touches against a stout Texans defense, regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cbc-d56e-afff-fefc26c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll confirmed that EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) is being “shut down.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc0-d968-a19b-5cf177ec0000</link>
      <description>Crosby is not going to like this. Hours ago, after the team ruled Crosby out for Week 17, FOX’s Jay Glazer reported that Crosby, disgruntled, had “left the building,” calling into question “his future in Vegas.” It seems likely that the decision to shut Crosby down, ostensibly for Week 18 as well, will be formalized with a move to injured reserve. Crosby leads the team with 53 quarterback pressures and 10 sacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc0-d968-a19b-5cf177ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc2-dc7a-af9b-dfff01640000</link>
      <description>Kittle did not practice this week, and reportedly told head coach Kyle Shanahan that he “should have a better answer by tomorrow” regarding his Week 17 availability. Kittle is no stranger to playing through injury, and although he is clearly less than 100.0 percent, he warrants TE1 treatment if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc2-dc7a-af9b-dfff01640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (ankle/knee) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccb-d968-a19b-5cfb8f2d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall has been practicing in a limited capacity this week, though we do not yet know his official participation level for Friday. If he can suit up against the Bears this weekend, he can only be viewed as a boom-bust FLEX option. Pearsall has demonstrated intriguing route running abilities this season, but knee and ankle injuries continue to slow him down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccb-d968-a19b-5cfb8f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) was not seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccf-d35e-a1bf-5dcfd8310000</link>
      <description>We do not expect Adams to play this week. The 33-year-old wide receiver has already aggravated the multi-week injury once, and the Rams (11-4) have secured a playoff spot. On the off chance he plays, he would be a candidate to score a touchdown, operating in his featured red zone role, but he makes for a dicey play overall. Just two days ago, ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported that the Rams may “shut down” Adams for the final two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccf-d35e-a1bf-5dcfd8310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders RB Raheem Mostert (knee/ankle) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-dc7a-af9b-dfffad9e0000</link>
      <description>Mostert has not been fantasy-relevant, but with the Raiders have shutting down TE Brock Bowers (knee) and EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee), we figure all skill position players are worth keeping an eye on. Mostert sits in second on the depth chart, with RB Zamir White and RB Dylan Laube behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-dc7a-af9b-dfffad9e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
