<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 18:01:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm (toe) is active for Week 16 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-d35e-a1bf-45c70bf00000</link>
      <description>As is Van Jefferson (back). It means this undermanned Titans skill corps is at least at full strength as it tries to steal a victory vs. the dazed and confused Chiefs. Inactive for the Titans are OL Brandon Crenshaw-Dickson, OL Garrett Dellinger, OL Drew Moss, DL Cam Horsley, LB Cedric Gray and S Erick Hallett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-d35e-a1bf-45c70bf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared WR Keon Coleman, K Matt Prater, S Darnell Savage, DT Jordan Phillips, OT Tylan Grable, and DT Larry Ogunjobi inactive for Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c3-dc7a-af9b-cffff2b60000</link>
      <description>Coleman didn’t record an official target in Week 15 against the Patriots and has been a healthy scratch on multiple occasions this season. Coleman has caught 36 passes for 355 yards and four touchdowns this season, but has caught just four passes in his last three games played.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c3-dc7a-af9b-cffff2b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared WR Jalin Hyatt, WR Ryan Miller, LB Demetrius Flanagan-Fowles, OLB Caleb Murphy, OG Jon Runyan Jr., DL Rakeem Nunez-Roches, and QB Russell Wilson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c4-d35e-a1bf-45c69dea0000</link>
      <description>Given the Giants’ injuries at wide receiver, it’s unfortunate that Hyatt still can’t find a spot on the game-day roster. With just five catches for 35 yards this year, he will likely be looking for a new team in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c4-d35e-a1bf-45c69dea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared RB Alvin Kamara, S Ugo Amadi, CB Rejzohn Wright, RG Cesar Ruiz, T Asim Richards, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, and DT Khristian Boyd inactive for Week 16 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff57650000</link>
      <description>Audric Estime is expected to function as the Saints’ lead back against the Jets with Kamara sidelined, though Evan Hull will mix in on passing downs. Estime can be played as a touchdown-dependent flex option in 12-team leagues while Hull is a desperation play in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c6-dc7a-af9b-cfff57650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared LT Ikem Ekwonu (knee) inactive for Week 16 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c2-da28-afbb-c5ffb2ba0000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu got in a limited practice on Friday, but it was not enough to be ready for Week 16 against the Buccaneers. Yosh Nijman will start in his place at left tackle. Panthers also declared WR Hunter Renfrow, LB Trevin Wallace, S Demani Richardson, DT Jared Harrison-Hunte, TE James Mitchell, and DT Tershawn Wharton inactive for Week 16 against the Buccaneers. Wallace (shoulder) and Wharton (hamstring) are out due to injury, while the others are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c2-da28-afbb-c5ffb2ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Davis is inactive for Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c7-d087-addf-f1f7e4c70000</link>
      <description>Davis didn’t play an offensive snap in Week 15 and has caught just seven passes for 88 yards this season. There’s no reason to continue stashing Davis in any format during the final three weeks of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c7-d087-addf-f1f7e4c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared WR Rashee Rice (concussion) inactive for Kansas City’s Week 16 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-dc7a-af9b-cfffad830000</link>
      <description>He was declared out on Friday, as were most of the other Chiefs inactives today. Rice has a chance to come back last week, though Gardner Minshew taking over at quarterback significantly reduces his fantasy upside. The rest of the Chiefs inactives are: CB Trent McDuffie (knee), OL CJ Hanson, OT Jaylon Moore (knee), WR Tyquan Thornton (concussion), DT Derrick Nnadi (illness) and RB Dameon Pierce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41c5-dc7a-af9b-cfffad830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts LT Bernhard Raimann (right elbow) will not play in Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41d1-da28-afbb-c5fd1bba0000</link>
      <description>Raimann got in one limited practice this week before being listed as questionable for Monday’s game. Downgrading him to out this early means he wasn’t that close to suiting up. Raimann will eye a Week 17 return. Luke Tenuta took over for Raimann in Week 15 and could be the next man up once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41d1-da28-afbb-c5fd1bba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Dolphins coach Mike McDaniel “is expected back next season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41f4-d087-addf-f1f45b250000</link>
      <description>As expected, Rapoport notes Tua Tagovailoa is not expected to return in 2026. The Dolphins will either have to eat over $90 million in dead cap to cut Tua or find a trade partner. They would still be on the hook for many millions of dollars if that happens. McDaniel has seemingly gotten the most out of Tagovailoa during their time in Miami. Opposing defenses have simply figured out every adjustment McDaniel made to his offense. Now the experiment is at an end. Quinn Ewers will draw the start this week. Per Rapoport, McDaniel believes Ewers “is what this offense needs to run properly.” We’re skeptical of that, but a strong showing from the rookie would go a long way in keeping McDaniel on the good side of ownership as he looks to keep his job into 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41f4-d087-addf-f1f45b250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Woody Marks (ankle) is not expected to play in Week 16 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41fc-d087-addf-f1fc88630000</link>
      <description>As Rapoport notes, expect plenty of Nick Chubb, who is expected to play through a rib injury today. Chubb should indeed lead the backfield, but it wouldn’t be surprising for Jawhar Jordan to see some work as well. Jordan ran for 101 yards on 15 carries with Marks going down early last week. As the top back versus a dead-on-arrival Raiders squad, Chubb is in the RB3 ranks for Week 16. Jordan is a high-risk RB4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-41fc-d087-addf-f1fc88630000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
