<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 21:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c565-def2-abdb-dd65e1fe0000</link>
      <description>Purdy is reportedly considered week-to-week after re-aggravating his toe injury in Week 4. A DNP today already puts him on the wrong side of questionable. Mac Jones is also banged up but managed a limited practice. Barring a setback, Jones should be expected to start for the 49ers in Week 6 against Tampa Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c565-def2-abdb-dd65e1fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c56a-dd4c-afb9-e7eb628e0000</link>
      <description>Jauan Jennings also missed the first practice of the week. Pearsall is still dealing with the PCL injury that popped up early in the season and finally forced him to miss time in Week 5. It looks like he will also miss Week 6 because of the knee issue. Assuming neither Pearsall nor Jennings can suit up, Kendrick Bourne will once again operate as the team’s top wideout. Bourne saw 11 targets last week and will be a WR2/3 if he is the last man standing on the depth chart by Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c56a-dd4c-afb9-e7eb628e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c56e-db72-a199-ff6f804e0000</link>
      <description>Jones initially suffered the knee injury during the preseason. He was healthy by Week 1 but eventually re-aggravated the issue early in the year. He has been playing through the injury in Brock Purdy’s absence. With Purdy unlikely to play this week, the 49ers will give Jones as much rest as he needs on practice days to make sure he is ready by kickoff. Jones is averaging 302 passing yards and two scores per week across three starts. In a potential shootout with the Bucs, fantasy managers can treat the journeyman passer as a high-end QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c56e-db72-a199-ff6f804e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers CB Joey Porter Jr. (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 6 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c569-d94a-a79d-cd6d08910000</link>
      <description>Porter is firmly on track to return following the Steelers’ Week 5 bye. Steelers LB Alex Highsmith’s limited participation is a positive, but one would have preferred to see him practice in full after rehabbing his injured ankle for three-plus weeks. Steelers CB Jalen Ramsey (hamstring) was sidelined today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c569-d94a-a79d-cd6d08910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c572-dd4c-afb9-e7f34ac50000</link>
      <description>Jennings missed Week 5 with the pair of injuries after playing through them in Week 4. San Francisco’s practice report is riddled with players who returned from various injuries too quickly, only to re-aggravate them and return to the sidelines. They will likely be extra cautious with Jennings, Brock Purdy, and Ricky Pearsall this time around. Kendrick Bourne, who saw 11 targets in Week 5, appears to be Mac Jones’ top wideout for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c572-dd4c-afb9-e7f34ac50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Rams are “interested in retaining” S Quentin Lake “if a deal makes sense.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c557-dd4c-afb9-e7d7937d0000</link>
      <description>Lake primarily lines up over the slot, but he has notably logged 89 combined defensive snaps lining up on the defensive line, in the box and at free safety this season. He boasts team highs in pass breakups (six ) and TFLs (five), ranks third on the team in tackles (25) and ties for seventh in quarterback pressures (four). The 2022 sixth-round pick should get a healthy pay bump, be it from the Rams or another team, this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c557-dd4c-afb9-e7d7937d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler added Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile and Rams DC Chris Shula to his list of “young defensive coaches” who could be head coaching candidates.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c580-d94a-a79d-cd8de1f60000</link>
      <description>Fowler previously named Chargers DC Jesse Minter and Packers DC Jeff Hafley and head coaching candidates in 2026. His list includes two new additions. Campanile is just five games into his tenure and is coming off an impressive showing against the Chiefs on Monday Night Football. Fowler notes that although the Jaguars “gave up yards against the Chiefs,” the defense “was highly disruptive and confused Patrick Mahomes in the biggest moment of the game,” a 99-yard pick-six from LB Devin Lloyd. We expect Campanile to remain in Jacksonville for 2026 at the very least, but the young defensive coordinator deserves credit for turning around a unit that was among the league’s worst in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c580-d94a-a79d-cd8de1f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c57c-d94a-a79d-cd7db9e70000</link>
      <description>It was a limited session for the rookie pass-rusher. Stewart suffered his ankle injury in Week 2 and has been out ever since. Today was his first practice since going down. It was only a limited session and he will likely need to get up to a full practice before retaking the field, but this is at least a step in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c57c-d94a-a79d-cd7db9e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c590-d94a-a79d-cd9d96d50000</link>
      <description>The injury’s severity has not yet been disclosed. As is the case with many head coaches, Saints head coach Kellen Moore reportedly tried to keep things vague when breaking the news to reporters, but he ultimately confirmed that the veteran running back did suffer a new injury today. Kamara has played through lower-body ailments on more than one occasion, and he will undoubtedly do so again this week if the training staff clears him. In the meantime, Saints No. 2 RB Kendre Miller must be rostered in 10- and 12-team leagues at this time. Kamara narrowly out-touched him, 12-11, last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c590-d94a-a79d-cd9d96d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c599-def2-abdb-ddf91a610000</link>
      <description>The Packers opened Watson’s practice window this week, meaning he is eligible to return from injured reserve at any point. He is still recovering from the torn ACL he suffered late in the 2024 season, but it appears to be going as well as anyone could have hoped for. It’s unlikely he plays this week, but Watson is nearing a return. Fantasy managers can begin to roster him in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c599-def2-abdb-ddf91a610000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
