<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Browning completed 14-of-25 passes for 125 yards in the Bengals’ 28-3, Week 4 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98de-d95b-addb-f8ded9ca0000</link>
      <description>Browning and the Bengals actually scored first in this one, effectively matriculating the ball downfield on the opening drive before coming away with three points. Once the scripted plays were gone, things fell apart. That was their only drive totaling more than six plays. They went three-and-out four times. To Browning’s credit, he was willing to target Ja’Marr Chase in tight coverage early, but the two simply failed to connect on Browning’s deep passes. Browning also rushed three times for four yards. He is a low-end QB2 against the Lions in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98de-d95b-addb-f8ded9ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Marr Chase caught 5-of-8 targets for 23 yards in the Bengals’ Week 4 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98f2-d95b-addb-f8f649110000</link>
      <description>This was tough to watch. The Bengals’ fill-in starter, QB Jake Browning, was willingly targeting Chase in tight coverage early on. On the ninth play from scrimmage, Browning unbelievably failed to notice Chase streaking downfield on a post route with no safety in sight, instead choosing to throw short to WR Mitchell Tinsley. Later in the game, Chase could be seen exasperatedly pleading his case to head coach Zac Taylor, who evidently had no answers. Chase is a borderline WR1/2 against the Lions next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98f2-d95b-addb-f8f649110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins caught 3-of-6 targets for 32 yards in the Bengals’ Week 4 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98e5-deb6-a7fd-dbffdac70000</link>
      <description>Higgins had a ceiling game when these teams faced off in Week 17 last year. The Bengals’ No. 2 wide receiver was seemingly headed toward a useful stat line this time, catching 2-of-3 targets for 25 yards on the first drive. The first of which was an acrobatic, contested back-shoulder reception. He then proceeded to catch just one pass for the rest of the night. Head coach Zac Taylor was unable to call an effective game once the opening script was used up. Higgins is just a WR3/FLEX with upside against the Lions next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98e5-deb6-a7fd-dbffdac70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase Brown rushed 10 times for 40 yards in the Bengals’ Week 4 loss to the Broncos, adding 3 receptions for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98f7-d95b-addb-f8f792710000</link>
      <description>Brown arguably functioned as the Bengals’ offensive focal point early on. He totaled seven combined carries and targets on his team’s first 16 plays. He was the only Bengals running back to log more than one carry all evening, and his 31 yards receiving were the second-most among Bengals pass catchers. The offense petered out after the opening script, however, and he was unable to deliver a usable stat line. Brown is a borderline RB2/3 against the Lions in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-98f7-d95b-addb-f8f792710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Jonathan Jones reports Tyreek Hill’s knee injury could keep him sidelined into the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9a84-deb6-a7fd-dbdf2c6f0000</link>
      <description>The horrific knee injury Hill sustained in Monday night’s win over the Jets, according to Jones, is “among the more devastating knee injuries you see in football” and could require more than a year of recovery time. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said Hill, 31, is facing “major reconstruction surgery of multiple ligaments.” Hill had to have his leg stabilized by medical staff before he could be carted to the locker room Monday night. His injury was among the most gruesome of the modern era, and could be career threatening. Hill has a potential out with his Dolphins contract — a path he seems likely to take after years of complaining about the franchise, his quarterback, and his head coach. Hill will likely be in another uniform next season if or when he’s ready to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9a84-deb6-a7fd-dbdf2c6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is “up in the air” for Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9aaf-deb6-a7fd-dbff478a0000</link>
      <description>Jackson left the Ravens’ Week 4 loss to the Chiefs with a hamstring injury and did not return to action. Head coach John Harbaugh said Jackson would not have re-entered the game even if the score had been closer, suggesting the hamstring issue is a longer-term issue for the superstar QB. If Jackson is sidelined this week against the Texans, Cooper Rush will be under center for Baltimore. That, of course, would be a major setback for the fantasy prospects of Zay Flowers, Mark Andrews, and the rest of the fantasy-relevant Ravens players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9aaf-deb6-a7fd-dbff478a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said he hopes QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9afa-d6e9-af9d-9afadb240000</link>
      <description>It’s become clear the Vikings will take their sweet time with getting McCarthy back into the lineup, if he gets his job back when he’s fully cleared. McCarthy is not wearing a boot or brace and is reportedly OK after his mysterious Week 2 ankle injury, which was only revealed after the game. Look for Carson Wentz to start this week against the Browns after completing 67 percent of his passes for four touchdowns and two interceptions over the past two outings. McCarthy should be on waiver wires for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9afa-d6e9-af9d-9afadb240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings OT Brian O’Neill (knee) is considered week to week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b25-deb6-a7fd-dbff4e050000</link>
      <description>O’Neill appears unlikely to suit up for the Vikings this week against a ferocious Browns front seven. The Vikings could be without multiple offensive line starters this week in London. Pro Football Focus grades O’Neill as 52nd out of 197 qualifying offensive linemen in pass blocking. Carson Wentz could face considering pressure against Myles Garrett and the Browns this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b25-deb6-a7fd-dbff4e050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) is questionable for Week 5 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b39-d95b-addb-fb7fec3f0000</link>
      <description>Purdy was an estimated DNP on Monday ahead of the Niners’ Thursday night game against the Rams. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said Purdy’s status remains “up in the air,” with Mac Jones ready to start for the 49ers if Purdy sits. “We will take every precaution to make sure Brock’s all right,” 49ers general manager John Lynch said, adding that Purdy had follow-up MRI exams on his toe following Week 4’s game against Jacksonsville. “I think he is. Now it’s just a matter of, can he turn it around on a short week?” Jones, meanwhile is dealing with a nagging knee injury that could limit his mobility. The Rams defense will be a good fantasy option against the injury-marred Niners offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b39-d95b-addb-fb7fec3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed WR Robbie Chosen, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b86-dca3-a9fb-bf9fbead0000</link>
      <description>The well-traveled journeyman will join the Washington practice squad ahead of Week 5. The Commanders are dealing with a spate of receiver injuries, including Terry McLaurin (quad) and Noah Brown (knee, groin). Chosen would only play a rotational role if he’s active for Week 5. He should remain on waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9b86-dca3-a9fb-bf9fbead0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
