<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5230-d56e-afff-f6f8661b0000</link>
      <description>Kamara will likely miss the remainder of the season with the knee and ankle issues. He hasn’t played since Week 12 and the Saints have been out of the playoff hunt for a while. They are only playing for a better draft pick at this point. With Kamara presumably out this week, Taysom Hill figures to lead the team in carries once again. He saw 12 rush attempts last week. Hill also caught four passes and threw one, a long touchdown to Chris Olave. He has entered the TE1 mix ahead of fantasy football championship week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5230-d56e-afff-f6f8661b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed C Ryan Kelly on injured reserve with a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5233-d56e-afff-f6fbbf260000</link>
      <description>Kelly has now suffered three concussions this season, and is up to six recorded concussions in his career. This is an extremely unfortunate end to Kelly’s first season in Minnesota. The talented center is still playing at a high level. His 82.2 PFF offense grade and 82.6 PFF run-blocking grade are both career bests. Kelly could choose to retire this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5233-d56e-afff-f6fbbf260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5233-d35e-a1bf-57f38afa0000</link>
      <description>MHJ returned from the heel injury last week. He was only targeted three times and caught just one pass for 14 yards. He is not on the fantasy radar for Week 17, but his return also put an end to Michael Wilson SZN. Wilson was also targeted just three times, though he did bring down two of his looks for 52 yards and a score. Wilson will sit on the WR3/4 border for his Week 17 matchup versus Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5233-d35e-a1bf-57f38afa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5230-d35e-a1bf-57f2f97b0000</link>
      <description>Henderson participated in warmups with the team during the portion of practice open to the media. We do not know whether Henderson did much in practice beyond that. Players often miss at least one game after suffering brain injuries, so his early-week participation is an encouraging sign for his Week 17 availability. Patriots veteran RB Rhamondre Stevenson should be rostered at this time, just in case Stevenson is unable to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5230-d35e-a1bf-57f2f97b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor (neck) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5248-d968-a19b-5af90d7c0000</link>
      <description>Taylor missed Week 16 with the neck issue and is on track to sit out at least one more game. He could ultimately miss the rest of the season, given that the Jets have nothing to play for over the next two weeks. Stone Smartt caught five passes for 34 yards in Taylor’s absence last week. He split reps with Jeremy Ruckert but does appear to be the preferred pass-catching option for the team. Smartt will sit on the TE2/3 border for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5248-d968-a19b-5af90d7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR DeMario Douglas (hamstring) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-522f-d35e-a1bf-57ef846c0000</link>
      <description>This is a bit surprising. Douglas exited Week 16 after suffering a hamstring injury. His early-week participation puts him on track to play. Hollins is not so lucky. The lanky speedster was sidelined on Wednesday by an abdominal injury, as was WR Kayshon Boutte (concussion). Rookie WR Kyle Williams would benefit if Hollins and Boutte are sidelined this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-522f-d35e-a1bf-57ef846c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter said he will likely have to revisit his shoulder injury in the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-524c-d968-a19b-5afd84b60000</link>
      <description>By “revisit,” we assume Carter means he will need to undergo surgery again. Carter told reporters he got multiple shots in both of his shoulders. The young defensive linemen underwent double shoulder surgery earlier this year. He is expected to return for Week 17 and play through the injuries for the remainder of the season. To no one’s surprise, Carter said he is not going to feel 100 percent during the final stretch of the Eagles’ season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-524c-d968-a19b-5afd84b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Romeo Doubs (wrist) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-524b-d56e-afff-f6ebdedd0000</link>
      <description>Doubs is good to go for the Packers’ Week 17 game against the Ravens. The Packers’ perimeter receiver is just a touchdown-dependent flex option though, having cleared 60 yards receiving just four times this season. The Packers’ quarterback situation is also concerning, with starting QB Jordan Love (concussion) and QB Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) both ailing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-524b-d56e-afff-f6ebdedd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell (calf) is practicing in full for Week 17 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-525a-dc7a-af9b-dfffd3d70000</link>
      <description>Mitchell was estimated as a limited participant for Tuesday’s walkthrough. A full practice today means he is good to go for Week 17. Mitchell touched the ball a season-high nine times last week but only managed 13 yards in total. He has as much home run potential as any back on a per-carry basis, but Mitchell is a dog to see double-digit touches in a game. He is stuck in the RB4 ranks for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-525a-dc7a-af9b-dfffd3d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (shoulder) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-525d-dc7a-af9b-dfffd2960000</link>
      <description>Watson played through chest and shoulder listings last week, catching just 2-of-6 targets for 17 yards after logging just two limited practice sessions. He briefly exited the game after colliding with WR Jayden Reed. Watson is seemingly in better health this week. Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) is also practicing fully this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-525d-dc7a-af9b-dfffd2960000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
