<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:06:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired Mike LaFleur as their new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1ab2-d042-afbc-7ff292da0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as an offensive intern with the Browns in 2014, studying under then-OC Kyle Shanahan. LaFleur followed Shanahan to the Falcons in 2015 after accepting an offensive assistant position. Evidently impressed with LaFleur’s development, Shanahan hired LaFleur as the 49ers’ passing game coordinator and wide receivers coach after Shanahan was hired as the team’s head coach in 2017. LaFleur shed the wide receivers coach title in 2019, and later accepted the Jets’ offensive coordinator position in 2021 after former 49ers DC Robert Saleh was hired as the Jets’ next head coach. LaFleur parted ways with the Jets in 2023 and was hired by Rams head coach Sean McVay as the Rams’ offensive coordinator. He has served in that capacity in each of the last three seasons, notably ceding play-calling duties to McVay, unlike his time in New York under Saleh. The Rams’ offense led the league in yards per play this season (6.1), while using creative play designs featuring play action, shifts and motion. LaFleur signed a five-year contract with his new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1ab2-d042-afbc-7ff292da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers hired Raheem Morris as their new defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa6-d89c-a1be-bfff10930000</link>
      <description>The news comes shortly after the Cardinals hired Rams OC Mike LaFleur as their next head coach. Morris was one of three finalists for that role. Morris now reunites with 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan. ESPN’s Adam Schefter notes that the two previously worked together with the Buccaneers (2004-2005), Commanders (2012-2013) and Falcons (2015-2016).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa6-d89c-a1be-bfff10930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Sean Duggan as their new defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-11cc-d042-afbc-7dde47070000</link>
      <description>The hiring reunites Duggan with former Packers DC and new Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley. Duggan, 32, entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as a Packers defensive assistant in 2024. He was promoted to linebackers coach in 2025, evidently impressing Hafley along the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-11cc-d042-afbc-7dde47070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings hired Ryan Nielsen as defensive run game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported today that Nielsen is being hired as the Vikings’ new defensive run game coordinator, though prior reporting suggested he may also coach the defensive line. He spent the 2025 season as a senior defensive assistant with the Bills. He served as the Jaguars (2024) and Falcons’ (2023) defensive coordinator in recent seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb is reportedly the “leading candidate” for the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy after interviewing for the role on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</link>
      <description>Webb, 31, withdrew from the Raiders’ head-coaching search late last week, after progressing through the second round of interviews. He also received requests to interview for the Ravens, Eagles, and Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancies and was previously linked to the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy. Only the Giants’ respective vacancy remains available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants completed an interview with former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz broke today’s news. He also reported back on January 6th, the same day Kingsbury parted ways with the Commanders, that Kingsbury was a candidate for the Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancy. Kingsbury has successfully schemed up offenses for mobile quarterbacks in the past. Giants QB Jaxson Dart fits the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports that NFL teams searching for a new defensive coordinator are “moving” on 49ers assistant head coach of defense Gus Bradley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers hired Raheem Morris as their new defensive coordinator earlier today, removing one high-profile candidate. Breer notes that either the Titans or Cardinals could hire Bradley as their next defensive coordinator, though the Cardinals’ ability to let Bradley call plays on defense gives them an “edge” over the Titans. He also notes that if the Titans miss out on Bradley, Falcons defensive pass-game coordinator Mike Rutenberg is “a name to watch.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland’s Mary Kay Cabot reports that the Browns plan to hire Jeff Blasko as their new tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1c0d-d89c-a1be-bfdf5da50000</link>
      <description>Blasko spent the 2025 season coaching Jets tight ends. He was hired by the Cowboys in 2020 as an assistant offensive line coach and was later promoted to run game coordinator and running backs coach in 2023. Blasko previously worked as an assistant offensive line coach for the Browns, alongside new head coach Todd Monken, back in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1c0d-d89c-a1be-bfdf5da50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced a multi-year deal with the City of Madrid and Comunidad de Madrid to host games beginning in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e81-d355-a5bd-9fd55e3d0000</link>
      <description>The NFL played its first Madrid game during the 2025 regular season and will now return to Madrid on a multi-year deal. The games will be played at Bernabéu Stadium, the home stadium for Real Madrid C.F. The league now has seven international games scheduled for the 2026 regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e81-d355-a5bd-9fd55e3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Steelers will interview Saints QBs coach Scott Tolzien for their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e8b-d355-a5bd-9fdf6c6c0000</link>
      <description>Tolzien joined the Saints for the 2025 season, but spent the previous five seasons with the Cowboys as a coaching assistant (2020 to 2022) and later as their QBs coach (2023 to 2024). His time with the Cowboys overlaps with Mike McCarthy’s tenure with the team, and he also spent three seasons with McCarthy while playing for the Packers. From a relationship standpoint, there’s a lot that makes sense about McCarthy’s interest in Tolzien, but this would be his first role as an offensive coordinator should he land the job, which could prove challenging given the current state of the Steelers’ roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1e8b-d355-a5bd-9fdf6c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
