<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tony Pollard (neck) is off Tennessee’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb8-d673-a39e-bfb974180000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full on both Thursday and Friday and should be good to go for the reeling Titans. Fantasy managers should treat Pollard as a low-end FLEX play given Tyjae Spears’ inroads into the running back platoon and the Chargers being favored by nearly 10 points on Sunday. There may not be much room — or much running in general — for more than a 40 total yard performance for Pollard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb8-d673-a39e-bfb974180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) is not on Tennessee’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bbb-d45b-affe-7fbf88b60000</link>
      <description>He was downgraded to DNP on Thursday, but bounced back with a full session on Friday to get off the questionable line. Okonkwo is nothing more than a mid-tier TE2 at this point, with a past month of 4/53, 6/46, and 4/48 results sandwiching a bagel in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bbb-d45b-affe-7fbf88b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs OT Jaylon Moore (illness) is questionable to play in Week 9 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb4-d713-ad9e-7ff46b990000</link>
      <description>Chiefs RG Trey Smith (back) joins Moore in the questionable column, while LT Josh Simmons (personal) has once again been ruled out. On the plus side, both Moore and Smith are expected to play, “barring setbacks.” This is a consequential game for the Chiefs (5-3) and the Bills (5-2) that could shift playoff seeding down the road. The Bills notably lost star DT Ed Oliver (biceps) for the season last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb4-d713-ad9e-7ff46b990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb2-d713-ad9e-7ff6ed220000</link>
      <description>McConkey was limited on Wednesday and Thursday before upgrading to full on Friday. The latter development is a good sign, though calf injuries are, of course, slightly worrying. The Chargers’ No. 1 wide receiver should be in fantasy lineups, though he carries at least minimal re-injury risk. Treat him as a WR1, per usual, against a fantasy-friendly Titans defense that just traded away its starting slot CB Roger McCreary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bb2-d713-ad9e-7ff6ed220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Pat Freiermuth (quad) is not on Pittsburgh’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bc7-d713-ad9e-7fd712140000</link>
      <description>He can be plugged right back into your TE2 spot if that’s what you want to do with your life. Outside of his 5/111/2 Thursday night explosion against the Bengals, Freiermuth has not cleared 31 yards or three catches all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bc7-d713-ad9e-7fd712140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions T Taylor Decker (shoulder) is questionable for Detroit’s Week 9 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bca-d713-ad9e-7fde9b110000</link>
      <description>Lions coach Dan Campbell said he expects him to play, and Decker continues to mostly suit up through this shoulder injury despite missing tons of practice time this season. It doesn’t look like Giovanni Manu will be needed this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bca-d713-ad9e-7fde9b110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) isn’t on Detroit’s final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bcc-d45b-affe-7fde635c0000</link>
      <description>He’s been trending in the right direction per Lions coach Dan Campbell and will wind up missing about three weeks with a shoulder injury that initially seemed likely to sideline him for the season. The Lions have been surrounding Amik Robertson with tons of depth pieces of late and will gladly welcome Arnold back into the fold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bcc-d45b-affe-7fde635c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) will not play in Detroit’s Week 9 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bce-d45b-affe-7fde0cf00000</link>
      <description>Dan Campbell has said that Joseph is “getting better, but it’s going to take a minute.” The safety left Week 7’s game against the Chiefs while trying to play through the injury. That update from Detroit’s head coach doesn’t sound promising for his status for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bce-d45b-affe-7fde0cf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Dolphins RB Ollie Gordon (ankle) is “day to day” with a sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bd0-d673-a39e-bfd181380000</link>
      <description>After the mini-bye, it’s possible that Gordon doesn’t miss much actual time. Perhaps he’ll get some maintenance days in practice this week. Gordon isn’t a must-roster at this point on standalone value but the Dolphins’ schedule in the fantasy playoffs makes him at least a somewhat-tempting hold in the event of a De’Von Achane injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bd0-d673-a39e-bfd181380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (hip) is not on Indianapolis’ final Week 9 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bd4-d713-ad9e-7fd43cff0000</link>
      <description>He’ll play and be a low-end FLEX dart against a Pittsburgh secondary that is hemorrhaging passing yards through the first eight weeks of the season. His return will cut into the ceilings for Alec Pierce and, perhaps, Tyler Warren. Michael Pittman remains the only sure-fire start in Indianapolis’ receiving corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3bd4-d713-ad9e-7fd43cff0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
