<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud (concussion) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17e-d82c-a79a-f3feab4f0000</link>
      <description>Stroud returned to practice last Tuesday but was downgraded to a DNP on Wednesday, the Texans’ final official practice before Thursday’s game. It seems like that was just maintenance for a player who had already been ruled out. Barring a setback, Stroud is on track to play in Week 13 against the Colts. Stroud will be a low-end QB2 in his first game since Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c17e-d82c-a79a-f3feab4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (concussion) will participate in a limited portion of practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c186-d90e-a9da-df8fdc320000</link>
      <description>McCarthy remains in the league’s concussion protocol but is making quick progress. Still, the Vikings appear to be prepping UDFA rookie Max Bromser to start. Bromser is taking the first-team reps in today’s practice. Given McCarthy’s struggles, this could be a chance for Bromser to take the job for the remainder of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c186-d90e-a9da-df8fdc320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said Max Brosmer will get the first-team reps in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c18a-d90e-a9da-df8f21350000</link>
      <description>J.J. McCarthy was at practice on Wednesday but only took part in individual drills. Brosmer is being prepared to start versus the Seahawks this week. The UDFA rookie will make his starting debut against a stout Seattle defense. He and the Vikings are also on the road for this game. Brosmer might be an upgrade over McCarthy, but he’s not even on the QB2 radar for fantasy purposes this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c18a-d90e-a9da-df8f21350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs OC Josh Grizzard compared Bucky Irving’s potential workload in Week 13 against the Cardinals to that of Chris Godwin in Week 12.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c18f-d82c-a79a-f39fbe2a0000</link>
      <description>Godwin returned to the lineup last week but was only on the field for 25-of-70 offensive snaps. Grizzard has mentioned multiple times that he does not expect Irving or Godwin to immediately play a full-time role in their first game back. He stuck to his word last week, and we would expect him to do so again on Sunday, assuming Irving is cleared for action. Normally a locked-in RB1, Irving will be a high-risk RB2 for his first game since Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c18f-d82c-a79a-f39fbe2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Packers did not activate WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) from injured reserve ahead of their Week 13 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c192-d90e-a9da-df9f79710000</link>
      <description>The Packers made a flurry of personnel moves on Wednesday, preparing the game-day roster for their Thanksgiving showdown against the division-rival Lions. Reed’s activation was not among them. The shifty slot receiver underwent two surgeries in September. One to correct a Jones fracture in his foot, the other to repair a broken collarbone. We do not yet know Reed’s Wednesday participation status. He logged three straight limited sessions, dating back to last Friday. He has a chance to return next week, when the Packers face the Bears in Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c192-d90e-a9da-df9f79710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived K Lucas Havrisik.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c199-d90e-a9da-df9f646a0000</link>
      <description>In three games with the Packers this season, Havrisik converted 4-of-4 field goals and 7-of-9 extra point attempts. His services are no longer needed with K Brandon McManus (quad) off the injury report. The Packers also signed WR Will Sheppard to the active roster and elevated LB Jamon Johnson and S Jaylin Simpson from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c199-d90e-a9da-df9f646a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (appendicitis) resumed practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a1-d6c4-abfb-d7a376a50000</link>
      <description>Harrison’s return puts him on track to play in Week 13 against the Buccaneers. He is expected to face stiffer target competition from WR Michael Wilson, who OC Drew Petzing said will be put “higher in the progression,” even with Harrison back on the field. Harrison’s productivity has been extremely volatile this season. Consider him a boom-bust WR2/3 in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a1-d6c4-abfb-d7a376a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed Cam Akers, formerly of the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c19b-d6c4-abfb-d79b78e10000</link>
      <description>Seahawks third-string running back George Holani is a candidate for injured reserve after suffering a hamstring injury in Week 12. Assuming he is placed on IR, Akers will take over his role for at least four games. The consummate system-knower, Akers has never directly crossed paths with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak, but has spent most of his career in similar systems via Sean McVay and Kevin O’Connell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c19b-d6c4-abfb-d79b78e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a8-d90e-a9da-dfafcda50000</link>
      <description>Bears LBs Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder) and LB Noah Sewell (elbow) were both sidelined again as well. The team needs these players to get healthy after placing LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) on injured reserve last weekend. The Eagles’ ground game should have a fruitful outing in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c1a8-d90e-a9da-dfafcda50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
