<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes Wink Martindale is an “early favorite” for the Jets defensive coordinator role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e78d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf5cff0000</link>
      <description>“The ’23 Giants tied for the league lead with 31 takeaways, which has to intrigue the turnover-starved Jets. Glenn jumped on Martindale early, interviewing him before the Jets’ season ended,” Cimini adds. Martindale had DC interviews with the Falcons and Colts last offseason and would certainly make the Jets more bombastic in one way or another. The Jets are the only team that has interviewed him in the 2026 offseason that we know of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e78d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf5cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Marc Raimondi reports that Bears assistant GM Ian Cunninham and 49ers director of scouring and football operations Josh Williams are “front runners” for Atlanta’s general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e790-d35e-a1bf-e7d2b15a0000</link>
      <description>Both also interviewed for Atlanta’s hand-created-for-Matt-Ryan “president of football” position, and the Falcons appear to have used those interviews as a starting point for their general manager position. Neither has come back for a second interview yet, with Atlanta only just announcing some new interviews for GM candidates today after spending the early offseason on the head coach and (ugh) “president of football” positions. Cunningham has ties to Ryan through his boss, Bears GM Ryan Poles, who played with Ryan at Boston College.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e790-d35e-a1bf-e7d2b15a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Eagles senior personnel director and advisor to the general manager Joe Douglas for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7a6-d968-a19b-fff7a3b20000</link>
      <description>Douglas spent the 2025 season in his current role, following a six-year stint as the Jets’ general manager. Before that, he served as the Eagles’ vice president of player personnel from 2016-2019. He was hired as the Bears’ director of college scouting in 2015 after spending 2000-2014 as a scout with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7a6-d968-a19b-fff7a3b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams designated RT Rob Havenstein (ankle/knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7bd-d56e-afff-e7fd2ae20000</link>
      <description>A high-ankle sprain plagued Havenstein for much of the season. He also reportedly added a knee injury to mix, shortly before being placed on injured reserve in mid-November. Getting their right tackle back in time for this week’s game against the Seahawks would be great for the Rams’ offense. He resumed practicing on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7bd-d56e-afff-e7fd2ae20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots designated WR Mack Hollins (abdomen) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e776-dc7a-af9b-efff51330000</link>
      <description>Hollins resumed practicing today, which gives him a chance to suit up for the Patriots’ AFC Championship Game against the Broncos. Hollins is a reliable blocker and a streaky producer, operating as a speedy field-stretcher for the Patriots. His return could reduce WR Kayshon Boutte’s snap share, though Boutte has caught 7-of-9 targets for 141 yards and one touchdown in two postseason games. He has a chance to retain the starting role even if Hollins returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e776-dc7a-af9b-efff51330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired Jesse Minter as their new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7cd-d56e-afff-e7ed33860000</link>
      <description>Minter, 42, served as the Chargers’ defensive coordinator under head coach Jim Harbaugh over the last two seasons. He also held the same role with Harbaugh’s Michigan squad from 2022-2023. He had a one-year stint at Vanderbilt, serving as defensive coordinator and safeties coach. He worked for former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh before that, signing on as a defensive assistant in Baltimore from 2017-2018. He was promoted to assistant defensive backs coach in 2019 and promoted again to defensive backs coach in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7cd-d56e-afff-e7ed33860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills completed an interview with Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7d7-d56e-afff-e7ff02410000</link>
      <description>Anarumo spent the 2025 serving as the Colts’ defensive coordinator after being fired by the Bengals in 2024. He held the same position with them for six years. Anarumo also received interview requests from the Giants and Titans during this interview cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7d7-d56e-afff-e7ff02410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</link>
      <description>Davis still has a chance to clear the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol, but he will probably need to upgrade to full participation tomorrow. Davis leads the team with 12 pass breakups this season. It would be great to have him on the field for New England’s AFC Championship Game against the Broncos, though Denver may opt for a run-heavy approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (shoulder) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</link>
      <description>Henderson is practicing fully this week, so his availability for the Patriots’ AFC Championship Game against the Broncos’ top-tier defense is not in jeopardy. He will continue sharing the backfield workload with veteran RB Rhamondre Stevenson, who is playing very well at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</link>
      <description>Landry still has a chance to play, though it would be nice to see him resume practicing tomorrow. The veteran pass rusher ranks third on the team in quarterback pressures (50), second in sacks (nine) and 10th in tackles (28). Patriots LB Marte Mapu (hip) was also absent on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
