<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce Jr. (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-598d-dfde-a1bd-5f8da1000000</link>
      <description>The first-round rookie has already made his presence known with two QB hits, eight pressures, and half-credit on a sack. Losing him this early in the year would be a frustrating blow for a young Atlanta defense. With cornerback A.J. Terrell also banged up, the Falcons could be without multiple starters on defense heading into Week 3 versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-598d-dfde-a1bd-5f8da1000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5991-dfde-a1bd-5f9dfa5e0000</link>
      <description>Mooney missed most of training camp and Week 1 with the shoulder injury. He was back for Week 2 but will likely be a mainstay of the Falcons’ injury report as the team attempts to keep him fresh. Mooney ran every single route for the Falcons last week and earned four targets. He only turned that into two catches for 20 yards, but better days should be ahead for the veteran receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5991-dfde-a1bd-5f9dfa5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5995-dfde-a1bd-5f9d31ec0000</link>
      <description>This isn’t Darrisaw’s first full session of the year and The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reported earlier this week that there’s “no guarantee” the star left tackle is back for Week 3. Darrisaw is still working his way back from the torn ACL he suffered in 2024 and the Vikings are not going to take any risks by rushing him back into the lineup. Vikings Center Ryan Kelly missed Wednesday’s practice with a concussion and is unlikely to suit up this week. Carson Wentz is set to play behind a greatly diminished offensive line for his first start in Purple and Gold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5995-dfde-a1bd-5f9d31ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Shemar Stewart (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5998-d1b3-a5dd-59f999a10000</link>
      <description>Stewart went down in the Bengals’ Week 2 win over the Jags and was spotted on crutches after the game. NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reported earlier this week that Stewart is considered week-to-week. A DNP on Wednesday all but guarantees he will miss the Bengals’ Week 3 date with the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5998-d1b3-a5dd-59f999a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC 2 Houston’s Aaron Wilson reports Texans WR Justin Watson will be “sidelined indefinitely” with an Achilles injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-599d-d1b3-a5dd-59fd15310000</link>
      <description>Per Wilson, it’s not a torn Achilles for Watson and he is expected to return at some point this season. Watson was placed on injured reserve, meaning he will miss at least four weeks. Watson was playing ahead of rookies Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins. With Christian Kirk expected to return this week, the rookies may have to wait a little longer to see the field more often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-599d-d1b3-a5dd-59fd15310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks released CB Shaquill Griffin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59aa-d1b3-a5dd-59fb4ced0000</link>
      <description>Griffin was immediately signed to the Seahawks’ practice squad. The team signed wide receiver Cody White from their practice squad to the active roster in a corresponding move. They made the opposite pair of moves last week. This is what peak roster management looks like.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59aa-d1b3-a5dd-59fb4ced0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 3 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59b1-d93f-ad9d-5bf702be0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs also had Xavier Worthy and Jalen Royals at practice on Wednesday. Brown didn’t appear limited by the ankle issue in Week 2, though he did manage just five targets after earning 16 in Week 1. With Worthy possibly returning for Week 3, Brown is set to return to a secondary role in the offense. Assuming Worthy does suit up, Brown will tumble into the WR4 ranks versus the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59b1-d93f-ad9d-5bf702be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (biceps) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59bc-d93f-ad9d-5bff0fae0000</link>
      <description>McConkey popped up on the Chargers’ first injury report of the week with a biceps injury. He was not visibly hurt in the Chargers’ Week 2 win over the Raiders, making his inclusion to the injury report an eyebrow-raiser. We don’t have much information on the injury yet, so fantasy managers should stay tuned throughout the week for updates. Keenan Allen and Tre Harris will see boosts should McConkey miss Week 3 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59bc-d93f-ad9d-5bff0fae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (back) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59ce-dfde-a1bd-5fcf45ee0000</link>
      <description>Engram was dealing with a calf injury heading into Week 2 and is now listed with a back injury to start Week 3. The 31-year-old has been getting limited looks early on with the Broncos, though it is difficult to tell how much of that is Sean Payton’s affection for Adam Trautman and how much of that is the injuries. Starting out the week not practicing due to an injury different from last week’s is not a good omen for Engram. Even if he plays against the Chargers in Week 3, Engram is downgraded to streamer tight end range for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59ce-dfde-a1bd-5fcf45ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The D.C. City Council approved the Commanders to build a stadium at the old RFK Stadium site with a vote of 11-to-2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59d6-dfde-a1bd-5fdf9ba00000</link>
      <description>The Commanders and owner Josh Harris finally got their last leg of approval and will officially be opening a new stadium in Washington, D.C., set to open in 2030. The D.C. City Council gave their second and final approval for a $3.8 billion project to develop in and around the old RFK Stadium site. This will bring the Commanders back to Washington, D.C. for the first time in three decades. A 65,000-seat stadium and more development around the site is in store as the Commanders begin the process of making a monumental move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-59d6-dfde-a1bd-5fdf9ba00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
