<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) will not return in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeba-dc7a-af9b-efbf5a290000</link>
      <description>Poyer went down with the hamstring issue in the second quarter. He was listed as questionable to return but the team eventually ruled him out after halftime. The Bills’ secondary will be undermanned for the rest of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeba-dc7a-af9b-efbf5a290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Davis suffered a knee injury in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb3-d35e-a1bf-eff3175a0000</link>
      <description>Davis was crushed by multiple defenders while trying to bring down a pass from Josh Allen over the middle of the field. He was unable to put weight on his left and needed to be helped off by trainers before being carted to the locker room. With Josh Palmer on IR, the Bills are dangerously thin at receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb3-d35e-a1bf-eff3175a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Raiders and Dolphins have requested interviews with Packers defensive coordinator Jeff Hafley for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aec6-dc7a-af9b-efffb6910000</link>
      <description>Hafley is up to five head coaching interviews now. The Falcons, Cardinals, and Titans have also requested interviews with him. Hafley has held his current position in Green Bay for two seasons. The Packers ranked 11th in points allowed this year and sixth in 2024. He was Boston College’s head coach before joining the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aec6-dc7a-af9b-efffb6910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Raiders and Cardinals have requested interviews with Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed0-d968-a19b-fef1d5530000</link>
      <description>LaFleur was fired by the Jets in the midst of a dreadful 2022 season. He landed on his feet in LA and immediately oversaw a top-10 scoring offense. Things went even better in 2025. The Rams led the league in scoring this year and Matthew Stafford will likely win his first career MVP. LaFleur is well-connected with a strong resume behind him and hasn’t gotten his shot at a head coaching gig yet. In a relatively weak hiring cycle, this could be his year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed0-d968-a19b-fef1d5530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen completed 28-of-35 passes for 273 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ 27-24, Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars, adding 11 carries for 33 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed5-d56e-afff-eefdf07a0000</link>
      <description>The passing game wans’t always lively for the Bills, but, per usual, Allen came up big when it mattered most. His longest completion of the day by air distance was a 36-yard strike off his back foot to Brandin Cooks. The absurd toss late in the fourth quarter eventually set up his second rushing touchdown of the day. Allen took a beating in this game. He was checked for a concussion early, hit his throwing hand on a lineman’s helmet shortly after that, and even had his leg rolled up at one point as well. He will likely show up on the injury report ahead of the Divisional Round, but that won’t stop him from being the best fantasy option for next week’s slate of games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed5-d56e-afff-eefdf07a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 18-of-30 passes for 207 yards, three touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Jaguars’ 27-24, Wild Card Round loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aee8-d35e-a1bf-efea8d530000</link>
      <description>After transforming into one of the league’s best quarterbacks over the second half of the regular season, Lawrence turned back into a pumpkin on the biggest stage. Though he did score three times, his two interceptions were both on him. The second pick was a throw into tight coverage on the Jags’ final drive that was tipped and made its way into the hands of Bills safety Cole Bishop, ending the game. It’s a nightmare ending to an otherwise triumphant season for the franchise. Lawrence’s 18 passing scores over his final seven regular season games propelled him to 29 on the year. He also punched in nine touchdowns on the ground with 359 rushing yards. He finished the year as the QB4. Lawrence finally found himself in an elite offensive system in 2025 and blossomed over the final two months. The next step will be sustaining that level of success for an entire season. Fantasy managers will be taking him in the middle of the QB1 ranks when early drafts roll around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aee8-d35e-a1bf-efea8d530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught all 12 of his targets for 82 yards in the Bills’ Wild Card Round win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aef1-d35e-a1bf-eff379a20000</link>
      <description>Facing a stout Jacksonville run defense, the Bills chipped away at the Jags with check-downs and screens to Shakir. His 12 catches in this game are three more than his previous career-high. No one on the team other than Shakir logged more than five targets. All in, Shakir earned a 34 percent target share. With Josh Palmer on IR and Gabe Davis now banged up, expect to see plenty more of Shakir in the Divisional Round. He will be a strong play on full PPR sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aef1-d35e-a1bf-eff379a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington caught 7-of-12 targets for 107 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aef5-dc7a-af9b-efffc9190000</link>
      <description>Washington had been pulling away as the Jags’ No. 1 receiver leading into the postseason. He may now carry that status into 2026 after more than doubling up the team’s No. 2 wideout by targets in this game. That was despite missing some time for a concussion evaluation. Including the postseason, Washington topped 100 yards in three of his final four games. He was barely involved in the offense early in the season, but injuries to several key players, namely Travis Hunter, elevated him to a starting role. Washington never looked back and finished the season with 847 yards and five touchdowns on 58 grabs. With Hunter, Brian Thomas Jr., and Jakobi Meyers all under contract for multiple years, it’s unclear how things will shake out for the receiver room in 2026. This will be one of the most debated situations for 2026 fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aef5-dc7a-af9b-efffc9190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Raiders have requested permission to interview Panthers DC Ejiro Evero for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a0b2-d56e-afff-e6faa6f40000</link>
      <description>The same is reportedly true of the Falcons. Evero has been on something of a three-year journey in Carolina, overseeing a strong unit in 2023, a disastrous one in 2024, and respectable one in 2025. We would consider him a long shot for either opening, but he’s clearly a name getting around in league circles. He also interviewed for openings following 2023. Evero turned 45 earlier this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a0b2-d56e-afff-e6faa6f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 1-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af02-d968-a19b-fff3ee000000</link>
      <description>With Parker Washington erupting for over 100 yards plus a score and Brian Thomas Jr. getting a touchdown of his own, there simply wans’t room in the struggling Jags’ passing game for Meyers to do much. Acquired midseason by Jacksonville, Meyers was brought in to backfill Travis Hunter’s role as a short and intermediate target for Trevor Lawrence. Meyers caught at least four passes in all but one of his nine regular season games with the Jags. The only miss was in his Jacksonville debut. He ended the year with 75 catches for 835 yards and three scores. He posted slightly better per-game numbers during his regular season appearances with the Jags. Meyers is the stable option in the Jaguars’ receiver room, but he might also have the lowest ceiling heading into 2026. Fantasy managers will likely treat him as a WR4 in early drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-af02-d968-a19b-fff3ee000000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
