<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 03:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars RB Brenton Strange (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f0-d82c-a79a-b3f4ac480000</link>
      <description>Strange logged two limited sessions last week before being downgraded on Friday. He did not play on game day. At this point, he is difficult to trust, though typically, two limited sessions put a player on track to play. He is only a stash option at this time. Check back tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f0-d82c-a79a-b3f4ac480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d82c-a79a-b3f7cf730000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals are likely just being cautious with their presumed starter, though RB Trey Benson (knee) is matching Knight as a limited participant thus far. Benson could return this weekend, though next week seems more likely. Assuming Knight is the starter, he should be able to return FLEX value against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e7-d82c-a79a-b3f7cf730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f6-d82c-a79a-b3f618820000</link>
      <description>Benson has a chance to suit up this weekend, though one imagines the Cardinals’ coaching and medical staffs hope to see him get through a full practice before doing so. If active, he will likely split work with RB Bam Knight (ankle), but Benson could be a league-winner down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f6-d82c-a79a-b3f618820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (illness) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e3-d82c-a79a-b3f7be160000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers’ locker room has been hit hard by an illness this week. Egbuka is technically on track to play against the Rams this week, though it would be great to see him upgrade to full participation on Friday. Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) practiced fully today, putting him on track to play. Godwin will command safety attention, at least to some degree, when he gets back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3e3-d82c-a79a-b3f7be160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f8-db57-afda-f7faed990000</link>
      <description>An illness has pummeled Buccaneers players this week, but the tough-as-nails Mayfield, perhaps unsurprisingly, is back in action. The Buccaneers quarterback could have both WR Emeka Egbuka (illness) and WR Chris Godwin (fibula) on the field this week, as the team takes on the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3f8-db57-afda-f7faed990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a405-d90e-a9da-bf0faf5a0000</link>
      <description>Stevenson remains in the questionable camp, having failed to graduate to full participation today. He still has decent odds of suiting up in Week 12 against the Bengals, though. If active, he will likely handle more touches than many would like after rookie RB TreVeyon Henderson’s three-touchdown showing in Week 11, but one imagines Henderson will at least retain the lead back role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a405-d90e-a9da-bf0faf5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Austin Hooper (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a402-d90e-a9da-bf0f5bcb0000</link>
      <description>Hooper should not be rostered anywhere, having earned two targets or fewer since Week 3. He may end up stealing an opportunity from TE Hunter Henry, but Hooper is mostly paid to run cardio in between blocking reps. The Patriots face the Bengals in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a402-d90e-a9da-bf0f5bcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (hand/wrist) exited in the first quarter of Week 12’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a418-d82c-a79a-b79ca1170000</link>
      <description>Allen was flushed from the pocket in the first quarter and tackled from behind by Will Anderson, who hopped on Allen’s back and rode him to the ground. Allen came down hard on his right hand/wrist, which slammed hard into the turf, and was in visible pain immediately after. Trainers came to the field to evaluate him, and Allen appeared to have shook things off by the time he made it to the sideline and he never entered the medical tent. He looks as if he’ll be ready to go for the next drive, but we’ll check back in when we know more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a418-d82c-a79a-b79ca1170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (hand/wrist) returned in the first quarter of Week 12’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a41f-d413-ad9f-b5df041e0000</link>
      <description>His injury must’ve just been a stinger. Or perhaps we later learn Allen his more superhuman than initially believed. Regardless, the 2024 MVP did not miss a snap and immediately fired a 22-yard pass to Gabe Davis on his first play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a41f-d413-ad9f-b5df041e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “contractual technicalities” in Brandin Cooks’ contract has stalled his release.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a43a-d90e-a9da-bf3f76060000</link>
      <description>Cooks and the Saints still plan to part ways once these technicalities are resolved. The veteran receiver will likely be released in the coming days and will be free to sign wherever he pleases if he clears waivers. Cooks has caught 19 passes for 165 scoreless yards this season. Wherever he lands, he will be little more than added depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a43a-d90e-a9da-bf3f76060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
