<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he “feels good about [him] being able to go” when asked about WR Davante Adams (hamstring) ahead of practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-dca3-a9fb-bfbb6b740000</link>
      <description>Adams will be limited in practice today, per McVay, and officially be listed as questionable. It seems likely that Adams will play based on how this sets up today, but hamstring injuries are tricky and Adams-reliant managers should have backup plans ready to go for Sunday if need be. Adams would remain on the WR2 line against the Colts if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-dca3-a9fb-bfbb6b740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid said WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) is expected to play.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbd6bb0000</link>
      <description>Worthy will reportedly sport a harness on his injured shoulder and it seems likely that he will be limited to some sort of snap count. Decoy treatment is possible, as are a handful of plays designed to feature his speed, ideally along the sideline so he can avoid contact by stepping out of bounds post-catch. Worthy must be treated as a boom-bust WR3 option, though the Ravens are currently allowing the second-most passing yards per game (266.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbd6bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers (shoulder) is not on New York’s final Week 4 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8748-deb6-a7fd-d7df22430000</link>
      <description>As expected, Nabers will start and play against the Chargers in Week 4. We’re expecting some target shuffling for the Giants with Jaxson Dart running the show, but nothing that should make Nabers anything but a WR1 play at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8748-deb6-a7fd-d7df22430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers ruled out RG Mekhi Becton (concussion) for Week 4 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8755-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa2c00000</link>
      <description>Neither Becton nor TE Will Dissly practiced all week. Dissly is sidelined by a knee injury, as is backup WR Derius Davis. C Bradley Bozeman was a limited participant on Thursday and Friday, nursing a back injury. Chargers RT Trey Pipkins III successfully rehabbed his knee injury to the point that he was able to practice in full over the last two days. If Pipkins can go, the Chargers have decent odds of holding their own against the Giants’ pass rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8755-deb6-a7fd-d7dfa2c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RT Darnell Wright (elbow) will not play in Chicago’s Week 4 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875c-d95b-addb-ef5e7ed90000</link>
      <description>The Bears also ruled out T.J. Edwards (hamstring) and Grady Jarrett (knee), none of the three players practiced at any point this week. Edwards will be missing his second game in a row. Wright’s absence will force Chicago into it’s tackle depth, perhaps leading to a start for Theo Benedet on the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875c-d95b-addb-ef5e7ed90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 4 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875f-dca3-a9fb-bfdf22540000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited sessions to create essentially the same situation he did last week, when he played off a questionable tag against the Cowboys. Nothing that Swift has done on the field in the first three weeks has looked especially promising, but he’s a starting running back against the Raiders, so he’s on the RB2 line for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-875f-dca3-a9fb-bfdf22540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) is questionable for Chicago’s Week 4 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8760-d6e9-af9d-8ff0e4ce0000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session for the first time all week on Friday. Loveland is not a worthwhile starter in fantasy leagues at this point as his volume is simply too low, but there’s still every chance that could change this year as the Bears start to get more used to what they have in him. Loveland is merely a TE2 until we see further signs of development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8760-d6e9-af9d-8ff0e4ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers ruled out TE Will Dissly (knee) for Week 4 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-deb6-a7fd-d7ffbaf80000</link>
      <description>Dissly is not fantasy-relevant on his own, but his absence frees up offensive snaps for Chargers rookie TE Oronde Gadsden II, who caught five targets for 46 yards in his first career game last week. Gadsden is worth stashing in 12-team leagues to see if Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh makes good on his stated intent to give Gadsden more opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-873b-deb6-a7fd-d7ffbaf80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans QB Cam Ward (ankle/calf) is not on Tennessee’s final Week 4 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-876f-d6e9-af9d-8fffc6000000</link>
      <description>It turns out that his limited practice on Wednesday was just a small breather for the rookie quarterback. He’ll be tough to trust against the Texans in Week 4, but with Derek Stingley (oblique) expected to sit, there’s a chance he’ll provide QB2 production in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-876f-d6e9-af9d-8fffc6000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) is questionable for Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-876d-dca3-a9fb-bffd30a50000</link>
      <description>Team reporter Jeff Zrebiec believes “Likely has a very good chance of making his season debut Sunday” after practicing in full on Friday. In June, Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said he wants to see Likely be “an All-Pro” this season. The team has handled Likely’s recovery smartly, so they are unlikely to throw caution to the wind. He can only be started as a boom-bust TE2 against the Chiefs. He should be rostered everywhere. Ravens LT Ronnie Stanley (ankle), OLB Kyle Van Noy (hamstring) and NT Travis Jones (knee) are all questionable. Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf), DT Broderick Washington (ankle) and DT Nnamdi Madubuike (neck) have been ruled out. Madubuike leads the team with 10 quarterback pressures and two sacks despite sitting out in Week 3. Madubuike, Washington and Jones anchor Baltimore’s 3-4 defense. Patrick Mahomes should be very comfortable in the pocket this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-876d-dca3-a9fb-bffd30a50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
