<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 6-of-9 targets for 57 yards and a touchdown in the Colts’ Week 9 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b5-d1e7-a1fa-5effe3cb0000</link>
      <description>Downs pushed his touchdown streak to three-straight games in this one after connecting with Daniel Jones for a four-yard score in the waning minutes. His nine targets set a new season high, but the Colts also dropped back an absurd 56 times in what was really a blowout loss despite the 27-20 final score. Downs is running hot, averaging 14.6 PPR points per game over his last three weeks, but over 40 percent of his fantasy production has come from touchdowns. He’ll make for a decent play in deep leagues next week against the Falcons but shouldn’t be viewed as much more than a WR3/WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b5-d1e7-a1fa-5effe3cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 12 times for 46 yards in the Falcons’ Week 9 loss to the Patriots, adding eight catches for 50 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b3-d673-a39e-e6b3fc3b0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons offense continues to run through Robinson as he saw 10 targets from Michael Penix Jr. on the day. Screen passes, checkdowns, and other movement behind the line of scrimmage to get Robinson going led to his eight receptions for 50 yards, though he went scoreless on the day. His longest run went for 15 yards, though the Falcons seldom ran the ball in the red zone; Drake London instead made three excellent catches for short scores. A 20-touch day shows Robinson’s consistent floor and the 23-year-old remains a high-end RB1 for Week 10 against the Colts in Berlin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b3-d673-a39e-e6b3fc3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 5-of-7 targets for 26 yards in the Colts’ Week 9 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46bc-d673-a39e-e6bd6d3f0000</link>
      <description>Warren’s seven targets were good for the second-most he’s seen in a game this season, but in a game where three Colts pass-catchers went for 50-plus yards, Warren was on the outside looking in. The rookie tight end was bottled up by the Steelers defense all afternoon, and never went for more than nine yards on any of his five receptions. His biggest play was a Daniel Jones fumble he recovered to keep a drive alive in the fourth quarter with the game already out of reach. Warren hasn’t run quite as hot as had been in previous weeks, but he still remains a must-start at a position that doesn’t offer a lot of upside. He’ll be on the TE1 radar in Week 10 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46bc-d673-a39e-e6bd6d3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Marr Chase caught 6-of-8 targets for 111 yards in the Bengals’ Week 9 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46bf-d45b-affe-57bf1a630000</link>
      <description>Chase was almost entirely uninvolved in the first half as the Bears double and triple teamed him, leaving Tee Higgins open down the field. Chase was third among Bengals pass catchers in targets and saw a relatively meager 20 percent of the team’s air yards. It was quite the role change for Chase, who had seen 54 targets over the previous three games as the apple of Joe Flacco’s eye. The pass heavy nature of the Flacco-era Bengals should continue giving Chase as much upside as any player in fantasy football. He’ll face the Steelers in Week 11 following the team’s Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46bf-d45b-affe-57bf1a630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-5 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 9 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b3-d1e7-a1fa-5efbae650000</link>
      <description>Getting healthier by the week, Jennings has now established a floor of four catches, a mark he has hit in three straight games. The bad news is that he hasn’t topped 45 yards since Week 2. His 11-yard score today was also his first touchdown since Week 2. Jennings is getting the job done but doesn’t have much of a ceiling. He will remain a solid WR3 option if Ricky Pearsall remains out for Week 10 when he and the 49ers take on the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46b3-d1e7-a1fa-5efbae650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed 10 times for 36 yards in the Vikings’ Week 9 win over the Lions, adding a one-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c0-d45b-affe-57d6d16f0000</link>
      <description>Mason was predictably taking a backseat to Aaron Jones until AJ injured his shoulder midway through the third quarter. It was all Mason from there on out, though as has been his theme this season, he did not produce exciting returns. Jones has reportedly escaped with only a sprained AC joint, and is tentatively expected to suit up for Week 10 against the Ravens’ soft run defense. Despite the matchup, Jones’ good health would render Mason a low-floor FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c0-d45b-affe-57d6d16f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed two times for 6 yards in the Falcons’ Week 9 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c1-d673-a39e-e6d105a20000</link>
      <description>Allgeier saw just two carries after getting in three limited practices due to a knee issue this week. The Falcons run game was not the team’s strength against the Pats and Robinson saw all the passing game usage as Atlanta trailed for most of the game. Allgeier is a premier handcuff moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c1-d673-a39e-e6d105a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle caught all four of his targets for 32 yards in the 49ers’ Week 9 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c2-d673-a39e-e6d336ce0000</link>
      <description>Kittle posted a nearly identical stat line as last week, this time without a touchdown to save his fantasy managers. He now has four catches in back-to-back games. On the other hand, Kittle has yardage totals of 0, 43, and 32 since returning from injured reserve. The floor appears to be intact, but we haven’t seen a ceiling game from the superstar tight end this year. While it’s been a frustrating year for fantasy drafters who selected Kittle, he remains in the top half of the TE1 mix for his Week 10 date with the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c2-d673-a39e-e6d336ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden II caught 5-of-5 targets for 68 yards in the Chargers’ Week 9 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c7-d1e7-a1fa-5eefbb7c0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden has now cleared 60 yards receiving in four straight games, while today was the second time during that timespan he led the Bolts in receiving. That is the long way of saying his production is for real and seemingly not going away. A glorified wideout up the seam, Gadsden is both compiling and offering big-play potential. That is all anyone can reasonably hope for out of their TE1. There are still going to be weeks where Gadsden ends up going 3/30 considering his target competition, but he simply can’t be left on fantasy benches ahead of Week 10 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c7-d1e7-a1fa-5eefbb7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught both of his targets for 34 yards in the 49ers’ Week 9 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c8-d673-a39e-e6d9bea10000</link>
      <description>Bourne began October with a pair of 142-yard games as the 49ers dealt with a slew of skill position injuries. He has totaled seven catches for 92 scoreless yards in three games since. With George Kittle and Jauan Jennings healthy, Bourne is off the fantasy radar heading into Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46c8-d673-a39e-e6d9bea10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
