<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 04:02:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said WR Zay Jones is in the concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73a0-dfde-a1bd-7fad4e160000</link>
      <description>Gannon added that the injury occurred on the team’s last offensive play of the game in their Week 3 loss to the 49ers. Jones has played around 50 percent of the offensive snaps in each of the first three games this season. Any missed time could provide more run for veteran slot man Greg Dortch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73a0-dfde-a1bd-7fad4e160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) was listed as a full participant on the team’s estimated practice report Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73b0-d93f-ad9d-7bf74d810000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks did not hold a practice Monday as they prepare to face the Cardinals on a short week, but the team’s listing of Charbonnet as a full participant is nonetheless striking after he missed Week 3 with a foot injury. Kenneth Walker managed just 53 percent of the team’s offensive snaps in the Week 3 win, the size of which can likely be explained by the extremely positive game script the Seahawks found themselves in against the Saints. It will be interesting to see how the snap and opportunity rates shake out should Charbonnet return to the lineup on Thursday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73b0-d93f-ad9d-7bf74d810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 20-of-28 passes for 202 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ 38-80, Week 3 win over the Lions, adding six yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73cd-dfde-a1bd-7fcdfd360000</link>
      <description>Goff’s 28 pass attempts were a product of the team’s successes on the ground, with David Montgomery (151 yards and two touchdowns) and Jahmyr Gibbs (67 yards and two touchdowns) taking over the game in the second half. The veteran signal caller made numerous elite throws, the highlight of which came on fourth down with just over two minutes remaining in the fourth quarter when he dropped a dime into the bread basket of alpha wide receiver Amon-Ra St. Brown. That drive would eventually culminate in a 31-yard Montgomery touchdown to push the lead to 14 points, a lead the Lions would not relinquish as they vault into a tie atop the NFC North with the Packers and Vikings. Up next for Goff and the Lions is a matchup against the surprisingly stout Cleveland defense in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-73cd-dfde-a1bd-7fcdfd360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed 12 times for 151 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens, adding 13 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7499-dfde-a1bd-7e9dacf20000</link>
      <description>Montgomery played well behind backfield mate Jahmyr Gibbs as far as snap rate and opportunity count are concerned. He put the Lions on his back when it mattered most, however, with carries of 72 yards and 31 yards in the fourth quarter, the latter of which put the Lions up by 14 points with under two minutes to play as he found paint for the second time. The bulk of Montgomery’s fantasy value remains tied to his high touchdown expectancy in one of the league’s top offenses, making him a more difficult weekly start than others drafted around him this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7499-dfde-a1bd-7e9dacf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 22 times for 67 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens, adding 32 yards on five receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a3-d1b3-a5dd-75f37e860000</link>
      <description>Gibbs handled 22 carries and six targets to the 13 opportunities of David Montgomery, but it was the latter back that stole the show while amassing 151 yards and two scores on the ground. Even so, the 28 opportunities were the most in a game in which Montgomery also was on the field during Gibbs’ three-year NFL career - a solid sign for what is to come for the talented back. Gibbs could find the sledding difficult again in Week 4 against a Cleveland defense leading the league in yards allowed per carry through three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a3-d1b3-a5dd-75f37e860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amon-Ra St. Brown caught 7-of-8 targets for 77 yards and a touchdown in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a7-dfde-a1bd-7eaf2a2e0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown remained an integral part of the offense on a night quarterback Jared Goff attempted just 28 passes. He also contributed to a touchdown run by Jahmyr Gibbs on a fourth down trick play to start the fourth quarter, during which he took a handoff from Jared Goff before pitching the football to Gibbs on the perimeter. He would also come up big late in the game when he caught a 20-yard dime from Goff on fourth-and-two while up by seven points. St. Brown can continue to be counted on as a weekly WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74a7-dfde-a1bd-7eaf2a2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 2-of-3 targets for 43 yards in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ab-dfde-a1bd-7eaf63430000</link>
      <description>Williams notched both of his receptions on the first drive of the game before disappearing from the game plan as Jahmyr Gibbs and David Montgomery dominated the work. He now has just 12 targets through three games, laying fantasy duds in all but his Week 2, 2-108-1 receiving line on four targets. Fantasy managers should remain patient with the talented fifth-year receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ab-dfde-a1bd-7eaf63430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam LaPorta caught all four targets for 33 yards in the Lions’ Week 3 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ae-dfde-a1bd-7eafeb980000</link>
      <description>LaPorta did most of his damage on third downs to move the chains, beating both man and zone coverage in key situations for the Lions. Quarterback Jared Goff attempted only 28 passes on a night Jahmyr Gibbs and David Montgomery stole the show, meaning fantasy managers will want to stay patient with the young tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ae-dfde-a1bd-7eafeb980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson completed 21-of-27 passes for 288 yards and three touchdowns in the Ravens’ 38-30, Week 3 loss to the Lions, adding 35 yards on seven carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b1-d93f-ad9d-7ef720760000</link>
      <description>The two-time MVP was sacked seven times while the Ravens managed only 54 offensive plays. The low play volume was largely caused by two long touchdown drives by the Lions, one for 96 yards and one for 98 yards, which combined to take 14:29 off the clock. Jackson got tight end Mark Andrews back on the fantasy radar with two touchdown passes to the veteran tight end, although the frustrating loss drops the Ravens to 1-2 ahead of a meeting with the Chiefs in Week 4. This is one that can’t be attributed to the perennial MVP candidate’s play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b1-d93f-ad9d-7ef720760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 12 times for 50 yards, one touchdown, and one fumble in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b6-d1b3-a5dd-75f794290000</link>
      <description>Henry lost a fumble deep in his own territory half way through the fourth quarter with the team down by four points, gifting the Lions a comfortable lead that they would not relinquish. His night started off hot as he would score from 28 yards out on the team’s first possession, but he managed just 22 yards on his other 11 carries against a stout Detroit defensive front. Things don’t get easier for the King when the Ravens travel to Kansas City to face the Chiefs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74b6-d1b3-a5dd-75f794290000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
