<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent K Eddy Pineiro worked out for the Bills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f258-de13-afdc-f6db93ee0000</link>
      <description>Fellow free agent kickers Zane Gonzalez and Greg Joseph also worked out for the Bills. Incumbent K Tyler Bass struggled last season and dealt with a pelvis injury in training camp. The Bills are likely just covering their bases, but Bass could be a risky fantasy pick at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f258-de13-afdc-f6db93ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers acquired Micah Parsons from the Cowboys in exchange for two first-round picks and DT Kenny Clark, and signed him to a four-year, $188 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f230-dbe3-a9bb-f273b7d60000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the extension “includes $120 million fully guaranteed at signing and makes Parsons the highest-paid non-QB in NFL history.” The Packers now field a formidable EDGE rush, with Parsons bookended by DL Rashan Gary. Clark, meanwhile, will line up next to DT Osa Odighizuwa, providing the Cowboys a solid, if unexciting, defensive tackle unit. The development undeniably downgrades the Cowboys’ ability to rush the passer, though, which puts the onus on the offense to keep the team in games. The Cowboys’ passing offense just became even more fantasy-friendly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f230-dbe3-a9bb-f273b7d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed OG Trevor Keegan, formerly of the Eagles, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f27f-dbe3-a9bb-f27f71390000</link>
      <description>Keegan appeared in one game for the Eagles last year and earned a 65.3 PFF run-blocking grade for his efforts. He will likely compete for a backup role with the Cowboys, who correspondingly waived WR Ryan Flournoy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f27f-dbe3-a9bb-f27f71390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Kendrick Bourne will visit the 49ers on Monday and the Commanders on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2b9-db7b-a5dd-f2bda4260000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that “the framework of a deal is in place for both.” The veteran wide receiver makes sense for both teams. Bourne is intimately familiar with 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan’s system, having spent 2017-2020 with them. Should he end up with the Commanders, he would serve as a fine rotational player who can be counted on to run routes on time. He is unlikely to return flex value with either team, though he could be relevant in 14-team leagues if Jauan Jennings (calf, contract) joins Brandon Aiyuk (knee) and Demarcus Robinson (suspension) on the sidelines early in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2b9-db7b-a5dd-f2bda4260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed CB Ambry Thomas, formerly of the 49ers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2cc-db7b-a5dd-f2cce8b10000</link>
      <description>Thomas broke his arm in August 2024 before bouncing from the 49ers’ active roster to the Colts’ and Vikings’ practice squads. In 2023, he recorded six pass breakups, one interception and 37 tackles with the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2cc-db7b-a5dd-f2cce8b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed LB Chazz Surratt, formerly of the 49ers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2f4-d332-a1fd-f6f62f7f0000</link>
      <description>Surratt will likely contribute on special teams. The Seahawks also waived S D’Anthony Bell, signed rookie LB Chris Paul Jr. and WR/RS Courtney Jackson to the practice squad and released RB Anthony Tyus III and OLB Jalen Gaines from the practice squad in corresponding moves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2f4-d332-a1fd-f6f62f7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ ProFootballTalk reports that Vikings S Harrison Smith “is dealing with a personal health issue and is expected to make a full recovery.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</link>
      <description>Smith has reportedly been dealing with the issue throughout August. Details on the matter have not yet been disclosed but the team will continue to evaluate him on a weekly basis. Smith, 36, remains an impactful player in the Vikings’ secondary. Hopefully, he is good to go for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots released S Jabrill Peppers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6ac-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff84be0000</link>
      <description>Peppers has $4.32 million in guaranteed money remaining on his contract for this season. The 29-year-old safety started 26 games over the last three seasons with the Patriots. New England could be looking to start Jaylinn Hawkins and rookie Craig Woodson now, according to ESPN’s Mike Reiss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6ac-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff84be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid told reporters WR Jalen Royals (knee) is unlikely to play in the Week 1 matchup against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6c7-de13-afdc-f6cf7ccf0000</link>
      <description>Reid told reporters “it’d be a real rush” for Royals (knee) to play in Week 1 and that “it doesn’t look like he’ll make this week.” With Rashee Rice also missing the game due to suspension, the Chiefs are going to be understaffed against the Chargers. The wide receiver room will be led by Xavier Worthy with Hollywood Brown, JuJu Smith-Schuster and Tyquan Thornton behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f6c7-de13-afdc-f6cf7ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans sign DT Timmy Horne, formerly of the Giants, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f24a-dbe3-a9bb-f25bc7560000</link>
      <description>Horne spent 2022 with the Falcons and was signed from their practice squad by the Giants in 2023. The Titans correspondingly released RB Jermar Jefferson and CB Amani Oruwariye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f24a-dbe3-a9bb-f25bc7560000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
