<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dulcich caught 5-of-5 targets for 49 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3873-d713-ad9e-7c7761110000</link>
      <description>Promoted from the practice squad eight days ago after the Dolphins lost Darren Waller to a pec injury, Dulcich wasn’t targeted against the Falcons in Week 8 but surprisingly caught just one fewer pass than each of Jaylen Waddle and De’Von Achane this evening. Although we would like to think it is something to build off of for a former hype merchant who is still only 25 years old, it is far more likely to be a fluke. Dulcich isn’t worth a re-draft FAAB expenditure ahead of Week 10 against the Bills. Maybe you can toss one more Hail Mary in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3873-d713-ad9e-7c7761110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed four times for 11 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins, adding a seven-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3877-d713-ad9e-7c770b6c0000</link>
      <description>Five touches for 18 yards is nothing to call home about, but this was the second consecutive week Mitchell out-touched Justice Hill. He was also cutting into Hill’s breather back snaps behind workhorse Derrick Henry. Hunting for sparks as they keep digging out of the hole from their 1-5 start, the Ravens are probably committed to increasing Mitchell’s role at Hill’s expense. Just don’t expect it to turn into 12-team league value any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3877-d713-ad9e-7c770b6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua said he is “ready to go” for Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a41-d45b-affe-7fd7a7eb0000</link>
      <description>We still have one day of practice to go, but it sounds like Nacua, who said he feels “fantastic” after Friday’s full practice, is shaping up for a return in Week 9. Head coach Sean McVay said at the start of the week that he expected Nacua to be good to go for this week’s game against the Saints, and things are clearly trending in that direction. We’ll see what happens on Friday, but it wouldn’t be surprising if Nacua was removed from the injury report entirely before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a41-d45b-affe-7fd7a7eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer said the Chiefs are “drilling down a little more at RB with Isiah Pacheco banged up.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a65-d713-ad9e-7e75f3610000</link>
      <description>Pacheco is considered “week-to-week” after suffering a sprained MCL in last week’s win over the Commanders. While the injury doesn’t appear to be one that will land him on injured reserve, Breer said the Chiefs could be eyeing a running back, along with a defensive tackle, before next week’s trade deadline. Injury aside, Pacheco has rushed for a pedestrian 78-329-1 on the season and hasn’t gone for more than 58 yards in a game. The number of available running backs at the deadline could be limited, but Breece Hall remains a popular name in the rumor mill, and ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported earlier that theBrowns could be open to dealing Jerome Ford. The trade deadline is set for November 4th, meaning every team, with the exception of those on bye, will get one more look at their rosters to see where things stand before finalizing any decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a65-d713-ad9e-7e75f3610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Jauan Jennings (ankle/rib/shoulder) is “getting better” ahead of Week 9’s game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a94-d713-ad9e-7ed4e7fc0000</link>
      <description>Jennings has been playing through a myriad of injuries throughout most of the season, which has noticeably slowed him on the one. Despite the injury issues, Jennings has been a full participant at practice this week, and Shanahan noted on Thursday that Jennings is “getting better” and is hopeful that the sixth-year receiver will show improved play on the field as he continues to heal. Despite his struggles, Jennings has seen seven or more targets in three of the six games he’s appeared in this season. He remains in play as a WR3/Flex option, with a chance to exceed those expectations if he can bounce back from these injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a94-d713-ad9e-7ed4e7fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall reports the Falcons “have yet to have any serious trade discussions with another team about Kirk Cousins.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ab7-d1e7-a1fa-7aff235d0000</link>
      <description>Whether or not the Falcons will deal Cousins to another team has been a discussion ever since Michael Penix took over as QB1 last season. In his first action of 2025 last week, Cousins underwhelmed to the tune of 173 scoreless yards on 31 attempts, although he was far from the only problem the Falcons had on offense against the Dolphins. This lack of “serious trade discussions” regarding the veteran quarterback suggests he’ll be sticking with the team once next week’s trade deadline passes on November 4th barring an unexpected development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ab7-d1e7-a1fa-7aff235d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars placed WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ac0-d1e7-a1fa-7aea245a0000</link>
      <description>Less than 24 hours after learning that Hunter suffered a knee injury in Thursday’s practice, the two-way player will now miss a minimum of four games because of said injury. According to Coen, the Jaguars are “currently assessing” the knee injury, which was of the non-contact variety, and the team still hasn’t determined how long Hunter’s absence could be. The rookie won’t be eligible to return until Week 13 at the earliest and now leaves the Jaguars short on both sides of the ball. The rookie has played on 323 offensive snaps per PFF compared to just 162 defensive snaps, and has seen 209 of his offensive snaps come from the slot. His absence should result in an expanded role for Parker Washington, who enters Week 9 averaging 4.7 targets per game, but could also be supplemented by Dyami Brown (shoulder) who was a full participant in Thursday’s practice. Both players make for interesting stashes heading into a generous Week 9 matchup against the Raiders but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than WR4/WR5s in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ac0-d1e7-a1fa-7aea245a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins fired GM Chris Grier.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ada-d673-a39e-bedb10f00000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter was the first to report the “mutual” split between Grier and the Dolphins. A long-time employee of the Fins, Grier got his start with the team in 2000 as a scout and worked his way up to general manager in 2016. The firing of Grier is the first major move the Dolphins have made following their dreadful 2-7 start to the season, and potentially buys head coach Mike McDaniel a little bit of time. Grier notably traded CB Jalen Ramsey and TE Jonnu Smith to the Steelers this past offseason in exchange for S Minkah Fitzpatrick, and then brought Darren Waller out of retirement to fill the void left by Smith. During his 10 years as the team’s primary roster builder, Grier failed to lead the team to a division title or playoff win. Once the Dolphins hit nine losses this season, they will have had five losing seasons under Grier. Senior personnel executive Champ Kelly is expected to take over as the team’s interim GM, and could have some big decisions to make ahead of next week’s trade deadline with the Dolphins looking like obvious sellers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ada-d673-a39e-bedb10f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel is expected to remain with the team through this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ae7-d673-a39e-bef7a55c0000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins made the decision to part ways with GM Chris Grier on Friday as their first move toward a front office rebuild following a 2-7 start to the season. McDaniel seems unlikely to retain his job past this season, but owner Stephen Ross will decide on his future once the season has concluded. McDaniel’s team has struggled in ways that once felt unimaginable after going 20-14 during his first two seasons while leading a top-10 scoring offense in his first three. Despite the early success, the Dolphins offense has imploded this season, ranking near the bottom of the league in points per game, yards per game, and EPA per play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3ae7-d673-a39e-bef7a55c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolf reports “multiple teams” have called the Dolphins about trading for Bradley Chubb and Jaelan Phillips.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3af4-d673-a39e-bef5c34c0000</link>
      <description>Interim GM Champ Kelly has five days to orchestrate some moves before Tuesday’s trade deadline. The Dolphins are sitting on a 2-7 record and have several players who could be of interest to contenders, with Chubb and Phillips likely topping the list in a league that covets pass rushers. Chubb, who has totaled four sacks this season, is still under contract through the 2027 season, while Phillips’ contract is set to expire at the end of this season. Phillips has managed three sacks in the nine games he has appeared in. After hesitating to pull the trigger on any trade requests before Week 9’s loss to the Ravens, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Dolphins looked to deal some players in hopes of recouping draft picks entering the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3af4-d673-a39e-bef5c34c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
