<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley Jr. (oblique) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab52e4d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans are reportedly preparing for Tremon Smith to start outside, which is good news for Titans deep-league plays like Calvin Ridley and Elic Ayomanor. The Texans defense played decently without Stingley against the Jaguars last week, but it only takes one big play allowed by Smith to build a good fantasy day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab52e4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (toe) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-823b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbbaef0000</link>
      <description>This makes him a little more likely to get off the questionable line for Sunday, even if it is a limited practice. Johnson is not a real fantasy option at this point, though we should be open to the idea that Jaxson Dart changes the distribution of New York’s targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-823b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbbaef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (back) is expected to resume practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8239-deb6-a7fd-d3ff6a040000</link>
      <description>The Broncos face the Bengals on Monday night, so today’s session is Denver’s first practice of the week. Engram’s return puts him on track to play. Whether he will be fantasy-relevant is a separate issue. For fantasy managers who are still holding him, the Bengals’ pushover defense provides a potential moment of clarity as to whether Engram has anything left in the tank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8239-deb6-a7fd-d3ff6a040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LB Zack Baun (knee) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab5211a0000</link>
      <description>Baun, LB Jihaad Campbell (triceps) and Adoree’ Jackson (groin) all took the day off on Wednesday, which was slightly alarming given the Eagles’ other defensive injuries. Eagles OLB Nolan Smith (triceps) and CB Jakorian Bennett were placed on injured reserve yesterday. Baun, Campbell and Jackson should all be good to go for Week 4, barring setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab5211a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8248-d6e9-af9d-8ad8a9720000</link>
      <description>Good news for a Jaguars receiving room that sorely missed Brown after he left Week 3’s game against the Texans with the shoulder injury. This would seem to get him on the path to being active for Week 4 against the 49ers, even if it is a limited session. Should Brown start, the lack of Travis Hunter targets would make him an intriguing WR4 stab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8248-d6e9-af9d-8ad8a9720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8251-dca3-a9fb-bfd9275e0000</link>
      <description>Swift was listed with a quad injury last week and remained limited through all three practices. He was active on game day, totaling 78 scrimmage yards and three receptions. The Bears reportedly love Swift’s pass-protection ability. One wonders if they could slide more rushing work to No. 2 RB Kyle Monangai while keeping Swift on the field for passing situations eventually. In the meantime, fantasy managers can expect Swift to play in Week 4 against the Raiders. He’s a borderline RB2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8251-dca3-a9fb-bfd9275e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (groin) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8243-d6e9-af9d-8ad3b0750000</link>
      <description>The Bears’ veteran tight end should be good to go for his team’s Week 4 game against the Raiders. Unfortunately, Kmet has earned just seven targets in three games and cannot be trusted as a TE1 in 12-team leagues, even with rookie TE Colston Loveland nursing a hip injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8243-d6e9-af9d-8ad3b0750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-825e-d6e9-af9d-8ade62ea0000</link>
      <description>That makes two straight absences for the Bears’ rookie tight end. He is on the wrong side of questionable for his team’s Week 4 game against the Raiders. Fantasy managers can continue stashing Loveland if they wish, though dropping him for a healthy tight end that is more involved in the passing game is understandable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-825e-d6e9-af9d-8ade62ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Kenny Moore II (Achilles) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8267-d6e9-af9d-8af7cf980000</link>
      <description>On Monday, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that Moore is expected to miss a few weeks with a calf injury. This week’s injury report instead lists Moore with an Achilles tendon injury, which increases concerns. The muscle and tendon are obviously connected, but the latter tends to be a more significant issue. Hopefully, he heals up without issue. Moore will be missed against the Rams in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8267-d6e9-af9d-8af7cf980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (NIR - Resting Vet/Knee) was limited in practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-824b-dca3-a9fb-bfdb12230000</link>
      <description>Jonnu Smith got the same treatment, with NIR/Hip on a limited session as well. We doubt these are anything serious based on the NIR tag, but we’ll go through the rigamarole just in case — if Warren were to sit in Week 4, Kenny Gainwell would be a solid volume-based RB3/FLEX play against a tough Vikings defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-824b-dca3-a9fb-bfdb12230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
