<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:05:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Former Giants interim coach Mike Kafka will join the Lions in a “high-ranking offensive staff role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</link>
      <description>He’s not the offensive coordinator — that’s Drew Petzing — but Kafka will apparently be another offensive mind in the room for Dan Campbell. It’s a coup for the Lions considering Kafka had interviewed to be an offensive coordinator in Detroit, Philadelphia, Tampa, and with the Giants this offseason. He’ll hope to rehab his coaching image after a fairly benign interim coach showing after Brian Daboll was swept out of power in New Jersey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc19-d968-a19b-fcf9c33c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills requested permission to interview Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase is reportedly meeting with the Browns right now in Los Angeles and Cleveland beat writers are picking out words carefully so they aren’t the ones saying he’s the favorite for the job despite the long interview, so perhaps this is a leverage play. It’s certainly no surprise to see the Bills interested, and they’ll reportedly have an in-person interview with Scheelhaase tonight. Scheelhaase also completed interviews with the Ravens, Raiders and Steelers this offseason. Scheelhaase would be yet another Sean McVay coaching tree disciple wherever he lands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc40-dc7a-af9b-ffff9dd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed a second interview with Bills OC Joe Brady for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc23-d968-a19b-fcf3ba750000</link>
      <description>Brady’s second interview with the Raiders was reportedly an in-person interview. The Bills’ offensive coordinator remains in play for head coaching openings with the Bills, Raiders, and Cardinals, although we can’t say with any amount of certainty if he has the inside edge for any of these jobs. Brady has been calling plays for the Bills since taking over for Ken Dorsey during the mid-way point of the 2023 season and also spent time calling plays for the Panthers from 2020-2021. If Brady doesn’t get a head coaching job, he should have plenty of suitors for offensive coordinator vacancies and may even return to the Bills in the right situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc23-d968-a19b-fcf3ba750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed a second interview with Rams passing game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc87-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b6a30000</link>
      <description>Scheelhaase is clearly one of the frontrunners for the head coach position in Cleveland but is also interviewing with the Bills for the same position later in the day. A copycat league continues to show great interest in the Sean McVay and Kyle Shanahan coaching trees, with Scheelhaase the next man up for a potential massive bump in responsibility. He has also interviewed with the Ravens, Raiders, and Steelers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fc87-d35e-a1bf-fdc7b6a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed former Vikings defensive pass game coordinator Daronte Jones as their next defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd25-d56e-afff-ffed09550000</link>
      <description>Jones booked no less than six interviews for defensive coordinator vacancies in the past two weeks, ultimately landing with the Commanders. Details of the signing are not yet available. Jones had a significant hand in a Minnesota defense that held opponents to the fewest pass yards per game in 2025 and now gets his first shot at defensive play calling duties in the Nation’s capitol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd25-d56e-afff-ffed09550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed a second interview with Broncos passing game coordinator Davis Webb for their head-coaching vacancy,</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd2b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf14bf0000</link>
      <description>Although an unlikely hire, Webb gained traction with the Raiders after a successful first interview and completed a second, in-person, interview with the franchise Monday. The 31-year-old has three years of coaching experience at the NFL level after a six-year career and would be attempting to make the leap from passing game coordinator to head coach, without ever having called offensive plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-fd2b-dc7a-af9b-ffbf14bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former NFL general manager said Jets head coach Aaron Glenn “did nothing” to change the team’s culture of losing.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffbc-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc9860000</link>
      <description>The former front office official told ESPN’s Rich Cimini that the lackluster effort on the part of Jets players was a telltale sign of a head coach who had not done anything to shift the team’s miserable culture, like his former boss, Dan Campbell, did in his first year with the Lions. Glenn “talked about swagger and toughness, but I didn’t see any of that. They played like a bunch of guys punching time clocks; they didn’t want to be there,” the former GM said. Glenn’s Jets struggled through a hopeless 3-14 season in 2025, posting one of the most lopsided scoring margins in recent NFL history. Glenn, a defensive specialist, gave total control of the defense to Steve Wilks, who was fired late in the season. New York was the first team in NFL history to go an entire season without an interception. Jets owner Woody Johnson will give Glenn another season to turn things around, Cimini said, because he was very much involved in hiring Glenn last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffbc-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc9860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers are expected to interview Cowboys tight ends coach Lunda Wells for the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffc4-d35e-a1bf-ffc67f5a0000</link>
      <description>Wells has a connection with newly hired Steelers head coach Mike McCarthy. Wells coached Dallas tight ends throughout McCarthy’s Cowboys coaching tenure and stayed in Dallas with Brian Schottenheimer, who took over when McCarthy was fired. Wells in early January got an offensive coordinator interview with the Commanders. It wouldn’t be a surprise to see him follow McCarthy to Pittsburgh as the Steelers undergo yet another offensive transition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffc4-d35e-a1bf-ffc67f5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNYTV’s Connor Hughes reports the Jets could hire former Panther head coach Frank Reich as the team’s offensive play caller.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffd9-d56e-afff-fff947e00000</link>
      <description>Reich, if he’s hired by the Jets, is expected to call plays for the team’s offense, per Hughes. That would mean current offensive coordinator Tanner Engstrand would be demoted following a 2025 season in which the talent-bare Jets offense had the NFL’s fourth lowest EPA per play and third lowest success rate. Hughes said Engstrand could maintain his OC title. Reich, a former NFL quarterback, served as offensive coordinator for the Chargers and Eagles before becoming the Colts’ head coach and then the Panthers’ head coach. Both head coaching tenures proved disastrous.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffd9-d56e-afff-fff947e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford said he would take “some time” to decide whether he’ll return to the Rams in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffe6-d968-a19b-fff73cd00000</link>
      <description>Stafford, 37, is coming off his best season as a pro, throwing a career-high 46 touchdowns alongside just eight interceptions. Stafford’s 2025 adjusted yards per attempt (8.82) was the best of his 17-year NFL career. “It’ll be a lot that goes into it,” Stafford said. “It’s a physical, a mental and emotional decision, a personal and a family decision as well. So, we’ll figure all that kind of stuff out with some time. ... I know I had a ton of fun playing football this season and had so much fun playing for the Rams. So when I’m ready to figure that out, I’ll be ready to figure that out. That moment isn’t right now.” Stafford is signed through the 2026 season and would count as a $48.2 million cap hit for the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ffe6-d968-a19b-fff73cd00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
