<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 21:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) will not play in Baltimore’s Week 1 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b84-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7967d0000</link>
      <description>He DNP’ed three times in a row and probably is at some risk of a weekend IR listing after not looking particularly close to coming back. Charlie Kollar will take over as Baltimore’s TE2 in Likely’s absence. Fantasy managers in shallow leagues who can’t stash Likely should probably cut bait and wait for him to get healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b84-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7967d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Gardner (fibula) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b86-de13-afdd-5fcf13250000</link>
      <description>The Jets will have their No. 1 cornerback on the field for their matchup with the Steelers. Over the summer, reports indicated that the Jets plan to switch to a man-coverage scheme and indicated that Gardner could operate in a shadow coverage role against opposing wide receivers. The Steelers’ one-man-show receiving corps, featuring DK Metcalf, should provide clarity immediately as to whether the shadow reports are true.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b86-de13-afdd-5fcf13250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed EDGE Za’Darius Smith to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8b-db7b-a5dd-bb8f57b90000</link>
      <description>After sitting out all offseason, Smith hooks on with the Eagles on a ring-chaser contract for the season. Smith had nine sacks as well as 50 hurries per PFF charting in 2025. He’ll give Philadelphia a sure-fire outside rusher on passing downs and possibly could have a bigger role than that depending on how thing shake out in the defensive line rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8b-db7b-a5dd-bb8f57b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles placed Ben VanSumeren (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b90-de13-afdd-5fdbb5430000</link>
      <description>The first injury of the season chronologically, blocking fullback VanSumeren looks likely to miss the rest of the season. He’ll miss at least the next four weeks, and the Eagles may look to find another fullback off the street or on someone else’s practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b90-de13-afdd-5fdbb5430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b95-dbe3-a9bb-3bd743390000</link>
      <description>He got in a third straight limited session on Friday. Most sourced reports expect Parsons to play, but it’s possible he’ll have a limited role in Week 1 as he acclimates to his new team and deals with the back injury. Green Bay would certainly like him available for passing downs in a must-win against the defending division champions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b95-dbe3-a9bb-3bd743390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Jordan Love (left thumb) is off Green Bay’s final injury report for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b97-de13-afdd-5fdfd0880000</link>
      <description>He’ll start against the Lions. Love had surgery on the thumb in the middle of training camp and has practiced in full all three days. Love is a borderline QB1 against the Lions to open the fantasy football season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b97-de13-afdd-5fdfd0880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9a-db7b-a5dd-bb9ea9c20000</link>
      <description>He got in a second straight limited session and seems to be on the optimistic side of questionable. Reed is a risky fantasy play, but with Dontayvion Wicks also questionable and Christian Watson opening up on the PUP list, he could get enough targets to make some hay in a WR3 role. As it has all offseason, this looks more like an open road for Matthew Golden to go nuclear than anything else.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9a-db7b-a5dd-bb9ea9c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b96-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7a4970000</link>
      <description>Horton’s training camp performance impressed Seahawks coaches to the point that they released veteran WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling. While MVS’ drops are legendary, he also boasts 60 combined starts, playing for the Packers and Chiefs. Horton’s downfield role and position on the depth chart lend themselves to volatile results, if he is even able to make good on the promise he showed this summer. He does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues currently, but for those wishing to stash a dart throw wide receiver, Horton fits the bill. Horton should have unencumbered access to the No. 3 wide receiver role this week, with Jake Bobo (concussion) and Dareke Young (hamstring) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b96-dbe3-a9bb-3bd7a4970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontyavion Wicks (calf) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 1 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9d-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf1b900000</link>
      <description>Ditto Savion Williams, as both got in three limited sessions and are likely on the optimistic side of questionable. Malik Heath could get involved if one of these two receivers gets ruled out ahead of the action on Sunday. As it is, Wicks profiles as a FLEX dart throw and Williams probably shouldn’t be started without either Wicks or Jayden Reed being ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b9d-dbe3-a9bb-3bdf1b900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks rule out WR Jake Bobo (concussion) for Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</link>
      <description>Both Bobo and LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) kicked the week off with promising limited practice participation statuses, but they were ultimately unable to get cleared for action. With Bobo out, rookie speedster WR Tory Horton (ankle) should operate as the clear-cut No. 3 wide receiver. Backup WR Dareke Young (hamstring) is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1b8a-d332-a1fd-9fbe2ea30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
