<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 1-of-4 targets for seven yards in the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6878-dc7a-af9b-efff3c730000</link>
      <description>19 of Caleb Williams’ 42 passes were directed at rookies Luther Burden and Colston Loveland, each of whom also scored a touchdown in a game with over 940 yards of total offense. The two teams became the first teams since at least 1970 to each score three or more touchdowns within the first 18 minutes, eventually combining for 49 points before the half. That makes it even more staggering that Moore was so little involved in the offense, particularly to fantasy managers relying on his services in Championship week. The emergence of Burden and Loveland and the presence of electric second-year receiver Rome Odunze make Moore a declining fantasy asset, even though his recently-signed extension ties him to the Bears through the 2029 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6878-dc7a-af9b-efff3c730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 24-of-33 passes for 303 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in the 49ers’ 42-38, Week 17 win over the Bears, adding 28 yards and two touchdowns on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6893-dc7a-af9b-efbf0b1e0000</link>
      <description>Purdy’s only blemish on an otherwise spectacular outing occurred on the first offensive play from scrimmage, when a tipped ball resulted in a pick-six to ignite the game environment in what would become one of the games of the season. The former Mr. Irrelevant completely willed the team to victory to keep their chances of the No. 1 seed in the NFC intact, something they’ll battle the Seahawks for on Sunday night. Arguably the most insane play was a touchdown pass to Kyle Juszczyk towards the end of the third quarter in which Purdy avoided two separate would-be sacks before nonchalantly flipping the ball to the perimeter for a score to his fullback. There were numerous highlight reel plays for Purdy on the evening — who finally looks healthy and is showing to be more than a Shanahan-driven point-and-click quarterback right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6893-dc7a-af9b-efbf0b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 23 times for 140 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears, adding 41 yards on four receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6899-d35e-a1bf-6ddb6dad0000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey accomplished something he had yet to do in his illustrious career by gaining more than 100 yards on the ground in the first half alone, amassing a ridiculous 121 rushing yards and 20 receiving yards in the first 30 minutes of play. A season-high 41-yard inside run was the primary contributor to the eruption. Although unlikely, McCaffrey needs 110 yards through the air in Week 18 to become the first running back in NFL history to accumulate 1,000 yards on the ground and through the air in the same season multiple times, with only he, Marshall Faulk, and Roger Craig accomplishing that feat to date. He can do so when the 49ers host the Seahawks in a battle for the No. 1 seed in the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6899-d35e-a1bf-6ddb6dad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall caught 5-of-8 targets for 85 yards in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall showed no wear after missing Week 16, immediately returning to lead the team in receiving on a night the two offenses combined for more than 940 yards of total offense and 80 points. The only thing he didn’t do for fantasy managers was find the end zone. He could have more target competition after it was reported that tight end George Kittle is likely to make a return to the game-day lineup when the 49ers host the Seahawks in Week 18 for a battle for the No. 1 seed out of the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a1-dc7a-af9b-efbf039d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 7-of-9 targets for 60 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</link>
      <description>Tonges was active throughout as a primary outlet for quarterback Brock Purdy over the middle of the field, also seeing numerous designed targets in the flat. His target total was bolstered by a game in which the two teams combined for over 940 yards of total offense and 80 points. Although the outburst in production was a welcome sight to fantasy mangers that scooped Tonges as a plan B option to Kittle, his role appears likely to take a significant hit with Kittle expected back for Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a4-d35e-a1bf-6de6538f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 2-of-4 targets for 42 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ four targets ranked behind fill-in tight end Jake Tonges, Ricky Pearsall, and Christian McCaffrey, but he saved his fantasy outing with a 38-yard touchdown in the fourth quarter to give the 49ers their final lead of the game. It was the first NFL regular season game in NFL history that was tied at seven, 14, 21, 28, and 35 points, with the 49ers eventually emerging victorious following an incomplete pass in the end zone as time expired. Jennings is unlikely to see his target volume surge significantly considering tight end George Kittle is expected to return to the game-day roster in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68a7-dc7a-af9b-efbf405c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Juszczyk caught 2-of-2 targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</link>
      <description>Juice scored on an unreal play from quarterback Brock Purdy in which the former Mr. Irrelevant evaded two would-be sacks to deliver the football to the left corner of the end zone and into the waiting hands of Juszczyk. The veteran fullback remains unlikely to see meaningful volume on a weekly basis but his moderate snap rates keep a sporadic touchdown within his range of outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-68aa-d35e-a1bf-6deaaf7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bears WR Luther Burden suffered a quad injury that’s not thought to be serious.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6a5a-d56e-afff-eefa9b740000</link>
      <description>Burden was one of two Bears receivers in the area of Caleb Williams’ target on the final play of the Bears’ Week 17 loss to the 49ers. The 22-year-old receiver remained down following the play and was subsequently carted to the locker room. It’s certainly encouraging news that Schefter reports the injury isn’t serious, though he also passes along that Burden will undergo additional testing. Following a breakout game with eight catches, 138 yards and a touchdown, Burden could be the Bears’ leading receiver in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6a5a-d56e-afff-eefa9b740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers T Trent Williams (hamstring) left San Francisco’s Week 17 game against the Bears and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab7-d968-a19b-7af753060000</link>
      <description>He played just one snap. Austen Pleasants replaced him. Williams being ruled out and seen hobbling on the sideline with what The Athletic’s Matt Barrows called a hamstring strain does not bode well for his availability for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab7-d968-a19b-7af753060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interim head coach Mike Kafka told reporters he has no doubts that QB Jaxson Dart has proven he’s a franchise quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab6-dc7a-af9b-efbfc5a40000</link>
      <description>Dart bounced back from a 33-yard performance in the Week 16 loss to the Vikings to throw for 207 yards in the win over the Raiders Sunday. The 22-year-old signal caller’s future with the organization is a topic for discussion with the Giants currently in control of the No. 2 overall pick in the 2026 NFL Draft and the team’s coaching situation in flux. While Kafka could remain the head coach next year, the Giants are said to be interested in speaking with a list of candidates that could include Notre Dame’s Marcus Freeman. In a sense, an endorsement from Kafka is relatively meaningless as he doesn’t currently have much of a say in the future direction of the franchise. Dart will have one more chance to make an impression against the Cowboys in Week 18 before what’s likely to be an offseason full of changes in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ab6-dc7a-af9b-efbfc5a40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
