<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 02:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 2-of-5 targets for 58 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff20-d651-a9df-ff350cbf0000</link>
      <description>Harrison cleared concussion protocol to return to the Cardinals’ offense this week. He was second on the team in targets behind Trey McBride, but only converted a pair of two long receptions. Harrison’s first target was punched out by the Packers, initially ruled a fumble but overturned to an incomplete pass. He made an excellent 35-yard sideline catch in the third quarter and drew a pass interference call, but was mostly held in check by the Packers defense. Harrison is in the high-end WR3 range coming out of the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff20-d651-a9df-ff350cbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports Titans president of football operations Chad Brinker and GM Bike Borgonzi will lead the team’s search for a new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2a-d99b-a1dd-ff2ec8a30000</link>
      <description>According to Florio, the Titans’ search for a new head coach is in the “beginning stages,” but the team does not plan to use an outside firm to conduct its search. Florio reports that the Titans plan to use an “extremely calculated process” to find their third head coach in four seasons, but we’ll see what truly comes of the search before passing judgment. The Titans have been an organizational disaster for the last several seasons and are on track to finish 2025 with their fourth-straight losing campaign. They’ll have plenty of time between now and the end of the season to say and do all of the right things as they work toward hiring a new coach, but whoever is hired will have their work cut out for them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2a-d99b-a1dd-ff2ec8a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 3-of-7 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2f-d651-a9df-ff3f82e60000</link>
      <description>Johnson and Daniel Bellinger combined for 11 targets and two touchdowns on the day. Most of Johnson’s production came on a 44-yard catch and run score in the fourth quarter in which he shed several tackles and barreled into the end zone. It was Johnson’s fourth touchdown of the 2025 season. He logged 36 routes to 21 routes for Bellinger. Though he’s not targeted at a high rate, Johnson will be a usable streaming option in Week 8 against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff2f-d651-a9df-ff3f82e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 6-of-12 targets for 95 yards in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff37-df81-ab9b-fff7f0c40000</link>
      <description>No other New York pass catcher saw more than seven targets. Robinson had a couple crucial fourth quarter receptions, and seemed to be Jaxson Dart’s primary target in high leverage situations. The back-and-forth game script led to a season high in targets for Robinson, who had 84 yards and a score last week against the Eagles. He’ll face off against the Eagles once again in Week 8 and should be considered a top-30 fantasy play as Dart’s top option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff37-df81-ab9b-fff7f0c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Jones caught 2-of-2 targets for 67 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff27-da18-a39b-ff37ba150000</link>
      <description>Jones made a pair of grabs in the Cardinals’ two minute drills, keeping possessions alive for Jacoby Brissett. He first converted a 43-yard reception in the first half to keep a scoring drive going for the Cardinals. His next target and catch came towards the end of the fourth quarter, catching a pass for 24 yards to continue the final Cardinals drive. Jones was oft-used last week with Marvin Harrison (concussion) exiting the game, but he took a backseat with Harrison back. Jones is best left on fantasy benches for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff27-da18-a39b-ff37ba150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 5-of-8 targets for 42 yards in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff3d-d99b-a1dd-ff3dc7c30000</link>
      <description>In a revenge game, Engram saw a season high eight targets for Bo Nix and ran a route on 43 of the Broncos’ 63 drop backs — a major increase in playing time and usage that could suggest bigger things for the veteran in the coming weeks. Engram, who now has 18 receptions over his past four games, remains a secondary or tertiary part of the Denver passing attack but could be useful in pass-heavy game scripts. The Broncos could see just that in Week 8 against the burnable Cowboys defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff3d-d99b-a1dd-ff3dc7c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Wilson caught 3-of-4 targets for 40 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 7 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff3c-d651-a9df-ff3da8080000</link>
      <description>Wilson continues his quiet season as the Cardinals’ No. 2 wide receiver on the outside. He saw two targets on the first drive of the game, including an incomplete end zone target. Marvin Harrison is still the lead wideout with Trey McBride the top pass-catcher, leaving crumbs for the rest of the Cardinals’ receivers. Wilson is a fantasy WR5 heading into a Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff3c-d651-a9df-ff3da8080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JK Dobbins had 14 rushes for 81 yards in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff41-d99b-a1dd-ff4d29ef0000</link>
      <description>Dobbins once again led the Denver backfield by a comfortable margin. RJ JHarvey saw had four rushes for zero yards and caught one of his two targets on the day. Much of Dobbins’ production came on a 32-yard scamper up the middle — one of the biggest plays of the day for a Broncos offense that struggle mightily for three and a half quarters. Dobbins’ workload has been nothing if not consistent: He’s had at least 14 rushing attempts in six of his seven games as the team’s lead back. In Week 8, Dobbins will face the league’s worst rush defense in Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff41-d99b-a1dd-ff4d29ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart completed 15-of-33 attempts for 283 yards, three touchdowns, and one interception in the Giants’ Week 7 loss against the Broncos, adding five rushes for 11 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff49-d651-a9df-ff5debd30000</link>
      <description>Dart was patient with his throws and delivered a handful of accurate downfield shots against an elite Broncos secondary. Two of his touchdowns went to New York tight ends; the other went to Cam Skattebo on a well-designed screen play in the red zone. Dart scored his rushing touchdown on a one-yard dive after an end zone pass interference in the final minute of the game. Dart mostly avoided the massive hits he’s taken in recent weeks, picking his spots to take off and run. He targeted Wan’Dale Robinson relentlessly, as he dd in Week 6 against the Eagles. Dart’s rushing upside will make him a weekly top-12 fantasy play going forward. He’ll play the Eagles once again in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff49-d651-a9df-ff5debd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 3-of-10 targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Broncos’ Week 7 win against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff4f-da18-a39b-ff5ffd260000</link>
      <description>Franklin, as usual, ran a bunch of empty routes as the de facto WR2 in the Broncos offense. His touchdown came on a fluky tip that ended up in Franklin’s hands near the back of the end zone — one of Bo Nix’s two passing scores on the day. Franklin hasn’t had more than 55 receiving yards in a game since Week 2, and mostly profiles as a deep league fantasy option in the balanced Denver offense. He’ll face the Cowboys in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ff4f-da18-a39b-ff5ffd260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
