<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 12-of-26 passes for 139 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Chargers’ 22-19, Week 14 win over the Eagles, adding 66 yards on 10 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01c7-d77b-adfb-cbc72a560000</link>
      <description>Herbert came into Monday listed as a game-time decision after having undergone surgery to address a broken bone in his non-throwing hand just seven days prior, willing the Chargers to an overtime victory over the defending Super Bowl Champions while leading the team in rushing. His two turnovers contributed to eight total turnovers in a hard-fought defensive battle, with three of those turnovers occurring on a wild three-turnover play. Even so, Herbert skillfully led the Chargers down the field in a two-minute drill to tie the game and send it into overtime, again leading the charge in overtime for the would-be game-winning field goal in the extra frame. Herbert took numerous hard hits that had him falling awkwardly to protect his surgically repaired left hand, with the veteran quarterback appearing to flex and favor the hand at multiple points during the game. The win sends the Chargers to 9-4 and into the 5-seed in the AFC, now two games behind the Broncos for the division lead. They get another tough opponent in Week 15 when they travel to face the desperate Chiefs on the road.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01c7-d77b-adfb-cbc72a560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal rushed 14 times for 44 yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles, adding 60 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01ce-d8cf-affb-bdeebcc10000</link>
      <description>Vidal drew his eighth consecutive start, this time sharing the backfield with former starter Omarion Hampton after the latter returned from injured reserve. Philadelphia’s vaunted defense made life difficult for Vidal on the ground but he quickly padded his counting stats with a 60-yard reception on the team’s first possession to set up a Hampton touchdown three plays later. The two should continue to share backfield work as Hampton works his way back into game shape, drawing another difficult matchup against the Chiefs in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01ce-d8cf-affb-bdeebcc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed 13 times for 56 yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles, adding 11 yards and a touchdown on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01d3-d005-a9bf-d9f761620000</link>
      <description>Hampton ceded the start to backfield mate Kimani Vidal but ended with the same number of touches, finding the end zone on the team’s first possession of the game on a four-yard strike to the flat. He walked into the end zone thanks to elite blocking from wide receiver Keenan Allen, who managed to take both his cornerback and a linebacker out of the play. Hampton should continue to see his usage ramped up as he works his way back into game shape, potentially in line to see a heavier workload when the Chargers travel to Kansas City to take on the desperate Chiefs in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01d3-d005-a9bf-d9f761620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught all three targets for 22 yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01d7-d8cf-affb-bdffb7fb0000</link>
      <description>Allen actually led all Los Angeles wide receivers in both catches and yardage on a night quarterback Justin Herbert attempted only 26 passes, but it was his block to spring running back Omarion Hampton’s touchdown that should be praised the most. His veteran savvy was on full display as he was able to take both his cornerback and a linebacker out of the play through expert blocking, allowing Hampton to walk into the end zone to cap a successful first drive. Allen has now gone seven weeks without usable counting stats in a fantasy setting, best returned to the waiver wire in shallow leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01d7-d8cf-affb-bdffb7fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 1-of-3 targets for 18 yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01db-da9b-a9bf-dfdf5f690000</link>
      <description>Sadly enough for fantasy managers counting on any Chargers pass-catchers, Harris’ 18 yards ranked third on the team behind Kimani Vidal and Keenan Allen. Quarterback Justin Herbert attempted only 26 passes in the defensive battle, leaving little room for lofty fantasy scores to emerge. Harris continues to see spotty volume as the fifth option through the air, best left on fantasy benches ahead of a difficult matchup with the Chiefs in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01db-da9b-a9bf-dfdf5f690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 1-of-5 targets for 12 yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01dd-d005-a9bf-d9fddcb50000</link>
      <description>McConkey led the team with five targets on a night Justin Herbert attempted only 26 passes, although that hardly helps fantasy managers that were counting on him in the final week before fantasy playoffs. The Chargers managed only 275 yards of total offense, squeaking by with an overtime victory thanks to five Cameron Dicker field goals and five takeaways. McConkey should be busier against the desperate Chiefs in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01dd-d005-a9bf-d9fddcb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 2-of-3 targets for eight yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01e1-da9b-a9bf-dfed7dd30000</link>
      <description>Johnston saw his fair share of lockdown coverage from Quinyon Mitchell in this one, although his three targets were largely a product of only 26 Justin Herbert pass attempts on a night the Los Angeles defense stepped up with five takeaways. Johnston remains a touchdown-dependent fantasy asset in a now-crowded receiving corps due to the emergence of tight end Oronde Gadsden, with the ever-present potential to see his volume curbed due to the strength of their defense and absence of the team’s starting tackles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01e1-da9b-a9bf-dfed7dd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 1-of-4 targets for seven yards in the Chargers’ Week 14 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01e4-da9b-a9bf-dfede2c20000</link>
      <description>Gadsden’s four targets actually ranked second on the team behind the five of Ladd McConkey, highlighting the defensive deadlock the Chargers found themselves in against the defending Super Bowl Champions. It has now been more than a month since Gadsden has caught more than three balls, although his emergence in the offense gives offensive coordinator Greg Roman yet another chess piece to attack opposing defenses. Gadsden could be busier in Week 15 when the Chargers take on the Chiefs on the road.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-01e4-da9b-a9bf-dfede2c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Ravens RB Keaton Mitchell’s knee injury is considered “minor.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-039d-d8cf-affb-bfbfcdc60000</link>
      <description>An MRI on Mitchell’s knee came back clean, per Fowler, following the Ravens’ Week 14 loss to the Steelers. Mitchell left the game in the second half with the knee issue after rushing for 76 yards on six carries, including an explosive 55-yard run. If Mitchell can practice in a limited capacity this week, he could suit up in Week 15 against the Bengals. Rasheen Ali would be the clear RB2 for Baltimore if Mitchell is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-039d-d8cf-affb-bfbfcdc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LT Parris Johnson (knee) is week-to-week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-03bd-d77b-adfb-cbbf81130000</link>
      <description>Johnson left Week 14’s loss to the Rams with an MCL injury and would seem likely to miss Arizona’s Week 15 game against the Cardinals. Losing Johnson ahead of a matchup with the ferocious Texans pass rush is bad news for Jacoby Brissett and the entire Cardinals offense. Brissett remains a solid streaming option based on pass volume alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-03bd-d77b-adfb-cbbf81130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
