<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said he hopes Drake London (knee) can play in Week 13.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d11-d1e7-a1fa-dffb0afc0000</link>
      <description>Morris confirmed London will miss the Falcons’ Week 12 game against the Saints. The head coach’s comments don’t inspire a lot of confidence that London will be able to suit up in Week 13. With Michael Penix (knee) done for the season and the team’s postseason hopes dwindling, the Falcons will likely be cautious with their superstar wideout. With London sidelined, Darnell Mooney becomes the team’s WR1. Kyle Pitts should see an increase in targets as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d11-d1e7-a1fa-dffb0afc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said QB Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 12 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d27-d1e7-a1fa-dfef1b600000</link>
      <description>Glenn confirmed that Justin Fields would once again be benched after his abysmal Week 11 outing against New England. Taylor will take over the Jets offense for now, starting with a tough matchup against a now-healthy Baltimore defense. Taylor’s insertion into the starting lineup likely means more drop back volume for Jets pass catchers. It could make Mason Taylor and perhaps AD Mitchell interesting in deeper formats, along with John Metchie, who last week against the Patriots had three catches for 45 yards and a touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d27-d1e7-a1fa-dfef1b600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Giants QB Jaxson Dart (concussion) is “trending” toward playing in Week 12 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d2b-d45b-affe-ddbfc2430000</link>
      <description>“Barring any setbacks,” Dart should be back for Week 12, Raanan added. Dart remains in the league’s concussion protocol following his Week 10 head injury against the Bears. His rushing role in the New York offense will be under scrutiny in the coming weeks after he took a series of massive hits as a runner in the weeks leading up to his Week 10 brain injury. More than half of Dart’s fantasy production this season has come on the ground. He’ll be a fringe starting option in 12-team formats if he suits up against Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d2b-d45b-affe-ddbfc2430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d40-d713-ad9e-fd5425a20000</link>
      <description>Thibodeaux missed the Giants’ Week 11 game against the Packers with a shoulder injury, and unless he can log a late-week practice this week, he’s likely out for Week 12 against the Lions. New York’s defense remains one of the league’s worst, with or without Thibodeaux. The Lions offense should make quick work out of the Giants this Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d40-d713-ad9e-fd5425a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Samaje Perine (ankle) is doubtful to play in Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d4d-d1e7-a1fa-dfef89ee0000</link>
      <description>Perine is still working his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 9. Chase Brown saw 24-of-27 backfield touches in Week 11. Perine’s continued absence will ensure a three-down role for Brown again this week, keeping him at the top of the RB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d4d-d1e7-a1fa-dfef89ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears designated CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d56-d673-a39e-bdd7181c0000</link>
      <description>Gordon will return to practice this week. Chicago has 21 days to activate him from injured reserve. Gordon aggravated a lingering hamstring issue early in the year and has been sidelined since Week 2. Both he and fellow defensive back Jaylon Johnson are practicing this week. The Bears could be getting healthy on defense just as they attempt to make a playoff push.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d56-d673-a39e-bdd7181c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d61-d45b-affe-ddf7746c0000</link>
      <description>Flacco hasn’t practiced on Wednesday since injuring his shoulder in Week 8. He should be back on the field for a limited session tomorrow and, barring a new development, won’t have a game day status after Friday’s session. We fully expect Flacco to suit up versus the Patriots on Sunday. He will remain a volume-based QB2, though his outlook will take a hit with Ja’Marr Chase suspended for one game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d61-d45b-affe-ddf7746c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d65-d673-a39e-bdf5eb670000</link>
      <description>The Ravens haven’t released their injury report yet, but we are assuming he is still dealing with the minor knee injury that cropped up last week. Jackson was held out of practice last Wednesday and returned for the following two sessions. He played in Week 11, though it was far from his best showing. Jackson threw for 193 scoreless yards with two interceptions and added a measly 10 yards on the ground. The knee issue may be affecting his play, even if it isn’t serious enough to keep him off the field entirely. Jackson should be able to suit up again this week, but fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on the Ravens’ injury report just to be safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d65-d673-a39e-bdf5eb670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams S Quentin Lake (elbow) underwent surgery and “the hope is he’s back before or during the playoffs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d70-d713-ad9e-fd74d75f0000</link>
      <description>Lake will presumably be placed on injured reserve, sidelining him for at least four weeks. Lake was having a breakout year before going down with the injury. He had 10 pass breakups, one interception, and one sack in 10 games, all of which were starts. Losing him will be a short-term blow to LA’s defense, but the good news is that it doesn’t sound like a season-ending injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d70-d713-ad9e-fd74d75f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
