<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans restructured S C.J. Gardner-Johnson’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</link>
      <description>According to KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson, the Texans are converting $7.75 million of Gardner-Johnson’s base salary into a $6.58 million signing bonus that will free up just over $3.086 million in cap space. Gardner-Johnson is in the second year of a three-year deal he originally signed with the Eagles in 2024, but can be released with no dead cap hit if the team opts to move on from him at the end of this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed DL Perrion Winfrey (back) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aeb-de13-afdd-6eeb77300000</link>
      <description>Winfrey will miss at least the next four games due to the injury. The veteran lineman, who was injured in practice last week, didn’t play in the team’s Week 1 contest against the Eagles due to his injury. He will now have some additional time away to rehab the injury. Winfrey last took a regular-season snap in 2023 and caught on with the Cowboys after a stint in the UFL earlier this spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aeb-de13-afdd-6eeb77300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray scrambling was “a point of emphasis for us.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acc-de13-afdd-6ecfb13d0000</link>
      <description>“I did think there were some high-leverage snaps in that game where he used his legs for our advantage and that’s what you want to see,” Gannon continued. Murray scrambled four times for 31 yards against the Saints in Week 1, last year he averaged just 2.4 scrambles per game per PFF data. It sounds like Murray is getting the green light to run more when he sees an opportunity and, per Theo Mackie, the Cardinals “tweaked some of their pass protection schematics in an attempt to open up more scrambling lanes for Murray up the middle.” It’s possible we see more running production out of Murray this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acc-de13-afdd-6ecfb13d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman suffered a high-ankle sprain in the team’s Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aff-d332-a1fd-beff4caf0000</link>
      <description>Perryman is considered week-to-week with the injury, per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. While we don’t know how much time the long-time vet could miss, whether or not he’s placed on injured reserve in the coming days will give us some clue as to how long the team expects his recovery to be. Perryman totaled 55 tackles and one sack with the Chargers last season, appearing in 11 games over that span. He has played in 12 or fewer games in every season dating back to 2022 and will almost certainly be facing a multi-game absence with this latest injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aff-d332-a1fd-beff4caf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said “I’ve got to be better there” when asked about running the ball only three times against 17 passes in the first quarter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b04-dbe3-a9bb-3b5745db0000</link>
      <description>“It’s one of those day-afters where you look back and say, ‘Alright, let’s look at how we really wanted to start that game and get those two runners going,’ because we think we’ve really improved in that area,” Payton continued. Bo Nix didn’t do much with the added volume and Denver eventually wound up rushing for five yards a carry against the Titans. It sounds like the Broncos could employ a more run-heavy approach against the Colts in Week 2, which should help J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b04-dbe3-a9bb-3b5745db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers DT Tershawn Wharton (hamstring) will miss 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b18-dbe3-a9bb-3b5bc8700000</link>
      <description>With four weeks in play, the Panthers might consider placing Wharton on injured reserve. “He was having a fantastic game,’' Panthers coach Dave Canales said of Wharton. “He had four tackles early on, and was really doing a good job of getting of blocks and making opportunities.’' The Panthers figure to remain easy to run on in Week 2, which is good news for James Conner and Trey Benson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b18-dbe3-a9bb-3b5bc8700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colby Parkinson suffered a sprained AC join in the Rams’ Week 1 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b22-dbe3-a9bb-3b73d5f20000</link>
      <description>This injury doesn’t bear any weight on the fantasy community, but Parkinson, who did play through the injury, appeared on 29 offensive snaps for the Rams last season and has been a key player on their offense since joining them last offseason. It’s possible he’ll play in Week 2 against the Titans, but if not, Davis Allen would appear next in line to play in 2TE sets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b22-dbe3-a9bb-3b73d5f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Eagles are hosting free agent WR Quez Watkins for a workout on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b2a-de13-afdd-6feb50410000</link>
      <description>Watkins was a sixth-round pick of the Eagles back in 2020 and caught 98 passes for 1,249 yards and six touchdowns during his four-year tenure with the team. He hasn’t played a regular season snap since 2023 and has also bounced around between the Steelers and Cardinals over the last two years. If signed, Watkins wouldn’t be any more than added depth to a receiver room that is currently five players deep. In addition to Watkins, the Eagles also hosted WR K.J. Osborn and DE Isaiah Foskey for workouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b2a-de13-afdd-6feb50410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said OG Kevin Dotson is week-to-week with a sprained ankle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b3b-d332-a1fd-bf3f8a430000</link>
      <description>Dotson suffered what is being called a lateral ankle sprain in the Rams’ Week 1 win over the Texans. The sixth-year pro is in his third year with the Rams and has started every game he’s appeared in since 2023. Whether or not Dotson lands on injured reserve will likely be determined in the coming days. For now, he’ll likely be replaced by backup guard Justin Dedich.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b3b-d332-a1fd-bf3f8a430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said “the number of snaps you can get Keaton (Mitchell) on offense are pretty limited” when asked about the decision to scratch him in Week 1 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b57aa630000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal quote for anybody stashing Mitchell in hopes of an eventual role emerging. Harbaugh highlighted the fact that Mitchell taking the field would be on “designer plays” that could tip off the defense as to who the ball is going to. For obvious reasons, Harbaugh has no interest in taking Derrick Henry or Justice Hill off the field to work in these plays, and said Mitchell also needs to improve on special teams if he hopes to see the field. There’s nothing to get excited about here as far as Mitchell is concerned. We’ll see if anything changes as the season progresses, but he holds no fantasy value at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b46-dbe3-a9bb-3b57aa630000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
