<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos TE Evan Engram (calf) is not on Denver’s final injury report for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3faf-d294-a19b-ffff4a2a0000</link>
      <description>He had back-to-back full sessions to finish out the week and it appears the calf injury that forced him from Week 1 isn’t serious. Engram will be on the low-end TE1 line against the Colts. The Broncos did not target him heavily before he left against the Titans, but it’s not worth panicking yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3faf-d294-a19b-ffff4a2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) will not play in Denver’s Week 2 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fb6-d86f-abdd-7fbfdaaa0000</link>
      <description>He did finally get in a limited practice session on Friday, but it wasn’t enough to sway the coaching staff. Greenlaw should have a better chance of suiting up in Week 3 given the practice session. It’s probably too soon to call him “close” to returning, but the odds are slowly going up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fb6-d86f-abdd-7fbfdaaa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin Jr. (ankle) did not practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fbe-dc44-a9d9-3ffe62340000</link>
      <description>Godwin’s downgrade could be part of the plan to ease him back in, so we are not sounding the alarm at this time. The veteran wide receiver is expected to return around Weeks 5 or 6, though we have a long way to go until then. For now, fantasy managers can assume that Godwin’s slow-paced recovery is on track until further notice. Buccaneers OT Tristan Wirfs was limited again on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fbe-dc44-a9d9-3ffe62340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder) is questionable to play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fc7-da67-a99f-fff7b2e30000</link>
      <description>Jennings returned to practice on Friday, though his practice participation status has not yet been released. If he practiced in full, his questionable tag could just be a formality. Jennings will be catching passes from Mac Jones, if active, which likely hurts his ceiling a tad. If he suits up, he profiles as a solid FLEX option against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fc7-da67-a99f-fff7b2e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (knee) is questionable to play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fad-d294-a19b-fffda5390000</link>
      <description>Williams briefly exited the 49ers’ Week 1 game against the Seahawks and exhibited a slight limp as he left the field. The 37-year-old blindside protector plays through injury whenever he can, so he seemingly has decent odds of suiting up. The Saints’ pushover pass rush will be without top EDGE Chase Young (calf), though, so the 49ers may be able to sneak past this opponent without Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fad-d294-a19b-fffda5390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RT Rob Havenstein (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fcd-dc44-a9d9-3fef924e0000</link>
      <description>The Rams entered the Week 2 practice week with their right tackle, RG Kevin Dotson and LG Steve Avila nursing ankle sprains. Good news for Matthew Stafford: Havenstein and Dotson have been cleared to play. The Titans’ pass rush is hardly a game-wrecker but it’s still nice to know that Stafford will have at least four-of-five starters in front of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fcd-dc44-a9d9-3fef924e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) has been removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fe7-dc44-a9d9-3fe757d50000</link>
      <description>Before injuring his ankle in mid-August, Watkins was competing for one of the team’s top-four wide receiver roles. Training camp reports indicated that the rookie looked good. Watkins is unlikely to meaningfully contribute this week but wide receiver-needy fantasy managers can stash him on benches to see how things shake out in the short term. 49ers RB Jordan James (finger) and will also make his 2025 debut this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3fe7-dc44-a9d9-3fe757d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts worked out free agent LB Duke Riley on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4005-d86f-abdd-45bd9a500000</link>
      <description>Riley briefly signed on with the Commanders this summer but his time with them was short-lived. The Colts also worked out CB Shemar Bartholomew, LB Milo Eifler, LB David Long, LB Raekwon McMillan and LB Ty Summers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4005-d86f-abdd-45bd9a500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB Tyler Badie could have a featured role in the passing game due to the “amount of pressure looks” expected from Colts DC Lou Anarumo in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-400b-da67-a99f-ccffd1620000</link>
      <description>Badie took 7-of-16 third-down snaps and 6-of-9 two-minute drill snaps against the Titans in Week 1. The usage reduces both J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey’s fantasy-scoring potential, and unfortunately for fantasy managers, it appears as though that usage will hold in Week 2. Broncos head coach Sean Payton believes Badie is “good in the [blitz] pickups” and in the passing game overall. Payton spent “quite a bit of time” preparing for Anarumo’s “exotic looks” on second and particularly third down. Apparently, both Payton and OC Joe Lombardi think Badie is the man for the exotic job, rather than Dobbins, who is known for his pass-pro chops, and Harvey, who was heralded as one of the 2025 rookie class’ top receiving backs. Dobbins can be treated as a high-end RB3/FLEX while Harvey can be viewed as a borderline RB3/4. Badie is only a floor-based FLEX option in very deep PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-400b-da67-a99f-ccffd1620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-402c-d86f-abdd-45bdefbd0000</link>
      <description>Bobo and WR Dareke Young (hamstring) will both be available this weekend. Jaxon Smith-Njigba was the only Seahawk to earn more than three targets in Week 1, returning anyone even mildly capable to the lineup is a plus. Bobo will likely compete with rookie WR Tory Horton for WR3 duties. S Julian Love (groin) and DT Jarran Reed (back) are good to go as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-402c-d86f-abdd-45bdefbd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
