<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 02:31:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 4-of-8 targets for 52 yards in a Week 8 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2321-d5d8-a3ff-fb6198700000</link>
      <description>With Calvin Ridley (hamstring) not playing, Ayomanor and Chimere Dike operated as the top pass-catchers in Tennessee. Of the two, Ayomanor is more of a deep threat, which means lower-percentage targets, but he did barely miss connecting with Cam Ward on a 50-yard pass in the first half. Ward evaded pressure in the pocket, and it seemed like Ayomanor stopped his route and then had to pick it back up again, and was unable to catch up to the pass. The Titans figure to trail often, so Ayomanor will see decent volume, but his role means that he’s more of a boom-or-bust option in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2321-d5d8-a3ff-fb6198700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 4-of-5 targets for 53 yards in a Week 8 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2323-dab4-a3fb-bb73d5cc0000</link>
      <description>With the Titans in comeback mode essentially all game, Okonkwo had a decent day. Still, the emergence of Gunnar Helm as an option in the passing game has capped Okonkwo’s ceiling and makes him more of a mid-tier TE2 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2323-dab4-a3fb-bb73d5cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos HC Sean Payton said Marvin Mims is in concussion protocol</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22d6-dab4-a3fb-bbf648d70000</link>
      <description>Mims will need to clear protocol if he hopes to suit up in Week 9 against the Texans. Mims did not catch a pass in the Broncos’ Week 8 win over the Cowboys, but reportedly suffered his concussion in thefinal minutes of the fourth quarter. Even if he does clear concussion protocol in time for next week’s game, Mims will be hard to trust as anything more than a deep league play after Troy Franklin finally broke out for 6-89-2 on eight targets while Mims saw only one target in the win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-22d6-dab4-a3fb-bbf648d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught 2-of-3 targets for 23 yards and a touchdown in a Week 8 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2326-dab4-a3fb-bb76c9510000</link>
      <description>Helm has steadily grown his role over the last few weeks, and while he’s not exactly in a committee with Chig Okonwko, he is consistently stealing away some snaps. Helm’s touchdown was the first of his professional career, and the rookie also made a really nice catch down the sideline for his other grab. He looks like a solid NFL player, so it will be interesting to see how his role grows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2326-dab4-a3fb-bb76c9510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman Jr. caught 8-of-9 targets for 95 yards and a touchdown in a Week 8 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2329-d245-adfb-b77f456d0000</link>
      <description>Pittman Jr. is the clear top receiving threat in Indianapolis, and continues to deliver plays for Daniel Jones to earn his new quarterback’s trust. Pittman Jr. made a few tough catches over the middle and then snagged a one-handed touchdown catch while he was being aggressively interfered with. He was still able to pull the ball away from the defensive back with one hand and pin it to his chest for the touchdown grab. Pittman is the only Colts receiver you can rely on every week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2329-d245-adfb-b77f456d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught 2-of-5 targets for 69 yards in a Week 8 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b98fb0000</link>
      <description>It was very much an Alec Pierce day. He hauled in an impressive 50-yard pass from Daniel Jones down the sideline but wasn’t able to do much else on the day. He is seeing a bigger workload than he had been at the beginning of the season, but his role as a deep threat on a team that wants to win by consistently running the ball means that his production will be really inconsistent for fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b98fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught all three of his targets for 39 yards and a touchdown in a Week 8 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232d-dab4-a3fb-bb7d13720000</link>
      <description>The touchdown was nice, and Downs has clear playmaking ability, but he was also fourth on the team in targets today. Being the fourth target on a team that wants to run the ball as often as the Colts do is not a great recipe for fantasy success. Downs will have his days, and he can make plays when given the opportunity, but unless the Colts get into a gamescript where they’re forced to pass, it’s going to be tough to rely on him in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232d-dab4-a3fb-bb7d13720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 4-of-5 targets for 53 yards in a Week 8 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232e-dab4-a3fb-bb7ef5030000</link>
      <description>It was a solid day overall for Warren, who continues to establish himself as the second most consistent option in the Colts’ passing game, behind only Michael Pittman Jr. However, he could have had a much bigger day. On a 21-yard screen pass in the third quarter, Warren had blockers in front of him and only had to beat one defender for an easy touchdown, but when he planted his feet to cut, he slipped and was tackled easily. It would have provided a nice splash play to his day, but he remains a low-end TE1 given his clear ability, but the lack of consistent passing volume in this Colts offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-232e-dab4-a3fb-bb7ef5030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports the Ravens could face “significant punishment” for their handling of Lamar Jackson’s injury status ahead of Week 8’s game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2340-d245-adfb-b75fc4180000</link>
      <description>As Florio notes in his article, the league is investigating “what was a clear violation of the injury reporting policy.” According to sources who spoke to Florio, the mishandling of Jackson on the injury report, whether intentional or not, created “very bad optics” that could force the league to take action. Another source said, “It’s an opportunity for the league to make a very strong statement on a very important topic.” As the popularity of gambling and fantasy sports continues to grow, we should expect all professional leagues to take the handling of these things very seriously, given what’s at stake from a product/consumer standpoint. Head coach John Harbaugh said after Sunday’s win over the Bears that the injury report gaffe was an “honest mistake” and removed himself from any involvement in the matter when he said he has no involvement in the team’s injury designations. The league will take its time to get to the bottom of whatever happened. While fines for the team/coaches feels all but certain, it’s worth wondering if a potential loss of draft picks could be in play given what Florio’s sources had to say. The Ravens face the Dolphins on Thursday night football in Week 9, and the team is hopeful Jackson will be under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2340-d245-adfb-b75fc4180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Steelers are hosting Marquez Valdes-Scantling for a visit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-235e-d5d8-a3ff-fb7f889d0000</link>
      <description>Should MVS sign with the Steelers, it would reunite him with Aaron Rodgers, with whom he spent four seasons in Green Bay. MVS started this season with the 49ers but was released earlier this month after being placed on injured reserve with a calf injury. The veteran receiver has caught four passes for 40 yards this season and went for 17-385-4 last season with the Saints. He’s unlikely to turn into a viable fantasy asset, whether he lands with the Steelers or another team this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-235e-d5d8-a3ff-fb7f889d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
