<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 22:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) is questionable to play in Week 13 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3e-d82c-a79a-ffbeb26d0000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor does not seem ready to play yet. The rookie wide receiver missed Week 12 after sitting out during the practice week, and he has failed to log a single full practice session since then. There is a chance he will be asked to play, but he would be at risk of suffering an in-game setback, and he is not producing at a must-start level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc3e-d82c-a79a-ffbeb26d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) is questionable to play in Week 13 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc4c-d6c4-abfb-de4f66b60000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo sandwiched a Thursday absence with two limited sessions. The veteran tight end continues to play through the injury, but he is barely fantasy-relevant. Even if Okonkwo takes the field against the Jaguars, he does not need to be in starting lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc4c-d6c4-abfb-de4f66b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle/IR) will not play in Los Angeles’ Week 13 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc55-d6c4-abfb-de5709750000</link>
      <description>More concerning yet, Hampton was spotted in a yellow non-contact jersey on Friday after not wearing one for either of the last two days. Perhaps it was just the Chargers being cautious with someone they knew they weren’t going to play on Sunday, but it’s also possible that he was further injured or had a setback in practice — Jim Harbaugh said “he looked good” and that everything is on track for the return, but wouldn’t say when the return would be. Kimani Vidal will tote the load for the Chargers against the Raiders and be a top-20 play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc55-d6c4-abfb-de5709750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker (glute) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc50-db57-afda-de72f55d0000</link>
      <description>Walker played through the injury last weekend, out-touching RB Zach Charbonnet 14-6. With Holani (hamstring) sidelined, the team signed free agent RB Cam Akers earlier this week. The Seahawks are expected to control the game with a run-heavy game script against the Max Brosmer-led Vikings this weekend, which should yield fantasy goodness for Walker. He is an RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc50-db57-afda-de72f55d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Jaylin Lane (hip) is not on Washington’s final Week 13 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc59-d90e-a9da-df5f8a270000</link>
      <description>With Terry McLaurin back, Lane won’t be more than a non-gimmick factor against the Broncos. He can be sent to waivers in all but the deepest leagues, as even when McLaurin was out he wasn’t making much of an impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc59-d90e-a9da-df5f8a270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc57-d6c4-abfb-de5746880000</link>
      <description>Nwosu is good to go, which is bad news for Vikings QB Max Brosmer. He accounts for 37 quarterback pressures and ties for a team-high eight sacks, boasting a 14.1 percent pass-rush win rate. Seahawks S Ty Okada (oblique) is questionable to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc57-d6c4-abfb-de5746880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Noah Brown (groin/IR) will not play in Washington’s Week 13 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc5b-d90e-a9da-df5fec450000</link>
      <description>Brown was full on Thursday, but did not practice on Friday with a rest designation. Zach Ertz, Terry McLaurin, and Deebo Samuel will be the only reliable Commanders fantasy options against Denver. Brown is still just in the first week of his 21-day window and it stands to reason he’ll be activated soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc5b-d90e-a9da-df5fec450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) is not on the injury report for Week 13 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc63-d82c-a79a-fff7e7100000</link>
      <description>We expect the team to announce his official activation from injured reserve soon. The speedy wide receiver practiced fully all week, so he should be ready for his typical snap share. The volatile fantasy producer cannot be counted on for FLEX value, but all it takes is one play. A classic boom-bust deep threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc63-d82c-a79a-fff7e7100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (toe) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc71-d6c4-abfb-de73ac420000</link>
      <description>He was limited on Thursday. This doesn’t look like an injury that has much of a chance to keep Henry out of MNF’s game against the Giants, where he’ll be a borderline TE1 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc71-d6c4-abfb-de73ac420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc6a-db57-afda-de7ad9fb0000</link>
      <description>Robinson is on track to play, but we are hoping to see him practice fully on Saturday. The shifty route runner’s 28.0 percent target share leads the team by 11.2 percent. Robinson is a rock solid WR3 with upside if active on Monday night against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-cc6a-db57-afda-de7ad9fb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
