<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ian Rapoport of NFL.com reports that the Bengals have agreed to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e310-db7b-a5dd-e31475fd0000</link>
      <description>Adam Schefter of ESPN reports that the deal will pay him $30 million in 2025; a $14 million raise from what he was owed, but he still will hit free agency in 2026 — assuming a long-term deal isn’t reached before that, of course. The 30-year-old will end his contentious holdout with the Bengals and should once again be among the best pass rushers in the league after accumulating 17.5 sacks in each of the past two seasons. The question now is whether this sets some sort of potential framework for Micah Parsons and his potential extension with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e310-db7b-a5dd-e31475fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes RB Ty Chandler won’t make Minnesota’s 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e318-db7b-a5dd-e31cb4e60000</link>
      <description>It’s been a theme of training camp that the Vikings simply don’t believe in Chandler’s ability to pass protect despite his explosiveness with the ball in his hands. Lewis thinks the team will instead roster Zavier Scott behind the combination of Aaron Jones and Jordan Mason at running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e318-db7b-a5dd-e31cb4e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders released WR Marquez Callaway.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31b-d332-a1fd-f73fbb5c0000</link>
      <description>Callaway ended the 2024 season on the Buccaneers’ roster, and has briefly spent time on both the 49ers’ and Raiders’ rosters this month. The Raiders also released WRs Phillip Dorsett and Colin Johnson, plus LB Jaylon Smith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31b-d332-a1fd-f73fbb5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions waived WR Jackson Meeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e325-de13-afdc-e7ef3e5c0000</link>
      <description>Meeks performed well in the preseason, and it will not be a surprise if the Lions bring him back on the practice squad. That’s assuming the 6-foot-2 wideout doesn’t find a new team, however, and his production in exhibition season makes him a prime candidate to find a new homer for a team needing playmakers on the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e325-de13-afdc-e7ef3e5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos waived DT Michael Dwumfour.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31c-db7b-a5dd-e31c5a590000</link>
      <description>He was signed only recently and looked fairly good against the Saints in Denver’s final preseason tune-up, notching a 79.7 PFF pass rush grade against ... well, backup linemen. Joining Dwumfour on the early cut list are DB Micah Abraham, LB Joaquin Davis, LB Andrew Farmer, DB Joshua Pickett, G Xavier Truss, and G Clay Webb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e31c-db7b-a5dd-e31c5a590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Diana Russini reports that the Raiders are signing Amari Cooper to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e328-dbe3-a9bb-f37bd5d00000</link>
      <description>It’s a return to the organization that drafted and developed Cooper into one of the better wideouts in the sport before he moved on to the Cowboys, Browns and Bills; respectively. The 31-year-old isn’t the same playmaker he was in those previous Silver and Black years, and he’s coming off a season where he caught 44 passes for 547 yards with four touchdowns with Cleveland and Buffalo. That being said, the Las Vegas depth chart offers very little competition, and it’s pretty easy to see him being one of Geno Smith’s top targets for the 2025 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e328-dbe3-a9bb-f37bd5d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed RB Phil Mafah (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32a-d332-a1fd-f73ef8b60000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four weeks. This gives Dallas a little runway to see if Jaydon Blue or Miles Sanders can establish a true pecking order behind Javonte Williams. Mafah, Dallas’ seventh-round pick this year, ran hard in the preseason and has a chance to be a factor later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32a-d332-a1fd-f73ef8b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released QB Mike White.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e327-db7b-a5dd-e3270a5d0000</link>
      <description>White had a brutal Week 18 showing for the Bills last year, completing 3-of-11 passes for 28 yards. He fared slightly better during the preseason this month, completing 12-of-24 passes for 166 yards and two touchdowns. He may be able to find a spot on an NFL practice squad this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e327-db7b-a5dd-e3270a5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said he’s “optimistic” about WR Tory Horton (ankle) being available for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</link>
      <description>Horton hasn’t practiced since leaving Seattle’s second preseason game with the ankle injury, but it doesn’t seem like he’s at any risk of starting the year on injured reserve based on this update. Horton isn’t someone you need to roster in your home fantasy league right away, but he’s got a chance to grow into a real role in year one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e335-de13-afdc-e7ffcb9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Buccaneers are releasing QB Kyle Trask.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will work out an injury settlement for Trask, as he’s currently dealing with a shoulder issue. A second-round pick for some reason in 2021, Trask has been the backup quarterback for the Bucs over the last four seasons, but that honor will now apparently go to Teddy Bridgewater. Trask is likely a practice squad player for a new organization in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e32b-db7b-a5dd-e32f2d100000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
