<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c71d-d6c4-abfb-d71f71710000</link>
      <description>It would be great to see Neal upgrade to full participation tomorrow. He is likely to start against the Dolphins’ fantasy-friendly run defense with RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) expectedly sidelined. Neal’s experience on passing downs should be a plus, though TE Taysom Hill could steal carries from the rookie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c71d-d6c4-abfb-d71f71710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (foot) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c720-d90e-a9da-df2fc3490000</link>
      <description>Waddle has made a habit of playing through injuries. He is on track to do so once again against the Saints in Week 13. Waddle can be safely expected to hog targets, operating as the Dolphins’ unquestioned No. 1 pass catcher. He is a borderline WR1/2 for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c720-d90e-a9da-df2fc3490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (pectoral) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c722-db57-afda-d7323ac00000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have been fine with playing Waller on a snap count thus far, so it is possible they let him play this weekend, even with the two limited sessions to begin the week. The 33-year-old tight end could need another week before the Dolphins activate him from injured reserve, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c722-db57-afda-d7323ac00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (appendicitis) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c724-db57-afda-d73695460000</link>
      <description>That makes two limited sessions for Harrison this week. The 23-year-old wide receiver still has a chance to return, but he is firmly in the questionable camp right now, and one wonders how ready he is to absorb hits, having had an appendectomy earlier this month. If he is active, he can be treated as a WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c724-db57-afda-d73695460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (left shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c725-db57-afda-d737026d0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield was surprisingly back at practice on Thursday despite having suffered an AC joint sprain in his non-throwing shoulder in Week 12. If active, Mayfield would, of course, be at risk of suffering an in-game setback. He would warrant consideration as a borderline QB1/2 as well, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c725-db57-afda-d737026d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c727-db57-afda-d737cd670000</link>
      <description>Godwin is expected to play a larger role than he did last week, in his return to action. The veteran wide receiver is still tough to trust despite the expected workload increase though. He can be treated as a FLEX option, whose prospects rise and fall with QB Baker Mayfield’s (shoulder) availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c727-db57-afda-d737cd670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR DeVonta Smith (shoulder/chest/illness) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c735-d82c-a79a-f7b543130000</link>
      <description>Smith is really going through it this week, but he upgraded to full on Friday after sitting out on Wednesday and Thursday, so he can be thrust into starting lineups as a WR3. The Eagles will likely focus on attacking a Bears’ run defense missing four linebackers this weekend, but Smith is remains a key figure in the offense regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c735-d82c-a79a-f7b543130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (groin) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c72c-db57-afda-d73e06a00000</link>
      <description>Barkley logged limited sessions on Tuesday and Wednesday. His return to full participation is great to see. The Bears placed one starting linebacker on injured reserve last weekend and ruled out three more linebackers this week. Barkley should be the offensive focal point on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c72c-db57-afda-d73e06a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Surtain (pec) practiced in full Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c73f-d6c4-abfb-d73f2c0c0000</link>
      <description>That places the veteran lockdown corner in line to return to the game-day roster for the first time since Week 8, potentially marking a substantial boost to one of the top defenses in the league. He’ll prepare to square off against the Jayden Daniel-less Commanders in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c73f-d6c4-abfb-d73f2c0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin (quad) practiced in full Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c741-d90e-a9da-df4f3fad0000</link>
      <description>It’s his first such showing since aggravating a quad injury in Week 8. McLaurin has missed the bulk of the previous eight games with the injury but appears to be on the precipice of a return for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c741-d90e-a9da-df4f3fad0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
