<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:30:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs requested an interview with Raiders RB coach Deland McCullough for their running backs coach vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b8e-d355-a5bd-8fdec05a0000</link>
      <description>Prior to taking his job with the Raiders last offseason, McCullough coached in the college ranks for four years. Before that, he coached Chiefs running backs from 2018-2020. Chiefs head coach Andy Reid is evidently hoping to recapture some of his old rushing attack’s magic. The Chiefs ranked 12th in yards per carry (4.5) during McCullough’s final regular season with the team. They averaged 4.2 this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b8e-d355-a5bd-8fdec05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed and interview with Texans assistant general manager James Liipfert for the general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bf8-d042-afbc-7ffa25ac0000</link>
      <description>Liipfert is reportedly a finalist, alongside Bears assistant general manager Ian Cunningham. Both candidates completed second-round, in-person interviews today. Liipfert operates as the director of college scouting within his current role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bf8-d042-afbc-7ffa25ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reports that the Dolphins are hiring Nathaniel Hackett as their new quarterbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bfb-dead-af9e-6fffe6500000</link>
      <description>The move reunites Hackett with new Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley. Hackett served as a Packers defensive analyst under Hafley, then the defensive coordinator, last year. Hackett also notably served as the Packers’ offensive coordinator from 2019-2021 before taking the Broncos’ head-coaching role in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bfb-dead-af9e-6fffe6500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR A.T. Perry, formerly of the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</link>
      <description>This move makes sense for the Steelers, who fielded a very thin wide receiver corps in 2025. Perry, 26, last played regular season snaps with the Saints in 2023, catching 12-of-18 targets for 246 yards and four touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos completed an interview with Bills QB coach Ronald Curry for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</link>
      <description>9NEWS’ Mike Klis notes that Broncos head coach Sean Payton was interested in hiring Curry as his offensive coordinator back in 2023. It did not work out. Curry was reportedly one of Payton’s “top” offensive assistants with the Saints from 2016-21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots QB Drake Maye (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c2a-dfd7-a5dc-0d6b45cb0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Mike Reiss reports that the Patriots switched up their routine today, moving the quarterback group’s throwing session to the portion of practice unavailable to media. When asked for his level of concern regarding Maye’s throwing-shoulder injury, Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said, “not much.” We fully expect Maye to play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks. Hopefully, he resumes practicing fully tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c2a-dfd7-a5dc-0d6b45cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb withdrew from the Raiders’ head-coaching search.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c47-d355-a5bd-8f57fd7e0000</link>
      <description>Webb interviewed for the Bills and Ravens’ head-coaching vacancies as well. Both jobs have been filled. Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Webb is considered a “prime candidate” for his current team’s offensive coordinator vacancy. He also received offensive coordinator interview requests from elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c47-d355-a5bd-8f57fd7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams hired Bubba Ventrone as their new special teams coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c51-dead-af9e-6cd774bc0000</link>
      <description>Ventrone began his coaching career in 2015 as an assistant special teams coach with the Patriots. He became the Colts’ special teams coordinator in 2018 before the Browns hired him as the assistant head coach and special teams coordinator in 2023. He is widely viewed as one of the NFL’s best special teams coaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c51-dead-af9e-6cd774bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that Panthers DC Ejiro Evero is “still in the mix” for the Raiders’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfa3970000</link>
      <description>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak is viewed as the favorite for the role, but Evero is evidently still in it. Per Fowler, Evero conveyed detailed plans for the offense and, specifically, the quarterback position during his in-person meeting with the Raiders. The presentation apparently went over well. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfa3970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired Ian Cunningham as their new general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfaf200000</link>
      <description>Reports consistently listed Cunningham as the favorite for this role. He also notably interviewed for the Falcons’ new president of football position before later interviewing for the general manager role. Cunningham signed on with the Ravens in 2008 as a personnel assistant and was later promoted to area scout in 2013. He became the Eagles’ director of college scouting in 2017 before taking their assistant director of player personnel job in 2019 and their director of player personnel job in 2020. He then accepted the assistant general manager role with the Bears in 2021 and has served in that role until now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfaf200000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
