<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 18:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sixth-round rookie Tyler Loop has been named the Ravens’ starting kicker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f2-d05a-adda-bff2f1a50000</link>
      <description>“He’ll be the kicker,” coach John Harbaugh confirmed after Saturday’s preseason game. “He’s earned it.” Loop was always the favorite to replace Justin Tucker by virtue of having draft capital. Despite his rookie status and strong if not impeccable college pedigree, Loop is immediately fantasy relevant as the kicker for one of the league’s highest-scoring offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f2-d05a-adda-bff2f1a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh revealed Keaton Mitchell’s injury is to his hamstring, but that he could return this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f5-d45c-a7fc-b7ffcdef0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a major concern, but the 23-year-old has now been sidelined over a week as he tries to challenge Justice Hill for change-of-pace work behind Derrick Henry. It all but guarantees he will begin the season as a somewhat distant No. 3 back, keeping him off the radar in most 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f5-d45c-a7fc-b7ffcdef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said “Russ (Wilson) is our starter” following the team’s preseason win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b82d-df63-a199-f92f4e990000</link>
      <description>We’ve finally reached the point where Daboll will be asked on a near-weekly basis who his starting quarterback is until the team inevitably inserts Jaxson Dart as QB1. The question isn’t unwarranted after Dart completed 14-of-16 passes for 137 yards and a touchdown against the Jets on Saturday night, but Wilson was always expected to open the season as the starter, and as of now, those plans haven’t changed. That said, the precision and command Dart showed on Saturday was impressive, and may lead to a changing of the guard that’s a bit sooner than expected. We should still expect Wilson under center in Week 1 when the Giants take on the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b82d-df63-a199-f92f4e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes “it’s clear from practice and game usage that second-year wide receiver Malachi Corley is on the roster bubble.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b839-d05a-adda-babb99100000</link>
      <description>During the 2024 NFL Draft, the Jets, under former head coach Robert Saleh and former GM Joe Douglas, traded two draft picks to move up and select Corley with the No. 65 overall pick. It’s been a disaster for Corley ever since, as the former Western Kentucky Hilltopper quickly fell out of favor with the old regime and caught just three passes for 16 yards across nine games. In Saturday’s preseason outing against the Giants, Corley played on 14 offensive snaps with the backups and failed to draw a target. He caught one pass for eight yards in the team’s first preseason game. Corely is a skilled player who drew comps to Deebo Samuel during the predraft process. If he doesn’t make the initial 53-man roster on cutdown day, there could be plenty of teams willing to take him on as a reclamation project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b839-d05a-adda-babb99100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said Andrew Thomas (foot) is taking his recovery day by day and “getting better.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b859-df63-a199-f97b12f10000</link>
      <description>Giants GM Joe Schoen said in July that Thomas should be good to go for Week 1 against the Commanders, but the team is in no rush to predict a return. Speaking on Sunday, Daboll said the decision to activate Thomas would be based on what Thomas and the team consider to be best. It’s about as predictable a response as we could expect. Thomas is rehabbing from a foot injury that ended his season in October and opened camp on the PUP list. If he is activated before camp ends, he would have roughly three weeks to be ready for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b859-df63-a199-f97b12f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot reports Shedeur Sanders (oblique) ‘tossed some short passes to tight end David Njoku in pregame warmups.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b89f-df63-a199-f9bf22d30000</link>
      <description>According to Cabot, Sanders’ throwing session has raised hopes that he will be able to get on the field in the Browns’ preseason finale against the Rams next week. The rookie missed Saturday’s game against the Eagles due to an oblique injury he suffered late in the week, but there’s hope that with enough time to recover, he should be ready for next Saturday’s game. Sanders could be one of several Browns quarterbacks to see action next week, as head coach Kevin Stefanski said he hopes to have all four quarterbacks healthy. It seems unlikely that Joe Flacco would suit up, but Sanders, along with Kenny Pickett and Dillon Gabriel, could all see ample reps as they look to solidify their spots on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b89f-df63-a199-f9bf22d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR/CB Travis Hunter (upper body) will not play in Sunday’s preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b8cb-df63-a199-f9eb309f0000</link>
      <description>Hunter is dealing with a non-specified upper body injury that was reported on Friday. Head coach Liam Coen hinted that Hunter might miss Sunday’s game due to the injury, but this appears to be a minor issue that shouldn’t carry over into Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b8cb-df63-a199-f9eb309f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Bengals “are listening to trade offers” for Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b8d3-d05a-adda-bad3343e0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport writes that “with contract talks at an impasse,” the Bengals are finally open to dealing the 2024 sack leader. A willingness to deal Hendrickson would have been better for everybody if the Bengals had considered this months ago, but now the four-time Pro Bowler will hope to find a new home and contract with just three weeks to go before the start of the season. Hendrickson has been holding in at Bengals camp since reporting on July 30th, and would likely need some time to ramp up for the start of the season. In theory, he should have several suitors on the market, but a trade could prove difficult given the pick compensation the acquiring team would have to give up, along with the money that would come from giving Hendrickson a new contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b8d3-d05a-adda-bad3343e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Panthers, Browns, and Colts are among the teams interested in trading for Trey Hendrickson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b910-df63-a199-f93b41c00000</link>
      <description>An in-division trade with the Browns feels like the most unlikely outcome, but we’ll assume any deal can be had with the right price. According to Schultz, the Bengals are “believed to want an impact player (or two) plus a draft pick” in exchange for Hendrickson’s services. It will be an obviously steep price to pay for any team that hopes to acquire the star pass-rusher, and any team willing to make the trade will also have to have room to sign Hendrickson to a new deal. We’ll see where things go from here, but for now, we have three teams to watch as trade negotiations spark up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b910-df63-a199-f93b41c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 8-of-10 passes for 77 yards and one touchdown in the Jaguars’ preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b91e-d45c-a7fc-bb1e89cf0000</link>
      <description>Lawrence played on two drives in the Jaguars’ second preseason game and saw four of his completions go for 10-plus yards. A strong first drive ended on a fumbled handoff between Lawrence and Tank Bigsby after Lawrence’s foot got caught up under his center when taking the snap. His second drive, however, ended on a seven-yard touchdown pass to Parker Washington and gave Lawrence his first touchdown of the preseason. Through two games, Lawrence has completed 14-of-17 passes for 120 yards and one touchdown and has taken no sacks on three pressures. For now, he’ll profile as a mid QB2 in fantasy but could be a candidate for a breakout season in his first year under Liam Coen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b91e-d45c-a7fc-bb1e89cf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
