<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea7-d8cf-affb-beaf7b140000</link>
      <description>Harris popped up on the injury report with a hip issue, though he still practiced in a limited capacity. The rookie has been used sparingly this season, but did bring in three passes for 49 yards with Quentin Johnston out in Week 15. Harris and Johnston (groin) are both limited Wednesday while WR/KR Derius Davis (ankle) did not practice. The Chargers’ wide receiver depth is mildly banged-up heading into Week 16 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea7-d8cf-affb-beaf7b140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC WR Makai Lemon has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2eb2-d1bc-a3fb-afb697c40000</link>
      <description>Lemon enters draft season as one of the country’s top wide receiver prospects. He finished junior year at USC with 79 receptions for 1,156 yards and 11 touchdowns, winning the Fred Biletnikoff Award for nation’s most outstanding receiver. The 21-year-old announced his intention to declare for the 2026 NFL Draft on social media, foregoing his remaining year of eligibility. Lemon has a chance to be the first USC wide receiver since Jordan Addison in 2023 to be selected in the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2eb2-d1bc-a3fb-afb697c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints signed RB Nyheim Hines to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ec5-d77b-adfb-eec7166d0000</link>
      <description>The Saints backfield is currently dealing with multiple injuries as neither Alvin Kamara (knee) or Devin Neal (ankle) practiced on Wednesday. As a result, the team has added Hines as depth on the practice squad behind Audric Estime and Evan Hull on the active roster. Neal is already ruled out for Sunday and Kamara is currently on the wrong side of questionable, so it is possible we see Hines on the field sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ec5-d77b-adfb-eec7166d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring) has a “2-4 week injury.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2efa-d1bc-a3fb-affe458e0000</link>
      <description>Cross has already been ruled out for Thursday’s Week 16 game against the Rams and is going to be out for longer, according to Rapoport. The Seahawks’ left tackle is expected to miss at least two weeks, but should return for Seattle’s playoff run. Backup Josh Jones will take over for Sam Darnold’s blindside in the meantime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2efa-d1bc-a3fb-affe458e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed EDGE Jeremiah Moon off the Panthers’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-31b2-d005-a9bf-f9b6de290000</link>
      <description>Moon played for the Steelers last year but didn’t make the roster for this season. The Panthers scooped him up and he has appeared in one game for them, playing exclusively on special teams. Moon will give the Steelers some extra depth after they lost T.J. Watt to a lung issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-31b2-d005-a9bf-f9b6de290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josina Anderson reports Bill Belichick has “upper-level personnel still fond of him in Atlanta, New York, and Cleveland.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3218-d005-a9bf-fa3cd03d0000</link>
      <description>That is presumably the New York Giants. She added, “There’s been recent interest expressed, at the very least, in speaking with Bill Belichick on an exploratory basis from two teams.” That is a lot of qualifiers tied to the supposed interest, but it does make sense. Every team without a head coach or considering moving on from their boss will be doing their due diligence over the next few months. Belichick is in the conversation for the greatest coach of all time. It would be irresponsible not to give him a call if you’re looking for a new boss. On the other hand, the game appeared to pass him by at the end of his time in New England. He then went to the college ranks, where controversy and failure followed close behind. North Carolina went 4-8 under his leadership in 2025. It wouldn’t be surprising for Belichick and UNC to agree that he is best fit for an NFL gig. Whether or not someone gives him the opportunity in the offseason remains to be seen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3218-d005-a9bf-fa3cd03d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts designated Anthony Richardson (eye) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3254-d8cf-affb-be7e2d470000</link>
      <description>The Colts now have three weeks to officially activate Richardson from injured reserve. Head coach Shane Steichen said he still has some vision limitations. As Rapoport notes, this is largely just to get him back on the practice field. The Colts are rolling with Philip Rivers for now and have Riley Leonard as a backup option in the meantime. Richardson is undoubtedly still at least a few weeks away from returning, if not more. Unless Rivers struggles mightily, Richardson will be relegated to backup duties once fully cleared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3254-d8cf-affb-be7e2d470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (knee/ankle) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3263-d8cf-affb-be6b028a0000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Matt LaFleur, the team will give Jacobs up until gametime before making a call on his status. That means he will be listed as questionable on the team’s final injury report, which will drop later today. Jacobs has not practiced at all this week, which is usually a sign that a player won’t suit up. However, Jacobs has been playing through his knee issues for weeks, and there has been no indication that his injury worsened in Week 15. Fantasy managers should be prepared for him to sit, even if he is truly questionable heading into the weekend. Emanuel Wilson would be in line for a workhorse role and an RB1 ranking if Jacobs can’t go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3263-d8cf-affb-be6b028a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said EDGE Drake Jackson (knee) will be able to play in Week 16 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3270-d8cf-affb-be7a9b630000</link>
      <description>Jackson hasn’t played since suffering a patellar tendon injury with the 49ers in 2023. Though the Commanders’ season is over, Jackson will get the opportunity to get some reps on tape before he heads into free agency in the spring. Jackson has six sacks in 23 career games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3270-d8cf-affb-be7a9b630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed (personal) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3286-d087-addf-b3f6a6330000</link>
      <description>Reed missed yesterday’s session while tending to a personal matter. After returning today, he will get cleared for Week 16 when the team releases its final injury report. With Christian Watson trending toward playing this week, expect a messy receiver rotation for the Packers, per usual. Reed will be stuck in the WR4 ranks if Watson plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3286-d087-addf-b3f6a6330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
