<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:04:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears rushed seven times for 26 yards in the Titans’ Week 9 loss to the Chargers, catching three passes for 36 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f2-d1e7-a1fa-5efa66e10000</link>
      <description>Spears and Tony Pollard more or less split snaps and touches down the middle as the Titans’ defense and special teams helped keep things interesting against the superior Chargers for the game’s first three quarters. L.A. pulled away in the final frame. Now headed on bye, the Titans will return against the Texans’ elite defense in Week 11. We suppose more Spears could be an adjustment for interim coach Mike McCoy, but we see little reason to expect this touches delineation to change. If it doesn’t, Spears will remain a lower-end FLEX option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f2-d1e7-a1fa-5efa66e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 1-of-3 targets for five yards in the Titans’ Week 9 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f5-d713-ad9e-6ef571b40000</link>
      <description>An awful fantasy line that does not include Dike’s 67-yard punt return score in the first quarter. That was the Titans’ most explosive play of the day, but it admittedly had little competition in a contest where Cam Ward completed only 12 passes. That stopped Dike’s recent modest momentum in its tracks, but he will undoubtedly remain a point of emphasis when the Titans come off bye in Week 11 against the Texans. Dike is an interesting young player, but not interesting enough to create consistent WR4 value in this awful offensive environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f5-d713-ad9e-6ef571b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 2-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Titans’ Week 9 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f7-d713-ad9e-6ef7a8610000</link>
      <description>Coming off a 53-yard Week 8, Okonkwo had little shot at a repeat as Cam Ward completely only 12-of-21 throws. Okonkwo is still drawing enough looks to provide last-gasp TE2 plausibility, but we certainly wouldn’t want to be counting on any Titans when they come off bye in Week 11 against the Texans’ elite defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f7-d713-ad9e-6ef7a8610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders declared CB Noah Igbinoghene, QB Josh Johnson, WR Terry McLaurin, LB Kain Medrano, T Trent Scott, T George Fant, and TE Colson Yankoff inactive for Week 9 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f7-d673-a39e-e6f703bd0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin’s status for Week 10 also appears to be in doubt, which could mark the second multi-game absence for the team’s top receiver already this season. Expect Chris Moore, Luke McCaffrey, and Jaylin Lane to divvy up the vacated snaps against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f7-d673-a39e-e6f703bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp is inactive for Week 9 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fb-d45b-affe-57ffebdb0000</link>
      <description>Kupp came into the weekend listed as questionable but ESPN’s Adam Schefter announced earlier in the day Sunday that it was likely Kupp would be sidelined for Sunday Night Football. The team made that speculation a reality when they released inactives 90 minutes prior to kickoff. Seattle will be down three of their top four wide receivers, with only Jaxon Smith-Njigba active, of the team’s normal contributors. Also inactive for the Seahawks are CB Derion Kendrick, QB Jalen Milroe, WR Jake Bobo, LB Jared Ivey, T/G Mason Richman, and WR Dareke Young.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fb-d45b-affe-57ffebdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Hoecht was carted off the field with an Achilles injury in Week 9 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fe-d1e7-a1fa-5efe33b90000</link>
      <description>Hoecht may not be a big name, but he’s been a massive difference maker for the Bills’ defense since he was reinstated from suspension. The 28-year-old couldn’t put any weight on his right leg when he hobbled off the field. Trainers huddled around him on the sideline before a cart was brought out. He was almost immediately ruled out with an Achilles injury, which is not a great sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fe-d1e7-a1fa-5efe33b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Helm caught a 15-yard pass in the Titans’ Week 9 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fc-d713-ad9e-6efc2f640000</link>
      <description>Helm’s fourth quarter reception was his lone target. This was his first one-look game since Week 4. The Titans have followed through on their word of getting the rookie fourth-rounder more involved. It’s just that floor and ceiling are both so difficult to come by in this offensive environment. Helm will not be a recommended TE2 when the Titans come off bye against the Texans in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46fc-d713-ad9e-6efc2f640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 26-of-37 passes for 273 yards and an interception in the Packers’ 16-13, Week 9 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46ee-d713-ad9e-6efe263f0000</link>
      <description>The Packers opted for a frustratingly run-heavy approach, keeping the ball on the ground for 15-of-26 first downs. Matt LaFleur eventually opened up his playbook late in the game, but it was too little too late for a Packers offense that managed just six points through 57 minutes of action. The Packers finally got their first touchdown of the game with less than three minutes left on the clock. The Panthers then marched down the field and knocked a game-winning field goal through the uprights. Green Bay also lost its biggest pass-catching weapon in this contest, Tucker Kraft, to a torn ACL. Even if the run-heavy approach didn’t work today, the loss of Kraft could convince Matt LaFleur to stick with his approach in Week 10 against the Eagles. Love will be stuck in the QB2 ranks for that game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46ee-d713-ad9e-6efe263f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elic Ayomanor caught 3-of-6 targets for 46 yards in the Titans’ Week 9 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4702-d673-a39e-e793de6e0000</link>
      <description>Ayomanor essentially repeated his Week 8 statline, which has more or less been his 2025 ceiling. Now the rookie wideout is left to ponder if veteran Calvin Ridley will remain with the Titans following Tuesday’s trade deadline. If so, Ayomanor will find himself as something of a de facto No. 1 wideout, but we still would not consider him a viable WR4 when the Titans come off bye in Week 11 against the Texans’ elite defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4702-d673-a39e-e793de6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore caught 4-of-6 targets for 72 yards in the Bears’ Week 9 win against the Bengals, adding one rush for 17 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f0-d673-a39e-e6f10f1e0000</link>
      <description>It was Moore’s best statistical output of 2025. He entered Week 9 with one touchdown on 26 receptions as a secondary part of Ben Johnson’s offense. On Sunday against a weak Bengals defense, Moore — dealing with a lingering groin injury — led Bears wideouts in catches and yards as Rome Odunze went without a catch on three targets. Moore saw a target on a meager 15 percent of his pass routes, however. He’s still not a prominent part of the Bears offense and should be considered a WR3/4 next week against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-46f0-d673-a39e-e6f10f1e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
