<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Trey Hendrickson (hip) is set to undergo core muscle surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc2-d77b-adfa-ffc3ea270000</link>
      <description>In a bit of a sourceoff, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport would only report that surgery is on the table, not that Hendrickson is “set to undergo” the surgery. Either way, undergoing the surgery would knock Hendrickson out for approximately six weeks, meaning his season would be over barring a miracle Bengals playoff appearance. It does feel like we’ve seen the last of Hendrickson for 2025, and it would appear that he’ll enter free agency unless the Bengals franchise tag him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffc2-d77b-adfa-ffc3ea270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) was limited in Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffd0-d005-a9bf-fff485620000</link>
      <description>It’s a new listing, and the first we’ve heard of a knee injury for the tight end after a 6/90 performance on Sunday. But given the fact that he was limited and not fully resting, we don’t think this is a serious concern for his Week 15 status just yet. Pitts figures to be the de facto Falcons WR1 if Drake London, as expected, remains sidelined on Thursday night. That hasn’t translated to more than TE1 PPR volume yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffd0-d005-a9bf-fff485620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (knee) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdc-d77b-adfa-ffdff03c0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimated report, but it’s a new listing for Tampa’s tight end. He’s not been particularly fantasy relevant since Tampa got Chris Godwin back, but this would seem to suggest there’s a chance he misses Week 15. Payne Durham is behind Otton in the pecking order at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdc-d77b-adfa-ffdff03c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers listed RB Bucky Irving (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdf-d8cf-affb-ffffc6640000</link>
      <description>Irving has been playing through the same shoulder injury since returning in Week 13, which may become the norm for the remainder of the season. The team listing him as a full participant on Monday’s report is a good sign for his Week 15 availability against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffdf-d8cf-affb-ffffc6640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons claimed WR Malik Heath off waivers from the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</link>
      <description>The 25-year-old receiver has a career 31/308/3 slash line in 37 games with the Packers and can be involved on special teams. The Falcons are at a point where they’re relying on David Sills every weekend. The waiver claim makes some sense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe8-d8cf-affb-ffeac4070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers listed QB Baker Mayfield (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</link>
      <description>Mayfield continues to be listed with the same left shoulder injury he has played through each of the last two weeks. We’ll assume he’s good to go for Thursday night’s game against the Falcons unless we hear otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffe2-d77b-adfa-ffe307be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL flexed the Patriots’ Week 16 game against the Ravens to Sunday Night Football.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffef-d005-a9bf-ffffb6770000</link>
      <description>The Bengals and Dolphins were initially slated to play on Sunday night in Week 16. They will now move to a standard 1:00 PM EST slot, while the Ravens and Patriots will prepare to play under the lights in a game that could still carry major playoff implications for both teams. As is the case with every Sunday night game on NBC, we will be waiting all day for this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ffef-d005-a9bf-ffffb6770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs OT Wanya Morris suffered a season-ending knee injury in Week 14’s loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-000e-d005-a9bf-d83e7fb00000</link>
      <description>Morris suffered a gruesome knee injury early in the first quarter of Sunday’s game against the Texans and was ruled out shortly after. The third-year tackle was replaced by rookie UDFA Esa Pole, who allowed three pressures on 42 pass-blocking snaps against one of the top pass-rushing defenses in the league. It’s yet another massive blow to a Chiefs offensive line that was already missing its two starting tackles prior to Morris going down. Pole will likely draw the start in Week 15’s game against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-000e-d005-a9bf-d83e7fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed LB Jason Pierre-Paul.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0021-d005-a9bf-d83504410000</link>
      <description>JPP hasn’t played an NFL snap since 2023. The 36-year-old pass rusher spent four seasons with the Buccaneers from 2018 to 2021 and split time with the Saints and Dolphins in his last season. If he’s elevated to the active roster, JPP wouldn’t serve as anything more than a situational pass rusher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0021-d005-a9bf-d83504410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers LG Ben Bredeson (knee) will not play in Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0027-d77b-adfb-caa7693e0000</link>
      <description>Beat writer Greg Auman reports that the Buccaneers may be without Bredeson “for multiple weeks” after the sixth-year tackle suffered a knee injury in Week 14’s loss to the Saints. Auman said the absence could be long enough to warrant Bredson landing on injured reserve, which would end his season. Bredeson has started all 11 games he’s appeared in this season, earning a PFF grade of 53.7 while allowing 20 pressures and one sack. Elijah Klein is listed behind Bredeson on the depth chart and will presumably draw the start on Thursday night against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0027-d77b-adfb-caa7693e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
