<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) said he is feeling good ahead of Week 9’s matchup against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b15-d713-ad9e-7f554a160000</link>
      <description>Flacco didn’t say if he expected to play in Sunday’s game, but that was clearly the vibe the veteran signal-caller was giving off on Friday when speaking with the media. Flacco and the Bengals plan to test his shoulder before ultimately deciding on his availability, but it sounds like he should be good to go in a plus matchup against the Bears barring any setbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b15-d713-ad9e-7f554a160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b1e-d713-ad9e-7f5ea5540000</link>
      <description>Young was a full participant in practice all week and was removed from the injury report on Friday. Despite initial concerns that he could miss multiple games with the ankle injury he picked up in Week 7, Young was only sidelined for one game and will be back under center against a stout Packers defense. Young will be hard to trust outside of 2QB/Superflex leagues even with a few good quarterbacks on byes this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b1e-d713-ad9e-7f5ea5540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Legette will play in Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b24-d45b-affe-7fb6cbcb0000</link>
      <description>Legette was never really at risk of missing Week 9’s game against the Packers after popping up with an illness on Thursday’s injury report. Legette has been an unreliable producer all season and saw one less target than Jalen Coker in last week’s blowout loss to the Bills. Legette can be left off Week 9 fantasy rosters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b24-d45b-affe-7fb6cbcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers listed OG Chandler Zavala (knee) as questionable for Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b29-d673-a39e-bfb9afe80000</link>
      <description>The Panthers didn’t open Zavala’s 21-day return window until this week, but the third-year guard was listed as a full participant in all three practices. Players who log a full week of practice tend to suit up come game day, so it’s possible this questionable designation is more cautious optimism than anything else. In addition to Zavala the Panthers also listed OG Damien Lewis (oblique), OT Taylor Moton (knee), S Nick Scott (groin), and LB Trevin Wallace (shoulder) as questionable for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b29-d673-a39e-bfb9afe80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) will not play in New England’s Week 9 game against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b46-d45b-affe-7fd697580000</link>
      <description>Vrabel also declined to get into if this would be a long-term injury, only saying it “certainly won’t be this week.” New England’s signing of D’Ernest Johnson and rumors of them scoping out the trade market sure seem to point to this not being a one-week ailment for Stevenson. TreVeyon Henderson is expected to be the main back this week for the Patriots, though we also wouldn’t be surprised if Terrell Jennings gets some run since the Patriots simply haven’t trusted Henderson enough this season to give him a huge workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b46-d45b-affe-7fd697580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendricks (hip) will be listed as doubtful for Week 9 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b2d-d45b-affe-7fbfb6320000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson was a DNP on Wednesday and Thursday, but Taylor clearly isn’t in a rush to rule out his star pass rusher before the weekend. Taylor said Hendrickson would be “day-to-day” to start the week after re-aggravating his hip injury in Week 8’s loss to the Jets. A player being listed as doubtful is generally a bad sign for their availability come game day, but it’s possible the Bengals wait to see how Hendrickson feels during pre-game warmups before making a decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b2d-d45b-affe-7fbfb6320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Taylor Rapp (knee) is “unlikely” to return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b56-d1e7-a1fa-7bfe58320000</link>
      <description>He underwent knee surgery, and whatever they found, it doesn’t sound like it was good. Rapp has already been placed on IR. Jordan Poyer and Cole Bishop were the main starters at safety last week, with Cam Lewis playing sparingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b56-d1e7-a1fa-7bfe58320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) will not play in Week 9 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b5e-d673-a39e-bfdf98de0000</link>
      <description>Ridley will now miss his third-straight game with the hamstring injury he suffered in Week 6 against the Raiders. The Titans will again hope that Van Jefferson, Elic Ayomanor, and Chimere Dike can step in to lead the team’s passing game against a defense that ranks in the top 10 in passing yards allowed and YPA allowed. In addition to Ridley the Titans also ruled out LB Arden Key and S Xavier Woods for Sunday’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b5e-d673-a39e-bfdf98de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL fined the Baltimore Ravens $100,000 for violating the league’s injury report policy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b59-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb2c690000</link>
      <description>Jackson was improperly listed as a full participant last Friday before being ruled out on Saturday. He did practice, but only ran the scout team, not the actual practice session team. The league reportedly determined that the listing was purely negligent and not about gaining a competitive advantage. The Ravens will never think about doing it again after such a devastating punishment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b59-d1e7-a1fa-7bfb2c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) will not play in Week 9 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b63-d673-a39e-bff3cf220000</link>
      <description>The 1-7 Titans will be without their defensive leader in a matchup against one of the league’s top offenses. It’s a tough break for a team that will also be without its WR1, as Calvin Ridley will miss a third-straight game with a hamstring injury of his own. Simmons has totaled 21 tackles and 4.5 sacks in seven games this season and will likely be replaced by C.J. Ravenell, who is listed behind him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3b63-d673-a39e-bff3cf220000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
