<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kendre Miller rushed eight times for 21 yards in the Saints’ Week 6 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da57-d94a-a79d-db5f1ab50000</link>
      <description>Miller added one grab for 11 yards on his lone target. The third-year back continued to cut into Alvin Kamara’s workload, but a 1B role between the tackles isn’t worth much on a team like the Saints. Miller has at least nine touches in each of his past four games but has posted just one usable fantasy week over that stretch. He is more of a thorn in the side of Kamara managers than a standalone fantasy bet heading into Week 7 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da57-d94a-a79d-db5f1ab50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 2-of-3 targets for 40 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 6 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da60-def2-abdb-df611a680000</link>
      <description>Kupp’s score, a third quarter 11-yarder against man coverage near the goal line, was his first as a Seahawk. Yet to have a 100-yard game, Kupp has surpassed 60 only once. He’s also yet to notch a 30-yard reception. With Jaxon Smith-Njigba dominating targets and AJ Barner emerging as a big-play/touchdown threat, Kupp is shaping up as a low-upside WR4 heading into Week 7 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da60-def2-abdb-df611a680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Knight rushed 11 times for 34 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 6 loss to the Colts, adding one catch for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da5b-d94a-a79d-db5fa6ce0000</link>
      <description>After reports had Knight playing ahead of Michael Carter before the Cardinals’ Week 6 game, fantasy managers were likely surprised to see Carter get the first backfield touch of the game. However, Knight came in on the same drive in the red zone and got a goal line carry for the touchdown. He out-snapped Carter 37-to-32 and got exactly one more touch than him on the day. Carter looks to be more of the passing-down back while Knight saw a slight preference on early downs with Emari Demercado (ankle) leaving the game early. The Cardinals have a frustrating backfield split for now, but Knight seems to have the preference for the red zone and early-down role. He is a fantasy RB3 for Week 7 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da5b-d94a-a79d-db5fa6ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Hunter caught 4-of-7 targets for 15 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 6 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da61-dd4c-afb9-ffe1e0140000</link>
      <description>So much for Hunter seeing more down-field targets, as had been suggested by ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe earlier in the week. The only impact Hunter made down the field on offense was somehow lining up offsides on what would have been a 54-yard Brian Thomas Jr. score in the third quarter. That’s called the “Kadarius Toney memorial snap.” Hunter did turn in some solid reps on defense, but the No. 2 overall pick is now sitting on 20 catches for 197 scoreless yards through six games played. Those kinds of numbers have him struggling for WR4 value in fantasy leagues. The earliest things might change is following the Jaguars’ Week 8 bye, keeping Hunter in the 46-50 range for next Sunday’s London road trip to face the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da61-dd4c-afb9-ffe1e0140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson is questionable to return in Week 6 against the Packers with a back injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ce-db72-a199-fbcf79f00000</link>
      <description>Packers TE Tucker Kraft decked Hendrickson with a hard chip-block late in the second quarter. The veteran pass rusher was later seen sitting on a cooler, grimacing and shaking his head while talking to trainers. With less than 30 seconds left in the half, and the Bengals’ offense on the field, trainers escorted Hendrickson to the locker room early, with one of them holding his helmet for him. He was ruled questionable to return shortly thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9ce-db72-a199-fbcf79f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 2-of-2 targets for 32 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 6 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da63-dd4c-afb9-ffe36c250000</link>
      <description>Harrison hit his head hard on the ground in the second quarter of the Cardinals’ loss to the Colts and was sent to concussion protocol. He was ruled out for the remainder of the game, finishing with two receptions for 32 yards from Jacoby Brissett. Fantasy managers should stay tuned to Harrison’s status throughout the week as his Week 7 is now in jeopardy. Should he miss time, Zay Jones will see a boost in opportunities moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da63-dd4c-afb9-ffe36c250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 3-of-3 targets for 71 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 6 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da67-d94a-a79d-db6f9f400000</link>
      <description>This was the second straight week Barner posted a new career high for yards, though he has still yet to surpass three targets only once. Today’s big statline was due to a second half 61-yard catch-and-run where Barner did the heavy lifting. Previously, he had only one catch longer than 20 yards all season. Barner is obviously showing something, but with Jaxon Smith-Njigba utterly dominating Sam Darnold’s limited volume, Barner is going to have a difficult time carving out anything other than the lowest-end TE2 value. The Texans await for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da67-d94a-a79d-db6f9f400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 6-of-10 targets for 98 yards in the Saints’ Week 6 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da5d-d94a-a79d-db5d6df20000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Olave was peppered with targets and did enough to keep fantasy managers content, logging 15.8 PPR points. Much like every other week, he failed to hit for a true spike game despite dominating the targets in New Orleans. Olave nearly found his ceiling with a long touchdown from Spencer Rattler, but the pass grazed off his fingertips at the goal line for an incompletion. Olave had multiple other deep shots that he failed to corral. Few players in the league earn as many targets as Olave every week, but his efficiency just isn’t there, and it’s hard to expect that to change in Week 7. He will remain a volume-based WR2 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da5d-d94a-a79d-db5d6df20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) was ruled out in Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da6c-def2-abdb-df6d1c160000</link>
      <description>Ridley picked up the hamstring injury in the second quarter and was seen with a large wrap around the injured leg. He could be facing an extended absence. In his place, Van Jefferson has functioned as the Titans’ top receiver. He could be worth a pick-up in deeper fantasy formats in the coming week if Ridley remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da6c-def2-abdb-df6d1c160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden II caught 6-of-8 targets for 68 yards in the Chargers’ Week 6 win against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da6e-def2-abdb-df6f00bd0000</link>
      <description>Ladd McConkey was the only Chargers pass catcher to see more targets than Gadsden, who has taken over as the team’s primary pass-catching tight end over the past few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da6e-def2-abdb-df6f00bd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
