<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill (oblique/calf) remained limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-db7b-a5dd-b66dc1d80000</link>
      <description>Hill doesn’t look to be in any real danger of missing time in Week 1, but playing through yet another set of injuries won’t be doing him any favors in fantasy football. There’s still a good chance he stumbles into plenty of value in Week 1 against a Colts cornerback room that can best be described as “veteran-laden,” but they won’t be playing Indianapolis every week. We’d like to see Hill get a full practice in on Friday to be confident that he’s got it all working, but he’ll be on the WR2/WR3 even if he is questionable on the final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-db7b-a5dd-b66dc1d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-d332-a1fd-967fc4fa0000</link>
      <description>Achane is being eased back into action and is on track to play in Week 1 against the Colts. Head coach Mike McDaniel has not been afraid to pile touches high on his stars’ plates when returning from injury. Achane is an RB1 for the occasion, though it would be nice to see him practice in full tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1669-d332-a1fd-967fc4fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson (hamstring) is not on the injury report for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1699-dbe3-a9bb-36db002a0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings managed Jefferson’s hamstring injury beautifully. He can be trusted to handle elite WR1 duties in primetime on Monday night. Fantasy managers should closely follow the health of Bears No. 1 CB Jaylon Johnson, who was known to be nursing a groin injury but also appeared on Thursday’s injury report with a calf injury. If Johnson is unable to play, Jefferson could take a significant number of snaps against every fantasy manager’s favorite cornerback, Tyrique Stevenson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1699-dbe3-a9bb-36db002a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins S Ashtyn Davis (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1686-dbe3-a9bb-36d739180000</link>
      <description>Dolphins backup CB Ethan Bonner (hamstring) did not practice and fellow backup DB Elijah Campbell was added to the injury report with a knee injury, suggesting he suffered a new injury in practice. The Dolphins’ secondary was already among the league’s most fantasy-friendly units—but now its depth is in trouble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1686-dbe3-a9bb-36d739180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WR Jalen Nailor (hand) is practicing in full for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ba-de13-afdd-56fb939d0000</link>
      <description>Nailor is firmly on track to suit up in Week 1 against the Bears. Unfortunately, he could be fourth in the passing game pecking order, playing behind Justin Jefferson, Adam Thielen and T.J. Hockenson. Nailor cannot be relied on to return FLEX value in 12-team leagues, instead profiling as a low-floor WR6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ba-de13-afdd-56fb939d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16c0-d332-a1fd-96f67a3e0000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw still has a chance to suit up for Week 1 against the Bears. J.J. McCarthy’s blindside protector tore both his ACL and MCL in Week 8 last year and has spent the offseason rehabbing the injuries. He was able to participate in team drills in late July, which was a positive sign for his early-season availability. Hopefully, he returns to practice by Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16c0-d332-a1fd-96f67a3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16bc-dbe3-a9bb-36fffb3b0000</link>
      <description>It’s a curious development for Smith, who was said to be dealing with a “health issue” in late August. NFL players generally play through illnesses, but this could be something to monitor. The Vikings’ defense is talented and well-coached, so they might be okay without him. It’s a story worth following, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16bc-dbe3-a9bb-36fffb3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) practice in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d3ffdd0000</link>
      <description>Taylor was limited yesterday so today’s upgrade is great news. In a perfect world, Taylor will kick back on the sideline and let Justin Fields lead the Jets to a decent record. Fields briefly dealt with a toe injury in training camp, though, so it’s good to have a reliable backup at the ready. Taylor does not need to be rostered in re-draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d2-dbe3-a9bb-36d3ffdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (quad) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d9-d332-a1fd-96ff834d0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw is trending toward missing Week 1 at this point, as he rehabs his second significant quad injury of the offseason. If he is active, it’s unlikely he plays a full complement of snaps. Broncos backup DT Malcolm Roach exited practice after suffering a calf injury today, which jeopardizes his availability for this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16d9-d332-a1fd-96ff834d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Jaydon Blue is inactive for Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ee-db7b-a5dd-b6ee00bb0000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal (seemingly) healthy scratch for Blue, who was an early summer hype merchant who slowly faded from fantasy consciousness after suffering a bruised heel and a low-ankle sprain in training camp. He was not listed on the injury report, but perhaps he needs more time. The Cowboys will instead roll with Javonte Williams and Miles Sanders as their two active backs. Williams will likely handle passing down duties while Sanders rotates in for change-of-pace rushes. The Cowboys also declared LB Shemar James, DT Mazi Smith, OT Ajani Cornelius, OL Hakeem Adeniji, OL Trevor Keegan and DT Perrion Winfrey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16ee-db7b-a5dd-b6ee00bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
