<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jamison Hensley reports Lamar Jackson (ankle) is practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb4-d8cf-affb-ffbec7bf0000</link>
      <description>Ravens OC Todd Monken said he expected Jackson to play yesterday, and a Thursday DNP appeared to be management for Jackson. We’re not expecting any surprises on Jackson’s status later this afternoon given the fact that the Ravens and Steelers are playing a must-win game for control of the top of the AFC North, but stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb4-d8cf-affb-ffbec7bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns listed Dylan Sampson (calf) as questionable for Week 14 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb1-d005-a9bf-ffb5a2e70000</link>
      <description>Sampson was a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday. He presumably logged a limited session on Friday to draw the questionable tag. Sampson has proven reliable in short spurts throughout the season, but the volume isn’t there to warrant starting him in fantasy this week against the Titans. While Sampson is questionable, the Browns did rule out TE Brenden Bates (ankle), DT Adin Huntington (knee), OG Wyatt Teller (calf), and QB Deshaun Watson (Achilles).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb1-d005-a9bf-ffb5a2e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (concussion) won’t play in Cleveland’s Week 14 game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb6-da9b-a9bf-ffbfa9b70000</link>
      <description>As expected, Conklin did not clear protocol and will be out for Sunday’s extremely NFL-Draft-Relevant showdown between the 3-9 Browns and 1-11 Titans. KT Leveston came on for Teller in the middle of Cleveland’s loss to the 49ers and figures to be part of the replacement plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb6-da9b-a9bf-ffbfa9b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is not on Cleveland’s final Week 14 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb9-d77b-adfa-efbbfa720000</link>
      <description>He has shrunk into a smaller role while the Browns have emphasized Harold Fannin Jr. down the stretch, so Njoku playing through this knee ailment is commendable but not exactly fantasy-notable. He’s been listed on the injury report with the knee injury in each of the last three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb9-d77b-adfa-efbbfa720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns listed Mason Graham (ribs) as questionable for Week 14 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb7-d77b-adfa-efb7a68f0000</link>
      <description>Graham popped up on Thursday as a limited participant and will officially be questionable heading into the weekend. The rookie tackle has totaled 31 tackles, five TFLs, and a half sack while helping anchor a Browns line that has been stout up front. Speaking with the media after practice, Graham said he expects to play on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efb7-d77b-adfa-efb7a68f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said he “hope[s]” Trey Benson (knee) will return this season, but “he’s just not there yet.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efbb-d8cf-affb-ffbbd1d20000</link>
      <description>When the deadline to activate Benson from his 21-day window was mentioned to Gannon, he noted “that doesn’t mean you can’t activate him and then he could possibly be down.” It doesn’t sound like Benson is particularly close to returning at this point. Zonovan Knight will continue to fill in as the lead back in the meantime for the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efbb-d8cf-affb-ffbbd1d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Greg Dortch (chest) won’t play in Arizona’s Week 14 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efbf-d8cf-affb-ffbf4c4d0000</link>
      <description>With the pills no longer being Dortched, the Cardinals worked in 30 snaps of Xavier Weaver in Week 13’s loss to the Buccaneers. We expect a heavy concentration of targets on Trey McBride and Michael Wilson this week with both Dortch and Marvin Harrison Jr. down for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efbf-d8cf-affb-ffbf4c4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (groin) is expected to play in Washington’s Week 14 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efc6-d005-a9bf-fff61d4b0000</link>
      <description>Brown will have to be activated off injured reserve before that can officially happen, but it seems a formality as he was practicing in full this week. The Commanders will finally have the passing game fully healthy against the Vikings, for what feels like the first time all season, in Week 14. Brown isn’t a fantasy play as we suss out his involvement level and if he’ll be on a snap count.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efc6-d005-a9bf-fff61d4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans C Lloyd Cushenberry (foot) won’t play in Tennessee’s Week 14 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efcf-d005-a9bf-fffffda30000</link>
      <description>Corey Levin started for the Titans in Week 13 and looks to have the role again this week. It’ll be the second week in a row that Cushenberry is sidelined with this foot injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efcf-d005-a9bf-fffffda30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (ankle) will play in Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efce-d77b-adfa-efcf82960000</link>
      <description>Jackson missed Thursday’s practice due to an ankle injury, but was back on the field on Friday. He was removed from the team’s final injury report and will be good to go in a pivotal AFC North matchup against the Steelers in a game that will decide the division leader heading into Week 15. Jackson has struggled since returning from injury. He’s thrown just one touchdown pass to three interceptions over his last four games and is averaging 21.0 rushing yards per game over that span. Jackson is a low-end QB1 against the Steelers this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-efce-d77b-adfa-efcf82960000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
