<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 23:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak said he wants to give RB Kenneth Walker III “more opportunities” but does not want to “discount” RB Zach Charbonnet and RB George Holani.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f4ab-df81-ab9b-feefbf770000</link>
      <description>Kubiak also celebrated Walker’s improvement “as a practice player,” and for being “very intentional about the things we’re asking him to work on.” Kubiak’s initial statement leaves room for interpretation as to whether the team actually intends to increase Walker’s workload, though. Just yesterday, The Athletic’sMike Dugarasked head coach Mike Macdonald about whether Walker had earned more work with his per-play efficiency, to which Macdonald said the team takes stats “into account,” but that they “have a plan for their RB usage.” Referring to Walker and Charbonnet, Macdonald added that both players are playing “high-level football” and that they will both keep being used. Until we see Walker significantly out-touch Charbonnet, we can only treat Kubiak’s comments as wishful thinking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f4ab-df81-ab9b-feefbf770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (hamstring) and WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) were seen participating in practice on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f52f-da18-a39b-ff3f4df50000</link>
      <description>Evans’ return to practice is less of a surprise. The veteran receiver had a planned rest day on Friday ahead of the Buccaneers’ Monday night tilt with the Lions in Detroit. Egbuka, on the other hand, made a quicker than expected return from his hamstring injury. With the Lions’ secondary already in shambles due to injuries and a Brian Branch suspension, Evans could be a borderline WR1 this week if Egbuka and Chris Godwin are out. Egbuka is a must-start option if he’s able to suit up for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f52f-da18-a39b-ff3f4df50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) has been ruled out for the Week 7 matchup against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f818-da18-a39b-fa1b998a0000</link>
      <description>Slayton hurt his hamstring in Week 5 against the Saints and hasn’t practiced since. The 28-year-old wide receiver was ruled out Saturday to no one’s surprise. A sliver of hope fantasy managers can cling to is that Slayton is yet to be placed on injured reserve, which assumes the Giants believe he can return to the field before missing four games. Lil’Jordan Humphrey led Giants receivers with eight targets against the Eagles last week and will be in line for more work with Slayton out once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f818-da18-a39b-fa1b998a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles told reporters WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) is a game-time decision for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f81c-d651-a9df-f91d53eb0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka made a surprise appearance on the practice field on Saturday. Now his head coach is calling him a game-time decision. Egbuka has a chance to play against the Lions depleted secondary and is a must-start option if he’s ultimately available. Fantasy managers will need to have a backup plan in place, though, with two games on Monday night this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f81c-d651-a9df-f91d53eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders downgraded WR Deebo Samuel (heel) to out for Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f879-da18-a39b-fa7bc95e0000</link>
      <description>Woof. Samuel’s absence leaves the Commanders extremely thin at pass-catcher with fellow wide receiver Terry McLaurin ruled out as well. Tight end Zach Ertz is listed as questionable, potentially leaving the team’s pass-catching corps in the hands of aging veteran Chris Moore, Luke McCaffrey, and Jaylin Lane. Expect a heavy dose of Jacory Croskey-Merritt for as long as the game environment allows against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f879-da18-a39b-fa7bc95e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Cardinals are expected to start Jacoby Brissett at quarterback Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f89e-df81-ab9b-fedf64b30000</link>
      <description>That is the most logical solution considering the team heads to their bye in Week 8, giving Murray a full three weeks of rest and rehab before returning to the active roster in Week 9. The offense utilized increased rates of play action and pre-snap motion in Week 6 with Brissett giving the team a greater ability to be under center as opposed to in shotgun and pistol, increasing the fantasy appeal of tight end Trey McBride and wide receiver Marvin Harrison Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f89e-df81-ab9b-fedf64b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8af-d651-a9df-f9bfcd420000</link>
      <description>Ward suffered a concussion in pre-game warmups in Week 6 and has now been placed on injured reserve, marking a massive blow to the secondary in Indianapolis. The freak accident will keep him out of the game-day lineup for the next four games, at minimum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8af-d651-a9df-f9bfcd420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers activated LB Khalil Mack and LB Denzel Perryman from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8e1-da18-a39b-faf31cf70000</link>
      <description>The Chargers get a solid boost to the interior of their defense ahead of a showdown against the Colts in Week 7, with both linebackers making their return from injured reserve. It’s a slight downgrade to the rushing matchup for Jonathan Taylor and we could see the Los Angeles defense generate more organic pressure on quarterback Daniel jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8e1-da18-a39b-faf31cf70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans activated NT T’Vondre Sweat (ankle) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8f0-d651-a9df-f9f58ba70000</link>
      <description>Sweat makes his return to a roster that has allowed the fourth most fantasy points per game to opposing backfields this season. Sweat has continually graded as a top performer against the run throughout this career, making his return a significant boost to a struggling unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8f0-d651-a9df-f9f58ba70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) for Week 7 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8f3-da18-a39b-faf3077a0000</link>
      <description>Kirk popped on the team’s injury report Friday with a hamstring injury and was subsequently ruled out for the team’s Monday Night Football game against the Seahawks. The veteran slot receiver has appeared in just three games for the Texans after joining their roster this offseason. His absence allows additional snaps for rookies Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f8f3-da18-a39b-faf3077a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
