<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 26 times for 83 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903e-d713-ad9e-fc7ee0ae0000</link>
      <description>Barkley struggled to get the wheels turning in the first half but made multiple nice runs in the fourth quarter to help the Eagles put the game away, coming close to ripping off chunk gains on multiple occasions in the final frame. Even so, fantasy managers that sunk a first round pick into the veteran are assuredly left wanting more as Barkley now has only two carries of 20 or more yards after amassing 17 such carries during his historic 2024 season. Of note, the Eagles lost center Cam Jurgens and offensive tackle Lane Johnson to aggravated injuries in this one, which is something to keep an eye on ahead of a Week 12 matchup with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-903e-d713-ad9e-fc7ee0ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 7-of-11 targets for 49 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9042-d713-ad9e-fc5656b60000</link>
      <description>Brown saw just two downfield targets while primarily working the short areas with slants and outs, an interesting approach considering the Lions were once again down multiple starters in the secondary. The increased targets appear to be more than coincidence after Brown was seen telling fantasy managers to drop him on a livestream of him playing Madden earlier in the week. The outspoken receiver is averaging the lowest yards per game of his standout career, and yet, the Eagles currently sit at an 8-2 record and in the driver’s seat for the only bye out of the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9042-d713-ad9e-fc5656b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 2-of-5 targets for 24 yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9046-d673-a39e-b4d71b7b0000</link>
      <description>That now makes seven of nine appearances in which Goedert has managed four receptions or fewer while playing for a seemingly dysfunctional offense now ranked 16th in points per game. Goedert derives the bulk of his fantasy value from an elite red zone role, meaning his weekly range of outcomes remains one of the widest at the position, of current TE1s. That doesn’t change ahead of a divisional tilt against the Cowboys in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9046-d673-a39e-b4d71b7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 1-of-5 targets for eight yards in the Eagles’ Week 11 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9049-d673-a39e-b4d98fed0000</link>
      <description>Smith doesn’t get a complete pass as he dropped his first target on the first play from scrimmage, but it is noteworthy that quarterback Jalen Hurts peppered A.J. Brown with 11 targets after the outspoken wide receiver was seen telling fantasy managers to drop him on a livestream of him playing Madden earlier in the week. The explosive receiver will look to get back on track in Week 12 when the Eagles face off against the porous defense of the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9049-d673-a39e-b4d98fed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Aaron Rodgers (fractured wrist) will undergo tests to determine whether or not he can play in Week 12 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9204-d713-ad9e-fe54693b0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers is dealing with a fracture in his left wrist, but according to Rapoport, whether or not Rodgers plays in Week 12 will be dependent on whether or not he can further injure himself and whether or not he can grip a football. The injury is to Rodgers’ non-throwing hand/wrist, which is good in theory, but there are obviously times he will need that hand to secure the ball and keep it away from a defender when pressured in the pocket. Rapoport said Rodgers “was described as 50-50" for next week, so we’ll see where things go from here in the coming days. If he’s unable to go, Mason Rudolph would draw his first start of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9204-d713-ad9e-fe54693b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the league will review the spitting incident that took place between Ja’Marr Chase and Jalen Ramsey in Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-920e-d673-a39e-b69fe8500000</link>
      <description>When asked why he punched Chase in Week 11’s win over the Bengals, Steelers corner Ramsey accused Chase of spitting on him, which the star receiver denied. Videos have since surfaced showing Chase clearly spitting in the direction of Ramsey, but whether or not there was any intent to spit on Ramsey is up for interpretation. The league will presumably look to determine whether or not Chase intended to spit on Ramsey during their review of the matter, but it’s possible that a one-game suspension could be handed down, similar to what we saw with Jalen Carter in Week 1 when he spat on Dak Prescott after the opening kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-920e-d673-a39e-b69fe8500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Nailor caught his lone target for 16 yards in the Vikings’ Week 11 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9224-d45b-affe-d7b65c5e0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career game in which he caught five balls for 124 yards and a score, Nailor was JJ McCarthy’s fourth option in this one. Nailor ran a route on 21 of the team’s 34 drop backs. Nailor likely won’t have much fantasy value unless Justin Jefferson or Jordan Addison miss time in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9224-d45b-affe-d7b65c5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colby Parkinson caught both of his targets for 14 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 11 win against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9229-d45b-affe-d7bf28830000</link>
      <description>Parkinson saw a bump in playing time and usage with Tyler Higbee sidelined with an ankle issue that could keep him sidelined in the coming weeks. Parkinson’s touchdown came on a short throw in the red zone; he broke a couple tackles to get the ball over the goal line. It was his second straight game with a touchdown. He was targeted on two of his nine pass routes against Seattle. Parkinson, with 11 receptions over his past four games, could be a decent streamer in Week 12 against the Bucs if Higbee is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9229-d45b-affe-d7bf28830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren said “I could have returned” when asked about the ankle injury he suffered in Week 11 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-923c-d673-a39e-b6bd50400000</link>
      <description>Warren was walking awfully gingerly on his ankle after going down in the third quarter of Sunday’s contest, so it’s a bit surprising to hear him say he believes he could have returned. Assuming that’s the case, we would expect Warren to have a chance to log some limited practice sessions this week, in hopes of playing in Week 12. His status will be one to monitor throughout the week, but if he’s unable to go, it will be Kenneth Gainwell drawing the start in his absence. Gainwell totaled 105 yards from scrimmage and two touchdowns on 16 touches in Sunday’s win and would profile as a high-upside RB2 if Warren is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-923c-d673-a39e-b6bd50400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Michael Penix is seeking a second opinion on what may be a season-ending knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9284-d673-a39e-b6957b470000</link>
      <description>Schefter adds that the initial diagnosis on Penix’s injury “is not encouraging.” It’s a complete 180 from what we heard yesterday when it was reported that the team believed Penix’s injury was similar to the one he suffered in Week 7 that sidelined him for Week 8. Knee injuries followed Penix throughout his college career. He saw his 2018 and 2020 seasons come to an end due to a torn ACL in his left knee, and it was his left knee he injured on Sunday. We’ll likely get an official word on his injury soon, but Kirk Cousins is now poised to take over as the Falcons’ QB1 for the foreseeable future, and perhaps, the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9284-d673-a39e-b6957b470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
