<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:04:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught all five of his targets for 70 yards in the Raiders’ Week 6 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dab8-d94a-a79d-dbbdfb060000</link>
      <description>Tucker made the most of his five targets in another run-heavy game script for the Raiders. Tucker remains a high-variance weekly fantasy play as Geno Smith’s preferred downfield option, though he’s seen more consistent opportunity with Brock Bowers (knee) on the sideline. Tucker now has 356 receiving yards on the season and should be seen as a deep league flex in Week 7 against the Chiefs. The Raiders might not be able to be as run-first as they have been against the vastly superior Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dab8-d94a-a79d-dbbdfb060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones completed 27-of-39 passes for 347 yards and two interceptions in the 49ers’ 30-19, Week 6 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dabe-d94a-a79d-dbbfff400000</link>
      <description>Laboring notably at points while dealing with his knee and oblique injuries, Jones posted respectable passing totals but threw a back-breaking interception in the fourth quarter that it looked like he didn’t even attempt to read out. His first pick, in the first quarter, was nearly a pick-six but Tampa Bay’s Kindle Vildor got caught by the turf monster twice on the return. Kyle Shanahan is working magic every week to get a banged-up Jones to throw for as much yardage as he has, but it’s clear that Jones is struggling when the easy buttons go away. A Sunday Night Football matchup against the rejuvenated (for now) Falcons pass defense would seem to be a QB2 spot for Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dabe-d94a-a79d-dbbfff400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports the Giants could lose a draft pick if the league determines they violated the concussion evaluation in Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dac4-db72-a199-facfa9900000</link>
      <description>Speaking on Football Night in America, Florio said the league is taking the review of the Giants’ Week 6 concussion evaluation of Jaxson Dart “very seriously.” Florio also points out that rookie RB Cam Skattebo entered the blue medical tent while Dart was being evaluated, which is a violation. According to Florio, the league will meet with “all relevant medical staff, coaches, and players” involved with the matter. This situation remains under review. We will be sure to check back with any updates as they are received.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dac4-db72-a199-facfa9900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield completed 17-of-23 passes for 256 yards and two touchdowns in the Buccaneers’ 30-19, Week 6 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dac3-dd4c-afb9-ffc354030000</link>
      <description>No Mike Evans? No Chris Godwin? No Emeka Egbuka in the second half? Well that’s just another normal day at the office for Mayfield. Mayfield darted a pair of long scores to Tez and Kameron Johnson to keep the Buccaneers in the driver’s seat for most of the second half, finally pulling away late. The 30-year-old quarterback absolutely shredded the middle of the field with Fred Warner lost to an ankle injury, completing 8-of-9 passes there for 145 yards and a touchdown. Potentially sans Egbuka, it’s hard to say that Mayfield’s ceiling will be sky high against the Lions next Monday night. But he’s also performed so well despite the loss of his weapons that we’re not quite taking him off the QB1 line either.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dac3-dd4c-afb9-ffc354030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Fred Warner dislocated and broke his ankle and will require surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dacb-db72-a199-facbb3af0000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Warner was carted from the field in an air cast after injuring his ankle. The veteran linebacker’s ankle was bent in an unnatural way, immediately leading to everyone fearing the worst. It’s another tough blow for a Niners team that has been decimated by injuries all season. Warner has been an Iron Man in the league since being drafted in 2018. He has missed only one regular season game in his career, but is now likely to miss the remainder of this season due to the nature of his injury and the surgery that will follow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dacb-db72-a199-facbb3af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 19-of-26 passes for 259 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Packers’ 27-18, Week 6 win over the Bengals, adding seven rushes for 26 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-daa8-d94a-a79d-dbadbd9e0000</link>
      <description>Love was very busy early on, carving up the Bengals’ defense as a passer and rusher as the Packers established a 10-0 lead in the first half. Love impressively picked up a few first downs on the ground to keep the chains moving, and has now run for 54 yards over the last two weeks. Love’s first-drive interception is forgivable. His pass protection abruptly collapsed on third down, and Love suddenly found himself flushed out to the right, pursued by two Bengals pass rushers, one of whom Love faceplanted with a sprinting stiff arm. He then attempted to force a completion to Doubs, but a Bengals defensive back successfully got a hand on the ball, tipping it back to S Geno Stone, who hauled it in. On the plus side, rookie WR Matthew Golden’s post-bye emergency gives Love another reliable receiver and forces defenses to play honestly. Love will again find himself on the QB1/2 borderline against the Cardinals next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-daa8-d94a-a79d-dbadbd9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings told reporters he is playing with five broken ribs and high and low ankle sprains.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dad5-dd4c-afb9-ffd51f290000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ injury troubles are no secret at this point, but the six-year vet is clearly going through it. He’s managed to suit up for four of the Niners’ six games this season despite breaking camp with a calf injury that threatened his Week 1 availability. Jennings caught just one pass for seven yards in the Niners’ Week 6 loss to the Buccaneers, but still managed to play on 53 offensive snaps, per PFF. While he’s clearly willing to gut it out on the field, it’s no secret that these injuries can hinder Jennings’ performance. Given the more specific details of his injury, Jennings becomes very difficult to trust in Week 7’s game against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dad5-dd4c-afb9-ffd51f290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 5-of-9 targets for 55 yards in the Packers’ Week 6 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dad6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7413b0000</link>
      <description>Doubs’ nine targets paced Packers pass catchers by four. He is the passing game’s clear-cut No. 1 weapon. Doubs continues to play very well in the Packers’ highly efficient offense, accounting for 4-of-12 passing game first downs gained. Although Doubs’ yardage production remains somewhat inefficient, he has Jordan Love’s trust, particularly when pressured, and should remain in WR3 slots against the Cardinals in Week 7. He also notably returned two punts for 14 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dad6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7413b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed 17 times for 54 yards in the 49ers’ Week 6 loss to the Buccaneers, adding seven catches for 57 yards on eight targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dada-db72-a199-fadb48500000</link>
      <description>These are the last four weeks of work on the ground for McCaffrey: 17/54, 22/57, 17/49, 17/52. The PPR WR2 part of the bet on McCaffrey has hit hard, but it’s been more like mixing Jaylen Waddle with Alfred Morris than prime McCaffrey. At least he finally scored a rushing touchdown this week. He’ll easily remain on the RB1 line against the Falcons, but that’s more a testament to the power of his PPR skills than to his actual explosiveness right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dada-db72-a199-fadb48500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson caught 3-of-3 targets for eight yards in the 49ers’ Week 6 loss over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dade-dd4c-afb9-ffdff1480000</link>
      <description>He managed just five snaps. Robinson’s fantasy value remains tethered to Christian McCaffrey’s health. He simply doesn’t see enough work to be startable at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dade-dd4c-afb9-ffdff1480000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
