<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) was not seen practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e1b-d1bc-a3fb-af3f7dac0000</link>
      <description>Saints rookie RB Devin Neal (hamstring) has been starting in Kamara’s stead, but Neal has already been ruled out this week. That leaves RB Evan Hull and RB Audric Estime to potentially compete for the starting role. Estime notably outplayed Hull last week. If Kamara can return, expect him to handle a sizable workload. The Saints face the lowly Jets this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e1b-d1bc-a3fb-af3f7dac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans (collarbone) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e33-d1bc-a3fb-af375ee10000</link>
      <description>Evans will likely have his reps limited during practice over the next few weeks. Making his triumphant return from the broken collarbone he suffered in Week 7, Evans was as good as anyone could have hoped on Thursday. He earned 12 targets, six of which were caught for 132 yards. Evans immediately returned to the No. 1 role in the Bucs offense and made the most of his many opportunities. He is in line for a WR2 ranking for Week 16 against Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e33-d1bc-a3fb-af375ee10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e35-d1bc-a3fb-af35845c0000</link>
      <description>Otton missed Week 15 with the knee issue. He was listed as doubtful after getting in a lone limited practice to end the week. It was a short turnaround to Thursday’s game, making it almost impossible for the banged-up tight end to play. He has a better shot of suiting up this week. With Mike Evans, Chris Godwin, and Emeka Egbuka all healthy, Otton will not be on the fantasy radar for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e35-d1bc-a3fb-af35845c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints ruled out WR Devaughn Vele (shoulder) for Week 16 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e30-d1bc-a3fb-af3452130000</link>
      <description>Vele flew too high, winning multiple contested catches in Week 15 against the Panthers. The 6-foot-5, 210-pound wide receiver will now miss Week 16 after picking up a shoulder injury last week. Ideally, Vele returns in time to play in at least one more game and continues to carve out a role as a possession receiver in the Saints’ offense for next year. Saints WR Chris Olave became QB Tyler Shough’s go-to receiver only after Vele left last week’s contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e30-d1bc-a3fb-af3452130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (neck) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3c-d1bc-a3fb-af3c0aa40000</link>
      <description>Williams’ injury was initially described as a left shoulder injury by the Sunday Night Football broadcast, but the official injury report corrects the record. Williams could be seen bending his neck to the left and moving his left arm while talking to the Cowboys’ training staff. After returning to the field, he would at times flex and extend the left arm as well, while occasionally bracing it against his side between plays. At this point, he is on track to face the Chargers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3c-d1bc-a3fb-af3c0aa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) is practicing fully for Week 16 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3e-d1bc-a3fb-af3ef23b0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson sandwiched an absence at last Thursday’s practice with two limited sessions. He return to full participation is a good sign. Last week, the Cowboys’ starting tight end caught just 2-of-4 targets for 16 yards. Although his health is on the upswing, he must face Chargers S Derwin James at times this week. He remains a TE1, but he may take a few hard hits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3e-d1bc-a3fb-af3ef23b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3a-d005-a9bf-fe3e21910000</link>
      <description>Spillane was a late addition to the injury report last week with a foot issue. He is now listed with an ankle injury, though we suspect they are one and the same. Spillane was active for Week 15 but did not play a snap. He was later spotted in a walking boot. Christian Ellis and Harold Landry also missed today’s practice. That is the Patriots’ top two tacklers and No. 1 pass-rusher all on the sidelines for Wednesday’s session. Their defense could be in a bind if all three are ruled out for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e3a-d005-a9bf-fe3e21910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4a-d77b-adfb-eecb5f1f0000</link>
      <description>Davis left Week 15 with the hip issue and did not return. Fellow cornerback Marcus Jones was also listed as a DNP today. He is dealing with a knee issue. With other starters in the front seven also out of practice, the Patriots could be severely undermanned for their Week 16 date with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4a-d77b-adfb-eecb5f1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4e-d005-a9bf-fe7e870e0000</link>
      <description>Higgins got in some limited practices last week but was ultimately ruled out on Friday. He will need to get upgraded to a full participant before being cleared from the league’s concussion protocol. No Bengal outside of Ja’Marr Chase and Chase Brown topped 20 receiving yards with Higgins sidelined for Week 15. If he isn’t cleared for Week 16, there isn’t a fantasy option worth adding for Cincinnati’s matchup with the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4e-d005-a9bf-fe7e870e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman reports that the Packers will place RB MarShawn Lloyd (calf/hamstring) back on injured reserve after activating him on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4b-d005-a9bf-fe7ffc550000</link>
      <description>This is a “procedural move” that will potentially allow the team to activate him later this season, in the event that they make a playoff run. Lloyd, 24, has had a brutal start to his career, plagued by lower-body injuries. He was placed on injured reserve after straining a hamstring in training camp. While rehabbing that injury, he picked up a calf injury. He then suffered another hamstring injury after the Packers activated him to return from injured reserve a couple of weeks ago. He should not be rostered in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4b-d005-a9bf-fe7ffc550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
