<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift rushed 17 times for 53 yards in the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings, adding 12 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c8f-d332-a1fd-bebfc9de0000</link>
      <description>Swift was the only Chicago back to register a carry in Week 1, adding five targets to his ledger to the one of rookie Kyle Monangai. Roschon Johnson was held out of this one with an injury, so it remains to be seen if Swift will continue forward with such a robust share of the opportunities out of the backfield once Johnson returns, but the Week 1 returns were promising for fantasy managers that invested a middle-round pick in the veteran back. Up next for Swift and the Bears are the Lions on the road in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c8f-d332-a1fd-bebfc9de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 6-of-9 targets for 36 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c92-de13-afdd-6edb97640000</link>
      <description>Preseason reports that Odunze would be featured in the offense in 2025 seemed to come to fruition in Week 1 as his nine targets handily led the team. He scored with just over two minutes remaining to bring the Bears within a field goal on a leak play from one yard out, saving his fantasy day in the process. Even so, the nine targets on 36 Caleb Williams pass attempts represent a solid 25 percent target market share and were four more than veteran DJ Moore saw. Odunze’s next opportunity to return a usable fantasy week comes in Week 2 on the road against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c92-de13-afdd-6edb97640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught both targets for 12 yards in the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c95-d332-a1fd-beb7e8570000</link>
      <description>Loveland had two catches early but was phased out of the offense as mounting struggles forced the team away from their game plan, eventually ceding crunch time work to veteran Cole Kmet. The Chicago offense looked lost after an opening possession touchdown, something head coach Ben Johnson will need to correct ahead of another divisional clash with the Lions in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c95-d332-a1fd-beb7e8570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olamide Zaccheaus caught 4-of-7 passes for 42 yards in the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c98-db7b-a5dd-ac9cabfd0000</link>
      <description>Zaccheaus finished second on the team in targets behind only Rome Odunze, likely seeing his volume spike due to increasing pressure from an aggressive Brian Flores Vikings defense. He remains on the fringe of fantasy consideration in deeper leagues as the WR3 in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c98-db7b-a5dd-ac9cabfd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy completed 13-of-20 passes for 143 yards and two touchdowns in the Vikings’ 27-24, Week 1 win over the Bears, adding 25 yards and a touchdown on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9a-db7b-a5dd-ac9ec45b0000</link>
      <description>McCarthy and the Minnesota offense went three-and-out on four of their first five possessions in the first half, and started the third quarter with a pick-six to fall into a 17-6 deficit. They would then go three-and-out their next two possessions before finding the end zone on their first three possessions of the fourth quarter to steal victory from the clutches of defeat. McCarthy connected with Justin Jefferson for his first professional touchdown pass before hitting running back Aaron Jones down the sideline for his second score. He would take on a rushing score 14 yards out on the next possession after scoring just three times on the ground during his collegiate career. The Vikings would hold on to get to 1-0 ahead of their home opener against the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9a-db7b-a5dd-ac9ec45b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed 15 times for 68 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears, adding seven yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9f-d332-a1fd-bebf8b0b0000</link>
      <description>Mason out-carried veteran Aaron Jones 15 to eight and averaged a solid 4.5 yards per carry in the win, making good on offseason promises that he would be heavily involved in the offense in 2025. The fact that he managed 15 carries in a game in which the Vikings trailed until the fourth quarter speaks volumes to his presence as the primary rusher after being acquired by the Vikings this offseason, and he is likely to remain heavily involved when the Vikings host the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2c9f-d332-a1fd-bebf8b0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones rushed eight times for 23 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears, adding 44 yards and a touchdown on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca2-de13-afdd-6eeb3e430000</link>
      <description>Jones managed just eight carries to the 15 of Jordan Mason but cashed in on a 27-yard receiving touchdown in the fourth quarter in the comeback victory. His 44 yards tied with Justin Jefferson for the team lead on a night the Vikings failed to get much going until the final frame. Jones is likely to cede more work on the ground than he has in the past after the team acquired Mason this offseason, but he remains an integral piece of the offense via his dynamism through the air. Jones’ next chance to return viable fantasy counting stats comes in week 2 when the Vikings host the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca2-de13-afdd-6eeb3e430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 4-of-7 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca5-de13-afdd-6eef5e070000</link>
      <description>The Vikings went three-and-out on six of their first nine possessions, with the other three resulting in two field goals and a pick-six thrown by J.J. McCarthy. Jefferson understandably had little production through the team’s early struggles but ignited a ferocious comeback with a fourth quarter touchdown in tight coverage to the middle of the end zone. Fantasy managers were surely wishing for more from their first-round pick but the touchdown eased the pain slightly. Jefferson will look to return to dominance when the Vikings host the Falcons in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca5-de13-afdd-6eef5e070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 3-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca8-de13-afdd-6eeb95fb0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson saw little fantasy success on a night the Minnesota offense went three-and-out on six of their first nine possessions, failing to find the end zone until the fourth quarter. They would score on three fourth quarter possessions to snatch the win from the Bears, but Hockenson was relegated to blocking duties as the Vikings looked to establish their ground game to open up play action late. That venture would be fruitful on the scoreboard but left Hockenson’s fantasy managers yearning for more from the veteran tight end. His next opportunity to return usable counting stats comes in Week 2 when the Vikings host the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ca8-de13-afdd-6eeb95fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Thielen failed to catch his only target in the Vikings’ Week 1 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</link>
      <description>Thielen saw a reduced snap rate in a game the Vikings preferred to operate from heavy personnel after continued shortcomings, eventually breaking through with three fourth quarter touchdowns to steal the win from the Bears. Thielen would make his mark felt on the field by catching a two-point conversion on the team’s penultimate score for his only counting stats of the game. Thielen remains an iffy fantasy bet ahead of a Week 2 meeting with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2cab-d332-a1fd-bebf3efe0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
