<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 19:01:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 1-of-2 targets for nine yards in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-dc7a-af9b-efffda780000</link>
      <description>Musgrave wasn’t involved despite the Packers throwing 46 times in the loss, and the 2023 second-round pick finishes a disappointing campaign with another ineffective fantasy outing. He ended the year with just 24 catches for 252 yards, and even after Tucker Kraft went down with his ACL injury in Week 9, he didn’t he didn’t make an impact with zero touchdowns and just one game with over four catches. The 25-year-old is under contract for one more year, and there’s no reason to think he should be on radars when draft season begins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ab6e-dc7a-af9b-efffda780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon McManus missed both field goal attempts while making 3-of-4 extra points in the Packers’ Wild Card Round loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-abd6-dc7a-af9b-efffa56e0000</link>
      <description>McManus missed two critical kicks; an extra-point that would have put the Packers up by 13 with two minutes left, and a field goal that would have extended the Green Bay lead to six. The 34-year-old made 24-of-30 field goals in 2025, but he went just 6-for-12 on kicks beyond 40 yards. He is signed through 2027, but there’s no guarantee that McManus will be back in Green Bay in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-abd6-dc7a-af9b-efffa56e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said LB T.J. Edwards suffered a fractured fibula in the team’s Wild Card Round win over the Packers and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad36-dc7a-af9b-efbf0e640000</link>
      <description>Edwards was carted to the locker room in the second quarter of Chicago’s stunning comeback victory over the Packers and did not return. He appeared in 10 games this year, logging 67 combined tackles, .5 sacks, and a pick-six. D’Marco Jackson took his spot in the lineup in the second half of Saturday’s game. Jackson has largely been a backup this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad36-dc7a-af9b-efbf0e640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said LT Ozzy Trapilo suffered a patellar injury in the team’s Wild Card Round win over the Packers and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad3d-d35e-a1bf-edff09ac0000</link>
      <description>The second-round rookie didn’t see much action early in the year but took over as the team’s starting left tackle in Week 12. He has held down that job ever since. Pro Football Focus has him graded as a top-40 tackle this year. Theo Benedet took his spot in the lineup late in Saturday’s game. He will presumably start in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad3d-d35e-a1bf-edff09ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad73-d35e-a1bf-edf380400000</link>
      <description>The coaching pool isn’t as deep this year as it was in 2025 when Ben Johnson and Liam Coen were both on the market. That, in turn, has teams like the Browns digging deeper into the McVay tree. Scheelhaase joined LA last year as an assistant and passing game specialist. He was promoted to passing game coordinator ahead of the 2025 season. Matthew Stafford went on to post career numbers this year, leading the league with 4,707 passing yards and 46 touchdowns. Scheelhaase is an under-the-radar name to watch for Cleveland. He will likely be in consideration for offensive coordinator gigs around the league as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad73-d35e-a1bf-edf380400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “a lot of people around the league have been wondering” if the Packers would be at the top of John Harbaugh’s list of head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad9c-dc7a-af9b-efbfae280000</link>
      <description>The Packers haven’t decided on Matt LaFleur’s future yet, but another early playoff exit has many speculating that they will move on from him in the coming days. As Schefter notes, Harbaugh is from the Midwest and his agent, Bryan Harlan, is the son of a former Packers president. It’s admittedly a tenuous link, but the dots are there for someone to connect. More importantly, the Packers would, in this scenario, be the only playoff team with a head coaching vacancy. Harbaugh wouldn’t need to spend any time rebuilding a defunct roster and could instead focus on getting Green Bay out of the Wild Card Round. They already have an answer at quarterback with Jordan Love and just spent big on defensive superstar Micah Parsons. We would expect Harbaugh to prefer Green Bay to any other landing spot if the team fires LaFleur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ad9c-dc7a-af9b-efbfae280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports teams “still believe there is a chance” Notre Dame head coach Marcus Freeman comes to the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adc0-d968-a19b-fdf12e0a0000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Freeman recently had his contract adjusted by Notre Dame to stay with the team. He also posted on social media late last year that he would be returning to the Fighting Irish. Still, a massive raise and a chance to coach in the pros could lure him away from college football. We suspect multiple teams will reach out to him just to be sure, though all signs point to him staying in the college ranks for another year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adc0-d968-a19b-fdf12e0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared RB Ty Johnson, LB Terrel Bernard, CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle), DT Larry Ogunjobi, S Darnell Savage, OL Tylan Grable, TE Keleki Latu inactive for the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adcf-d35e-a1bf-edcf93820000</link>
      <description>Johnson suffered the ankle injury in the Bills’ final game of the regular season. He only practiced once this week before being listed as questionable. Ray Davis will see more work in his absence. James Cook could also be used more on passing plays, upping his fantasy value for Sunday’s DFS slate. Kicker Matt Prater is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-adcf-d35e-a1bf-edcf93820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Dyami Brown, RB DeeJay Dallas, OL Cole Van Lanen, TE Hunter Long, DL Emmanuel Ogbah, and DT Maason Smith inactive for the Wild Card Round against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ade0-d35e-a1bf-ede276a80000</link>
      <description>Van Lanen has played all over the formation this year, filling in wherever needed. The team recently rewarded his versatility with a three-year extension. He has been starting at left tackle as of late. Walker Little will likely slide back to left tackle for this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ade0-d35e-a1bf-ede276a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington left the Jaguars’ Wild Card Round game against the Bills to be evaluated for a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae39-dc7a-af9b-efbf7e230000</link>
      <description>Washington left the game in the first quarter for the concussion evaluation. He was quickly taken to the locker room after getting shaken up. Jakobi Meyers and Brian Thomas Jr. would be asked to step up if Washington cannot return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae39-dc7a-af9b-efbf7e230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
