<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans fired DC Dennard Wilson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e70f-d35e-a1bf-e7cff9010000</link>
      <description>The Titans recently hired defensive-minded head coach Robert Saleh, who will implement his own defensive scheme. Wilson held the Titans’ defensive coordinator role for the past two seasons. He has coached in the NFL since 2012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e70f-d35e-a1bf-e7cff9010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons interviewed Texans assistant general manager James Liipfert for their general managers vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e71d-d35e-a1bf-e7df09b20000</link>
      <description>Liipfert spent nine years serving in various scouting roles with the Patriots (2009-2017) before signing on with the Texans. As the Texans’ assistant general manager, he specifically operates as the director of college scouting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e71d-d35e-a1bf-e7df09b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Skipper retired after nine seasons in the NFL.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e730-dc7a-af9b-efbf36e50000</link>
      <description>Skipper spent time on the Cowboys, Broncos, Patriots, Raiders and Colts’ practice squads after entering the NFL as an undrafted free agent in 2017. He was signed to the Texans’ active roster in 2019 before signing on with the Lions later that year. Although he bounced between the Lions’ active roster and other practice squads after that, the six-plus seasons spent on the Lions’ active roster ultimately define his career. He caught a nine-yard touchdown pass against the Bills in Week 15, 2024. He is reportedly volunteering as an offensive line coach at this year’s East-West Shrine Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e730-dc7a-af9b-efbf36e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley said he’ll hire an offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e73b-d968-a19b-fffb78a30000</link>
      <description>Reading between the lines, it doesn’t sound like Dolphins OC Frank Smith will return in 2026. He got interviews with the Panthers and Seahawks for their head-coaching vacancies in 2024 and had a four-year run of success with the Dolphins despite not ever calling players under Mike McDaniel. Smith could be an intriguing staff addition with Miami’s success running the football last year for a number of teams, be it as an OC or a run-game coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e73b-d968-a19b-fffb78a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami OT Francis Mauigoa declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e756-d56e-afff-e7fe01db0000</link>
      <description>Per ESPN’s Adam Schefter, Mauigoa is expected to be one of the top picks in the 2026 NFL Draft. He allowed eight sacks in three regular seasons at Miami. PFF charts him as having been beaten by a defender only five times in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e756-d56e-afff-e7fe01db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan M. Alexander believes Nick Chubb won’t return to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e74f-d968-a19b-ffff826d0000</link>
      <description>Asked in a mailbag column if the Texans would pursue a veteran back in free agency, Alexander noted that he believes Dare Ogunbowale could return to the Texans, but flatly said Chubb won’t. The 30-year-old vet will try to catch on elsewhere in a short-yardage role in 2026. The Texans could make an offseason move to sign or draft a back to split time with Woody Marks. Or perhaps both.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e74f-d968-a19b-ffff826d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan said the Dolphins need to “find our guy” at quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e76c-dc7a-af9b-efff348d0000</link>
      <description>“So yes, we will find our guy, but we’re going to make sure that we’re building the infrastructure along the way so when we do find our trigger man -- whoever that may be, whether it’s Tua, Quinn [Ewers] or somebody that’s not in the building -- we have a team that he can go play and win with,” Sullivan continued. It sounds like the Dolphins new management feels like the current quarterback room is at ground zero, and Sullivan further added “we will draft quarterbacks every year, if not every other year, because I think you have to.” Neither Tua Tagovailoa nor Quinn Ewers appear to be on firm ground with the new regime. Tagovailoa is a likely post-June 1 release, while Ewers could be traded if another team was willing to part with enough for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e76c-dc7a-af9b-efff348d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes Wink Martindale is an “early favorite” for the Jets defensive coordinator role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e78d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf5cff0000</link>
      <description>“The ’23 Giants tied for the league lead with 31 takeaways, which has to intrigue the turnover-starved Jets. Glenn jumped on Martindale early, interviewing him before the Jets’ season ended,” Cimini adds. Martindale had DC interviews with the Falcons and Colts last offseason and would certainly make the Jets more bombastic in one way or another. The Jets are the only team that has interviewed him in the 2026 offseason that we know of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e78d-d35e-a1bf-e7cf5cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Marc Raimondi reports that Bears assistant GM Ian Cunninham and 49ers director of scouring and football operations Josh Williams are “front runners” for Atlanta’s general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e790-d35e-a1bf-e7d2b15a0000</link>
      <description>Both also interviewed for Atlanta’s hand-created-for-Matt-Ryan “president of football” position, and the Falcons appear to have used those interviews as a starting point for their general manager position. Neither has come back for a second interview yet, with Atlanta only just announcing some new interviews for GM candidates today after spending the early offseason on the head coach and (ugh) “president of football” positions. Cunningham has ties to Ryan through his boss, Bears GM Ryan Poles, who played with Ryan at Boston College.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e790-d35e-a1bf-e7d2b15a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested an interview with Eagles senior personnel director and advisor to the general manager Joe Douglas for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7a6-d968-a19b-fff7a3b20000</link>
      <description>Douglas spent the 2025 season in his current role, following a six-year stint as the Jets’ general manager. Before that, he served as the Eagles’ vice president of player personnel from 2016-2019. He was hired as the Bears’ director of college scouting in 2015 after spending 2000-2014 as a scout with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7a6-d968-a19b-fff7a3b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
