<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers promoted assistant QB coach and pass game specialist Mike Bercovici to pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e80000</link>
      <description>Bercovici recently interviewed for the Commanders’ offensive coordinator vacancy, but the Panthers opt not to let Bercovici walk. Bercovici, 32, began his coaching career at Arizona State as a graduate assistant in 2019. He signed on with the Cardinals in 2020 as a coaching assistant before being promoted to offensive assistant in 2022. He joined the Panthers’ coaching staff in 2023 and has been there ever since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles head coach Nick Sirianni said the organization wants to “continue to evolve as an offense.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2f7-dc7a-af9b-cfff10a10000</link>
      <description>Sirianni and Eagles general manager Howie Roseman held a press conference today, where they discussed former OC Kevin Patullo’s recent firing and how the team plans to find his replacement. Both individuals want to “do what’s best for this football team” and hope to find “the guy [that] best fits us.” Given Roseman’s involvement, the team is likely seeking a creative, proven and analytically-minded coach for their offensive coordinator vacancy. Former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel and former New York Giants head coach Brian Daboll are reportedly “at the top” of the Eagles’ list for the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2f7-dc7a-af9b-cfff10a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When asked about potentially trading WR A.J. Brown, Eagles general manager Howie Roseman said Brown is “a great player” and it is “hard to find great players.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c30b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7a7a0000</link>
      <description>In short, Roseman complimented his No. 1 wide receiver while refusing to say whether the team is open to trading him. Per Roseman, when the Eagles “go out in free agency and the Draft,” they are " trying to find great players who love football and [Brown is] that guy.” It is the type of answer one expects to hear from a smart general manager who is willing to make big moves, and it gives the audience very little to go on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c30b-dc7a-af9b-cfbf7a7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) is questionable for Buffalo’s Divisional Round game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c325-d35e-a1bf-c7e7998f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson got in a limited session on Thursday, which is very similar to his Friday limited last week after two DNPs that also got him to the questionable line. Our guess is that he’s on the pessimistic side of questionable. If Johnson doesn’t play, Ray Davis will be a threat for a higher snap count than usual again and be a potential DFS play for the Divisional Round slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c325-d35e-a1bf-c7e7998f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee/calf) is not on Buffalo’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c328-dc7a-af9b-cfbf6daa0000</link>
      <description>Kincaid got in three limited sessions this week, a slight downgrade from the one full and two limiteds he saw ahead of the Wild Card round. He’s simultaneously so banged up that it’s hard to expect much and also one of the few players in the Bills passing game that Josh Allen can trust. He’s a hard player to square on this week’s DFS slate, though he obviously is a worthwhile play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c328-dc7a-af9b-cfbf6daa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen (foot/knee/finger) is not on Buffalo’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32a-d35e-a1bf-c7ea9e9b0000</link>
      <description>He practiced in full each of the last two days and said earlier this week that he “felt better” than he had ahead of the last two games. Allen will roll into this game against the Broncos off a sublime performance vs. the Jaguars and should be trusted in DFS lineups — obviously he’s a threat to be the QB1 in any given week of the season, so he remains so in a four-game slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32a-d35e-a1bf-c7ea9e9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Terrel Bernard (calf) is questionable for Buffalo’s Divisional Round game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfc4670000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited practice sessions this week, likely enough to toe a true questionable line. Bernard would replace one of Matt Milano or Shaq Thompson if he’s able to play on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfc4670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Buccaneers’ autonomous offensive coordinator role could appeal to former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel, who “is very coveted” by teams with offensive coordinator vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c323-dc7a-af9b-cfbf57780000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers, Eagles, Lions and Chargers are interested in hiring McDaniel for their offensive coordinator vacancies. ESPN’s Jeff Darlington notes that the Eagles, Lions and Chargers are all run by offensive-minded head coaches. Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles previously held defensive coordinator roles with the Buccaneers (2019-2021), Cardinals (2013-2014) and Eagles (2012). He allows his offensive coordinators “full autonomy of the offense,” which could appeal to a former head coach like McDaniel, who may wish to avoid butting heads with an offensive-minded head coach over scheme and staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c323-dc7a-af9b-cfbf57780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills interviewed Ravens assistant special teams coach Anthony Levine for their special-teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32f-d56e-afff-e7ef978f0000</link>
      <description>Levine, a long-time special teams standout for the Ravens in a decorated playing career, is the latest to interview for the Buccaneers special teams coordinator job. Levine may or may not be interested in coming along with John Harbaugh to join the Giants, so he has a lot of options on paper. The Buccaneers also reportedly interviewed Eagles special teams coordinator Michael Clay for the role in what would be a lateral move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c32f-d56e-afff-e7ef978f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers interviewed passing-game coordinator Marcus Brady for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c332-dc7a-af9b-cfbf379f0000</link>
      <description>Brady is the first candidate to interview for the Chargers’ OC role, and undoubtedly not the last. He did interview for the Bucs and Patriots OC openings last year., as well as for three vacancies for an OC role in 2024. The veteran passing-game coordinator coordinated the Colts offense briefly in 2021-2022 — those were the Carson Wentz and Matt Ryan/Sam Ehlinger/Jeff Saturday year,s if you want help dating yourself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c332-dc7a-af9b-cfbf379f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
