<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec believes Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) will not play in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ee4-da67-a99f-fef5ff880000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Likely upped his activity level and did work out in front of members of the training staff. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport speculated that this could mean a Week 3 debut for Likely. His return sounds like it isn’t too far away, but it will be at least one more week on the sideline for the contract-year tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ee4-da67-a99f-fef5ff880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Quinshon Judkins is questionable for Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eea-dc44-a9d9-3feecb810000</link>
      <description>Judkins’ availability comes down to how well he knows the playbook and if his conditioning is up to snuff. The rookie missed all of training camp while he and the Browns quibbled over his contract details. Judkins’ ongoing legal situation prevented the two sides from reaching a deal, though the Browns eventually gave him a fully guaranteed contract anyway. Judkins returned to practice on Thursday after meeting with league officials on Wednesday. With just two practices under his belt over the past three months, his role will likely be minor if he is out there at all on Sunday. Judkins needs to be rostered in all fantasy formats, but fantasy managers should give it a week before getting him in their lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eea-dc44-a9d9-3feecb810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (eye) is questionable for Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eee-dc44-a9d9-3feed7500000</link>
      <description>Defensive tackle Mike Hall remains out with a knee issue. Conklin suffered the eye injury in Week 1 and was also listed with an elbow issue on Week 2’s injury report. He was limited in practice throughout the week, suggesting he will suit up on Sunday. Cornelius Lucas will take Conklin’s spot in the lineup if the latter is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eee-dc44-a9d9-3feed7500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said inside linebackers coach Zak Kuhr will call plays on defense in Week 2 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ef2-d294-a19b-fef264970000</link>
      <description>Defensive coordinator Terrell Williams is currently away from the team for medical reasons. Kuhr took over his duties earlier this week and will continue in that role on Sunday. While it’s not ideal to switch play-callers this early in the year for continuity purposes, Kuhr gets a potentially great matchup versus a Miami offense that looked dead on arrival last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3ef2-d294-a19b-fef264970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Ranaan reports “multiple players ... told ESPN unprompted” last year that an offense where the ball was “force-fed” to Malik Nabers was unsustainable.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eec-dc44-a9d9-3fee04ef0000</link>
      <description>Nabers himself admitted as much after Week 1, saying that the Giants should “spread the ball around to every guy.” It’s possible that this means nothing — the Giants sure didn’t change much after last season — but perhaps this is a collective squeaky wheel situation where Nabers sees fewer targets in Week 2. We’d bet on what we’ve been seeing, which is another 10-target Nabers game and (likely) a loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3eec-dc44-a9d9-3fee04ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) will not play in Week 2 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3efd-d294-a19b-fefd18450000</link>
      <description>He once again did not set foot on the practice field all week. Gonzalez’s return doesn’t appear especially close at this point, and it’s starting to look like the Patriots should have just placed him on injured reserve. He’ll enter Week 3’s injury tracking as a question mark to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3efd-d294-a19b-fefd18450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) will not play in Week 2 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f01-d86f-abdd-7fbdc4b50000</link>
      <description>Neither will T’Vondre Sweat, who has been sidelined with an ankle injury. Oli Udoh looks to be next in line for snaps at right tackle for Tennessee. It’s a big downgrade for Cam Ward’s protection as the rookie quarterback continues to fight against his supporting cast to produce aesthetically pleasing statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f01-d86f-abdd-7fbdc4b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said Chimere Dike has “earned more opportunities as a receiver.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f06-d86f-abdd-7fbff2030000</link>
      <description>Dike played just 10 snaps last week, it’s possible he makes major in-roads towards Tyler Lockett’s role in the offense after the veteran started out drawing only a single target in 33 snaps during Week 1’s loss to Denver. Dike probably isn’t on the mainstream fantasy radar yet, but he could be an interesting pickup in deep leagues and should be someone to monitor on the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f06-d86f-abdd-7fbff2030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints EDGE Chase Young (calf) will not play in Week 2 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f0b-d86f-abdd-7fbf15690000</link>
      <description>A minor #RevengeGame narrative is snuffed out as Young hasn’t practiced due to the calf injury since the season began. Trevor Penning (toe) joins Young on the inactive line. New Orleans managed four sacks without Young against the Cardinals in Week 1, but Kyler Murray gave them a little help on those.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f0b-d86f-abdd-7fbf15690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OT Taliese Fuaga (knee) is questionable for Week 2 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f0e-da67-a99f-ffff89c10000</link>
      <description>Fuaga said he was optimistic he’d play on Thursday and was able to get in back-to-back limited sessions to end the week. It does sound like his inflamed patellar tendon is going to cause him some trouble, as it did in Week 1, and may need to be managed throughout the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f0e-da67-a99f-ffff89c10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
