<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports it is still “uncertain” if Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) will play in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-067e-d332-a1fd-967e4a6b0000</link>
      <description>Schefter said that Parsons may need an epidural prior to the game and that the star rusher has been dealing with an “L4/L5 facet joint sprain” in his back. We don’t really know how much stock to put into this given Parsons said he’s feeling great on Friday — it almost reads like a Cowboys source dumping what they know to make the trade look better because of the details on what the Cowboys wanted Parsons to do. It does sound like perhaps the idea that Parsons’ back injury was pure cover-up is off-base. Parsons practiced in what appeared to be a limited basis today per ESPN’s Rob Demovsky.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-067e-d332-a1fd-967e4a6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes 49ers WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) “doesn’t seem too far off.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0695-db7b-a5dd-a695f9050000</link>
      <description>But, he adds, the team might place Watkins on IR to make room for Kendrick Bourne if Bourne ends up signing with the 49ers. It sounds like Watkins has missed his chance to make a fantasy impact piece early in the season either way, but he’s still worth monitoring in dynasty leagues after making a lot of noise early in training camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0695-db7b-a5dd-a695f9050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) still considered day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0691-d332-a1fd-96b76de20000</link>
      <description>Head coach Raheem Morris said Mooney participated in Monday’s jog through, but still said the veteran receiver will remain day-to-day ahead of the first official practice on Wednesday. Mooney has been dealing with a shoulder injury since July and did log a practice late last week. We’ll see where things stand on Wednesday when the first practice report is released, but it sounds like he’s trending in the right direction ahead of Week 1’s game against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0691-d332-a1fd-96b76de20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Najee Harris (eye) is cleared for contact and there’s a chance he plays in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06a3-dbe3-a9bb-36f3e4f80000</link>
      <description>Things have been trending in a positive direction for Harris over the last two weeks, but Harbaugh has yet to out-and-out say that he will play in Week 1. Greg Roman said a few weeks ago that Omarion Hampton will split snaps with someone in Week 1 — Harris if he plays, or (likely) Hassan Haskins if Harris sits. We’ll be monitoring Harris’ practice status all week but being cleared for contact is a good sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06a3-dbe3-a9bb-36f3e4f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Quentin Johnston has cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06b3-db7b-a5dd-a6b704b20000</link>
      <description>Johnston’s role in the offense remains murky after the Keenan Allen addition. We suspect that Johnston will be battling the inconsistent Tre’ Harris for snaps and targets outside, but either way this is probably only news for DFS contests at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06b3-db7b-a5dd-a6b704b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaire Alexander (knee) did not practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06be-db7b-a5dd-a6be15490000</link>
      <description>We’re in midseason form. Alexander has not practice since August 9th per The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec. There’s still plenty of time for him to get cleared this week, but nobody should be surprised if Alexander misses Week 1 after this long of a layoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06be-db7b-a5dd-a6be15490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ac-de13-afdd-46ef3a310000</link>
      <description>Likely underwent foot surgery on August 1 and hasn’t been on the field since. The fourth-year tight end avoided opening the season on injured reserve, suggesting he will be able to return before Week 4, but he’s far from a lock to play in Week 1 against the Bills. The Ravens don’t have to release their first official practice report until Wednesday, which should give us a better sense of Likely’s availability for Week 1. Even if he is active, he’ll be hard to rely on in fantasy with Mark Andrews still operating as the team’s top tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ac-de13-afdd-46ef3a310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he expects Matthew Stafford (back) to start against the Texans in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ed-db7b-a5dd-a6eda16b0000</link>
      <description>We’re expecting Stafford to continue to be managed through practices, but so far his back injury doesn’t seem like it’ll keep him from setting foot on the field on opening day. Jourdan Rodrigue of The Athletic said recently she believes the injury is going to need to be managed throughout the season, so Stafford is probably best-approached as a risky QB2 in superflex leagues at this time. For a quarterback who is very bound to the pocket, a first-game test against Will Anderson and Danielle Hunter presents a real challenge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ed-db7b-a5dd-a6eda16b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Alaric Jackson returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06c9-de13-afdd-46cb4eb60000</link>
      <description>Jackson was diagnosed with blood clots in June, but has been trending toward being ready for Week 1. The fact that he was able to suit up for a Monday practice suggests he’s still trending in the right direction, and the team said the plan will be to start him in Week 1 against the Texans if all goes well this week. Jackson earned a PFF pass blocking grade of 79.5 last season, allowing just three sacks and 22 pressures on 502 dropbacks. If he is unable to start, D.J. Humphries looks like the most likely candidate to step up in Jackson’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06c9-de13-afdd-46cb4eb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevon Diggs said there’s a 75-80 percent chance he plays in Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0704-d332-a1fd-9736aa9a0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys open the season on the road against the Eagles on Thursday night. The veteran corner’s status was reported as “up in the air” earlier by NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, and that appears to still be the case based on Diggs’ comments. Diggs said earlier that he would be ready to go by Week 4 at the latest, but his practice availability will give us a better look at how he projects for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0704-d332-a1fd-9736aa9a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
