<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said “I expect the guys that we have here to give it what they got one more time,” when asked about expectations for Week 18’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b90-dc7a-af9b-efbff87b0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like most of Detroit’s regulars will be going against the Bears in Week 18, though perhaps if there’s any long-term concern about a particular injury, a player or two could sit. Detroit has nothing to play for but can still spoil Chicago’s bid to be the No. 2 seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b90-dc7a-af9b-efbff87b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Lamar Jackson’s status is “to be determined. ... We’ll know a lot more on Wednesday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b9c-d56e-afff-effc9cbe0000</link>
      <description>Not exactly a ringing endorsement for Jackson to play in Week 18, but Harbaugh will leave the door open and we’re sure we’ll get at least one Jackson practice appearance given the stakes. It does feel like Jackson has simply given all he has physically and hasn’t been able to play at full strength since Week 3 or 4. Jackson’s practice status will be one of the hottest topics of Week 18, we’d put him on the pessimistic side of questionable to open the week based on this quote. Harbaugh offered a “If Lamar’s ready to go, he’s playing, that’s it.” If not, it’ll be Tyler Huntley trying to win the AFC North for the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b9c-d56e-afff-effc9cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer told reporters that Dak Prescott will play in Week 18 against the GIants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b91-dc7a-af9b-efbf69350000</link>
      <description>It’s a little weird that the Cowboys have to keep telling people the starting quarterback is going to start, but, here ya go. Prescott will get the start in the finale against the Giants with a chance to add to his numbers in a game that means nothing outside of where the teams will draft come April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6b91-dc7a-af9b-efbf69350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel told reporters that Minkah Fitzpatrick is “day-to-day” with his calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ba7-d35e-a1bf-6fe73c9b0000</link>
      <description>McDaniel stressed that Fitzpatrick doesn’t want to be shut down. The 29-year-old safety didn’t play against the Buccaneers in Week 18, and with Miami eliminated from playof contention there isn’t a great reason outside of pride for the safety to play. He still might.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6ba7-d35e-a1bf-6fe73c9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said the Texans will play their starters in Week 18’s game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bbe-d56e-afff-effe56270000</link>
      <description>They can still win the division and get as high as the No. 3 seed, so, yes, we expected this to be the outcome. Any fantasy leagues in the wilderness relying on Woody Marks, Nico Collins, and C.J. Stroud need not worry about them not playing. At least as long as this game doesn’t get out of hand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bbe-d56e-afff-effe56270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) would undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc5-d56e-afff-efedb9580000</link>
      <description>He’ll almost certainly be placed on injured reserve ahead of Week 18’s game against the Buccaneers. Sanders broke his ankle on Carolina’s first play from scrimmage yesterday against the Seahawks. The 2024 fourth-rounder enters the 2026 offseason in the third year of his rookie contract having not taken a noticeable step forward in his sophomore year while struggling through a midseason high-ankle sprain. He doesn’t figure to offer a lot in fantasy leagues in 2026 from where we sit at the end of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc5-d56e-afff-efedb9580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said “I didn’t do a good enough job of [getting Tetairoa McMillan the ball] last week and we’ll make sure that that comes alive.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc9-dc7a-af9b-efff2c690000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers who started McMillan in Week 17 are wondering if this could have been brought to Canales’ attention before yesterday’s 1/5 dud. Carolina’s passing game appears to go through fits and starts. McMillan remains a good WR2 bet for those of you playing in Week 18 leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bc9-dc7a-af9b-efff2c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn told reporters that it’s “still a stretch” that Marcus Mariota (quad/Hand) plays in Week 18 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd1-d56e-afff-eff964520000</link>
      <description>Quinn did say that “there’s still hope” that Mariota can get back on the field for the finale against Philadelphia. Assuming Mariota isn’t able to get back on the field, it’ll be Josh Johnson under center again for the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd1-d56e-afff-eff964520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A “prominent NFL agent” told The Athletic’s Mike Sando that “The biggest story of the offseason is going to be Lamar [Jackson]. That is going to be crazy.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bcf-d35e-a1bf-6fcf65c00000</link>
      <description>Jackson did not agree to a contract extension with the Ravens ahead of the season and is set to have a $74.5 million cap hit in 2026, a year in which the Ravens have plenty of other contracts to get ahead of. We don’t necessarily know if we believe a Lamar Jackson trade will be a big offseason storyline, but it’s not the first time the sourced have brought us the idea of a Lamar Jackson trade this December — Dan Graziano and Jeremy Fowler talked about it last week. Certainly between his injury-plagued and disappointing season, the fact that he is his own agent, and the fact that he turns 29 in January, there is room for a value disagreement between the Ravens and Jackson. You can see how both sides could come to the understanding that their futures would be better apart. Usually cooler heads prevail. It’s certainly worth noticing that there is some potential for a Jackson trade this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bcf-d35e-a1bf-6fcf65c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles coach Nick Sirianni said “we’re still thinking through” whether the team would play their starters in Week 18.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd9-d56e-afff-eff91d8e0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles can climb as high as the No. 2 seed, guaranteeing themselves a game against the Packers in the Wild Card round and getting a second home game should they advance. Meanwhile, the No. 6 seed will be the third-place NFC West squad. Philadelphia is locked into No. 2 or No. 3. Ultimately, with Josh Johnson on the other sideline, the Eagles probably have a little room to dabble with Tanner McKee if they really want to in Week 18. It doesn’t sound like we’ll know for sure until Wednesday or Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6bd9-d56e-afff-eff91d8e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
