<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) will play in Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-034e-d99b-a1df-3b4ef5b30000</link>
      <description>It was reported over the weekend that Egbuka had “a real chance to play” after returning to practice for a limited session on Saturday. Now, according to Rapoport, Egbuka’s pregame workout “went well,” putting him in position to suit up for a clash between to NFC titans. After suffering his injury in Week 6 against the 49ers, the initial fear was that Egbuka would miss at least one game. Given what we know about soft-tissue injuries, it’s hard to know how effective Egbuka will be without a full week of rest. Fantasy managers choosing to play him in what is undoubtedly a plus matchup do so at their own risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-034e-d99b-a1df-3b4ef5b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roquan Smith (hamstring) said he expects to play in Week 8 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0382-d651-a9df-6b97797e0000</link>
      <description>Smith has missed the last two games with a hamstring injury but was able to log a practice in his return from the Ravens bye week. With several days to go until Sunday’s game against the Bears, Smith is clearly trending in the right direction heading into a pivotal matchup with the Ravens’ season on the line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0382-d651-a9df-6b97797e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin, OG Luke Haggard, S Sebastian Castro, DL C.J. Brewer, CB Kindle Vildor, and RB Josh Williams inactive for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038a-df81-ab9b-7fcf743b0000</link>
      <description>The two key fantasy players here, Irving and Godwin, were ruled out long before Monday. While they are both out, rookie Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) who suffered an injury a week ago, is able to suit up and will play opposite Mike Evans in a game that should be ripe for fantasy scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038a-df81-ab9b-7fcf743b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions OT Taylor Decker (shoulder) is active for Week 7 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038d-d99b-a1df-3b8dd4960000</link>
      <description>Decker was questionable entering the week and was a DNP on Saturday after logging limited practices the previous two days. The veteran tackle hasn’t played since Week 4’s game against the Browns, and should provide an immediate boost to the passing game and protecting Jared Goff. While Decker is active, the Lions have declared CB Terrion Arnold, DL Quinton Jefferson, S Kerby Joseph, CB Avonte Maddox, S Jammie Robinson, RB Sione Vaki, and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Monday night’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-038d-d99b-a1df-3b8dd4960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans (hamstring) is active for Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</link>
      <description>Evans was trending in this direction all week, but will officially return on Monday night against the Lions. The veteran receiver will pair up with rookie Emeka Egbuka, who is going to attempt to play through a hamstring injury of his own after going down in Week 6 against the 49ers. Assuming they’re both in top shape, Evans and Egbuka should give Baker Mayfield plenty to work with in a game that is expected to feature a lot of scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0392-df81-ab9b-7fd795480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings listed J.J. McCarthy (ankle) as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</link>
      <description>Just over 24 hours ago, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said “don’t be surprised” if Carson Wentz starts in Week 8. The decision to start Wentz will be spun as one that came down to the health of McCarthy’s ankle, but ever since McCarthy was unexpectedly diagnosed with a high-ankle sprain after a Week 2 loss to the Falcons, questions have been raised about the team’s commitment to him as their starter. McCarthy was limited in all of practice last week. Another week of limited practices would suggest he is close to a return even if Wentz draws another start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0395-df81-ab9b-7fd74d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Wentz (shoulder) was listed as limited on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</link>
      <description>The injury is to Wentz’s non-throwing shoulder, which should be a good sign for his availability overall. Whether or not Wentz plays in Week 8 against the Chargers likely comes down more to the health of J.J. McCarthy (ankle) than his own and whether or not the Vikes are ready to hand the keys back to the 2024 first-rounder. Wentz has thrown for 1,072-5-4 in four games for the Vikings this season but struggled mightily in his last outing against the Eagles (313-0-2). He’ll be a fantasy QB2 if he starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0396-d99b-a1df-3b9e28310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Brock Purdy (toe) “will continue like he did last week” when asked about his Week 8 availability.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-039f-df81-ab9b-7fdf54340000</link>
      <description>Purdy practiced in a limited capacity all of last week and ultimately didn’t suit up for Week 7’s game against the Falcons. Based on Shanahan’s comments Monday, we would assume Purdy will again be a limited participant in practice this week, but it could be too early to say if Mac Jones will again be under center when the Niners take the field in Week 8 against the Texans. Purdy’s status remains one to watch, but we’ll wait for official confirmation from the team before ruling him out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-039f-df81-ab9b-7fdf54340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspended Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw for one game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b3-da18-a39a-dbb371460000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw was seen sprinting up to the official after the team’s game-winning field goal in their historic comeback victory against the Giants. A flag was immediately thrown on the field and the league levied a one-game suspension Monday after reviewing the incident. Greenlaw is likely to appeal but he is currently slated to miss the team’s Week 8 game against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b3-da18-a39a-dbb371460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Titans released WR Tyler Lockett.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b5-d651-a9df-6bb5f4e30000</link>
      <description>The veteran receiver asked for, and was granted, his release from the team Monday. Lockett managed just 51 total offensive snaps the previous three games as the team turned to their youth, with rookie slot man Chimere Dike seeing a corresponding jump in usage during that span. Lockett will be free to sign with another team at 4 pm ET Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03b5-d651-a9df-6bb5f4e30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
