<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Calvin Ridley (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f49-d45b-affe-7fdfb98d0000</link>
      <description>Ridley looks like he may need another week off before returning, though he still has Friday to upgrade his participation level. If active, Ridley is difficult to trust. He is no longer a difference-making wide receiver at age 30 and the Titans face the Texans’ top-tier pass defense. Consider him a classic boom-bust FLEX if he is cleared to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f49-d45b-affe-7fdfb98d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans TE Chig Okonkwo (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f4e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee8dad0000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo is clearly still impacted by the foot injury, coming off the Titans’ Week 10 bye. The Titans face the Texans this weekend, lowering Okonkwo’s already limited ceiling, assuming he is active. The veteran tight end is just a TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f4e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee8dad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f69-d1e7-a1fa-7feb02370000</link>
      <description>McConkey has made a habit of playing through manageable injuries, having already been listed with biceps and calf issues this season. We expect him to suit up and perform, per usual, in Week 11 against the Jaguars. Hopefully, he upgrades to full participation on Friday, and this is a non-issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f69-d1e7-a1fa-7feb02370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) will start in Week 11 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f69-d1e7-a1fa-7feb60660000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan confirmed post-practice that both Purdy and Pearsall are good to go this week. While both players are coming off lengthy absences, they fortuitously get the Cardinals’ fantasy-friendly defense to shake off any remaining rust. Purdy is a borderline QB1/2 this weekend, while Pearsall can be started as a volatile WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f69-d1e7-a1fa-7feb60660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (shin) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f85-d45b-affe-7f9777c20000</link>
      <description>The Chargers’ volatile perimeter wide receiver is on track to play, though a Friday upgrade would be heartening for his FLEX viability. Over the last four games, Johnston has thrice finished in the WR20-WR39 range, with one finish as the overall WR96 throw in for good measure. Check back tomorrow to see what Friday holds for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f85-d45b-affe-7f9777c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers TE Oronde Gadsden II (quad) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f90-d713-ad9e-7fd4875b0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden is firmly on track to play in his normal role this weekend against the Jaguars. The breakout rookie tight end was forced from play in Week 10 after taking a linebacker’s knee to his lower quad, but Gadsden appears to be good to go. At a position bereft of playmakers, the Chargers have found one in Gadsden, who can be safely started as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f90-d713-ad9e-7fd4875b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MMQB’s Albert Breer reports that the Jets are expected to start QB Justin Fields tonight against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f94-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe620e0000</link>
      <description>The Jets leave their weekly quarterback decision shrouded in mystery to maintain a competitive advantage. Fields started last week and kept the team from losing by maintaining a lead established by two special teams touchdowns. We’ll see if it works out for them once again. Fields is a highly volatile fantasy starter, capable of breaking long gains and delivering costly turnovers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f94-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe620e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9a-d673-a39e-ff9b16170000</link>
      <description>Thomas’ return from a high-ankle sprain remains up in the air. The disappointing second-year wide receiver has vastly underperformed while playing through myriad injuries. He may try to gut it out once again, even if he fails to practice in full tomorrow, but he would be a volatile WR3 if that is the case. Ideally, he practices in full on Friday. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9a-d673-a39e-ff9b16170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR AD Mitchell is active for Week 11 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9d-d45b-affe-7f9f501e0000</link>
      <description>It’s an intriguing situation. The crafty route runner and problematically error-prone player has a chance to carve out a starting role on his new team. Jets No. 1 WR Garrett Wilson (knee) was placed on injured reserve earlier today. For those needing a wide receiver stash candidate, Mitchell fits the bill, though expectations must be tempered. The Jets declared CB ﻿﻿﻿Azareye’h Thomas, RB ﻿﻿Khalil Herbert, LB ﻿﻿Ja’Markis Weston, EDGE Braiden McGregor and TE ﻿﻿Jelani Woods inactive for Week 11 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9d-d45b-affe-7f9f501e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (knee) is active for Week 11 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fa2-d45b-affe-7fb6a4cc0000</link>
      <description>Jennings will give it a go as the Patriots’ short-yardage back, though he is tough to trust as more than a touchdown-dependent FLEX. The Patriots declared DT Joshua Farmer, G Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito, RB Rhamondre Stevenson, LB Christian Elliss, TE Austin Hooper and WR Kayshon Boutte inactive for Week 11 against the Jets. Stevenson will miss his third straight game with a toe injury, while Boutte will miss his second straight game with a hamstring injury. Last week, rookie WR Kyle Williams scored a 72-yard touchdown by catching one of his two targets. He should be rostered where available, but he makes for a zero-floor, boom-bust FLEX starter this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fa2-d45b-affe-7fb6a4cc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
