<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) was not seen during the media portion of practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaea-d005-a9bf-fafe6a160000</link>
      <description>It’s almost sure to go down as another DNP — London’s eighth in a row — and Raheem Morris saying that London has a chance to play feels like it’s an iffy one at best from where we sit Thursday. London will almost undoubtedly be on the questionable line if he can summon up some kind of effort in practice on Friday, but we’d have to say he’s on the pessimistic side of it without some major positive reporting appearing in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaea-d005-a9bf-fafe6a160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaec-da9b-a9bf-feedb6a30000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if Rodgers wasn’t up for Week 14’s game against the Ravens — it’s a huge game in the AFC North standings — but he didn’t exactly deliver a lot to the table in Week 13. From a fantasy perspective, he’s a low-end superflex QB2 at best. And after his 117-yard scoreless performance, you can argue he should be even lower.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaec-da9b-a9bf-feedb6a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Texans DL Tim Settle (foot) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaef-d005-a9bf-faff4d0e0000</link>
      <description>Garafolo notes that Settle should be recovered ahead of the 2026 season. Settle posted a career-best 71.3 PFF defense grade, posting 16 hurries in 215 pass rush snaps in the middle. He’ll turn 29 ahead of next season and should have a rotational interior role somewhere in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaef-d005-a9bf-faff4d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf2-dce4-a1da-faf6c2770000</link>
      <description>Odunze is unfortunately on the wrong side of questionable, having missed two practices already this week. It is possible that the Bears (9-3) are just playing things safe in the lead-up to a division-rival showdown against the Packers (8-3-1), but backup plans should be made at this time. Odunze’s participation level on Friday will, hopefully, provide clarity as to his Week 14 status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf2-dce4-a1da-faf6c2770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf4-da9b-a9bf-fefde3670000</link>
      <description>Monangai is coming off a Week 13 showing in which he entered the game listed with a knee injury before rushing 22 times for 130 yards and one touchdown. Seeing the Bears ease him into practice with a new ankle injury is unsurprising. We expect Monangai to play in Week 14, ideally with a full practice session on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf4-da9b-a9bf-fefde3670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS’ Jonathan Jones reports it is “unlikely” Deshaun Watson sees game action in the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb04-d77b-adfa-eb87821a0000</link>
      <description>Neither Shedeur Sanders nor Dillon Gabriel are having their practice reps taken by Watson. Jones believes it is “quite possible, if not likely,” Cleveland carries Watson on their 2026 roster as part of a quarterback competition — another huge four-quarterback battle is possible if one of Sanders or Gabriel is not traded. Jones goes on to call the Watson contract “unmovable” while noting that the Browns have two first-round picks and could trade up for another quarterback prospect in this year’s draft. The ol’ nothing is settled, but nothing is settled gambit. Watson has a realistic chance of actually playing next year, but whether he’ll be able to outperform Gabriel and Sanders after tearing his Achilles and playing horrible football for the Browns in 2023 is anyone’s guess.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb04-d77b-adfa-eb87821a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) is expected to play in Week 14 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf4-da9b-a9bf-fefdcb5a0000</link>
      <description>Lions LT Taylor Decker (shoulder/rest) and C Graham Glasgow (knee) are also expected to play. No word yet on Lions LG Kayode Awosika (foot). Likely having 3-of-4 injured starters on the field is good news for QB Jared Goff, who must face the Cowboys’ top-tier pass-rush unit this evening. Hopefully, the group can improve its health in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaf4-da9b-a9bf-fefdcb5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (hip/knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb12-da9b-a9bf-ff1fd5970000</link>
      <description>His Wednesday DNP was likely just a rest day after taking a beating on his six targets against the Texans. Downs should be up for Week 14 based on this update, but he’s at best a risky FLEX given his spot in the pecking order for the Colts offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb12-da9b-a9bf-ff1fd5970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens OC Todd Monken said he expects QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) to play in Week 14 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb17-d005-a9bf-fb3764ba0000</link>
      <description>Monken’s statement was hardly enthusiastic, noting Jackson was unable to participate today, but he does believe Jackson will be active on game day. The Ravens’ quarterback is becoming difficult to trust as a fantasy starter, but the elite dual-threat traits he has consistently shown for years keep him at the tail-end of the QB1 group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb17-d005-a9bf-fb3764ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt (toe) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb23-d005-a9bf-fb3745770000</link>
      <description>Patrick Queen (glute) was able to get in a limited session. It sounds like things are moving in the right direction for Pittsburgh’s front seven ahead of Sunday’s must-win showdown with the Ravens. Watt could be cleared off the injury report entirely tomorrow, while Queen probably has a slim chance of that and should at least make the questionable line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb23-d005-a9bf-fb3745770000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
