<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:28:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) is inactive for Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73a830000</link>
      <description>Despite being limited in practice throughout the week, the Bills will opt to play it safe with Kincaid. The third-year tight end would have been coming off one of the best performances of his career (6-108-0) in last week’s loss to the Patriots, but will instead sit this one out in hopes of getting a little extra rest before the Bills’ Week 7 bye. Fantasy managers in need of an emergency option can look for Dawson Knox, who should be available in most leagues. In addition to Kincaid, the Bills also declared WR Curtis Samuel, LB Jimmy Ciarlo, LB Matt Milano, and OT Chase Lundt inactive for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df87-dd4c-afb9-ffc73a830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared WR Darnell Mooney, WR Ray-Ray McCloud, CB Clark Phillips, RB Nathan Carter, CB Billy Bowman, DL LaCale London, and OL Jack Nelson inactive for Week 6 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df8d-def2-abdb-dfede9000000</link>
      <description>Mooney was ruled out before the weekend but McCloud, who has played the third-most snaps of any receiver on the roster, is a surprise scratch. Third-year pro Casey Washington is expected to see an increase in snaps on Monday night and has seen nine targets on 63 routes run this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df8d-def2-abdb-dfede9000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray-Ray McCloud will not play in Week 6 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df93-dd4c-afb9-ffd303cd0000</link>
      <description>Any hopes that McCloud would see an increased role with Darnell Mooney (hamstring) can be cast aside. McCloud who ranks third this season in snaps among Falcons receivers, won’t be suiting up on Monday, giving way to backups Casey Washington and Jamal Agnew to see bigger roles. McCloud has caught six passes for 64 yards this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df93-dd4c-afb9-ffd303cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said the hope is to get TE George Kittle back at practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df98-dd4c-afb9-ffd9a1080000</link>
      <description>Kittle remains on injured reserve but it sounds like the team intends to open his 21-day practice window this week. Kittle could then be activated and make his return to the active roster against the Falcons on Sunday. Ricky Pearsall has missed the previous three games while Jauan Jennings has reportedly been dealing with multiple rib fractures, making Kittle’s potential return of great importance to a 49ers team that currently finds themselves tied with the Seahawks and Rams atop the NFC West. Fantasy managers will want to track Kittle’s status closely this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df98-dd4c-afb9-ffd9a1080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars ruled out LB Devin Lloyd (calf) and TE Quintin Morris (groin) for Week 7 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df9c-db72-a199-ffdff8ab0000</link>
      <description>Both players will not travel to London after being ruled out, with Lloyd’s absence creating a substantial hole to fill in the defensive interior for the Jaguars. Ventrell Miller was tasked with additional snaps following Lloyd’s departure in Week 6 and stands as the likeliest player to step into the vacated role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-df9c-db72-a199-ffdff8ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jets WR Garrett Wilson (knee) is expected to miss “a couple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfa0-db72-a199-ffebeb9d0000</link>
      <description>An MRI Monday revealed the alpha wide receiver hyperextended his knee in the loss to the Broncos. While he avoided a major knee injury, it is likely to cost him a couple weeks. The winless Jets are unlikely to rush one of their franchise players, leaving the team with very little depth at wide receiver for multiple games. Fantasy managers are likely better off avoiding this team altogether in the absence of Wilson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfa0-db72-a199-ffebeb9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel is active for Week 6 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfaf-dd4c-afb9-ffefb75b0000</link>
      <description>Samuel came into Monday listed as questionable but was seen moving well in a pre-game workout, ultimately doing enough to gain clearance to suit up against the Bears. He continues to play through multiple nagging injuries, something that has been more or less required with both Terry McLaurin and Noah Brown missing multiple games. That will be the case again Monday, meaning Samuel should once again soak up additional pass game usage. Inactive for the Commanders are QB Josh Johnson, WR Terry McLaurin, LB Ale Kaho, LB Kain Medrano, G Brandon Coleman, WR Noah Brown, and DT Eddie Goldman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfaf-dd4c-afb9-ffefb75b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared K Cairo Santos, DT Grady Jarrett, WR Jahdae Walker, DE Tanoh Kpassagnon, LB Ruben Hyppolite, G Luke Newman, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 6 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfc3-d94a-a79d-dfcf9b3b0000</link>
      <description>Jake Moody will handle kicking duties for the Bears after being cut by the 49ers earlier this season. Santos’ next opportunity to kick for the Bears comes in Week 7 against the Saints. The rest of the inactives carry no real surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfc3-d94a-a79d-dfcf9b3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT DaQuan Jones (calf) will not play in Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfd6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7786d0000</link>
      <description>Jones reportedly suffered a calf injury in pre-game warmups and will not play against the Falcons in Week 6. Jones leads Buffalo’s defensive tackles in snaps played this season and the team will likely adopt a looser rotation at the position to fill the void.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfd6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7786d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Joshua Palmer (lower leg) is questionable to return to Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e008-def2-abdb-fd699fba0000</link>
      <description>Palmer was tackled awkwardly in the second quarter Monday as he appeared to have his leg caught under him and twisted. He remained down on the field before being helped to the medical tent. No further update has yet to be provided from the team, but it did not look good in real time. Palmer caught both targets for 60 yards prior to the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e008-def2-abdb-fd699fba0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
