<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:43:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR A.T. Perry, formerly of the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</link>
      <description>This move makes sense for the Steelers, who fielded a very thin wide receiver corps in 2025. Perry, 26, last played regular season snaps with the Saints in 2023, catching 12-of-18 targets for 246 yards and four touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos completed an interview with Bills QB coach Ronald Curry for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</link>
      <description>9NEWS’ Mike Klis notes that Broncos head coach Sean Payton was interested in hiring Curry as his offensive coordinator back in 2023. It did not work out. Curry was reportedly one of Payton’s “top” offensive assistants with the Saints from 2016-21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots QB Drake Maye (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c2a-dfd7-a5dc-0d6b45cb0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Mike Reiss reports that the Patriots switched up their routine today, moving the quarterback group’s throwing session to the portion of practice unavailable to media. When asked for his level of concern regarding Maye’s throwing-shoulder injury, Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said, “not much.” We fully expect Maye to play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks. Hopefully, he resumes practicing fully tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c2a-dfd7-a5dc-0d6b45cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb withdrew from the Raiders’ head-coaching search.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c47-d355-a5bd-8f57fd7e0000</link>
      <description>Webb interviewed for the Bills and Ravens’ head-coaching vacancies as well. Both jobs have been filled. Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Webb is considered a “prime candidate” for his current team’s offensive coordinator vacancy. He also received offensive coordinator interview requests from elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c47-d355-a5bd-8f57fd7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams hired Bubba Ventrone as their new special teams coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c51-dead-af9e-6cd774bc0000</link>
      <description>Ventrone began his coaching career in 2015 as an assistant special teams coach with the Patriots. He became the Colts’ special teams coordinator in 2018 before the Browns hired him as the assistant head coach and special teams coordinator in 2023. He is widely viewed as one of the NFL’s best special teams coaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c51-dead-af9e-6cd774bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that Panthers DC Ejiro Evero is “still in the mix” for the Raiders’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfa3970000</link>
      <description>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak is viewed as the favorite for the role, but Evero is evidently still in it. Per Fowler, Evero conveyed detailed plans for the offense and, specifically, the quarterback position during his in-person meeting with the Raiders. The presentation apparently went over well. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfa3970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired Ian Cunningham as their new general manager.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfaf200000</link>
      <description>Reports consistently listed Cunningham as the favorite for this role. He also notably interviewed for the Falcons’ new president of football position before later interviewing for the general manager role. Cunningham signed on with the Ravens in 2008 as a personnel assistant and was later promoted to area scout in 2013. He became the Eagles’ director of college scouting in 2017 before taking their assistant director of player personnel job in 2019 and their director of player personnel job in 2020. He then accepted the assistant general manager role with the Bears in 2021 and has served in that role until now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c5d-d042-afbc-7ddfaf200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c74-d042-afbc-7df62b020000</link>
      <description>While it would be nice to see Darnold practice fully, he threw for 346 yards and three touchdowns while managing the oblique injury last week. His availability for Super Bowl LX against the Patriots is not in jeopardy. The Seahawks will practice at home on Friday and Saturday before flying to San Jose.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c74-d042-afbc-7df62b020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers agreed to terms with former Raiders DC Patrick Graham to the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cc3-dead-af9e-6cc717990000</link>
      <description>The news was broken by Josina Anderson. Graham is only 47 years old but is becoming a coordinating lifer, spending the past four years in Vegas and a year in Miami before that. A Bill Belichick acolyte, Graham’s Steelers connection comes from his year on Mike McCarthy’s Packers staff in 2018. The Raiders’ defense was not “the problem” for the Silver and Black last season, but it certainly wasn’t the solution, either. Graham will have more to work with in the Steel City. It’s not a needle-moving hire, but it’s not a bad move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cc3-dead-af9e-6cc717990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Giants will interview Chargers QBs coach Shane Day for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cde-dead-af9e-6cdf3e830000</link>
      <description>Schultz claims Day was a “serious candidate” for an L.A. promotion before head coach Jim Harbaugh eventually settled on big-named organizational outsider Mike McDaniel. Coaching in the NFL or FBS since 2006, Day has spent most of his time in the big leagues, including time on Kyle Shanahan’s staff. He has never been a play-caller or offensive coordinator, while this would make for an unusual jump from one brother’s staff to another. John might be wondering why he wasn’t good enough for Jim’s job, but we digress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0cde-dead-af9e-6cdf3e830000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
