<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired former Jets OC Tanner Engstrand as their pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1a66-d042-afbc-7ff6c2250000</link>
      <description>Engstrand was one-and-done as the Jets’ offensive coordinator after the team decided to move on once they realized they would strip him of play-calling duties. The 43-year-old coach will now oversee the Falcons’ passing game under head coach Kevin Stefanski, a role that he also had from 2022 to 2024 with the Lions. Engstrand won’t have Ben Johnson as offensive coordinator to make his passing game look good in Atlanta, but hopefully a familiar role will give him a chance to rebound following a rough year with Gang Green.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1a66-d042-afbc-7ff6c2250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak “intends to try to work out a deal to become the next head coach of the Raiders.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1a70-d629-a1bc-ba7da7c30000</link>
      <description>No move could become official until after the Super Bowl, but after meeting with both the Cardinals and Raiders in-person before departing for San Francisco, it sounds as if Kubiak will be off to Vegas early next week. Assuming the two sides agree to a deal, Kubiak would take over as the lead man for the Raiders, who hold the No. 1 overall pick in this year’s draft and are expected to take Indiana QB Fernando Mendoza with that pick. Kubiak took over a Sam Darnold led Seahawks offense this season and helped lead them to a third place finish in total points while also ranking eighth in yards. He would take over a Raiders team that was among the worst in league offensively last season, and that has multiple issues on the offensive side of the ball outside of quarterback. Kubiak joining the Raiders means the Cardinals would be the only team in the league still left with a head-coaching vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1a70-d629-a1bc-ba7da7c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers completed an interview with former Bills ST coordinator Matthew Smiley for their special teams coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa7-d042-afbc-7ff70b5b0000</link>
      <description>Smiley coached in the college ranks from 2005-2012 before making the leap to the NFL in 2013 as the Jaguars’ assistant special teams coordinator. He made a lateral move in 2017, joining former Bills head coach Sean McDermott’s staff in the same role. Smiley was then promoted to special teams coordinator in 2022 and served in that role for three seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa7-d042-afbc-7ff70b5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired Mike LaFleur as their new head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1ab2-d042-afbc-7ff292da0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as an offensive intern with the Browns in 2014, studying under then-OC Kyle Shanahan. LaFleur followed Shanahan to the Falcons in 2015 after accepting an offensive assistant position. Evidently impressed with LaFleur’s development, Shanahan hired LaFleur as the 49ers’ passing game coordinator and wide receivers coach after Shanahan was hired as the team’s head coach in 2017. LaFleur shed the wide receivers coach title in 2019, and later accepted the Jets’ offensive coordinator position in 2021 after former 49ers DC Robert Saleh was hired as the Jets’ next head coach. LaFleur parted ways with the Jets in 2023 and was hired by Rams head coach Sean McVay as the Rams’ offensive coordinator. He has served in that capacity in each of the last three seasons, notably ceding play-calling duties to McVay, unlike his time in New York under Saleh. The Rams’ offense led the league in yards per play this season (6.1), while using creative play designs featuring play action, shifts and motion. LaFleur signed a five-year contract with his new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1ab2-d042-afbc-7ff292da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers hired Raheem Morris as their new defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa6-d89c-a1be-bfff10930000</link>
      <description>The news comes shortly after the Cardinals hired Rams OC Mike LaFleur as their next head coach. Morris was one of three finalists for that role. Morris now reunites with 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan. ESPN’s Adam Schefter notes that the two previously worked together with the Buccaneers (2004-2005), Commanders (2012-2013) and Falcons (2015-2016).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1aa6-d89c-a1be-bfff10930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins hired Sean Duggan as their new defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-11cc-d042-afbc-7dde47070000</link>
      <description>The hiring reunites Duggan with former Packers DC and new Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley. Duggan, 32, entered the NFL’s coaching ranks as a Packers defensive assistant in 2024. He was promoted to linebackers coach in 2025, evidently impressing Hafley along the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-11cc-d042-afbc-7dde47070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings hired Ryan Nielsen as defensive run game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported today that Nielsen is being hired as the Vikings’ new defensive run game coordinator, though prior reporting suggested he may also coach the defensive line. He spent the 2025 season as a senior defensive assistant with the Bills. He served as the Jaguars (2024) and Falcons’ (2023) defensive coordinator in recent seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b05-d042-afbc-7fd74f700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos pass game coordinator and QB coach Davis Webb is reportedly the “leading candidate” for the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy after interviewing for the role on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</link>
      <description>Webb, 31, withdrew from the Raiders’ head-coaching search late last week, after progressing through the second round of interviews. He also received requests to interview for the Ravens, Eagles, and Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancies and was previously linked to the Bills’ head-coaching vacancy. Only the Giants’ respective vacancy remains available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b23-d042-afbc-7ff3ae5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants completed an interview with former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</link>
      <description>NFL insider Jordan Schultz broke today’s news. He also reported back on January 6th, the same day Kingsbury parted ways with the Commanders, that Kingsbury was a candidate for the Giants’ offensive coordinator vacancy. Kingsbury has successfully schemed up offenses for mobile quarterbacks in the past. Giants QB Jaxson Dart fits the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b43-d89c-a1be-bfdf38bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer reports that NFL teams searching for a new defensive coordinator are “moving” on 49ers assistant head coach of defense Gus Bradley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers hired Raheem Morris as their new defensive coordinator earlier today, removing one high-profile candidate. Breer notes that either the Titans or Cardinals could hire Bradley as their next defensive coordinator, though the Cardinals’ ability to let Bradley call plays on defense gives them an “edge” over the Titans. He also notes that if the Titans miss out on Bradley, Falcons defensive pass-game coordinator Mike Rutenberg is “a name to watch.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1b39-d355-a5bd-9f7d17cd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
