<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:30:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeff Darlington reports that Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) will start in Super Bowl LX against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f36-d042-afbc-7ff69a560000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation, but we will continue to update Darnold’s practice participation level and his official game status. Darlington adds that Darnold was limited again today, as has been the case since he suffered the injury during the Seahawks’ final Divisional Round practice. He threw for a season-high 346 yards against the Rams in the NFC Championship Game, assuaging all performance-related concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2f36-d042-afbc-7ff69a560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals hired Matt Merritt as their new running backs coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ffc-d629-a1bc-bffd672e0000</link>
      <description>Merritt spent the last two seasons coaching running backs at the University of Miami. He previously worked for USF, Georgia Southern, Tennessee, James Madison, and Ohio State. Merritt also participated in two NFL coaching fellowships. The first was with the Bengals in 2016. The second was with the 49ers in 2019, where Cardinals head coach Mike LaFleur then served as the passing game coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ffc-d629-a1bc-bffd672e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants completed interview with ASU offensive coordinator and QB coach Marcus Arroyo for their quarterback coach vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3019-d042-afbc-7ddb5ab10000</link>
      <description>Arroyo has held his current roles with ASU for the last two years. In his first season on the job, Arroyo notably featured current Giants RB Cam Skattebo as the team’s offensive focal point, dialing up 248 carries and 40 targets the burly back across the full college season. Arroyo sat out the 2023 season after being relieved of his head-coaching duties after a three-year stint at UNLV. He has one season of NFL coaching experience under his belt, having served as the Buccaneers’ quarterbacks coach in 2014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3019-d042-afbc-7ddb5ab10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions hired Steve Oliver as their new tight ends coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3023-d355-a5bd-bf77af890000</link>
      <description>Oliver initially joined the Lions’ coaching staff as an offensive quality control coach in 2021. He was promoted in 2023, becoming the team’s assistant offensive line coach under offensive line coach and run game coordinator Hank Fraley. Oliver notably played for Fraley as an offensive lineman at the University of San Diego in 2012. Oliver will now coach a position group led by star TE Sam LaPorta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3023-d355-a5bd-bf77af890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested an interview with Chiefs assistant QB coach Dan Williams for their quarterbacks coach vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d89c-a1be-bfff0a470000</link>
      <description>Williams signed on with the Chiefs as a coaching intern in 2019. He was the assistant to the head coach from 2020-2021 and spent 2022 as an offensive assistant. He became the offensive quality control coach and assistant quarterbacks coach in 2023. Bringing Williams aboard as a young quarterback’s mentor could make a lot of sense for the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d89c-a1be-bfff0a470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Cowboys will play in “the NFL’s first-ever regular-season game next season in Rio de Janeiro.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3053-d355-a5bd-bf57c9540000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys’ opponent has not yet been revealed. This is the second international game to be announced today. The 49ers will also play the Rams in Melbourne, Australia next season. The Chiefs and Chargers notably played in São Paulo, Brazil in Week 1 of 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3053-d355-a5bd-bf57c9540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ff9-d89c-a1be-afff8c300000</link>
      <description>Spillane resumed practicing today after sitting out on Wednesday. He missed Weeks 14-18 with the same ankle injury, but managed to return for postseason play. Spillane aggravated the injury in the AFC Championship Game, yet remained confident that he would play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks. Today’s return is a good sign. Unfortunately, Patriots LB Harold Landry (knee) was downgraded today after logging a limited session on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ff9-d89c-a1be-afff8c300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d042-afbc-7dff11c90000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters earlier today that he is “confident” Emmanwori will play in Super Bowl LX against the Patriots. Shortly thereafter, ESPN’s Jeff Darlington said that Emmanwori underwent imaging on the injured ankle and, in a poorly worded report, indicated that Emmanwori avoided a high-ankle sprain. The rookie safety notably suffered a high-ankle sprain in the same ankle back in Week 1, causing him to miss Weeks 2-4. Hopefully, Emmanwori resumes practicing tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d042-afbc-7dff11c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3063-d89c-a1be-bfff852c0000</link>
      <description>This is great news. A report from this afternoon indicated that Darnold would again participate in a limited capacity, as he has done since injuring his oblique during the Seahawks’ final Divisional Round practice. Darnold is ready to go for Super Bowl LX against the Patriots. Seahawks LT Charles Cross (foot) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3063-d89c-a1be-bfff852c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired Lou Esposito as their new defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3083-d89c-a1be-bfdff8d00000</link>
      <description>This will be Esposito’s first time coaching in the NFL. Esposito spent the last two seasons coaching Michigan’s defensive line. From 2017-2023, he served as Western Michigan’s defensive coordinator and defensive line coach. He spent time coach at smaller schools like Davenport and Ferris State before that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3083-d89c-a1be-bfdff8d00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
