<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 3-of-3 targets for 30 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d968-a19b-f8fbbd0c0000</link>
      <description>Gadsden was unable to deliver a high-end performance against the Patriots, but he continued to show off his ability to get open on in-breaking routes. The talent should serve him well in his second NFL season next year. The fifth-round rookie caught 49-of-68 targets for 664 yards and three touchdowns this season, far surpassing expectations given his draft capital. A knee injury suffered by veteran TE Tyler Conklin allowed Gadsden to remain active on game day in Week 3. He seized the opportunity, catching 5-of-6 targets for 46 yards in his first NFL game. Gadsden finished as the half-PPR TE16 this year as the Chargers spread the ball around down the stretch. Gadsden has a wide range of outcomes in 2026, but will probably be drafted as a low-end TE1 due to his upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ba-d968-a19b-f8fbbd0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Dissly earned zero targets in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d1-d56e-afff-f6f998a80000</link>
      <description>Dissly caught 11-of-15 targets for 97 yards this season. The veteran tight end has one year remaining on his contract, but the team can save $4 million by releasing him while taking only a $1.5 million hit in dead money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d1-d56e-afff-f6f998a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeAndre Lambert-Smith did not play in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da22390000</link>
      <description>A hamstring injury suffered in Week 18 kept the situational deep threat sidelined against the Patriots. He caught 5-of-12 targets for 51 yards and one touchdown in his rookie season. Lambert-Smith will get the chance to earn a spot on the game-day roster this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da22390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed one time for minus-one yard in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da021c0000</link>
      <description>Hampton was evidently just an emergency option for the Chargers this evening. The big-bodied back, drafted 22nd overall by the Chargers, dealt with injuries in both ankles this season. He was sidelined in Weeks 6-13 after fracturing his left ankle in Week 5. He then injured his right ankle late in the season, though it is unclear when exactly it happened. The Chargers rested key starters in Week 18, Hampton among them. He rushed 124 times for 545 yards and four touchdowns, and caught 32-of-34 targets for 192 yards and one touchdown. Hampton warrants low-end RB1 treatment entering 2026, but his inability to stay on the field in his rookie season is a bit concerning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0d8-d35e-a1bf-f5da021c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimani Vidal rushed 11 times for 31 yards in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots, adding two receptions for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0e8-d35e-a1bf-f5eab9aa0000</link>
      <description>Vidal functioned as the Chargers’ clear-cut lead back against the Patriots this evening. The compact back proved his value this season, playing effectively as a featured starter with Omarion Hampton sidelined by ankle injuries for much of the year. Vidal rushed 155 times for 643 yards and three touchdowns, and caught 16-of-20 targets for 136 yards and one touchdown. It is unclear whether he will offer standalone FLEX value in 2026, but he has proven himself as a high-upside bench stash option moving forward. He banked four weekly RB1 finishes this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0e8-d35e-a1bf-f5eab9aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaret Patterson did not play an offensive snap in the Chargers’ Wild Card loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ef-d56e-afff-f6ef96810000</link>
      <description>Patterson operated as the Chargers’ No. 3 running back this season, rushing 41 times for 159 yards and one touchdown, and catching 3-of-4 targets for eight yards. He is a free agent this offseason. Patterson is unlikely to be a late-round fantasy target in 2026, but he could fill in as a rotational player for a team hit hard by injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b0ef-d56e-afff-f6ef96810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers expected to try to work out a new contract with head coach Matt LaFleur.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeca-d56e-afff-eeeaaa3e0000</link>
      <description>The Packers have made it known through various reports in the last week that they intend to discuss a new contract with LaFleur after the season. The tenor of those potential discussions likely hasn’t changed much, despite outside noise after the Packers lost in all-too-familiar fashion in the playoffs once again. Green Bay doesn’t want LaFleur, who has one year left on his contract, to enter next season as a lame-duck. The Packers can somewhat afford to play hardball with LaFleur in contract negotiations now. The organization isn’t known for paying coaches top tier money and LaFleur may not be in position to ask for that anymore, despite a 76-41-1 record. Upgrading from LaFleur to someone like John Harbaugh would be even less cost-effective for the Packers. Teams around the league with head coaching vacancies are keeping tabs on LaFleur in case these negotiations fall apart as he’d be a top candidate if he were to become available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeca-d56e-afff-eeeaaa3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters QB Matthew Stafford (finger) is “good to go” for the Divisional round matchup against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b2f2-d56e-afff-f6fab4680000</link>
      <description>Stafford is dealing with a sprain on his right index finger. The 37-year-old quarterback suffered the injury early in the win over the Panthers in the Wild Card round. He never came out of the game. The Rams will go as far in these playoffs as Stafford can take them. His finger injury doesn’t appear to be a serious impediment at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b2f2-d56e-afff-f6fab4680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel told reporters CB Christian Gonzalez (head) remains in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b317-d56e-afff-f7ff9bcf0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez suffered a concussion in the second half of the Patriots Wild Card game victory over the Chargers on Sunday. The 23-year-old cornerback was having an excellent game with no catches allowed and two pass breakups on five targets in 27 coverage snaps. Gonzalez will have to clear concussion protocol sometime this week to be available for the Divisional matchup against the Texans or Steelers. It would be a big loss for the Patriots defense if his injury lingers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b317-d56e-afff-f7ff9bcf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (knee) told reporters he thinks he will play in the first month of the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b338-d56e-afff-f7f8b8af0000</link>
      <description>Parsons is recovering from a torn ACL. He plans to be back on the field as early as September. The 26-year-old EDGE told reporters Week 1 is his optimistic target return date, while Week 3 is the more realistic target return date. Either way, Parsons doesn’t anticipate beginning next season on injured reserve, which is a significant development for the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b338-d56e-afff-f7f8b8af0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
