<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-821b-d6e9-af9d-8a9b9a430000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks listed Charbonnet as questionable to play in tonight’s game despite the 24-year-old running back practicing in full all week. Forecasting his expected workload is difficult, given the listing, but two Seahawks running backs have totaled double-digit carries in all three games this season. Charbonnet is an RB3/FLEX option against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-821b-d6e9-af9d-8a9b9a430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Cardinals LT Paris Johnson (knee) is expected to play against the Seahawks on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8225-d95b-addb-ea6770330000</link>
      <description>Johnson was questionable and missed Week 3 on the questionable line with this knee injury. Arizona’s top left tackle should help give Kyler Murray a little extra time against a fierce Seahawks front on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8225-d95b-addb-ea6770330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LG Aaron Banks (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8228-d95b-addb-ea6e616f0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Morgan looks like a candidate to get a full game at guard with Banks injuring himself in Week 3 and not practicing in either of the first two sessions of the week. It won’t keep you away from any Packers — this is the Cowboys defense we’re talking about — but it might make their rushing effectiveness go down a bit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8228-d95b-addb-ea6e616f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens ruled out DL Nnamdi Madubuike (neck) for Baltimore’s Week 4 game against Cleveland.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-822a-deb6-a7fd-d3ff89110000</link>
      <description>Madubuike did not practice at any point last week and looks like a potential injured reserve candidate. John Harbaugh told reporters that he was “concerned” about it but that he’s “not really in a position to comment on it.” That sounds ominous. It’s good news for Kansas City’s running game, which you should probably avoid anyway. (Maybe you can justify a Kareem Hunt FLEX this week?) Travis Jones (knee) did return to practice, but Baltimore’s run defense has been weak this year and doesn’t seem to be getting much healthier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-822a-deb6-a7fd-d3ff89110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (concussion) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8230-dca3-a9fb-bfb9f11c0000</link>
      <description>It would seem unlikely that he’ll make it active based on missing the first two practices of the week, but if Pierce is to make it he’ll need to show something on Thursday. If Pierce is out, Adonai Mitchell will take over at outside receiver and could be an interesting flier given how the Colts offense has played so far this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8230-dca3-a9fb-bfb9f11c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (calf) resumed practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8225-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf5540000</link>
      <description>On Wednesday, McMillan told reporters that he would be good to go for Week 4. His return indeed puts him on track to play. As long as he avoids suffering a setback, he will be out there against the Patriots. Through three career games, McMillan has twice finished as a WR3 and once as a WR4. He is best viewed as a WR3 again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8225-dca3-a9fb-bfbdf5540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts DT DeForest Buckner (back) practiced on Thursday and told reporters he’d play in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8232-dca3-a9fb-bfbb90540000</link>
      <description>We weren’t too worried about Buckner, who has been an ironman for the Colts, not playing. Buckner had suited up for 17 games in each of 2021-2023 before missing five games in 2024. Indy’s defense would be a contrarian play against a Rams offense that looks loaded to take advantage of their cornerback issues in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8232-dca3-a9fb-bfbb90540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) was seen working off to the side at practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-820c-dca3-a9fb-bf9d3d070000</link>
      <description>Injured players doing solo work on a side field typically get listed as non-participants on that day’s injury report. We expect this to be the case with Legette. He was limited in practice last week but was ultimately ruled inactive before Week 3 kicked off. This suggests a setback may have occurred. Regardless, Legette does not need to be rostered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-820c-dca3-a9fb-bf9d3d070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley Jr. (oblique) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab52e4d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans are reportedly preparing for Tremon Smith to start outside, which is good news for Titans deep-league plays like Calvin Ridley and Elic Ayomanor. The Texans defense played decently without Stingley against the Jaguars last week, but it only takes one big play allowed by Smith to build a good fantasy day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8235-d6e9-af9d-8ab52e4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (toe) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-823b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbbaef0000</link>
      <description>This makes him a little more likely to get off the questionable line for Sunday, even if it is a limited practice. Johnson is not a real fantasy option at this point, though we should be open to the idea that Jaxson Dart changes the distribution of New York’s targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-823b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbbaef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
