<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:31:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jawhar Jordan rushed eight times for 36 yards in the Texans’ Week 17 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-628c-d35e-a1bf-67ce0a980000</link>
      <description>Jordan out-snapped veteran RB Nick Chubb 11-to-5 and out-touched him 8-to-1 against the Chargers on Saturday. After starting RB Woody Marks took a hard hit from Chargers OLB Khalil Mack in the fourth quarter, it was Jordan, not Chubb, who replaced Marks briefly in the lineup. He is the Texans’ No. 2 running back and should be stashed accordingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-628c-d35e-a1bf-67ce0a980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 21-of-32 passes for 236 yards, one touchdown and one interception in the Chargers’ 20-16, Week 17 loss to the Texans, rushing six times for 37 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-628e-d35e-a1bf-67ce303e0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ pass rush put hits on Herbert from start to finish, sacking him five times for 35 yards. Herbert was visibly wincing in pain after being sacked at the end of the Chargers’ first drive, bracing his left arm against his body as the punt unit took the field. Despite the physical toll, Herbert willingly scrambled throughout the contest and even dropped Texans CB Derek Stingley en route to a 28-yard gain. Herbert deserves credit for sticking with TE Oronde Gadsden II, linking up with the rookie tight end for a one-yard touchdown in the third quarter. Gadsden had dropped three passes before that, one of them clanging off his hands and into LB Azeez Al-Shaair’s for an interception on the Chargers’ sixth drive. Herbert is a borderline QB1/2 against the Broncos in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-628e-d35e-a1bf-67ce303e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 5-of-8 targets for 98 yards in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6299-d56e-afff-e6f99bce0000</link>
      <description>Johnston’s day was highlighted by a 60-yard gain on a go route down the left sideline, after running right past Texans CB Tremon Smith. The play fittingly occurred right after Smith put a late hit on QB Justin Herbert, who may have been looking to embarrass the defender. A few plays before that, Johnston got open on a comeback route, hauling in a 16-yard gain along the left sideline. He impressively beat Texans CB Kamari Lassiter on a 12-yard out route on the following drive and later picked up a first down inside the Texans’ red zone, helping to set up TE Oronde Gadsden III’s one-yard touchdown reception. Johnston is a boom-bust FLEX against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6299-d56e-afff-e6f99bce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 1-of-2 targets for 31 yards in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62a4-d968-a19b-7af55cfa0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ pass rush disrupted the Chargers’ passing offense for much of the day. On the Chargers’ 12th drive, McConkey got open along the left sideline via a corner route and successfully secured the 31-yard pass. He also returned two punts for 13 yards. The Chargers’ talented, young wide receiver is a WR2/3 against the Broncos in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62a4-d968-a19b-7af55cfa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 1-of-3 targets for 17 yards in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62a7-dc7a-af9b-efbfffd30000</link>
      <description>Allen has disappointed for some time. This week is no different. He contributed a costly drop on third down, leading to a punt on the Chargers’ third drive. It was also the Chargers’ third punt of the day. Allen later failed to secure a back-shoulder pass in the end zone from 10 yards out, late in the game. He should not be in re-draft lineups next week against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62a7-dc7a-af9b-efbfffd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordon Riley (Achilles) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 18 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6280-d56e-afff-e6e8befa0000</link>
      <description>Riley was roled up on Derrick Henry’s touchdown run and needed a cart. The 27-year-old is obviously in danger of missing Week 18 against the Vikings as well as the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6280-d56e-afff-e6e8befa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 3-of-6 targets for 32 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62ab-d968-a19b-7afba3630000</link>
      <description>Gadsden had quite the volatile day. He first chipped in a six-yard gain on a checkdown pass during the Chargers’ fourth drive. Two drives later, Gadsden got open at the Texans’ five-yard line against Texans LB Azeez Al-Shaair. Instead of securing the target and powering in for the score, Gadsden swiped at an albeit high, fast pass, bobbling it behind him and into Al-Shaair’s hands for the interception. He dropped his next target, two drives later. He earned a 13-yard end zone target two drives after that, but Texans CB Kamari Lasster broke up the pass. Chargers QB Justin Herbert stuck with the young tight end, though, connecting with him for a one-yard touchdown via a delayed post route for Herbert’s lone passing touchdown of the day. Gadsden remains a TE1 in re-draft against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62ab-d968-a19b-7afba3630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed 14 times for 29 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans, adding eight receptions for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62af-d35e-a1bf-67ef2c5d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ defense dominated the trenches in this one. Hampton’s five-yard rushing touchdown, late in the fourth quarter, was his longest run of the day. Fortunately, he is a talented three-down player, which allows him to remain on the field in passing situations, either as a checkdown weapon or as a reliable pass protector. He played well in both phases. Hampton is a low-end RB1 against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62af-d35e-a1bf-67ef2c5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 1-of-1 targets for eight yards in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans, rushing once for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b5-dc7a-af9b-efbfdbd30000</link>
      <description>Harris sure looks speedy. Unfortunately, the Texans’ defense kept the Chargers’ offense in check for much of the day. The rookie wide receiver was given the ball on an end-around from the Texans’ 15-yard line. Although he failed to score a touchdown, seeing the youngster get a red zone touch was heartening. He is a boom-bust FLEX against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b5-dc7a-af9b-efbfdbd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b4-d56e-afff-e6fca6b70000</link>
      <description>Wicks picked up the concussion during the third quarter. The 24-year-old will miss the remainder of Week 17, and his status for the finale against the Vikings next week will be dependent on how he recovers and if he can exit the protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b4-d56e-afff-e6fca6b70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
