<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 2-of-3 targets for 13 yards in the Eagles’ Week 10 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7150-d673-a39e-f5d1f17d0000</link>
      <description>The low volume was a product of a game environment in which quarterback Jalen Hurts attempted only 26 passes. The two teams played to a 0-0 tie at the half as each team biased their attack to the ground game, leaving Brown with his lowest target total since a one-target outing in Week 1 against the Cowboys. Inconsistent volume remains highly likely as we head down the back stretch of the 2025 fantasy season, something fantasy managers need not worry about ahead of a Week 11 home matchup with the pass-funnel Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7150-d673-a39e-f5d1f17d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 4-of-6 targets for 43 yards in the Eagles’ Week 10 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7153-d713-ad9e-7d57f6190000</link>
      <description>Goedert notched three of his four receptions on the team’s opening possession of the second half and did not manage another catch the rest of the way. Both offenses struggled to move the football consistently as the two teams failed to score a single point in the first half, with a field goal to start the third frame the difference. Goedert remains a touchdown-aided TE1 ahead of a Week 11 meeting with the Lions in Philadelphia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7153-d713-ad9e-7d57f6190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love completed 20-of-36 passes for 176 yards in the Packers’ 10-7, Week 10 loss to the Eagles, adding 28 yards on five carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7157-d1e7-a1fa-7bff36300000</link>
      <description>A week after going 1-for-5 in the red zone, the Packers started this one by failing to score a single point until 5:49 remaining the fourth quarter. Even so, they had a chance to tie the game as time expired but kicker Brandon McManus missed a would-be Lambeau record 64-yard field goal to send the Packers to their second consecutive home loss and a 5-3-1 record. Play calling seemed to doom the Packers in this one as they continued to batter running back Josh Jacobs into a brick wall on early downs throughout the first three quarters, routinely forcing Love to convert third-and-middle situations. Love also lost a fumble in the red zone at the end of the first half, a mistake that ultimately proved the difference in a tightly contested game. His once-promising fantasy utility took another hit in this one as now-lead receiver Romeo Doubs departed with a chest injury, forcing the veteran signal caller to play most of the second half with Dontayvion Wicks, Malik Heath, and Savion Williams as his top pass-catchers considering Tucker Kraft was lost for the season and rookie wide receiver Matthew Golden was unable to play with a shoulder injury. Love and the Packers now regroup ahead of a Week 11 matchup with a Giants team that just fired its head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7157-d1e7-a1fa-7bff36300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 21 times for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 10 loss to the Eagles, adding 33 yards on five receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-715f-d713-ad9e-7d5f84be0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs accounted for 107 of the team’s 261 yards in a game played without Tucker Kraft and Matthew Golden, with the Packers also losing wide receiver Romeo Doubs early in the third quarter. The team has now dropped consecutive home games to drop to 5-3-1 after holding the inside track to the lone bye out of the NFC through the first eight weeks. Jacobs reclaimed his role as one of the true workhorse backs remaining in the league now that he is past the calf injury that plagued the last month of his season, and fantasy managers can once again treat him as a locked-in RB1 ahead of a road meeting with the reeling Giants in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-715f-d713-ad9e-7d5f84be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson caught 2-of-4 targets for 45 yards in the Packers’ Week 10 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7163-d673-a39e-f5f3c3010000</link>
      <description>The headline should summarize Green Bay’s offensive performance from this one. The team managed only 262 yards of total offense and failed to score until under five minutes remaining in the fourth quarter, with a Jordan Love fumble in the red zone to end the first half ultimately proving the difference in a tightly contest, 10-7 loss. Watson was not supposed to be this involved immediately after returning from a torn ACL suffered in Week 18 of the 2024 season, but mounting injuries have made it a necessity. The team played without Tucker Kraft, who will miss the rest of the season his own torn ACL, and rookie wide receiver Matthew Golden in this one and also lost Romeo Doubs to a chest injury in the third quarter. Watson could be asked to step up further when the team travels to face the Giants in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7163-d673-a39e-f5f3c3010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught 4-of-8 targets for 38 yards in the Packers’ Week 10 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7167-d673-a39e-f5f7a3bb0000</link>
      <description>Wicks saw the most snaps for a team playing without Tucker Kraft and Matthew Golden, stepping into the lead receiver role with the departure of Romeo Doubs early in the third quarter. He made a couple nice grabs but also committed one drop, appearing to be on the wrong page as quarterback Jordan Love on two other incompletions. That continues to be par for the Wicks course as the third-year receiver consistently alternates between flashes of brilliance and mental mistakes. Even so, he could be called on at an elevated rate once more when the Packers take on the reeling Giants in Week 11, pending multiple injury statuses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7167-d673-a39e-f5f7a3bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught all three targets for 23 yards in the Packers’ Week 10 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-716a-d713-ad9e-7d7e88a80000</link>
      <description>Musgrave failed to live up to the lofty shoes he is filling the Green Bay offense following the season-ending injury to Tucker Kraft, used mostly as a blocker in a game the Packers focused their efforts on the ground game. His next chance to return usable counting stats comes in Week 11 against a reeling Giants team that just fired its head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-716a-d713-ad9e-7d7e88a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said the team would not open Brandon Aiyuk’s practice window ahead of Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bed-d713-ad9e-6ffdeb380000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Shefter reported last week that AIyuk — coming back from a catastrophic 2024 knee injury — is expected to return to the Niners lineup at some point this season. That might mean a December return if Aiyuk’s practice window is not opened in the next week or two. The team has said Aiyuk’s recovery has been more complicated than expected. Until he returns, Jauan Jennings and Ricky Pearsall — who could return from a knee injury in Week 11 — will operate as the Niners’ top two wideouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bed-d713-ad9e-6ffdeb380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns won’t open Deshaun Watson’s 21-day practice window ahead of Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7346-d673-a39e-f7d719300000</link>
      <description>Watson, according to Cleveland.com’s Mary Kay Cabot, has made “excellent progress” in recovering from his re-ruptured Achilles tendon but won’t start practicing this week. Cabot said Watson “must first pass his medical exams before being permitted to practice. Once he’s cleared, the Browns must be reasonably sure he’ll be ready for action before they open the window.” Browns QBs coach Bill Musgrave said Watson, 29, is determined to return to game action one day. “I know he wants to play a lot of football again,” Musgrave said. “He feels like he’s got a lot of tread left on his tires.” There remains very little chance Watson, who has played 19 games since the start of the 2022 season, will suit up for Cleveland in 2025. Dillon Gabriel will be under center in Week 11 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7346-d673-a39e-f7d719300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow (toe) said he’s targeting a Week 13 return to game action.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73af-d1e7-a1fa-7bef78600000</link>
      <description>The oft-injured Burrow, who suffered his toe injury in Week 2, said the Bengals’ record and postseason hopes could factor into whether he returns this season. “We’ll see how these next couple weeks go,” Burrow said in his first news conference since the injury. “There’s a lot that goes into it. There’s a lot of variables that you have to consider.” Burrow on Monday practiced for the first time since September, “throwing passes to receivers not facing any defenders,” according to ESPN’s Ben Baby. Burrow, Baby said, “sported a different pair of shoes during his limited practice and acknowledged there is additional hardware in his cleats.” Joe Flacco is set to start Week 11 against the Steelers. Burrow should be rostered in all fantasy formats in case he returns in the season’s final month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-73af-d1e7-a1fa-7bef78600000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
