<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed FB Adam Prentice, formerly of the Saints, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9ca-d90d-a5bd-bbdb654f0000</link>
      <description>Prentice’s signing makes sense, at least in the short term. The Broncos’ starting FB Michael Burton is dealing with a hamstring injury. It’s unlikely the team will keep two fullbacks on the active roster, though. The Broncos correspondingly placed OG Nick Gargiulo on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9ca-d90d-a5bd-bbdb654f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Daniel Oyefusi reports that the Browns are expected to announce their starting quarterback for Week 1 soon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9b7-d90d-a5bd-bbff0acc0000</link>
      <description>Joe Flacco, now 40 years old, is somehow the only healthy quarterback on the Browns roster. Both Kenny Pickett and Dillon Gabriel are nursing hamstring injuries, though Gabriel played in preseason Week 2 and suffered no setbacks. Shedeur Sanders, meanwhile, is dealing with an oblique injury. Flacco has also reportedly been the steadiest performer in practice. It is likely his job to lose. He is not fantasy-relevant in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9b7-d90d-a5bd-bbff0acc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank Bigsby rushed two times for six yards and caught 1-of-1 targets for 19 yards in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 2 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9fd-d05a-adda-bbff96480000</link>
      <description>Bigsby returned the opening kickoff for 36 yards before handling the first play from scrimmage, a two-yard run up the middle. Last week, Travis Etienne started and played nearly the entire first drive. This week, Bigsby got the start and stayed on-field for 7-of-9 first-drive snaps. He clocked two snaps on the second drive but after that, his day was done. His best play came via a 2nd-and-8 screen pass, which he took across the field while forcing two missed tackles and setting up his blocks well. It was a good showing for Bigsby, as he and Etienne jockey for the Week 1 starting role. Bhashul Tuten should not be discounted, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9fd-d05a-adda-bbff96480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne Jr. rushed three times for 24 yards and caught 1-of-1 targets for eight yards in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 2 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba0b-d90d-a5bd-ba5b705a0000</link>
      <description>Etienne subbed in for both third downs on the Jaguars’ first offensive drive. He then played 6-of-8 snaps on the second drive before being done for the day. Etienne and Tank Bigsby will seemingly duke it out for the starting job next week, though Bhayshul Tuten continues to play well behind them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba0b-d90d-a5bd-ba5b705a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed 10 times for 35 yards and one touchdown and caught 1-of-1 targets for six yards in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 2 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9d4-d05a-adda-bbd68d610000</link>
      <description>Tuten continues to look good, playing with the second team. Though he stands just 5'9/209, Tuten’s ability to fight through contact and move the pile on inside runs really jumps off the screen. He scored his second preseason touchdown on a three-yard run up the middle against the Saints, muscling past DB Jordan Howden, who attempted to go low on the spry rookie rusher. He should continue to be drafted as a high-upside bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9d4-d05a-adda-bbd68d610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. caught 2-of-4 targets for eight yards and rushed once for two yards in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 2 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba10-d05a-adda-ba92feb50000</link>
      <description>Thomas’ creative preseason usage continued in this one.He took 6-of-16 snaps lined up in the slot, with one such play resulting in a sneaky handoff. The talented, young receiver is a WR1 entering year two as a pro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba10-d05a-adda-ba92feb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports that the Commanders “have been shopping RB Brian Robinson Jr. to teams around the NFL.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba20-df63-a199-fb2b212e0000</link>
      <description>Robinson averaged fewer than 4.0 yards per carry in five of his final seven games last year, and the Commanders are said to be focused on creating more explosive plays this season. Enter Day 3 rookie RB Jacory Croskey-Merritt, who has steadily earned the coaching staff’s praise through spring and summer practices. The team also has RB Chris Rodriguez Jr. under contract this year, who boasts a career 4.9 YPC average through two seasons operating as a rotational rusher. Robinson is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. If the front office feels good about Croskey-Merritt and Rodriguez, it makes sense for them to send Robinson away in exchange for future draft capital or a young player at a position of need.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba20-df63-a199-fb2b212e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 2-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 2 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba2f-d90d-a5bd-ba7f49460000</link>
      <description>Olave was on the field for 18-of-18 first-team snaps with Tyler Shough, which is a great sign for his ankle health. His concussion history, coupled with the Saints’ questionable quarterback situation, enhances his risk, but fantasy managers are advised to continue drafting Olave as a high-upside seventh-round pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba2f-d90d-a5bd-ba7f49460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught 3-of-3 targets for 15 yards in the Saints’ preseason Week 2 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba50-df63-a199-fb7bf0ac0000</link>
      <description>Shaheed played all 18 first-team reps alongside Tyler Shough and Chris Olave. He kicked inside, tying for a first-team-high seven snaps lined up in the slot. Adding quick-hitting layup routes from the slot will go a long way toward stabilizing Shaheed’s weekly scoring. His 13th-round PPR ADP makes for an easy click.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba50-df63-a199-fb7bf0ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Rattler completed 18-of-24 passes for 199 yards, one touchdown and one interception and rushed three times for 19 yards and one two-point conversion in the Saints’ preseason Week 2 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba67-d05a-adda-bae798c80000</link>
      <description>Rattler looked better than Tyler Shough did, though Rattler had the benefit of facing backups. The Saints are in an unenviable situation. Their rookie quarterback is failing to outplay their preferred backup. Fortunately, fantasy managers need not draft either player in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ba67-d05a-adda-bae798c80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
