<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Falcons OC Zac Robinson is meeting with the Eagles to discuss their offensive-coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c81a-d56e-afff-eefa7d600000</link>
      <description>Robinson is a branch off the Sean McVay coaching tree and has spent the last two seasons guiding the Falcons’ offensive unit. The 39-year-old coach led an offense that ranked 13th in points scored in 2024 but saw it fall outside the top 20 last season, thanks in part to injuries and the limited quarterback play of Michael Penix and Kirk Cousins. A lateral move to an offense with far more elite playmakers would bode well for Robinson, who could develop into a future head coaching candidate if he excels in his next OC role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c81a-d56e-afff-eefa7d600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with former Raiders head coach Antonio Pierce for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c812-d56e-afff-eefa7c200000</link>
      <description>Pierce had also been on the docket for the Giants, but with John Harbaugh all but sewn up it feels unlikely to happen. It does not feel likely that Pierce, 47, will rejoin the head coaching ranks this offseason. He spent 2025 as a CBS Sports analyst, which gives him a natural link to Falcons “president of football” Matt Ryan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c812-d56e-afff-eefa7c200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports he’s “hearing” Kevin Stefanski is the favorite for the Falcons head-coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c82c-d35e-a1bf-cdee99920000</link>
      <description>Stefanski has met with the Falcons, Ravens, Dolphins, Giants, and Titans so far. Obviously it doesn’t look likely he’ll be getting the Giants gig. Stefanski would seem like a strong fit with “president of football” Matt Ryan as he tries to re-establish some Shanaclan roots in the Atlanta offense. And Stefanski is used to quarterback quagmires after the last few years, so that part of the job might give him less pause than it would for some others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c82c-d35e-a1bf-cdee99920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RG Kevin Dotson (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Los Angeles’ Divisional Round game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c489-d56e-afff-e6e9677c0000</link>
      <description>Dotson was injured in Week 16 against the Seahawks when LB Derick Hall “unnecessarily stepped on” Dotson’s left leg after a play. Hall received a one-game suspension for the act. Dotson’s return is good news for the Rams’ offense. He is a capable interior blocker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c489-d56e-afff-e6e9677c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s James Boyd reports Colts coach Shane Steichen was “noncommital” to a role for Anthony Richardson in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c832-dc7a-af9b-cfbf093e0000</link>
      <description>He also notes that Chris Ballard “openly theorized about [Riley] Leonard being the team’s backup in 2026" while saying that he believes both Richardson and the team could benefit from a divorce. We doubt that Richardson would bring back much draft capital at this point, but every bit of it might matter for a team that dealt two first-round picks for Sauce Gardner. Richardson could be a low-cost or rehab option for teams this offseason in what looks to be a pretty barren quarterback market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c832-dc7a-af9b-cfbf093e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s James Boyd believes Michael Pittman “appears to have two options: restructure his contract or play somewhere else in 2026.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c837-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa0ee0000</link>
      <description>Pittman “basically admitted after the Colts’ regular-season finale that he might have played his last game for the franchise.” The franchise stalwart has a $29 million cap hit in 2026 and would free up $24 million for the Colts if he were cut. Entering his age-29 season, it’s possible that Pittman generates some low-end trade interest ahead of free agency if he’s willing to restructure his contract for other teams. It’s also possible the Colts simply cut him or restructure him and keep him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c837-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa0ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out WR Nico Collins (concussion) for Houston’s Divisional Round game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c83a-d35e-a1bf-cdfa779b0000</link>
      <description>Collins was unable to practice throughout the week. Texans slot WR Christian Kirk operated as the team’s No. 1 wide receiver last week, and is likely the best bet to do so again against the Patriots. It is an unfortunate development for Collins, who also missed his team’s Week 8 game against the 49ers due to concussion. Texans rookie WRs, Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel, have a chance to rise to the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c83a-d35e-a1bf-cdfa779b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams QB Jimmy Garoppolo (back) is questionable for Los Angeles’ Divisional Round game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c843-d968-a19b-d8f3e16a0000</link>
      <description>Garoppolo hasn’t needed to throw a pass all year, which is funny given how concerned we all were about Matthew Stafford’s back in August. Garoppolo popped up on the injury report as a DNP with this back injury on Thursday, though Sean McVay said he “expects” Garoppolo to play. Stetson Bennett would be Stafford’s backup if Garoppolo is inactive Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c843-d968-a19b-d8f3e16a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) is questionable for Chicago’s Divisional Round game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84a-d968-a19b-d8fba2930000</link>
      <description>Despite the questionable listing, we expect Odunze to play on Sunday. This is the exact same pattern (limited, limited, full) that he had ahead of the Wild Card round — the only difference is that Odunze was cleared off the injury report altogether for that one. Odunze had a 2/44 game in his return against the Packers after missing Weeks 14-18 with the foot injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84a-d968-a19b-d8fba2930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (knee) is not on Chicago’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84d-d56e-afff-eeed5cdf0000</link>
      <description>He produced a 6/64/1 receiving line against the Packers in the Wild Card round on seven targets and is likely in line for the same kind of volume as the Bears manage Rome Odunze’s foot. Moore will definitely be a DFS consideration this week behind Colston Loveland and Luther Burden in what would figure to be the highest-scoring game of the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84d-d56e-afff-eeed5cdf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
