<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 15:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports there is a “strong chance” Chris Godwin (ankle) plays in Week 4 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c52-d6a5-adff-fed74bf20000</link>
      <description>Schefter said the same of left tackle Tristan Wirfs, who is still working his way back from a knee injury he suffered in training camp. Both players returned to practice multiple weeks ago, giving them plenty of ramp-up time heading into Week 4. Per Schefter, Wirfs and Godwin are expected to get reps with the starters in practice this week. If all goes well, both should be back in the lineup for Week 4 against the Eagles. Godwin will be competing with rookie Emeka Egbuka for snaps out of the slot. If Godwin takes that role and looks like his old self, he could be back in the WR2 ranks as early as Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c52-d6a5-adff-fed74bf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Bengals “plan to stick with Jake Browning and not trade for another veteran quarterback.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c60-d6a5-adff-fee571ad0000</link>
      <description>Schefter mentioned more high school football stats than sources in his tweet, so it’s unclear if he’s getting this “report” from the team or if it’s just informed speculation. Either way, it does look like the Bengals will ride out Joe Burrow’s foot injury with Browning under center. Browning went 4-3 as a starter in 2023 and led the league with a 70.4 percent completion rate. He threw 12 touchdowns to seven interceptions and averaged 267 yards per game in his starts. The team then signed him to a two-year contract extension in the offseason. Browning is one of the league’s better backups and starting-caliber quarterbacks aren’t readily available via trade. There is a chance Burrow returns late in the year, but fantasy managers should be operating as if Browning is the Bengals’ starter for the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c60-d6a5-adff-fee571ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) is “expected to have his snaps monitored and potentially limited based on how he feels” in Week 3 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c6d-d6a5-adff-feed6fd60000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported yesterday that Egbuka is expected to suit up. The rookie only got in one practice before being listed as questionable for Week 3. Fantasy managers should be cautious with Egbuka entering his third NFL game. His production has largely been touchdown-based and now there’s a chance he is even less involved as the Bucs manage his workload. Egbuka is, at best, a high-risk WR3 for his Week 3 date with the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c6d-d6a5-adff-feed6fd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bears CB Jaylon Johnson is likely to undergo core muscle surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c74-d6a5-adff-fef56b9b0000</link>
      <description>Johnson is meeting with Dr. William Meyers of The Vincera Institute later this week, with the assumption that surgery will be the preferred option. Per Rapoport, Johnson could return in the second half of the season if he ends up undergoing the procedure. Johnson missed the first two games of the year while dealing with the injury. The fact that the Bears did not put him on injured reserve suggests the injury was worse than they initially expected. Johnson is one of many defenders out for Week 3, putting the Cowboys’ passing attack in a great spot to put up points with ease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c74-d6a5-adff-fef56b9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Brock Purdy (toe) is not expected to play in Week 3 against the Cardinals but “could be in line to start next week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c9e-d6a5-adff-fedfb6ee0000</link>
      <description>Purdy practiced in a limited capacity this week and Kyle Shanahan even toyed with the idea of using him as the backup quarterback today. Even with some light reps in practice, Purdy was always a long-shot to suit up versus the Cardinals. Mac Jones will make his second start as a 49er after throwing for 279 yards and three scores last week. He has some QB2 juice for Superflex leagues. According to Rapoport, Purdy is progressing better than expected, making a Week 4 return a possibility. That will ultimately depend on how he looks in practice next week. If Jones plays well again, Shanahan could feel less of a need to rush his starter back into the lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6c9e-d6a5-adff-fedfb6ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “no one has called” the Falcons about trading for Kirk Cousins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ca4-d6a5-adff-fee53d8e0000</link>
      <description>Atlanta’s asking price on their over $180 million backup is simply too high. Per Rapport, the Falcons want a team trading for Cousins to eat some of his lofty contract and give up a “premium pick.” One of those stipulations might be tennable for some teams, but asking for both is a non-starter. Barring a sudden change of heart, the Falcons appear content to hold onto Cousins as a high-end backup to Michael Penix until next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ca4-d6a5-adff-fee53d8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Dolphins owner Stephen Ross “plans to be patient” with head coach Mike McDaniel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ca8-dfde-a1bd-7ead31b50000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have more players-only meetings than wins this year after suffering their third loss on Thursday to the Bills. McDaniel was heralded as the league’s next great offensive mind after reviving Tua Tagovailoa’s career in 2022. Miami made the playoffs with a 9-8 record and did so again in the following season with 11 wins. They failed to reach the Divisional Round in either postseason appearance. The team then missed the playoffs last year and now sits at 0-3. Rapoport cites a strong relationship between McDaniel and Ross as part of the reason the team plans to be patient with their head coach. He also noted McDaniel’s recent contract extension. McDaniel has two years left on his deal worth more than $18 million. Though he may have a longer leash than most struggling coaches, McDaniel still needs to turn things around in a hurry. Even if the team doesn’t part ways with him during the season, a head coaching change at some point in the next six months feels inevitable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ca8-dfde-a1bd-7ead31b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Tracy Wolfson reports the “expectation” is for J.J. McCarthy (ankle) to return in Week 7 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cb2-dfde-a1bd-7ebf19980000</link>
      <description>The Vikings have a two-week stay in Europe after Week 3 and then get their bye in Week 6. Wolfson notes that McCarthy’s timeline could be moved up depending on how he is feeling, though we fully expect Minnesota to focus on Week 7 as the return date. The fact that they didn’t put him on injured reserve, which would have forced him to miss at least four games, corroborates the timeline Wolfson laid out. Carson Wentz will start in the meantime. Given McCarthy’s struggles, Wentz could be a short-term upgrade for the Vikings’ pass-catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cb2-dfde-a1bd-7ebf19980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Burrow (turf toe) could return mid-December.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cb7-d93f-ad9d-7ef72dea0000</link>
      <description>As expected, Rapoport said Burrow will be out a minimum of 12 weeks. He also included plenty of qualifiers when talking about a potential return for Burrow. The most important caveat he made was the fact that the Bengals need to have something to play for late in the season if Burrow is going to step back on the field this year. If Jake Browning struggles and the Bengals are out of the playoff hunt late in the year, Burrow is all but guaranteed to close the season on the sidelines. Browning went 4-3 as a starter in a similar situation in 2023. He led the league in completion rate (70.3 percent) and threw 12 touchdowns to seven interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cb7-d93f-ad9d-7ef72dea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Adrian Martinez will be the backup to Mac Jones in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cbe-dfde-a1bd-7ebf78770000</link>
      <description>This means Brock Purdy will be inactive, as expected. Kyle Shanahan put on a brave face and floated the idea of Purdy being the backup earlier this week, but that was a lie even Shanny himself couldn’t believe. Purdy will stay on the bench for another week as he nurses toe and shoulder injuries. He is reportedly eying a Week 4 return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cbe-dfde-a1bd-7ebf78770000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
