<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed DL Jordon Riley (Achilles) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7119-dc7a-af9b-ffbf08820000</link>
      <description>They also sent CB Kamal Hadden to IR after both Hadden and Riley suffered season-ending injuries against the Ravens in Week 17. Both players are at risk of missing time in training camp, if not spending time on the PUP list during the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7119-dc7a-af9b-ffbf08820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported the Browns and Raiders have done “preliminary research” on a coaching change.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7165-d968-a19b-79f5782b0000</link>
      <description>What exactly that entails, Fowler doesn’t actually get into, but he says “those are two places I see as like — they’ve done their preliminary research for a potential move, doesn’t mean they’re likely to do it or that they’ve decided yet.” We blurbed yesterday that Ian Rapoport doubts the Raiders will keep Pete Carroll. It sure sounds like the Browns and Stefanski should also be on the radar for a firing (or potentially a trade) once Week 18 unfolds. Stefanski gave up playcalling to Tommy Rees in early November and was reportedly less than thrilled when the Browns traded Joe Flacco to the Bengals. If the Browns did move on from Stefanski, he would be a strong candidate to pick up a new head coaching gig this offseason after twice winning the AP Coach of the Year award in 2020 and 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7165-d968-a19b-79f5782b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (back) will not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7193-d56e-afff-f7fb01ea0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers will conduct a walkthrough today, though McCaffrey will not participate. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan told reporters that McCaffrey’s back is “a little stiff.” Trainers tended to McCaffrey’s back between drives, late in the fourth quarter during the 49ers’ Week 17 win over the Bears. He returned and played effectively. We expect him to do so this week as well, though backup RB Brian Robinson must be rostered wherever he is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7193-d56e-afff-f7fb01ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said TE George Kittle (ankle) has “a chance to play” in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719a-dc7a-af9b-ffbf4f300000</link>
      <description>Great news. Kittle will be a limited participant in Tuesday evening’s walkthrough. The talented tight end sat out in Week 17 after missing practice all week. Backup TE Jake Tonges caught 7-of-8 targets for 60 yards and one touchdown in Kittle’s stead. If Kittle is unable to face the Seahawks on Saturday, Tonges will again be a viable streamer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719a-dc7a-af9b-ffbf4f300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) was limited on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719e-d56e-afff-f7fe22ad0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers are hosting only a walkthrough this evening. Logging a limited session is a plus for Pearsall, who has been plagued by lower-body injuries this season. He looked great running routes against the Bears last week, and can be treated as a WR3 with upside against the Seahawks’ tough defense in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719e-d56e-afff-f7fe22ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said LT Trent Williams (hamstring) has “a chance to play” in Week 18 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719e-d35e-a1bf-75de1af90000</link>
      <description>Williams will not participate in the 49ers’ walkthrough this evening and was forced from Week 17 after just one snap. Consider him firmly in the questionable camp for the team’s divisional showdown against the Seahawks in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-719e-d35e-a1bf-75de1af90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vikings are “working on a new deal” with DC Brian Flores.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-71a2-d968-a19b-79f36c430000</link>
      <description>As things currently stand, we are “two weeks from the open market.” Two weeks is a short time period, but things can move quickly in the NFL. Just yesterday, Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio reported that “various high-level executives” believe Flores will “most likely be a candidate” for a head-coaching job this offseason. The Vikings would surely love to keep their brilliant defensive coordinator, who schemes up bamboozling blitzes on a weekly basis. The Vikings’ 62.8 percent blitz rate leads the league by 19.9 percent and their 44.3 percent QB pressure rate leads the league by 2.0 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-71a2-d968-a19b-79f36c430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (elbow/hip) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7235-d35e-a1bf-77f73b180000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks face the 49ers on Saturday. The winner secures both wins the NFC West and earns the NFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. Barner has developed into a reliable contributor in the Seahawks’ passing game despite playing through multiple injuries this year. He is a boom-bust TE1 for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7235-d35e-a1bf-77f73b180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed (concussion) was limited on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-71c2-d35e-a1bf-75c29bd90000</link>
      <description>This is a positive update for Shaheed, who was forced from last week’s game against the Panthers. The Seahawks face the 49ers on Saturday, and the winner takes home the NFC West crown while also securing the NFC’s No. 1 playoff seed. Having Shaheed on the field would be extremely helpful for Seahawks QB Sam Darnold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-71c2-d35e-a1bf-75c29bd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (back) is expected to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-74aa-d35e-a1bf-75ea354a0000</link>
      <description>Jackson missed Week 17’s matchup with the Packers after suffering a back contusion against the Patriots in the previous week. While the 28-year-old quarterback’s absence was unfortunate for fantasy managers in the championship round of the playoffs, the Ravens still beat the Packers without Jackson, setting up a winner-take-all date with the Steelers this week. Rapoport said the Ravens thought Jackson would play last week, but he wasn’t even able to practice. He’s expected back on the practice field Wednesday and it’s difficult to imagine him missing a game of this magnitude without a setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-74aa-d35e-a1bf-75ea354a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
