<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Josina Anderson reports the Ravens will interview Broncos defensive coordinator Vance Joseph for the team’s open head coaching position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9b87-d968-a19b-dbf74c900000</link>
      <description>Joseph has been defensive coordinator for one of the league’s top defenses in the Broncos since 2023. He led a crew that allowed the second-least yards and third-least points to opponents during the 2025 regular season. Joseph was previously the defensive coordinator for the Cardinals and Dolphins with a stint as the Broncos’ head coach from 2017-2018. He could get his second chance to become a head coach this cycle and the Ravens, who had a struggling defense this season, will interview him for the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9b87-d968-a19b-dbf74c900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Giants will interview former Raiders HC Antonio Pierce for the team’s open head coaching position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9181-dc7a-af9b-dfbf701d0000</link>
      <description>Pierce took over as the Raiders’ interim head coach after Josh McDaniels was fired midway through the 2023 season and went 5-4 in the second half of the season. He was brought back for 2024, which was a disaster as the Raiders went 4-13, and was subsequently fired. While that is the extent of Pierce’s head coaching resume, his history with the Giants runs deep. A linebacker who played under Tom Coughlin in New York, Pierce made the Pro Bowl in 2006 and was an integral part of the Giants’ Super Bowl run in 2007. Whether that is enough to distinguish himself amongst a group of candidates that could include John Harbaugh and Kevin Stefanski remains to be seen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9181-dc7a-af9b-dfbf701d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers fired OC Josh Grizzard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9df5-d56e-afff-fffda4650000</link>
      <description>While Bucaneers head coach Todd Bowles told reporters Wednesday that he’ll remain in charge in 2026, someone was needed in the wreckage after Tampa Bay went 2-8 in its last 10 games and missed the playoffs. Grizzard is out after one season as the Buccaneers offensive coordinator, a running theme under Bowles, who’ll have his fifth OC in five years in ’26. Grizzard attempted to run back Liam Coen’s offensive from 2024, when the Bucs were fourth in the league in scoring, but his Bucs managed just 22.4 points per game (18th in the league). Baker Mayfield will be on his eighth different offensive coordinator in the last nine seasons in ’26.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9df5-d56e-afff-fffda4650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins fired head coach Mike McDaniel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9e3c-d35e-a1bf-dffe09730000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are moving on from their head coach after four seasons, according to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter. McDaniel met with owner Stephen Ross this week and Ross decided to move on from the 42-year-old coach despite his contract running through 2028. McDaniel’s Dolphins made the playoffs in his first two years, but were bounced in the Wild Card round each time and failed to make the playoffs each of the last two seasons. While the Dolphins held out the longest of any team that fired their coach so far, the writing was on the wall for McDaniel after a 1-6 start this season. There are now eight head coaching vacancies around the league. McDaniel could be a candidate for the Browns head coaching position, according to a previous report from ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler, though an offensive coordinator position could also be an option for McDaniel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9e3c-d35e-a1bf-dffe09730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders CB Marshon Lattimore “was taken into custody for carrying concealed weapons” and “later released pending further investigation.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ae6-dc7a-af9b-dfff8ae10000</link>
      <description>Lattimore was taken into custody by Lakewood Police, located just outside of Cleveland, Ohio. More details on the issue have not yet been shared. Lattimore has one year remaining on his contract with the Commanders, though the team can save all $18.5 million that he is scheduled to make in 2026 by releasing him this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ae6-dc7a-af9b-dfff8ae10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested to interview Broncos assistant head coach and special teams coordinator Darren Rizzi for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9aeb-d56e-afff-feebcf6f0000</link>
      <description>Rizzi took over as the Saints’ interim head coach during the 2024 season. Both the Saints and Jets interviewed Rizzi for their head-coaching vacancies the following summer. Rizzi ended up reuniting with Broncos head coach Sean Payton instead. Payton had previously hired him as the Saints’ special teams coordinator back in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9aeb-d56e-afff-feebcf6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers fired QB coach Thad Lewis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a93-d35e-a1bf-dfd3c4ba0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers have now fired their quarterbacks coach and offensive coordinator, Josh Grizzard, while offensive consultant Tom Moore announced his retirement. Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles is evidently ready to implement a new offense in 2026, likely under the advisement of whoever is hired to fill the team’s offensive coordinator vacancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a93-d35e-a1bf-dfd3c4ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers fired ST coordinator Thomas McGaughey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ed0-d35e-a1bf-dfd26f310000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers have now fired three coaches since announcing head coach Todd Bowles will remain for 2026. The team parted ways with offensive coordinator Josh Grizzard and QB coach Thad Lewis before firing McGaughey. Offensive consultant Tom Moore, 87, retired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ed0-d35e-a1bf-dfd26f310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB Ty Johnson (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9eef-dc7a-af9b-dfff74620000</link>
      <description>The Bills could simply be giving Johnson, their reliable passing down back, an extra day of rest. Thursday absences are often bad signs, though. If he can resume practicing tomorrow, he should be good to go for his team’s Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars. With QB Josh Allen nursing a foot injury, having Johnson available for checkdown passes would be beneficial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9eef-dc7a-af9b-dfff74620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed their interview with Broncos DC Vance Joseph.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef2-dc7a-af9b-dfffe30c0000</link>
      <description>That was fast. Just yesterday, Josina Anderson broke the news that Joseph was set to interview with the Ravens. Prior reports indicate that the Giants, Raiders, Titans, and Cardinals had requested to interview Joseph for their head-coaching vacancies as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9ef2-dc7a-af9b-dfffe30c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
