<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:25:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon said the team will not open Kyler Murray’s (foot) 21-day return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</link>
      <description>Kedon Slovis will get at least one more game as Jacoby Brissett’s backup. Murray hasn’t played since Week 5 and was eventually benched for Jacoby Brissett, who outperformed Murray during his multi-week absence. Murray is under contract through the 2028 season, but there’s a good chance his time with the team will come to an end this offseason. The same can be said of Jonathan Gannon, but that’s a conversation for another day. The Cardinals don’t have anything to play for at this point, and any decisions to part with Murray could factor into whether the team decides to activate him at all over the final five weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbd9-d82c-a79a-fbdd5fdf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys listed Tyler Guyton (ankle) as a DNP on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbeb-d6c4-abfb-dfebfd510000</link>
      <description>Guyton suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12’s win over the Eagles and was sidelined for Week 13’s game against the Chiefs. Given the nature of his injury, it seems unlikely that he would be ready to go with less than two weeks of recovery time. We’ll see if his status changes later in the week, but we could be looking at another start for Nate Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbeb-d6c4-abfb-dfebfd510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys listed WR KaVontae Turpin (shoulder) as a full participant on Monday’s estimated practice report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbef-d6c4-abfb-dfefc22c0000</link>
      <description>Turpin played through the same shoulder injury in Week 13’s win over the Chiefs. The Cowboys’ special teams ace has posted a meager 19-260-1 receiving line this season and isn’t on the fantasy radar for Week 14 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbef-d6c4-abfb-dfefc22c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) “still has to be given final medical clearance to play.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbf6-d6c4-abfb-dff7334b0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said the “plan is to see where Reed is at by the end of the week.” The Packers opened Reed’s 21-day return window ahead of Week 12’s game against the Vikings, and still have time before they need to decide whether to activate him or shut him down for the season. Reed suffered a broken collarbone in Week 2’s game against the Commanders and has caught just three passes for 45 yards and one touchdown this season. Reed continues to practice with the team in hopes of being cleared soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dbf6-d6c4-abfb-dff7334b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions placed CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc10-d6c4-abfb-de13c78a0000</link>
      <description>Arnold suffered a shoulder injury in Week 13’s loss to the Packers and will now miss at least the next four games as a result. The second-year corner has appeared in eight games this season while making seven starts, and registered his first career interception in Week 9 against the Vikings. Arnold has allowed just 23 receptions on 41 targets this season, per PFF, earning a coverage grade of 53.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc10-d6c4-abfb-de13c78a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers designated RB MarShawn Lloyd (hamstring) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc12-d90e-a9da-df1f6c730000</link>
      <description>Lloyd has yet to take a snap in 2025. The second-year back landed on injured reserve with a hamstring injury to start the season, and has been working his way back ever since. Injuries have completely derailed the start to Lloyd’s career, as he’s appeared in just one game since being drafted 88th overall by the Packers last season. Even if he does work his way back to the field this season, he’ll likely be buried behind both Josh Jacobs and Emanuel Wilson on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc12-d90e-a9da-df1f6c730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Kyle Juszczyk is dealing with a fractured rib.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc22-db57-afda-de32752b0000</link>
      <description>Juszczyk will be evaluated after the 49ers’ Week 14 bye. The veteran fullback has totaled 20 receptions for 187 yards and one touchdown this season, and continues to serve primarily as a run blocker in Shanahan’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc22-db57-afda-de32752b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed K Joshua Karty to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc3a-d6c4-abfb-de3bb4bb0000</link>
      <description>The move comes just three days after the team waived the veteran kicker. He had been a healthy inactive for three straight games prior to his release, but it appears the team wants to keep him close as they continue their march to the postseason. Harrison Mevis is expected to continue on as the starter, at least for the time being, after going a perfect 17-for-17 on PATs and 2-for-2 on field goal attempts in his four games with the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc3a-d6c4-abfb-de3bb4bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared QB Tommy DeVito, G Jared Wilson, S Brenden Schooler, T Marcus Bryant, OLB Bradyn Swinson, TE CJ Dippre, and DT Khyiris Tonga inactive for Week 13 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc3e-d90e-a9da-df3f2e890000</link>
      <description>Offensive tackle Marcus Bryant is probably the most notable inactive for the Patriots considering he was expected to serve at the swing tackle against the Giants. DeVito will be inactive, as has been the case since being claimed by the team in August.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc3e-d90e-a9da-df3f2e890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux, WR Jalin Hyatt, ILB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles, CB Jarrick Bernard-Converse, OLB Victor Dimukeje, OT James Hudson III, and QB Russell Wilson inactive for Week 13 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc52-d82c-a79a-ffd6c8ef0000</link>
      <description>Thibodeaux’s inactivity does not come as a surprise after he was ruled out earlier in the week. It does, however, go down as a significant absence for the Giants as they set their sights on an upset win over the Patriots on Monday Night Football. The fact the team did not place the veteran pass rusher on injured reserve likely means he is nearing a return, which appears likely to come when they come back from their Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dc52-d82c-a79a-ffd6c8ef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
