<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:02:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 4-of-7 targets for 26 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f89-d93f-ad9d-7fcf1eba0000</link>
      <description>Kelce made it through this one absent any mental mistakes, which now makes one in a row. That didn’t mean he was without the sideline drama as he was seen in a tiff with head coach Andy Reid in the second quarter while the Chiefs were playing the Giants to a 6-6 game. He finished second on the team in targets but continues to see other pass-catchers operate as the primary options through the air, this time being Tyquan Thornton. Kelce remains elite at generating separation in the short area of the field and can pick up third downs with the best of them, but his fantasy value is quickly deteriorating beyond a usable asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f89-d93f-ad9d-7fcf1eba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson completed 18-of-32 passes for 160 yards and two interceptions in the Giants’ 22-9, Week 3 loss to the Chiefs, adding 27 yards on five carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f8d-d1b3-a5dd-6ffd33e00000</link>
      <description>The Giants’ final possession of the game summarized Wilson’s night, when the team drove the field down 22-9 with under four minutes to play before Wilson threw three uncatchable balls and tried a quarterback draw that was met by three defenders at the line of scrimmage. The fans in New York let both Wilson and head coach Brian Daboll hear it throughout the second half, a mood that only let up when the team trot rookie Jaxson Dart onto the field for two consecutive plays in the fourth quarter. The Giants continue their string of difficult opponents to start the season in Week 4 when they host the Chargers, before a Week 5 meeting with the Saints. Wilson’s days as the starter under center appear to be numbered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f8d-d1b3-a5dd-6ffd33e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Skattebo rushed 10 times for 60 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs, adding 61 yards on six receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fa5-dfde-a1bd-7fad059e0000</link>
      <description>Skattebo served as he primary back following the first-quarter injury to Tracy, who departed the contest with a shoulder injury after a hit on the sideline. The tenacious rookie made good on the opportunity, leading the team in both rushing a receiving against a stout Kansas City defense. Fantasy managers need not wait on word of Tracy’s injury as it would be difficult to envision the team turning back to the veteran following the returns from Skattebo. He immediately vaults into the RB2 discussion the rest of the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fa5-dfde-a1bd-7fad059e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers caught 2-of-7 targets for 13 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fba-d93f-ad9d-7fff11870000</link>
      <description>Nabers had no chance against Steve Spagnuolo’s game plan, which involved heavy rates of double coverage and safety help against the talented second-year receiver. The poor showing goes down as his worst professional box score after never failing to crack four receptions until this point. A Week 4 matchup against the Chargers represents another difficult task for Nabers and quarterback Russell Wilson to overcome, a game that could spark a change at quarterback in New York if the returns do no improve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fba-d93f-ad9d-7fff11870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 1-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fc7-d6a5-adff-ffc755400000</link>
      <description>The catch he did make came on fourth down with the team down by 13 in the fourth quarter, giving them a sliver of hope as the clock counted down to under five minutes remaining. The Chiefs had a very clear game plan to limit the offensive success from the Giants, which involved double teams on Malik Nabers and dropping linebackers to clog the middle of the field to account for Robinson. The veteran slot man will look to get back on track when the Giants host the Chargers in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fc7-d6a5-adff-ffc755400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught all four targets for 30 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fd3-d93f-ad9d-7fd72edf0000</link>
      <description>Slayton remains well behind both Malik Nabers and Wan’Dale Robinson in the target pecking order despite finishing second in the team in receiving behind running back Cam Skattebo, beating both other receivers on the night. It will be difficult to trust Slayton as anything more than a bye week desperation start moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fd3-d93f-ad9d-7fd72edf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fda-d1b3-a5dd-6ffb427a0000</link>
      <description>Johnson now has six catches for 49 yards through three games and has not yet lived up to the offseason hype. He can safely remain on, or be returned to, waiver wires, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6fda-d1b3-a5dd-6ffb427a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Noah Fant suffered a concussion in the Bengals’ Week 3 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-715a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf6ee80000</link>
      <description>Fant will now need to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to suit up in Week 4 against the Broncos. Fant has been a key part of the Bengals’ offense through the first three weeks, drawing 14 targets over that span while totaling 12 catches for 80 yards and a score. Even if he’s able to clear protocol in time for next week, Fant shouldn’t be valued as anything more than a boom-or-bust TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-715a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf6ee80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said “we’ll talk about that today as a staff” when asked about Justin Fields returning as QB1 after he clears concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-719c-d6a5-adff-f7dded3c0000</link>
      <description>Glenn followed up his initial statement by adding, “Justin came in as our starter. He’s been our starter. Tyrod was the backup.” If we’re attempting to read between the lines, one might infer that Glenn referencing both QB’s statuses in the past tense could be a sign a change is coming, but we’ll wait until Glenn offers up a clearer explanation on where things stand ahead of Week 4. Fields still needs to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to play next week against the Dolphins, but Taylor played well enough against the Buccaneers to nearly earn the Jets their first win of the season, and held up well under pressure. Even if Fields does return as the starter, it’s safe to assume he’ll be on a short leash after his Week 2 debacle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-719c-d6a5-adff-f7dded3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Ben Standig reports the Commanders are meeting with free agent S Darnell Savage on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71e6-dfde-a1bd-7fef08550000</link>
      <description>The Commanders’ meeting with Savage comes a day after the team lost safety Will Harris to a fractured fibula. While we don’t yet know the extent of Harris’ injury, the decision to meet with Savage this early suggests he will miss significant time. Savage was released by the Jaguars last week after appearing in the first two games to start the season in a backup role. He’s a seven-year vet with 82 games of starting experience under his belt and could immediately fill a key role if called upon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-71e6-dfde-a1bd-7fef08550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
