<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:02:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (thumb) returned to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdcf-d45c-a7fc-bfdfb52f0000</link>
      <description>Love underwent surgery to correct a ligament issue on his non-throwing hand, but was away for less than a week. The Packers’ QB1 was sporting a glove on his hand, but appears to be on track to be ready for Week 1 when the Packers play host to the Lions. Love finished as the QB20 in fantasy points per game last season and had only six top-12 weeks. He’ll profile most weeks as a mid QB2 in an offense that’s expected to feature plenty of Josh Jacobs after leading the league with a 53 percent neutral rush rate last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-bdcf-d45c-a7fc-bfdfb52f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) returned to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be01-d45c-a7fc-be1b98ce0000</link>
      <description>Our national nightmare is over. After refusing on Saturday to say if Stafford worked out as planned, the Rams’ QB1 took to the field in full pads and jersey on Monday, looking ready for his first taste of training camp practice. Stafford has been dealing with a back injury for weeks and, at one point, had an epidural to help with the pain. Stafford has endured numerous injuries throughout his 16-year career, including multiple back injuries. Head coach Sean McVay said last week that part of Stafford’s absence last week was due to function and pain tolerance, which doesn’t seem great. The Rams are going to do what they can to have Stafford ready for the season, but we wouldn’t assume he’s a lock to start Week 1 until we see how he progresses in the coming weeks. If he’s unable to go at any point in the season, Jimmy Garoppolo would take the reins at QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be01-d45c-a7fc-be1b98ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (undisclosed) was spotted in a non-contact jersey on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be13-df63-a199-ff3bf58d0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from last week, when Stevenson was completely sidelined in practice. Stevenson is dealing with an undisclosed injury that was first announced last Tuesday, but could be trending toward a full return by the end of the week. The fifth-year back could be on the wrong side of a split backfield after rookie TreVeyon Henderson has impressed through two preseason games, rushing for 5-38-1 while also returning a kick return for a 100-yard score. We’ll be sure to provide any updates on Stevenson’s availability as they are announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be13-df63-a199-ff3bf58d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns named Joe Flacco as the starting QB for Week 1 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be20-df63-a199-ff2bf77d0000</link>
      <description>This comes to the surprise of nobody. The Browns opened camp with what was announced as a four-way quarterback competition, but Kenny Pickett, rookie third-rounder Dillon Gabriel, and rookie fifth-rounder Shedeur Sanders never stood much of a chance at unseating the 40-year-old signal-caller. Flacco led the Browns to a playoff appearance in 2023 when he threw for 1,616-13-8 in five starts on his way to winning AP Comeback Player of the Year. Last season with the Colts, Flacco threw for 1,781-12-7 in eight games, proving again to be prone to turnovers while playing more loosely and freely than in his days in Baltimore. While Flacco will open the season as the Browns’ starter, we would expect to see a few different starters under center before the season is up. He’ll profile a mid-QB2 against the Bengals in what could be a high-scoring affair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be20-df63-a199-ff2bf77d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent WR Gabe Davis is scheduled to meet for a second time with the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be38-d45c-a7fc-be3ab1f70000</link>
      <description>Davis met with the Steelers in early June but left without a deal. The former Jaguar was released this offseason with a failed physical designation and has been looking for work all offseason. In one season with the Jags, Davis caught 20-of-42 targets for 239 yards and two touchdowns and saw his season cut short by a torn meniscus. The Steelers have a need for an outside receiver opposite DK Metcalf, but it’s fair to wonder how much Davis has to offer after being released one year into a three-year, $39 million contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be38-d45c-a7fc-be3ab1f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns and RB Quinshon Judkins have been unable to agree to a deal despite the criminal charges against Judkins being dismissed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be43-d45c-a7fc-be5bd3430000</link>
      <description>The NFL still plans to run its own investigation into Judkins and the domestic battery charges that led to his arrest in July. The police report that followed Judkins’ arrest said “bruising was clearly evident” on the woman he allegedly assaulted, which undoubtedly complicates the Browns’ decision to sign him even if he won’t be charged in court. We’ll see if a deal can be reached before the start of the season, but it wouldn’t be surprising if a decision is put off until the league concludes its investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be43-d45c-a7fc-be5bd3430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said the team will continue to take things “a day at a time” with Matthew Stafford (back).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be4c-df63-a199-ff6feb330000</link>
      <description>McVay declined to comment on any future plans for Stafford, leaving us to wait until tomorrow to see if the veteran quarterback will practice for a second consecutive day. Stafford was a full participant in the hour that he did practice, and ran 26 plays of team drills, according to Rams beat writer Wyatt Miller. Stafford’s return to the field is a good sign, but we’re a long way from having any confidence about his Week 1 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be4c-df63-a199-ff6feb330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Hollywood Brown (ankle) is “taking it slow and we don’t want any setbacks” when asked about Brown playing in Kansas City’s final preseason game on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be6f-d45c-a7fc-be7fbccd0000</link>
      <description>Brown returned to practice today and all the starters are tentatively planning to play at least a little bit in Kansas City’s third preseason game. It looks like Brown should be fully healthy for the start of the regular season, even if he doesn’t chance playing on the ankle on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be6f-d45c-a7fc-be7fbccd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Commanders and Brian Robinson have mutually decided he will not play in Monday’s preseason game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be71-d05a-adda-bef3ced50000</link>
      <description>This comes a day after it was announced that the Commanders have explored potential trades for the fourth-year back. Robinson is seemingly being phased out of the offense in favor of rookie seventh-rounder Jacory Croskey-Merritt and veterans like Austin Ekeler, Jeremy McNichols, and Chris Rodriguez, and struggled late last season. During the final seven games of the regular season, Robinson rushed 86 times for 338 yards (3.9 YPC) and two touchdowns, and managed just 129 yards on 36 carries in the postseason. Croskey-Merritt has turned in an impressive camp and has been touted by some beat writers as the potential favorite to lead the backfield at some point in the season. Should Robinson be traded or cut, that could pave the way for JCM to see a meaningful workload early on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-be71-d05a-adda-bef3ced50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
