<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Jets, 49ers, and Vikings are “monitoring the trade market for potential wide receiver additions.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7a5-de13-afdc-c7efe5e20000</link>
      <description>All three teams would make sense as a landing spot for disgruntled Commanders WR Terry McLaurin, who has sat out Washington’s training camp and is reportedly unhappy with the lack of progress toward a new deal with the Commanders. The Vikings will be without Jordan Addison for the season’s first month, meaning Jalen Nailor will likely work as the team’s WR2. The Jets, meanwhile, have the league’s thinnest wide receiver room behind Garrett Wilson. The 49ers will be without Brandon Aiyuk for a while, and Jauan Jennings is reportedly dealing with a calf injury and unhappy with his current contract. McLaurin’s fantasy stock would be highest in Washington, though San Francisco would be a good landing spot statistically for the 30-year-old wideout. He’d take a major hit if he’s dealt to the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7a5-de13-afdc-c7efe5e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan M. Alexander reports Joe Mixon (ankle, foot) could land on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7b1-de13-afdc-c7fb190e0000</link>
      <description>That would mean Mixon, dealing with lingering foot and ankle issues, would miss at least the first four weeks of the regular season. Mixon is already an iffy option for Week 1. He hasn’t been seen out at practice, nor has he worked off to the side, which would indicate he’s not two to three weeks away from returning from the foot or ankle injury he suffered off the field this past offseason,” Alexander said of Mixon, who rushed for 1,016 yards and 11 touchdowns over 14 games in 2024. Texans officials have been vague about Mixon’s status two weeks ahead of the team’s Week 1 game against the Rams. “Joe is kind of working through it,” general manager Nick Caserio said Tuesday. “We’ll kind of take it one day at a time. Once we get a little closer, we’ll probably have a better idea of where he’s going to be. But Joe is working hard trying to get himself back ready to go.” Nick Chubb, according to Alexander, “will likely serve as the lead back until Mixon returns, whenever that may be.” Chubb would probably share the backfield workload with Dameon Pierce and pass-catching specialist Woody Marks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7b1-de13-afdc-c7fb190e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan M. Alexander believes Nick Chubb will “likely” work as the Texans’ lead back if Joe Mixon (foot, ankle) misses time in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7ba-de13-afdc-c7fb34380000</link>
      <description>Alexander said the Texans signed Chubb this offseason specifically because they feared Mixon would miss time with a foot/ankle injury he suffered this offseason. Though Mixon is unlikely to miss the entire regular season, the veteran could land on the PUP list to start the season, according to Alexander. That would cost Mixon the first four weeks of the regular season and perhaps put Chubb in the RB1 role. One of the most inefficient rushers in the NFL last season, Chubb, 29, had 25 yards on five rushing attempts last week against the Panthers in the Texans’ second preseason matchup. Rookie Woody Marks led the backfield with 40 yards on seven carries. Marks would likely work as the primary pass-catching back if Mixon were to miss time, while Chubb splits early down duties with Dameon Pierce. Chubb will be touchdown dependent even as the team’s de facto No. 1 back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7ba-de13-afdc-c7fb34380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports RB Zach Charbonnet “is going to have a significant role in the Seattle Seahawks’ backfield this season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7cc-d332-a1fd-d7feb0490000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet has impressed Seahawks coaches, including new offensive coordinator Klint Kubiak, throughout the offseason and into training camp while Ken Walker has missed significant time with an ongoing foot issue. Walker has managed just four practices over the past month, according to Henderson. Charbonnet hasn’t missed any time, and rushed fore 45 yards on just five carries last week against the Chiefs. “While no one with the Seahawks has publicly acknowledged that the RB1 job is up for grabs, Walker’s ongoing availability issues and the way Charbonnet continues to impress the organization suggests that Seattle’s backfield could be more of a timeshare than a typical starter-backup arrangement,” Henderson said. Kubiak, meanwhile, said availability will weigh heavily in who carries the load in the Seattle backfield this season. Kubiak said he’s seeking backs “that are available for the whole game. The best backs that I’ve been around are super smart ... Our top two guys are doing some really good things, but Charbonnet, his mental approach to the game is extremely impressive. He does not flinch.” Charbonnet is an excellent fantasy pick for drafters who fade the running back position in the opening rounds, while Walker remains a risky option with some upside if he can manage to stay healthy in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c7cc-d332-a1fd-d7feb0490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel said De’Von Achane’s absence from practice is “preventative.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c812-d332-a1fd-de36d8fa0000</link>
      <description>Achane is expected to sit out practice through the rest of the week and could be closely managed until the Dolphins’ Week 1 game against the Colts. “Calves are the ones that you have to be super proactive [with], especially with explosive players,” McDaniel said when asked about how the team is handling Achane ahead of the regular season, adding that NFL trainers have “horror stories” of players coming back too soon from calf injuries and aggravating the injury or tearing their Achilles tendon. If Achane sits out the season opener while recovering from his calf issue, Jaylen Wright would take over as Miami’s RB1, with rookie RB Ollie Gordon serving as a complementary option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c812-d332-a1fd-de36d8fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Patriots are open to trading S Kyle Dugger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c819-db7b-a5dd-e81db30e0000</link>
      <description>Schultz said the Patriots are keen on getting rid of Dugger ahead of the regular season, and are willing to eat part of his hefty contract to get a deal done. Dugger has been unhappy with his reduced role this offseason. There are several teams interested in acquiring Dugger, graded by Pro Football Focus in 2024 as the league’s fourth worst safety. Dugger last year allowed a completion on 79 percent of the passes that came his way. There’s a good chance he’s on another roster by Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c819-db7b-a5dd-e81db30e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed QB Tyson Bagent to a two-year contract extension worth $10 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c84c-dbe3-a9bb-f85fbe8b0000</link>
      <description>The deal has another $6 million in incentives linked to playing time and production for the backup quarterback, who has impressed Bears head coach Ben Johnson this offseason. Bagent in 145 pass attempts over the past two seasons has a 66 percent completion rate an a lowly adjusted yards per attempt of 4.5. He has six interceptions to three touchdowns over those two seasons, and would step in as Chicago’s starting QB should Caleb Williams miss time or get benched in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c84c-dbe3-a9bb-f85fbe8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans activated CB L’Jarius Sneed (knee) from the active/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c876-de13-afdc-ceff835c0000</link>
      <description>Sneed told reporters that he is confident he’ll play in Week 1’s game against the Broncos, but only worked on individual drills in his first day off the PUP list today. It will be a big boost for the Titans secondary if Sneed can play and be as effective as he was for the Chiefs before the trade — Sneed appeared in only five games last year for Tennessee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c876-de13-afdc-ceff835c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears DB Terell Smith (knee) tore his patellar tendon in Chicago’s second preseason game and will miss the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c879-d332-a1fd-de7f2de40000</link>
      <description>The 2023 fifth-round pick has proven to be an exceptionally good depth piece thus far, posting PFF coverage grades (in a 584-snap sample size over two years) of 76.5 in 2024 and 65.4 in 2023. He’s mostly played as an outside corner. Chicago’s depth chart behind Tyrique Stevenson, Jaylon Johnson (also hurt) and Kyler Gordon is shaky enough that the team might pursue outside help at final cuts. Smith will be on the final year of his rookie deal in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c879-d332-a1fd-de7f2de40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins activated Darren Waller (old) off the active/PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c87d-dbe3-a9bb-f87f9c060000</link>
      <description>Waller will be available for Thursday’s joint practice with the Jaguars. It’s hard to gauge Waller’s fantasy value as Jonnu Smith’s replacement without knowing how healthy Tyreek Hill and Jaylen Waddle will play this year, but he likely starts out as a lower-end TE2 due to how fragile he’s been throughout his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c87d-dbe3-a9bb-f87f9c060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
