<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs released TE Robert Tonyan.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8f6-db7b-a5dd-e8f698bb0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs cut Tonyan after signing him to a one-year deal this offseason. However, Kansas City Star’sSam McDowellreports the plan is for Tonyan to return to the team. The Chiefs also released LB Cole Christiansen, S Mike Edwards, DT Mike Pennel, and DT Marlon Tuipulotu. They also waived CB Elijhah Badger, DE Owen Carney, CB Ajani Carter, T Dalton Cooper, S Jacobe Covington, WR Mac Dalena, T Chukwuebuka Godrick, G C.J. Hanson, CB Azizi Hearn, WR Jimmy Holiday, DT Coziah Izzard, LB Cam Jones, CB Kevin Knowles, C Joey Lombard, DT Fabien Lovett, DE Nate Matlack, S Glendon Miller, LB Xander Mueller, QB Chris Oladokun, T Esa Pole, WR Hal Presley, WR Key’Shawn Smith, CB Melvin Smith, TE Geor’Quarius Spivey, TE Tre Watson, RB Michael Wiley, and S Major Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8f6-db7b-a5dd-e8f698bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers released WR Rakim Jarrett.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e918-db7b-a5dd-e91c6c220000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers cleared up their wide receiver group with final cuts, waiving Rakim Jarrett after already waiving Trey Palmer. They also waived CB Tre Avery, DL Eric Banks, QB Connor Bazelak, DL C.J. Brewer, S Will Brooks, WR Garrett Greene, DL Mike Greene, G Luke Haggard, WR Dennis Houston, DL Nash Hutmacher, DL Dvon J-Thomas, LB Nick Jackson, RB Jase McClellan, T Tyler McLellan, T Lorenz Metz, OLB Warren Peeples, OLB Jose Ramirez, S Shilo Sanders, C Ben Scott, TE Tanner Taula, RB Owen Wright, CB JayVian Farr, LB Antonio Grier, C Jake Majors, T Raiqwon O’Neal and CB Roman Parodie. They released DL Adam Gotsis, CB Bryce Hall, WR Jacob Harris, G Michael Jordan, and G Sua Opeta. Terminated for non-football injury was LB Anthony Walker and waived for non-football illness was DL Desmond Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e918-db7b-a5dd-e91c6c220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens released RB Myles Gaskin.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e92f-dbe3-a9bb-f97f92d50000</link>
      <description>Gaskin was brought in as a camp body by the Ravens, who have their running back room set. They now release him, along with CB Thomas Graham Jr., RB D’Ernest Johnson, WR Keith Kirkwood, WR Anthony Miller, and DL Brent Urban. They also waived WR Jahmal Banks, S Beau Brade, WR Malik Cunningham, G Darrian Dalcourt, OL Garrett Bellinger, OLB Malik Hamm, S Desmond Igbinosun, S Keondre Jackson, DL Jayson Jones, QB Devin Leary, T Gerad Lichtenhan, ILB Chandler Martin, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, DL Adedayo Odeleye, DL C.J. Okoye, G Jared Penning, DL C.J. Ravenell, CB Marquise Robinson, OLB Kaimon Rucker, C Nick Samac, FB Lucas Scott, and TE Scotty Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e92f-dbe3-a9bb-f97f92d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers released QB Taylor Heinicke.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e947-d332-a1fd-ff776d840000</link>
      <description>The Chargers had re-signed Heinicke this offseason, but choose to keep Trey Lance as the primary backup quarterback. The team also released CB Harrison Hand, S Tony Jefferson, LB Kana’i Mauga, RB Nyheim Miller-Hines, LB Del’Shawn Phillips, WR Jalen Reagor, and OT David Sharpe. They also waived G Karsen Barnhart, CB Trikweze Bridges, WR Dalevon Campbell, DL TeRah Edwards, WR Luke Grimm, LB Kylan Guidry, DL Christopher Hinton, WR JaQuae Jackson, LB Emany Johnson, G Nash Jone, C Josh Kaltenberge, TE Stevo Klotz, LB Tre’Mon Morris-Brash, OT Ryan Nelson, CB Myles Purchase, OLB Garmon Randolph, WR Brenden Rice, RB Raheim Sanders, CB Nehemiah Shelton, DL Nesta Jade Silvera, OT Corey Stewart, OG Branson Taylor, QB DJ Uiagalelei, RB Kimani Vidal and TE Thomas Yassmin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e947-d332-a1fd-ff776d840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars have acquired WR Tim Patrick from the Lions in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eb67-d332-a1fd-ff771b1c0000</link>
      <description>Patrick joined the Lions last year and had 394 yards and three touchdowns. The 31-year-old provided size at 6-foot-5 as well as production. He figures to take on a similar role with the Jaguars, who were looking for a bigger receiver that can also block. For the Lions, rookie Isaac Teslaa could be in line to replace Patrick as the WR3 after a loud preseason where he had three touchdowns. Kalif Raymond will also be in that mix. Detroit could’ve kept Patrick around as a depth option this year, but opted to recoup some draft capital after trading up to take Teslaa. The Lions gave Patrick as $2.5 million contract this offseason that included a $1.25 million signing bonus, which the Lions will retain as a dead cap hit after the trade. Patrick’s fantasy stock was nearly nonexistent with the Lions and doesn’t seem to have improved much at all going to a similarly crowded Jaguars receiver room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eb67-d332-a1fd-ff771b1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed S Daniel Thomas.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eb83-d332-a1fd-ffb7d1ef0000</link>
      <description>Thomas had spent his entire five-year career with the Jaguars, but was released earlier this week. The Lions were looking for depth at the safety position since seventh-round pick Dan Jackson went on injured reserve in training camp. Thomas was considered a special teams ace with the Jaguars and figures to have most of his impact on special teams with the Lions as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eb83-d332-a1fd-ffb7d1ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed S Jordan Poyer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eba5-de13-afdc-efef37b40000</link>
      <description>Poyer made first-team All-Pro in 2021 and went to the Pro Bowl in 2022 while playing with the Bills. The 34-year-old safety spent 2024 with the Dolphins, where he started 16 games and had 98 tackles. The Bills already have Cole Bishop and Taylor Rapp as starting safeties and Poyer was brought back as a member of the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eba5-de13-afdc-efef37b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings have acquired Adam Thielen, a conditional seventh-round pick and a future fifth-round pick from the Panthers in exchange for a fifth-round pick and a future fourth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebce-dbe3-a9bb-fbdf887e0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings are essentially getting Thielen, a fan favorite who represents much-needed wide receiver depth, for a future fourth-round pick. Jonathan Jones of CBS reports the team will attempt to rework Thielen’s contract, none of which will be absorbed by the Panthers. For the Vikings, Thielen is a familiar face who had a resurgence last year and can adequately fill-in for Jordan Addison, who is suspended for the first three games of the season. For the Panthers, they get a solid return for a 35-year-old receiver and open up playing time for young receivers Xavier Legette and Jalen Coker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebce-dbe3-a9bb-fbdf887e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio told reporters Joe Mixon (ankle) will be re-evaluated after four weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebed-d332-a1fd-ffff1d7f0000</link>
      <description>Caserio was noncommittal when discussing the 29-year-old running back with reporters. Mixon was placed on the reserve/non-football injury list and is set to miss at least the first four weeks of the season, at which point he’ll be re-evaluated. When asked if he anticipates Mixon playing at all this season, Caserio said, “We’ll see, we’ll take it one day at a time.” Mixon should be off fantasy draft boards at this point. Nick Chubb will begin the year as the Texans’ starting running back with Dameon Pierce and Woody Marks waiting in the wings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebed-d332-a1fd-ffff1d7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins GM Chris Grier told reporters De’Von Achane (calf) is expected to play in Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebf6-dbe3-a9bb-fbf783c10000</link>
      <description>Achane hasn’t been practicing as a preventative measure, but the 23-year-old running back is expected to play against the Colts in Week 1. Surely he’ll be back on the practice field by next week if he’s going to be active against the Colts. While nothing has changed with Achane’s status, the Dolphins continue to project confidence in the third-year back. With the fantasy community well aware of Achane’s calf issue, he could be a value in the middle of the second round as long as he doesn’t suffer a setback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ebf6-dbe3-a9bb-fbf783c10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
