<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth was not targeted in the Steelers’ Week 4 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-917a-d6e9-af9d-9bfafaab0000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth caught three passes in each of his first two games but dipped to one grab last week. This was his first game without a target since Week 16 of 2023. Arthur Smith has a few schemed plays for Jonnu Smith every week and is otherwise focused on getting the ball to his wide receivers. That leaves no fantasy value to be had for Freiermuth. Fantasy managers can cut him on the next run of waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-917a-d6e9-af9d-9bfafaab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers was carted from the Giants’ Week 4 game against the Chargers with a right knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9187-d6e9-af9d-9b97fa740000</link>
      <description>Nabers was formally ruled out at halftime. Leaping to make a potential down-field catch in the second quarter, Nabers’ right leg buckled as he planted to leap. He was then seen grabbing his knee in mid-air before coming down. The Giants immediately called for the cart. Nabers put a towel over his head as he was being taken to the locker room. Nabers frequently limps on and off the field, but this certainly appeared different than his usual injury issues. Fantasy managers need to be prepared for the worst.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9187-d6e9-af9d-9b97fa740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleb Johnson rushed six times for 22 yards in the Steelers’ Week 4 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-917e-d95b-addb-f97eb0040000</link>
      <description>Johnson didn’t touch the ball in Week 3 after making an egregious special teams mistake in Week 2. With Jaylen Warren out for today’s game, Johnson was elevated to RB2 duties versus Minnesota. He looked solid on the ground but did drop his only target. It was a step in the right direction for the rookie, even if he doesn’t have any fantasy appeal heading into the Steelers’ Week 5 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-917e-d95b-addb-f97eb0040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Mason rushed 16 times for 57 yards in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-918e-d95b-addb-f9ce17e70000</link>
      <description>Mason coughed up a fumble-six in the first quarter, but the play was overturned upon review. Mason’s leg was out of bounds when he reached out to corral the loose ball. He only needed to touch the ball for the play to be dead, and he did just that. It was an otherwise uneventful day for Mason, who also caught three balls for 15 yards. Aaron Jones has two more games on injured reserve, meaning Mason will continue to dominate the backfield in Week 5 against the Browns, keeping him in the RB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-918e-d95b-addb-f9ce17e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 4-of-5 targets for 39 yards in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9194-dca3-a9fb-bd9da9440000</link>
      <description>Hockenson caught his first touchdown of the year last week but is still looking for his first game with more than five catches of 50 yards. He earned a measly 12 percent target share this week. The return of Jordan Addison is also going to make targets even harder to come by in Minnesota. Hockenson is dangerously close to falling out of the TE1 ranks heading into Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9194-dca3-a9fb-bd9da9440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Nailor caught 1-of-4 targets for two yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-919c-deb6-a7fd-d3dfae410000</link>
      <description>Nailor split the WR3 duties with Adam Thielen and even running back Zavier Scott in this game. He caught a two-yard touchdown toss in the fourth quarter and brought down a two-point conversion grab. Nailor is a solid rotational player for the Vikings but doesn’t have much fantasy value heading into Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-919c-deb6-a7fd-d3dfae410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) inactive for Jacksonville’s Week 4 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a2-deb6-a7fd-d3ff9ca60000</link>
      <description>Brown got in limited sessions on Thursday and Friday, but this will add to Parker Washington’s streamer appeal. Also inactive for the Jaguars are: RB Cody Schrader, OL Wyatt Milum, DT Khalen Saunders, DL Danny Striggow, LB Yasir Abdullah and S Kahlef Hailassie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a2-deb6-a7fd-d3ff9ca60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) is active for San Francisco’s Week 4 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a4-deb6-a7fd-d3ff676f0000</link>
      <description>Jennings was expected to play and is doing so off a questionable tag. Also inactive for the 49ers are: CB Renardo Green (neck), DL CJ West (hand), WR Jordan Watkins (calf), WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling, RB Jordan James and LB Nick Martin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a4-deb6-a7fd-d3ff676f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zavier Scott caught 6-of-8 passes for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a6-d6e9-af9d-9bb6ce750000</link>
      <description>Scott is the Vikings’ backup running back with Aaron Jones on injured reserve, but he was used in a hybrid role versus Pittsburgh. Scott, who played wide receiver at UConn, ran routes from the backfield, slot, and out wide in this game. He only saw two carries and rushed for just one yard. Carson Wentz attempted 46 passes, juicing the counting stats for his receivers, but a 17 percent target share is also impressive from Scott. He will hit the RB4 radar for Minnesota’s Week 4 date with the Browns in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a6-d6e9-af9d-9bb6ce750000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
