<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Hassan Haskins (chest) is officially active for Week 7 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-d651-a9df-fdbd88ae0000</link>
      <description>Haskins will rotate in behind RB Kimani Vidal, who out-touched Haskins 21-7 last week. Vidal is an RB2 for the occasion, while Haskins is a touchdown-dependent FLEX. The big-bodied running back was added to the injury report with a chest injury on Friday, but practiced in full that day. The Chargers declared LT Joe Alt (ankle), RT Trey Pipkins III (knee), S Elijah Molden, LB Troy Dye, WR KeAndre Lambert Smith, EDGE Kyle Kennard and CB Nikko Reed inactive for Week 7 against the Colts. Chargers OLB Khalil Mack (elbow) and LB Denzel Perryman (ankle) will play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-d651-a9df-fdbd88ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons suffered a hamstring injury in Tennessee’s Week 7 game against the Patriots and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc1-da18-a39b-ffd3207c0000</link>
      <description>The Titans’ best player was declared questionable in the first half before being formally ruled out after the break. It’s a classic “what else could go wrong?” for a team that just fired its head coach. Considering the lost state of Tennessee’s season and Simmons being potential trade fodder, he could be looking at a multi-week absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc1-da18-a39b-ffd3207c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxx Crosby (knee) is doubtful to return in Week 7 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd26-d651-a9df-fd37d8ad0000</link>
      <description>Crosby exited in the second quarter with a knee injury and could be seen on the sidelines receiving treatment from trainers. Crosby seldom takes plays off or misses games, so it’s safe to assume this as a somewhat serious injury to the star pass rusher and it wouldn’t be surprising if the team opted to sideline him with a Week 8 bye coming up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd26-d651-a9df-fd37d8ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrance Ferguson caught his only target for 31 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 7 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc1-d651-a9df-fdd5cb040000</link>
      <description>The rookie’s second catch of the year came on a shot play over the middle of the field in the fourth quarter. The Jags were never in the game to begin with, but Ferguson’s score put the final nail in the coffin. Ferguson is nowhere near the fantasy radar, but it’s good to see the rookie getting more involved as the season goes on. He remains an interesting dynasty stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc1-d651-a9df-fdd5cb040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared WR Josh Downs, WR Ashton Dulin, TE Will Mallory, RB Tyler Goodson, DT Eric Johnson II, S Reuben Lowery III and OT Luke Tenuta inactive for Week 7 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-d651-a9df-fdbd8b700000</link>
      <description>Downs (concussion) and Dulin (chest) were sidelined all week. Their absences give embattled WR Adonai Mitchell a chance to prove himself after costing the Colts a win with his celebratory, goal-line fumble in Week 4. Mitchell cannot be trusted to return FLEX value, though. Expect Daniel Jones to rely heavily on WR Michael Pittman Jr. and TE Tyler Warren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-d651-a9df-fdbd8b700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendre Miller has been ruled out for the rest of Week 7 against the Bears with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdcf-d651-a9df-fddfe8210000</link>
      <description>Miller injured his knee in the second quarter but was able to walk into the locker room under his own power. He will not return to the game, but the Saints will hope that the injury isn’t serious. Miller finished the day with one carry for seven yards. Expect some more work for Devin Neal and also Taysom Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdcf-d651-a9df-fddfe8210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dre Greenlaw (quad) is active for Week 7 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc6-d99b-a1dd-ffce026d0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw will make his season debut after suffering a quad injury in the summer. He’ll suit up for the Broncos in a matchup against a rejuvenated Giants offense led by Jaxson Dart. Broncos declared LB Jonah Elliss, S J.T. Gray, DT Jordan Jackson, DE Sai’vion Jones, and CB Ja’Quan McMillian inactive against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdc6-d99b-a1dd-ffce026d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (calf/illness) is active for Week 7 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-df81-ab9b-ffff94140000</link>
      <description>Jacobs entered Sunday’s game against the Cardinals as a true questionable due to a calf issue and illness. He was limited due to the illness on Wednesday and Thursday, but practiced in full Friday. Fantasy managers experienced some panic as the Packers listed him as questionable, adding a calf issue to his designation, but the 27-year-old is active. This keeps Emmanuel Wilson on fantasy benches, while Jacobs is a start - even if his workload may be limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdbc-df81-ab9b-ffff94140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders declared WR Deebo Samuel Sr. (heel), WR Terry McLaurin (groin), QB Josh Johnson, LB Ale Kaho, LB Kain Medrano, G Brandon Coleman and T George Fant inactive for Washington’s Week 6 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd6-da18-a39b-ffd772df0000</link>
      <description>Samuel and McLaurin were both ruled out, Samuel on Saturday. Dorance Armstrong (hamstring) is playing off a questionable tag after not practicing in all three sessions this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fdd6-da18-a39b-ffd772df0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
