<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 15:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Giants have “no sense of urgency” with regards to their quarterback situation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4529-d86f-abdd-45bdcf260000</link>
      <description>Specifically, there is no sense of urgency to “to bench Russell Wilson and start rookie Jaxson Dart.” The report only exists, of course, because there is already very much a sense of urgency in the public discourse. Per Schefter, the team is leaving itself wiggle room. “It doesn’t mean a change can’t come soon at the quarterback position, but the Giants would prefer that it not happen anytime soon, according to sources.” That, we believe, but it will come sooner rather than later if Wilson continues to play like he did in the Giants’ opener against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4529-d86f-abdd-45bdcf260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) is expected to play in Week 2 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4818-d294-a19b-ecf801350000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu missed Week 1 after undergoing an emergency procedure late in training camp. He was limited in practice throughout the past week and even got in one light session ahead of Week 1. He now appears to be good to go, which is good news for Bryce Young and the Panthers’ offense. Few teams looked worse than Carolina in Week 1 as they struggled to get anything going versus Jacksonville. With Ekwonu back in the fold, there are no excuses for Young in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4818-d294-a19b-ecf801350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Browns RB Quinshon Judkins will have his snaps “closely monitored” in Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-481f-d86f-abdd-4dbf210c0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added, “Expect him to have the snaps of a backup RB as he ramps up.” Judkins missed all of training camp while away from the team. He was dealing with legal and contract issues throughout the offseason, costing him all of camp and Week 1. He is good to go for Week 2, though it’s safe to assume he is less than familiar with the Browns’ playbook. His conditioning is likely lacking as well, given how little he practiced this summer. The Browns’ backfield is one to avoid for Week 2, but it should become more condensed as the season progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-481f-d86f-abdd-4dbf210c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts EDGE Laiatu Latu (hamstring) is not expected to play in Week 2 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4823-da67-a99f-ccf7fc890000</link>
      <description>The Colts are now down a starting corner in Charvarius Ward and a starting EDGE in Latu. Indy’s first-round pick from 2024, Latu had a quiet rookie season but was already making his presence felt this year with an intercpetion in Week 1. Bo Nix struggled in Week 1 despite the Broncos coming away with the win. He should fare better against the banged-up Colts defense later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4823-da67-a99f-ccf7fc890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “it would not be a surprise” if Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) misses Week 2 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4830-dc44-a9d9-4f767f250000</link>
      <description>Smith hasn’t given much detail on his illness but did say on Thursday he expects to be back in less than three weeks. It’s safe to assume he will miss Week 2, but a Week 3 return to face the Bengals isn’t out of the cards. Theo Jackson and Josh Metellus will start at safety for Minnesota this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4830-dc44-a9d9-4f767f250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports “there is optimism” Jauan Jennings (shoulder) will play in Week 2 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4835-dc44-a9d9-4f77efa50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport still called Jennings a game-time decision, but it’s a step in the right direction for the veteran wideout. Jennings suffered the shoulder injury in San Francisco’s Week 1 win over the Seahawks and barely practiced this week. He got in a single limited session to close the week before being listed as questionable. Healthy or not, Ricky Pearsall may have already passed him in the pecking order for targets after seeing seven looks to Jennings’ five in Week 1. Fantasy managers will need a backup plan if they are counting on Jennings for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4835-dc44-a9d9-4f77efa50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jets TE Mason Taylor (ankle) is expected to play in Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-483d-d294-a19b-ecfd26b70000</link>
      <description>Taylor missed a chunk of training camp with a high-ankle sprain and then suffered another injury in the same ankle in Week 1. The good news is that he managed a full practice on Friday, likely indicating the team was simply playing things safe with the rookie when they held him out of Wednesday’s practice. Taylor was only targeted once in Week 1 despite playing every snap. He isn’t on the fantasy radar right now but could earn more targets as he learns the ropes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-483d-d294-a19b-ecfd26b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewOrleans.Football’s Nick Underhill reports Saints LT Taliese Fuaga (knee) is expected to play in Week 2 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4847-da67-a99f-ccf7e5aa0000</link>
      <description>Fuaga missed Wednesday’s practice, causing some concern that the second-year tackle wouldn’t suit up for Week 2. He returned for two limited sessions and told reporters he was optimistic about his availability for today’s game. Fuaga is good to go and will be protecting Spencer Rattler’s blindside once again this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4847-da67-a99f-ccf7e5aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the 49ers “are not optimistic” that Brock Purdy (toe) will play in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4859-dc44-a9d9-4f7f431f0000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter’s source, “Next week will be tight, but he progressed a lot this week.” Previous reports have said Purdy is dealing with a form of turf toe and could miss as many as five weeks. He has already been ruled out for Week 2. All signs point to Mac Jones getting multiple starts. Jones should be able to execute the basics of Kyle Shanahan’s scheme, putting him in the QB2 mix for fantasy purposes. He should be added in all 2QB and Superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4859-dc44-a9d9-4f7f431f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Shedeur Sanders “let it be known to Baltimore that he didn’t want to be on a roster with Lamar Jackson” during the 2025 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4862-d86f-abdd-4dff414e0000</link>
      <description>According to Schefter, the Ravens were ready to draft Sanders with the No. 141 overall pick before it was conveyed to the team that Sanders did not want to sit behind Jackson. Sanders would have undoubtedly been forced to spend years on the bench had the Ravens drafted him, but he was hardly in a position to negotiate after falling well outside of the first two days of the draft. Sanders wound up in Cleveland via the No. 144 pick and is still nowhere near starting an NFL game. He currently sits at third on the Browns’ depth chart behind Joe Flacco and Dillon Gabriel. While Sanders certainly saw his draft stock plummet for reasons other than his on-field resume, he appears to have shot himself in the foot multiple times during the draft process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4862-d86f-abdd-4dff414e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
