<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught all six targets for 91 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ba-dfde-a1bd-7ebf587e0000</link>
      <description>Andrews ranked second in targets and caught two of the three passing touchdowns from Lamar Jackson, resurrecting his fantasy season in the process. The Ravens managed only 54 offensive plays on a night the Lions dominated the time of possession battle, which helps to explain the modest 27 pass attempts from Jackson. The veteran tight end gets another difficult matchup against Steve Spagnuolo’s Chiefs defense in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74ba-dfde-a1bd-7ebf587e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 5-of-7 targets for 61 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74bc-d6a5-adff-f6fdc5b40000</link>
      <description>Bateman knotted the game at 14 at the end of the second quarter from three yards out, adding the bulk of his yardage in the fourth quarter as the Ravens played from behind. His seven targets marked a season high, keeping him firmly in touchdown-or-bust territory for fantasy managers as bye weeks creep closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74bc-d6a5-adff-f6fdc5b40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 2-of-3 targets for13 yards in the Ravens’ Week 3 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74c6-d93f-ad9d-7ec731e20000</link>
      <description>Flowers was never able to get anything going against an aggressive Lions defense, managing catches of just seven and six yards. The Ravens weren’t able to attack down the field in the face of mounting pressure from the Detroit defensive front, evidenced by the seven sacks taken by quarterback Lamar Jackson. The three targets were a far cry from the 10 targets per game he averaged in the first two games of the season, sending fantasy managers a sharp reminder of his boom or bust nature in this offense. He gets another difficult matchup against the Chiefs in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-74c6-d93f-ad9d-7ec731e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) will miss 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f47-dfde-a1bd-7fcfcad30000</link>
      <description>Tracy went down with an apparently serious shoulder injury during Sunday night’s loss to Kansas City and did not return to the game. Now he could miss up to a month as he recovers from a dislocated shoulder. Cam Skattebo, who had 16 touches for 121 yards and a touchdown against the Chiefs, will function as the Giants’ lead back. Devin Singletary will likely take on RB2 duties, and could be thrust into the RB1 role should Skattebo get dinged up while Tracy is sidelined. Skattebo’s pass game involvement will make him a weekly top-15 fantasy play, starting this week against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f47-dfde-a1bd-7fcfcad30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes it “seems inevitable” that QB Jaxson Dart will take over as the Giants’ starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7705-dfde-a1bd-7f8d59ba0000</link>
      <description>Giants head coach Brian Daboll was noncommittal on Monday when asked if Russell Wilson will keep the team’s starting job after his disastrous Week 3 outing against the Chiefs. “Having left the door wide open to a quarterback change, it seems inevitable that Daboll will walk through it and make the switch to rookie Jaxson Dart,” Duggan said. “But it’s on brand for this regime to lack decisiveness on such a critical decision.” Though ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported before the Giants’ Week 3 meltdown against KC that there was “no urgency” in benching Wilson, the veteran’s performance against the Chiefs may have sealed the deal. He completed just 56 percent of his passes for 160 scoreless yards and two interceptions. He even threw the ball away on fourth and goal in the fourth quarter. Dart would be a boon for Malik Nabers and the rest of the Giants’ pass catchers. He should be rostered in all superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7705-dfde-a1bd-7f8d59ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said the team wouldn’t start J.J. McCarthy (ankle) until he’s fully healthy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-772b-d6a5-adff-f7efac4a0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell said he wouldn’t consider starting McCarthy again until his ankle injury no longer affects his mobility and practice participation. “First and foremost,” O’Connell said, “he’s got to get healthy. And then, I don’t think it’s one of those things where it’s, hey, he’s healthy the night before a game, we’re going to throw him out there and say, ‘Hey, go figure it out’ type of thing.” It was unclear whether McCarthy is guaranteed the starting gig when he’s ready to return to game action. Carson Wentz was serviceable in the Vikings’ Week 3 blowout win against the Bengals, completing 70 percent of his passes for 170 yards and two touchdowns. Only eight quarterbacks had a higher EPA per drop back than Wentz in Week 3. CBS Sports’ Tracy Wolfson reported on Sunday that the Vikings expected McCarthy back for Week 7. If Wentz is playing well and the team is winning, it wouldn’t be a surprise for McCarthy to serve as Wentz’s backup for the remainder of the season after his catastrophic start to the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-772b-d6a5-adff-f7efac4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans head coach Brian Callahan said he’s turning over offensive play-calling duties to QB coach Bo Hardegree.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7751-d93f-ad9d-7fd7a0250000</link>
      <description>The move comes after a miserable start to the 2025 season for Callahan’s offense, which ranks last in yards per play (3.2), second to last in first downs, and second to last in offensive success rate. Cam Ward has struggled mightily in a predictable and somewhat vanilla offensive scheme. Ward has been among the most inaccurate quarterbacks through three games. It’s unclear how the offense might shift under Hardegree, but it would hardly be a surprise if Callahan is fired in the next week weeks, barring a miraculous turnaround for the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7751-d93f-ad9d-7fd7a0250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud reports Mike Evans (hamstring) is expected to miss 3-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7758-d6a5-adff-f7ddfe520000</link>
      <description>Evans reportedly has a “low grade” hamstring issue, the latest in a long string of hamstring woes for the 32-year-old wideout. Evans would seem unlikely to land on injured reserve if the team believes he can come back for Week 7. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler said the hamstring injury “is not considered as bad as last year’s” — which cost Evans three games — and that Evans “plans to work to get back as soon as possible, possibly beating the timeline.” With Evans sidelined, Emeka Egbuka should be an uptick in targets and air yards as the Bucs’ de facto WR1, and a top-12 weekly wideout. Sterling Shepard, who had four receptions for 80 yards last week against the Jets, would likely work as the team’s No. 2 wideout for the next few weeks. Shepard should be rostered in most 12-team leagues for the time being. Chris Godwin (ankle), meanwhile, could make his return to action while Evans is sidelined, further complicating Tampa’s target distribution and pass-catching pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7758-d6a5-adff-f7ddfe520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports QB Jaxson Dart will start in Week 4 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7769-d1b3-a5dd-7779c1730000</link>
      <description>Russell Wilson may have sealed his fate with a fourth quarter throwaway on fourth down on the red zone as the Giants tried to mount a comeback against the Chiefs. Wilson completed just 56 percent of his throws against KC for 160 scoreless yards and two picks. Dart instantly becomes fantasy viable in superflex formats and even some deeper one-QB leagues thanks to his rushing and aggressive play style. Dart completed 32 of 46 passes for 372 yards, three touchdowns, and no interceptions over three preseason affairs. His adjusted completion rate was 78 percent, according to Pro Football Focus. The rookie should provide a boost for Malik Nabers — who leads the NFL in air yards — and Wan’Dale Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7769-d1b3-a5dd-7779c1730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Terry McLaurin “is getting additional opinions” on his injured quad and could miss Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7772-d1b3-a5dd-7773232a0000</link>
      <description>One of the league’s healthiest teams in 2024, Washington is dealing with a string of injuries to important players, including Austin Ekeler (Achilles), Jayden Daniels (knee), and now McLaurin, who left Sunday’s win against the Raiders with a quad issue. That McLaurin, 30, is seeking additional opinions on the injury could mean that he’s in for a multi-week absence. If McLaurin is out for Week 4, Luke McCaffrey could have some deep league appeal after catching three passes for 56 yards and a touchdown against the Raiders. McCaffrey was targeted on a strong 30 percent of his routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7772-d1b3-a5dd-7773232a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
