<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 3-of-4 targets for 25 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 2 win over the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5055-d86f-abdd-55fd27690000</link>
      <description>We wrote Otton’s Week 1 returns off due to positive game script, but it’s harder to do so in a game Baker Mayfield attempted 38 passes. He should continue to play heavy snaps for the Buccaneers but is difficult to trust in managed leagues, until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5055-d86f-abdd-55fd27690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 13-of-24 passes for 207 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ 20-19, Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers, adding 27 yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5057-d86f-abdd-55ff12a30000</link>
      <description>Stroud threw his first touchdown of the season to Nico Collins on the team’s opening possession, largely struggling to move the football for the rest of the game until retaking the lead on a 25-yard Nick Chubb run with just over two minutes remaining in the fourth quarter. The struggles of a piecemeal offensive line continue to be an issue for Stroud, whose team now falls to 0-2 and immediately find themselves looking up at the 2-0 Colts in the AFC South. The Texans also continue to play with little pass-catching help behind Collins in the absence of Tank Dell and Christian Kirk, with no pass-catcher commanding more than four targets against the Buccaneers. Up next for Stroud and the Texans are the Jaguars on the road in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5057-d86f-abdd-55ff12a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Chubb rushed 12 times for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers, adding 29 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-505b-d86f-abdd-55fff2a10000</link>
      <description>Chubb managed just 18 yards on the ground before a 25-yard touchdown run with just over two minutes remaining in the fourth quarter, highlighting Houston’s struggles on the ground behind a struggling offensive line. He did notch a 27-yard reception on the team’s first possession, which would end in a Nico Collins touchdown from 29 yards out on the following play. Chubb remains the lead back for the Texans in the absence of Joe Mixon but is nothing more than a fantasy RB3 with touchdown-driven RB2 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-505b-d86f-abdd-55fff2a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks rushed three times for 14 yards in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers, adding 37 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-505f-d294-a19b-f4ffbd300000</link>
      <description>Marks was clearly the most explosive back for the Texans against a stout run defense. Lead rusher Nick Chubb managed just 18 yards on his first 11 carries before a go-ahead touchdown run from 25 yards out. Marks could eventually usurp the established veteran, but fantasy managers appear for a sizable wait. In the meantime, Marks deserves a spot at the end of fantasy benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-505f-d294-a19b-f4ffbd300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins caught 3-of-9 targets for 52 yards and a touchdown in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5061-da67-a99f-dcf5f4ce0000</link>
      <description>Collins found paint for the first time this season on the team’s first possession, scoring from 29 yards out on a highlight reel catch where he managed to get both feet inbounds along the sideline of the end zone on an over-the-shoulder grab. The 52 yards brings his season total to just 77 through two weeks, highlighting growing concerns for fantasy managers that invested a late first-round pick in the rising star receiver. Collins is likely to be busy once again when the Texans face the Jaguars on the road in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5061-da67-a99f-dcf5f4ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Hutchinson caught 2-of-3 targets for 29 yards in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5065-dc44-a9d9-576742a90000</link>
      <description>Hutchinson continued to see the second most snaps for a Texans team without both Tank Dell and Christian Kirk, but the fantasy returns have not been there for the young receiver. Not only that, but Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel loom on the roster to potentially eat into his role as the season wears on. Either way, fantasy managers can safely return Hutchinson to the waiver wire ahead of a Week 3 meeting with the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5065-dc44-a9d9-576742a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught his only target for 28 yards in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5068-d86f-abdd-55fd60610000</link>
      <description>Higgins played well behind Xavier Hutchinson for the second straight week, leaving both him and fellow rookie Jaylin Noel afterthoughts in the offense even in the absence of both Tank Dell and Christian Kirk. Noel saw no targets in Week 2. Fantasy managers that invested in either rookie wide receiver for the Texans surely are left wanting more, and decisions are going to have to be made on whether or not they deserve a roster spot in leagues with shallow benches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5068-d86f-abdd-55fd60610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 3-of-4 targets for 29 yards in the Texans’ Week 2 loss to the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-506c-d294-a19b-f4fc07550000</link>
      <description>Schultz now has just 57 scoreless yards through two games to start the 2025 campaign, even ceding targets to recent practice squad elevation Harrison Bryant following Cade Stover’s injury. Schultz could eventually return viable counting stats but it has been difficult with the offense struggling to start the season. Fantasy managers are likely forced to hold on and hope for the best moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-506c-d294-a19b-f4fc07550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Mack is questionable to return in Week 2 against the Chargers with an elbow injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5065-dc44-a9d9-576730110000</link>
      <description>Mack headed to the locker room while holding his arm and exiting the contest, and he’ll undergo imaging to determine if there’s any structural damage. The 34-year-old’s status for the remainder of the game — and potentially the coming weeks — should be updated shortly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5065-dc44-a9d9-576730110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Mack (elbow) has been ruled out for the remainder of Monday’s Week 2 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50a0-da67-a99f-dcf5592d0000</link>
      <description>Mack underwent imaging on his elbow, and the results of that testing hasn’t been made public. The 34-year-old defender seems unlikely to be ready to go against the Broncos in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-50a0-da67-a99f-dcf5592d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
