<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine (ankle) is doubtful to return in Week 9 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4603-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb66720000</link>
      <description>Perine suffered a frightening lower body injury on a first half kick return. After writhing in agony for a while, Perine popped up, ran to the Bengals sideline, and sat on the bench, where he cried out in pain as trainers tried to treat his injury. Perine has been splitting the backfield workload with Chase Brown, accounting for a significant number of two minute drill snaps (and routes). Perine’s absence would be a fantasy boon for Brown if he’s forced to miss time with the ankle issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4603-d1e7-a1fa-5eeb66720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is active for Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-460b-d673-a39e-e69bde8c0000</link>
      <description>Both Kamara and Shaheed remained limited throughout all three practices this week. Kamara is a borderline RB2/3 while Shaheed, who injured his hip on the Saints’ final Week 8 drive, is a WR3. Saints CB Alontae Taylor (shoulder) is also active. The Saints declared DT John Ridgeway, DT Khristian Boyd, CB Rejzohn Wright, DB Ugo Amadi, OG Xavier Truss and TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden inactive for Week 9 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-460b-d673-a39e-e69bde8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt suffered a right ankle injury in Los Angeles’ Week 9 game against the Titans and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4612-d673-a39e-e693274c0000</link>
      <description>Rolled up late in the second quarter, Alt required the assistance of a cart to reach the locker room. He appeared rather dismayed, though does not mean it’s a season-ending injury in this case. It does likely mean another multi-week absence, and perhaps a stint on injured reserve after Alt did everything he possibly could to get back quickly from his first ankle sprain. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4612-d673-a39e-e693274c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) exited Week 9 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4609-d673-a39e-e6990b2a0000</link>
      <description>Boutte left Week 9 against the Falcons with a hamstring injury suffered in the first half. He had one target that sailed incomplete on the sideline prior to his exit. Boutte is Drake Maye’s deep target; we will likely see more Mack Hollins while Boutte is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4609-d673-a39e-e6990b2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (ankle) is active for Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4610-d713-ad9e-6e5419f20000</link>
      <description>Nacua injured his ankle while attempting to secure an end zone target in Week 6. He sat out the Rams’ Week 7 game against the Jaguars, but fortunately for the Rams, they were on bye in Week 8, allowing him to miss just one game in two weeks. He should be started as a high-end WR1 against the Saints. The Rams declared QB Stetson Bennett IV, RB Jarquez Hunter, CB Darious Williams, OL Beaux Limmer, OL David Quessenberry and DE Desjuan Johnson inactive for Week 9 against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4610-d713-ad9e-6e5419f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft (knee) is questionable to return in Week 9 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4617-d673-a39e-e69751770000</link>
      <description>Kraft slammed his knee into the back of a Green Bay linemen on a running play and immediately crumpled to the ground. He stayed on the field for a while before limping off the field with the help of trainers. Kraft rode the cart to the locker room after a brief stay in the medical tent. While the team is listing him as questionable, it would be a surprise to see Kraft back on the field today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4617-d673-a39e-e69751770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Rashid Shaheed (hip) is active for Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4610-d45b-affe-579611f10000</link>
      <description>Shaheed injured his hip on the Saints’ final Week 8 drive and remained limited in practice all week. He is good to go, though, and can be started as a WR3. Trade rumors continue to swirl around Shaheed, with the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline looming. It remains to be seen whether the Saints will ultimately choose to move the talented 27-year-old player who is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the season. He possesses the type of downfield receiving talent that could instantly improve a passing offense lacking deep speed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4610-d45b-affe-579611f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 9 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4624-d45b-affe-57b65c080000</link>
      <description>Golden walked to the locker room in the middle of the third quarter before being listed as questionable. The rookie had two catches for nine yards before exiting. With Tucker Kraft also injured, the Packers will lean on Romeo Doubs and Christian Watson in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4624-d45b-affe-57b65c080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud (concussion protocol) left Houston’s Week 9 game against the Broncos and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4626-d673-a39e-e6b7ca5e0000</link>
      <description>Stroud was 6-for-10 for 79 yards before leaving, his helmet hit the turf when he slid late and was hit by Kris Abrams-Draine. Davis Mills took over and will presumably be in the superflex conversation in Week 10 if Stroud can’t clear protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4626-d673-a39e-e6b7ca5e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
