<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught 4-of-4 targets for 30 yards in the Jets’ Week 11 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80b6-d45b-affe-d5b626de0000</link>
      <description>It was business as usual for Taylor, who has now gone for 34 or fewer yards in three of his last four games. The rookie tight end is a reliable safety blanket for Justin Fields, but has seen his fantasy stock slip a bit since his 12-target game against the Cowboys in Week 5 against the Cowboys. Fantasy managers in desperate need of help at tight end should continue to avoid Taylor, who has averaged just 4.8 targets per game since Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80b6-d45b-affe-d5b626de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 9-of-11 targets for 105 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80bb-d45b-affe-d5bf93b80000</link>
      <description>Diggs posted his third 100-plus yard game of the season in Thursday’s win over the Jets while also turning in his second double-digit target performance of the year. The veteran receiver was involved early in this one, hauling in three receptions on the Patriots’ opening drive that ended with a seven-yard touchdown run by TreVeyon Henderson. He later popped up for back-to-back gains of 21 and 18 yards in the third quarter on another drive that ended with a Henderson score, and also hauled in a 22-yard reception early in the fourth quarter. Diggs has gone for 14-151-1 in his last two games on 19 targets and will face a porous Bengals defense in Week 12. He’ll be firmly on the WR2 radar in next week’s game, which should be ripe for fantasy points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80bb-d45b-affe-d5bf93b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught 4-of-5 targets for 64 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c1-d45b-affe-d5d753bb0000</link>
      <description>It wasn’t the 106-yard effort we saw from Hollins in Week 10’s win over the Buccaneers, but the veteran receiver continues to be a reliable target for Drake Maye with Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) sidelined. Hollins made back-to-back big plays on the Patriots’ second possession, ripping off gains of 19 and 20 yards to help set TreVeyon Henderson up for his second rushing score in as many possessions. Hollins has gone for 10-170-0 on 15 targets over the last two weeks and has been targeted on 24.6 percent of his routes over that span. He’ll remain hard to trust outside of deep leagues, but in a plus Week 12 matchup against the Bengals, he’ll have some appeal as a WR4 if Boutte misses a third-straight game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c1-d45b-affe-d5d753bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 3-of-3 targets for 36 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c6-d673-a39e-a4d7b2910000</link>
      <description>Douglas’ three targets were good for fifth-most on the team, as both Hunter Henry and TreVeyon Henderson out-targeted him in this one. The third-year slot receiver converted a key fourth-and-short early in the game, but saw his longest gain of 26 yards come on a third-down catch after a defender failed to touch him once he fell to the ground. Douglas is a reliable, sure-handed slot receiver who is on pace for his worst statistical season since entering the league in 2023. There’s just not enough consistent production to make him a reliable option, meaning fantasy managers can continue to fade him in Week 12 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80c6-d673-a39e-a4d7b2910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 4-of-6 targets for 45 yards in the Patriots’ Week 11 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80cc-d45b-affe-d5deb2330000</link>
      <description>It’s just the second time since Week 5 against the Bills that Henry has surpassed 40 yards, and he has only one touchdown to show for it over that span. Henry remains good for his weekly 4-to-6 targets per game, but could have a chance at a decent Week 12 matchup against a Bengals defense that is allowing the third-most targets per game (9.8) and fourth-most receptions per game (6.8) to opposing tight ends since Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-80cc-d45b-affe-d5deb2330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints owner Gayle Benson said any idea of firing GM Mickey Loomis is “ridiculous.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8278-d45b-affe-d7fe87030000</link>
      <description>Benson added that she is “very pleased with what [Loomis] has accomplished, acquired and is building.” It’s quite the endorsement from a team owner whose team is one loss away from a second consecutive losing season, and is looking like a lock to hold a top-five pick in next year’s draft. Loomis has been with the Saints since 2013 and enjoyed years of success when Sean Payton and Drew Brees were in the building, but things look a bit different now. Last year’s team imploded after an impressive 2-0 start, and this offseason they unexpectedly loss Derek Carr to retirement due to a shoulder injury. With questions still remaining at quarterback and Alvin Kamara entering the twilight of his career, Loomis has plenty to address on offense this offseason, and has a number of aging vets on defense. Benson’s endorsement of him would suggest he’ll be safe entering next offseason, but 2026 could be a true prove-it year for the long-time GM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8278-d45b-affe-d7fe87030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chop Robinson has cleared concussion protocol and will play in Week 11 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-82cb-d45b-affe-d7df25880000</link>
      <description>Robinson suffered a concussion in Week 9 and missed Week 10’s game against the Bills as a result. Now, after logging a full week of practice, Robinson will be good to go for Sunday’s game against the Commanders as the Dolphins look to win back-to-back games for the first time this season. Robinson has totaled eight tackles and one sack for the Dolphins this season and should see plenty of opportunities to get after Marcus Mariota with Jaelan Phillips now in Philly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-82cb-d45b-affe-d7df25880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Chubb (foot) was added to Friday’s injury report and is questionable for Week 11 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8310-d1e7-a1fa-dbfae6220000</link>
      <description>Chubb was a surprise addition to Friday’s report and was listed as limited. It’s never a good sign when a player is added to Friday’s report, so Chubb’s status will be one to watch when inactives are announced 90 minutes before kickoff. The veteran pass rusher has totaled 28 tackles, five sacks, and five TFLs this season after missing all of 2024 due to a torn ACL. If he’s unable to go on Sunday, veteran Matt Judon could see an uptick in snaps after playing in a limited role for most of the season. In addition to Chubb, the Dolphins also listed WR Dee Eskridge (shoulder) and CB Rasul Douglas (foot/ankle) as questionable for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8310-d1e7-a1fa-dbfae6220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) has been ruled out for Week 11’s game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8331-d45b-affe-d7b7ffda0000</link>
      <description>Even with Friday’s practice still to go, McDermott didn’t hesitate to rule out Kincaid, who was a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday and viewed as a long shot to play early in the week. His absence will open the door for Dawson Knox to draw the start in Week 11, but Knox shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a desperation play for fantasy managers. Knox has caught 12 passes for 155 yards and one touchdown this season and hasn’t gone for more than 37 yards in any game. In addition to Kincaid, the Bills also ruled out Phidarian Mathis due to a shoulder injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8331-d45b-affe-d7b7ffda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Khalil Shakir (ankle) is “in a good spot” ahead of Week 11’s game against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8332-d45b-affe-d7b6c2fb0000</link>
      <description>We’ll provide an update on Shakir’s official game status once it’s released, but McDermott is clearly optimistic about Shakir’s Week 11 availability after logging limited practices in back-to-back days to open the week. Shakir led the Bills with seven receptions for 58 yards in last week’s loss to the Dolphins, and would be in line for a sizable role on Sunday against the Buccaneers with Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) already ruled out. We’ll see where things go from there, but Shakir is clearly trending in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8332-d45b-affe-d7b6c2fb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
