<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 03:18:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Drake London (hip) will be day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278c-dab4-a3fb-bffc7d840000</link>
      <description>London was a late addition to the team’s injury report last week and ended up being ruled out before Sunday’s game against the Dolphins. We don’t know much about the severity of his injury, but London was initially removed from the injury report before being added back to it over the weekend and then ruled out. It’s clear the team was hoping he could play through it, so it’s also possible the decision to sit him on Sunday was more so out of precaution. His day-to-day status to open the week suggests he’ll have a good chance of playing in Week 9 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278c-dab4-a3fb-bffc7d840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals released RB Michael Carter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278f-d5d8-a3ff-ffefaa480000</link>
      <description>Fired on his day off. Carter drew the start for the Cardinals in Weeks 5 and 6, and rushed for 18-51-2 in Week 5 against the Titans. Despite the volume, it was a relatively underwhelming day from an efficiency standpoint, which led to him being out-touched by Zonovan Knight the following week. The Cardinals clearly didn’t love what Carter had to offer — or not offer — to a running back room in need of help with James Connor and Trey Benson both sidelined. Zonovan Knight now figures to see a lead role for the Cardinals in Week 9 when they take on a Cowboys defense that has been vulnerable on the ground. Knight could be a volume-based RB2 play in what looks like a plus matchup on paper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-278f-d5d8-a3ff-ffefaa480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dre Greenlaw is eligible to return from suspension in Week 9 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27a7-deb1-a39b-27af9b2b0000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw served his one-game suspension for verbally threatening a referee after the Broncos’ Week 7 comeback win against the Giants. Greenlaw was sidelined for Week 8 as a result of his actions, but should be back and in the starting lineup next week when the Broncos visit the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27a7-deb1-a39b-27af9b2b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he is “very confident” in QB Lamar Jackson being available for Thursday Night Football against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27b7-d245-adfb-b7ff61c50000</link>
      <description>Speaking to media Monday, Harbaugh stated that he was “very confident” in the perennial MVP’s status for Week 9 against the Dolphins on Thursday Night Football. The team has yet to release their initial injury report but it certainly sounds like Jackson is in line to return from a three-game absence, during which the team went 1-2. The improbable win over the Bears kept the team within striking distance in the AFC North, now two games behind the division-leading Steelers. A late-season surge is not out of the question in Baltimore, and a return from Jackson could be just what the team needs to make a run at the playoffs during the second half of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27b7-d245-adfb-b7ff61c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said “it’s too early to say” whether QB Brock Purdy will play in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27c8-dab4-a3fb-bff8a80f0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan didn’t close the door on a potential return to the game-day roster for Purdy but also wasn’t overly confident in Purdy’s status, adding that the team would “see how he’s doing on Wednesday.” Purdy has appeared in just two games this season as he battles a turf toe injury but appears to be inching closer to a return. The 5-2 49ers fell a half game behind both the Seahawks and Rams with the loss in Week 8 to the Texans but remain in a position for a late-season surge towards the playoffs. Fantasy managers will want to track the veteran starter’s status when the team releases their first injury report of the week Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27c8-dab4-a3fb-bff8a80f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders declared QB Jayden Daniels, CB Noah Igbinoghene, K Matt Gay, LB Ale Kaho, T Trent Scott, T George Fant, and TE Colson Yankoff inactive for Week 8 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27cd-d5d8-a3ff-ffed57380000</link>
      <description>Marcus Mariota will start under center for the Commanders for the third time this season after one win and one loss. The Commanders find themselves on the outs in the playoff picture as the midway point in the season approaches, badly needing a win against the surging Chiefs. They will also be without their place kicker as Matt Gay is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27cd-d5d8-a3ff-ffed57380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared CB Kristian Fulton, WR Jalen Royals, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, G Trey Smith, T Josh Simmons, and DE Malik Herring inactive for Week 8 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27de-dab4-a3fb-bffe04a60000</link>
      <description>The offensive linemen were ruled out earlier in the week, something that could expose quarterback Patrick Mahomes to unwanted pressure against a Commanders defense blitzing at the fifth highest frequency this season. Fulton remains sidelined while Mitchell continues to be the odd man out in the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27de-dab4-a3fb-bffe04a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2806-d5d8-a3ff-f96779730000</link>
      <description>Vadels-Scantling signs with the Steelers on an undisclosed contract following a successful visit earlier in the day. MVS was released from the 49ers after four appearances but previously played with Steelers quarterback Aaron Rodgers in Green Bay. It looks like a depth move for a team searching for consistent production from ancillary pieces behind alpha receiver DK Metcalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2806-d5d8-a3ff-f96779730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Broncos CB Patrick Surtain (pectoral) is week-to-week with a strained pectoral.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-280a-deb1-a39b-290e3a760000</link>
      <description>Surtain was unable to finish the team’s Week 8 win over the Cowboys, leaving in the first half what is now known as a pectoral strain. He will miss multiple games with the ailment, likely leaving Kris Abrams-Draine to soak up additional work on the perimeter in the immediate future. Schefter adds that the team is likely to consider injured reserve for the reigning Defensive Player of the Year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-280a-deb1-a39b-290e3a760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota completed 21-of-30 passes for 213 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Commanders’ 28-7, Week 8 loss to the Chiefs, adding 28 yards on eight carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28c9-d245-adfb-bddfa2590000</link>
      <description>Mariota seemed to be doing enough to threaten an upset on the road, passing for 155 yards in the first half in what was a 7-7 game at the break. The wheels fell off the rest of the way with the Commanders failing to move the football with any sort of consistency in the second half. Two turnovers on downs and an interception in the red zone in the first half stalled any momentum, but the Washington defense kept the team in the game - at least enough to keep the team competitive through two frames. The Commanders drop their third straight contest and are now in need of a mid-season intervention, which could come in the form of a return to health of second-year quarterback Jayden Daniels for a difficult test at home against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28c9-d245-adfb-bddfa2590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
