<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers placed LB Junior Colson (shoulder) on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</link>
      <description>Colson started just one game in his rookie season as a 2024 third-round pick, posting a PFF coverage grade of 34.0. He was a possibility to challenge Denzel Perryman for playing time in 2025, but that will go by the wayside now that he’s missing the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed19-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bbc430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed RB Audric Estime to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb76520000</link>
      <description>The second-year back will get a fresh start in Philadelphia, perhaps eventually pushing A.J. Dillon off the roster. Also on Philadelphia’s practice squad are: LB Chance Campbell, WR Elijah Cooks, G Kenyon Green, TE E.J. Jenkins, CB Brandon Johnson, OLB Patrick Johnson, TE Cameron Latu, WR Terrace Marshall, QB Kyle McCord, CB Parry Nickerson, T Hollin Pierce, OLB Antwaun Powell-Ryland, CB Eli Ricks and S Andre Sam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb76520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Mike Reiss reports the Patriots are planning to waive Javon Baker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed37-de13-afdc-efffecac0000</link>
      <description>New England has an open spot on their practice squad and wants Baker back, but he can gauge interest leaguewide before committing to a return. This doesn’t come as a huge surprise given New England’s remaking of the wideout room, and most reports about Baker this offseason believed that he was squarely on the roster bubble after a 1/12 rookie season on four targets. He played 90 offensive snaps in his first year with the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed37-de13-afdc-efffecac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed G Cole Strange and WR Malachi Corley to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3b-db7b-a5dd-ed3f0b7d0000</link>
      <description>Strange picked a great landing spot after getting released yesterday, as the Browns have almost zero starting linemen with guaranteed contracts for 2026. Corley will look to develop his skills and could perhaps challenge for an end-of-roster spot later in the season. The Browns also added QB Bailey Zappe, TE Brendan Bates, TE Sal Cannella, WR Kaden Davis, S Christopher Edmonds, DT Ralph Holley, CB LaMareon James, DT Sam Kamara, RB Ahmani Marshall, DE Julian Okwara and RB Trayveon Williams to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3b-db7b-a5dd-ed3f0b7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed Jacob Cowing (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3f-db7b-a5dd-ed3fe5020000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four games of the season. Cowing dealt with problems in the hamstring throughout training camp and ultimately won’t be able to take advantage of a golden chance while Brandon Aiyuk is out early in the season. The 49ers re-signed P Thomas Morstead to take Cowing’s spot on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed3f-db7b-a5dd-ed3fe5020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed42-de13-afdc-efcb6c1a0000</link>
      <description>It doesn’t sound like he’s in any danger of missing Week 1 at this point. Yosh Nijman would be the backup left tackle if that changed for whatever reason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed42-de13-afdc-efcb6c1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers GM John Lynch said the team is “hopeful but not sure on Week 1" when asked about Jauan Jennings (calf).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed4a-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bd5cb0000</link>
      <description>He additionally noted that the 49ers would not be trading Jennings. It certainly looks like it’s up in the air who will start next to Ricky Pearsall in Week 1, with Marquez Valdes-Scantling and Russell Gage looking like the most likely names at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed4a-dbe3-a9bb-fd5bd5cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals signed QB Brett Rypien to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed75-d332-a1fd-ff7714700000</link>
      <description>He’ll be the third quarterback in Cincinnati this year behind Joe Burrow and Jake Browning. Also joining the Cincinnati practice squad are: RB Gary Brightwell, S Russ Yeast, OT Devin Cochran, OT Andrew Coker, CB Jalen Davis, LB Joe Giles-Harris, G Jaxson Kirkland, CB Bralyn Lux, C Seth McLaughlin, RB Kendall Milton, WR Jordan Moore, LB Maema Njongmeta, DE Isaiah Thomas and WR Isaiah Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed75-d332-a1fd-ff7714700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims (groin) left Wednesday’s practice with an injury and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb95680000</link>
      <description>Per Adam Schefter, the team is “not overly concerned.” Still, it wouldn’t be surprising if his practice time were limited leading up to Week 1. Should Mims be ruled out, Troy Franklin or Pat Bryant could assume a bigger role against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed31-de13-afdc-effb95680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed QB Sam Ehlinger to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed96-db7b-a5dd-ed96b3f50000</link>
      <description>A tale as true as time: the third quarterback was released at last cuts and found his way to the practice squad. Joining Ehlinger on the Broncos practice squad are: G Calvin Throckmorton, CB Reese Taylor, LB Jordan Turner, FB Adam Prentice, WR Michael Bandy, WR A.T. Perry, CB Jaden Robinson, S Delarrin Turner-Yell, ILB Garret Wallow, TE Caleb Lohner, OL Joe Michalski, LB Levelle Bailey and CB Quinton Newsome.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ed96-db7b-a5dd-ed96b3f50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
