<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Giants quarterbacks coach Shea Tierney to the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-06f8-d452-afdd-f7fbe2b30000</link>
      <description>Tierney has spent much of his career with new Titans offensive coordinator Brian Daboll. Starting as an offensive analyst under Daboll at Alabama, Tierney followed him to the Bills as offensive assistant, and then the Giants as quarterbacks coach. He now arrives in Tennessee to partner with Daboll again to develop 2025 No. 1 overall pick Cam Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-06f8-d452-afdd-f7fbe2b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Eagles interviewed Colts offensive coordinator Jim Bob Cooter for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0700-db99-adfc-27d24f2d0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are still searching for their next offensive coordinator, now having interviewed the Colts’ Jim Bob Cooter both virtually and in-person. Cooter is offensive coordinator of the Colts, coaching offenses with rotating quarterbacks and Jonathan Taylor as the constant since 2023. The Eagles bringing him in for a second interview indicates Cooter is a finalist for the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0700-db99-adfc-27d24f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler said he expects the Browns to “shake up” the quarterback room this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0708-d452-afdd-f73bff550000</link>
      <description>In an appearance for ESPN Cleveland radio, Fowler said he would “expect the Browns to add” to the quarterback room in the offseason. Fowler mentioned Alabama draft prospect Ty Simpson and impending free agent Malik Willis as options to “shake up” the quarterback situation under new head coach Todd Monken. Shedeur Sanders and Dillon Gabriel were underwhelming as rookies while Deshaun Watson is still in Cleveland coming off an Achilles injury and still holding a large cap hit. If Fowler’s words are any indication, we could see another name or two added to the mix this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0708-d452-afdd-f73bff550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0748-d452-afdd-f77b28440000</link>
      <description>It is still the week before Super Bowl week, but teams still must release practice report estimations on Wednesday. The Seahawks had Darnold listed as limited due to his oblique injury, no different than his last week of practice. The oblique has not visibly hampered him and a limited listing this early before the Super Bowl indicates Darnold is still good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0748-d452-afdd-f77b28440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots QB Drake Maye (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-074e-d927-a99f-af6ed9a30000</link>
      <description>Maye seemingly injured his right shoulder in the AFC Championship victory over the Broncos, though it does not look to be a major issue. Teams need to release practice reports on Wednesday despite it being the week before the Super Bowl, so the early injury listings should be taken with a grain of salt. However, it is encouraging news that Maye was listed as limited. The 23-year-old is not yet in jeopardy of missing the Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-074e-d927-a99f-af6ed9a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets interviewed former Panthers head coach Frank Reich for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-075b-df77-a39d-475b6d540000</link>
      <description>Reich has been heavily rumored to take over as the Jets’ offensive play-caller since the team let go of offensive coordinator Tanner Engstrand. The 64-year-old was head coach of the Colts for five seasons, followed by one season at the helm of the Panthers, making history as the first head coach to be fired midseason in back-to-back seasons. He was Stanford’s interim head coach for a bit in 2025 and is currently a senior advisor for the program. While Reich looks to be the favorite, the Jets also interviewed former Chargers OC Greg Roman, Dolphins quarterbacks coach Darrell Bevell, Bills quarterbacks coach Ronald Curry, and Cowboys tight ends coach Lunda Wells for their offensive coordinator vacancy. A decision could be expected soon, though given the tumultuous nature of Aaron Glenn’s head coaching tenure, we would not be surprised if the process is lengthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-075b-df77-a39d-475b6d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Ravens wide receivers coach Greg Lewis to the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-07ca-df77-a39d-47cb00780000</link>
      <description>Lewis is a former NFL wide receiver who spent the past three seasons as the Ravens’ wide receivers coach. He previously worked with Titans general manager Mike Borgonzi in Kansas City from 2017-2022, first as receivers coach, then as running backs coach. New head coach Robert Saleh added Brian Daboll as offensive coordinator and is now starting to build the rest of the offensive staff with Lewis’ hire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-07ca-df77-a39d-47cb00780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers hired Western Michigan DC Chris O’Leary to the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-003e-dc7a-af9f-cfbf6e450000</link>
      <description>If that seems random, it’s less so than it appears on the surface, as O’Leary served as the Bolts’ safeties coach in 2024. O’Leary apparently earned internal raves for his 2024 work with Derwin James, then went on to coordinator one of the nation’s best scoring defenses at Western Michigan. Before his Chargers and WMU stops, O’Leary spent six seasons at Notre Dame. It’s a somewhat outside-the-box hire, but a seemingly good one for a team tasked with replacing Jesse Minter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-003e-dc7a-af9f-cfbf6e450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Broncos defensive passing game coordinator and assistant head coach Jim Leonhard for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0688-db99-adfc-26daae330000</link>
      <description>Leonhard was an NFL safety for 10 years, including a season with the Ravens, before becoming a coach. He coached college ball, primarily at Wisconsin, for eight years before joining the Broncos. With Denver’s defense emerging as one of the league’s best units over the past two seasons, Leonhard now has multiple teams reaching out to him about their defensive coordinator vacancies. He also has an interview with the Bills lined up. Leonhard would join Jesse Minter, another rising star among defensive coaches, if he lands the Baltimore job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0688-db99-adfc-26daae330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Commanders defensive pass game coordinator Jason Simmons will join the Steelers “in a prominent defensive role.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-09ea-d452-afdd-fffb6fdb0000</link>
      <description>Simmons originally interviewed for the Steelers’ defensive coordinator vacancy, but that role went to Patrick Graham. Now Simmons will reunite with Graham and head coach Mike McCarthy. Simmons got his start as a coach in Green Bay and wound up spending nearly a decade there. He has since held the title of defensive pass game coordinator for the Panthers, Raiders, and Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-09ea-d452-afdd-fffb6fdb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
