<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 23:03:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Turron Davenport believes the Titans could use more run-pass options with Cam Ward in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1038-d042-afbc-7dfa7d600000</link>
      <description>Davenport points out that Brian Daboll ran RPOs on 12.6 percent of their plays last year, fourth-most in the league, and notes that Ward had a lot of success running them in college at Miami. We don’t know that Ward is an upper-tier NFL athlete in space, but every bit of rushing production could help him for fantasy football purposes. Perhaps being in a scheme he’s more familiar with could help as well. Ward, who sprained his AC joint in the Titans’ Week 18 loss to Jacksonville, does not currently have a timetable to return to the field but Titans GM Mike Borgonzi said he was “doing well.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1038-d042-afbc-7dfa7d600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos completed an interview with Commanders assistant head coach and pass game coordinator Brian Johnson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1061-d89c-a1be-bfff85340000</link>
      <description>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn brought Johnson aboard less than two weeks after being hired, back in February 2024. Johnson served as the Eagles’ quarterbacks coach from 2021-2022 before being promoted to offensive coordinator in 2023. Johnson took the same employment path at Florida before that, going from the quarterbacks coach in 2018-2019 to offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1061-d89c-a1be-bfff85340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury is “expected to be in the mix” for the Giants offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1068-d355-a5bd-9f7cc0c20000</link>
      <description>Jim Bob Cooter and Alex Tanney will get interviews over the weekend, but Kingsbury is at the top of Raanan’s list in this article. Kingsbury interviewed for the Giants head coaching vacancy already, and though it would perhaps seem a strange fit with John Harbaugh, it’s possible that Kingsbury is running out of better non-Ravens options this offseason as the Chiefs, Lions, Chargers, Eagles, Buccaneers, Titans, Dolphins and Falcons have already all filled vacancies and the only unsettled head-coaching situations are in Las Vegas and Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1068-d355-a5bd-9f7cc0c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor reports the Chiefs are “expected” to have a new starting running back for the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-106e-d042-afbc-7dfe482e0000</link>
      <description>He drops this in a note about Kansas City’s lack of explosion in 2025, a year in which impending free agent Isiah Pacheco was not able to manage a single run of 20 or more yards. New OC Eric Bieniemy, per Taylor, “will be tasked with putting together the correct run-blocking scheme for the Chiefs.” With both Pacheco and Kareem Hunt impending free agents and only gadget back Brashard Smith under contract, this report is not much of a surprise. The Chiefs will likely contend for one of the better free agent backs in this class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-106e-d042-afbc-7dfe482e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL is projecting the salary cap to increase from $279.2 million in 2025 to more than $300 million in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1061-d424-a3fd-f7795c910000</link>
      <description>The exact range is said to be $301.2 million to $305.7 million per club. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero notes that this is nearly $100 million more than the $208.2 million salary cap in 2022. The exact number will be finalized before free agency begins on March 11th.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1061-d424-a3fd-f7795c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed GM Brian Gutekunst to a contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1081-d042-afbc-7dd300520000</link>
      <description>Terms were not announced, but this was the expected outcome even after Green Bay’s playoff meltdown against the Bears in the Wild Card round. Gutekunst has done a great job of getting a wide base of talent for the Packers, and finally shook the “lack of star power” haters with a fearless trade for Micah Parsons before the season. Now without a first-round pick, the Packers will hope they can build enough talent around Jordan Love and Parsons for the team to be trending in the right direction for next year’s playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1081-d042-afbc-7dd300520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions GM Brad Holmes said that OC Drew Petzing will call plays in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1085-d89c-a1be-bfdf1c160000</link>
      <description>Well, what he really said was “look, it’s his offense. It’s not something where he’s got to do something else or be like – this is his show, man.” Holmes praised Petzing’s “impressive” job calling plays despite Arizona’s personnel issues and noted that Petzing isn’t married to a system so much as a philosophy to “maximize personnel of what’s available.” We’re not totally sold on Petzing’s work in Arizona, but it’s clear that NFL decision makers saw it differently. How the Lions change schematically in Petzing’s view will be a very real question over the next six months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1085-d89c-a1be-bfdf1c160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired Bears offensive coordinator Declan Doyle as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-10c3-d355-a5bd-9fd7aca00000</link>
      <description>It’s a bit of a surprise because Doyle removed his name from consideration for the Eagles job ... but this is Lamar Jackson. The Ravens were able to interview Doyle for a “lateral” move by giving him control of the playcalling. Doyle, who was on Sean Payton’s staff in Denver before being poached by Ben Johnson to the offensive coordinator role, has some powerful roots in some of the NFL’s best offenses. He also has never called plays before and was born in 1996, so there is some risk here. The Ravens are betting on pedigree. We’ll be fascinated to see what Doyle says at his introductory presser, as Baltimore’s focus on offense could raise or lower ceilings for some of the most high-profile players in the fantasy game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-10c3-d355-a5bd-9fd7aca00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter said Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak is “definitely” getting either the Raiders or Cardinals’ head-coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1083-d424-a3fd-f79bef2c0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders and Cardinals were among the first five teams to ask for interviews with Kubiak. He has consistently been linked to the Raiders, and co-owner Tom Brady has notably called multiple Seahawks games as of late. Kubiak impressed viewers early in 2024, running a then-healthy Saints offense that was eventually hampered by injuries down the stretch. Fortunately, the Seahawks’ offense has largely enjoyed good health this season, allowing Kubiak to establish himself as a top-tier play caller. Across the full season, the Seahawks rank fourth in yards per play (5.9) and second in yards per pass play (8.49).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-1083-d424-a3fd-f79bef2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Seth Wickersham and Brady Henderson reports that the Paul G. Allen Trust will put the Seahawks up for sale after Super Bowl LX.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-10de-d042-afbc-7dde98230000</link>
      <description>Allen’s sister, Jody Allen, is the executor of the trust and has a “directive from her late brother to eventually sell both [the Seahawks and Trail Blazers] and donate the proceeds to charity.” Per the report, “Sportico values the Seahawks at $6.59 billion” and “one team executive told ESPN that the Seahawks could fetch $7 billion to $8 billion.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-10de-d042-afbc-7dde98230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
