<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:02:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 5-of-9 targets for 65 yards in the Colts’ Week 16 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49a4-d56e-afff-efec0a3f0000</link>
      <description>Downs tied with rookie tight end Tyler Warren for the team lead in targets and ranked behind only Alec Pierce in receiving yardage, relied on heavily out of the slot against the heavy zone rates of the 49ers. The 2025 season was not as kind to Downs’ fantasy managers as initially thought heading into the year, with Warren’s breakout a large reason why. He’ll enter the final year of his rookie contract in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49a4-d56e-afff-efec0a3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman caught 4-of-5 targets for 32 yards in the Colts’ Week 16 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49a8-d968-a19b-59f9473f0000</link>
      <description>Pittman trailed rookie tight end Tyler Warren and slot receiver Josh Downs in targets while Alec Pierce erupted for two touchdowns, routinely finding it difficult to shake free on the perimeter against the zone-heavy 49ers. Veteran quarterback Philip Rivers simply relied heavily on his targets over the middle of the field, something that could change if the team elects to turn back to Riley Leonard under center for the final two games of the regular season now that they are eliminated from the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49a8-d968-a19b-59f9473f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 3-of-9 targets for 30 yards in the Colts’ Week 16 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49ab-d35e-a1bf-4deb46d40000</link>
      <description>Warren tied for the team lead with nine targets, his second consecutive game leading the team in targets with Philip Rivers under center. That could change for the final two weeks of the regular season with the Colts now eliminate from the playoffs, potentially turning back to rookie Riley Leonard to finish out the season. Either way, Warren remains one of the more intriguing young tight ends in the league and appears primed to return significant value for dynasty managers moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-49ab-d35e-a1bf-4deb46d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Brooke Pryor reports DK Metcalf’s suspension could void $45 million in contract guarantees.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4b7e-d56e-afff-effee8930000</link>
      <description>Metcalf plans on appealing the two-game suspension that was handed down after his altercation with a fan in Detroit on Sunday. Metcalf said the fan, Ryan Kennedy, used a racial slur — an accusation Kennedy has denied through a lawyer. Metcalf had reported Kennedy to Seahawks team security in a previous trip to Detroit to play the Lions before he was traded to the Steelers. If the two-game suspension is upheld, the Steelers offense will likely revert to a run-heavy approach for the final two games of the regular season against the Browns and Ravens. Calvin Austin and Adam Thielen could see an uptick in targets, along with Kenneth Gainwell and Darnell Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4b7e-d56e-afff-effee8930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said RB TreVeyon Henderson is in the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c05-d968-a19b-5cf5460f0000</link>
      <description>Henderson suffered the head injury in the first half on Sunday night against the Ravens and did not return to the game. He could very well miss Week 17 against a miserable Jets defense that has been more than generous to opposing backs in recent weeks. Rhamondre Stevenson, who had eight carries for 51 yards and a touchdown against Baltimore in Week 16, would profile as a must-play option in 12-team formats if Henderson is sidelined. Both backs are in play for Week 17 if Henderson clears the protocol and suits up against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c05-d968-a19b-5cf5460f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said WR Kayshon Boutte is in the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c09-d56e-afff-eee93f6b0000</link>
      <description>Boutte sustained the head injury in Week 16 against the Ravens while catching four passes for 35 yards. He would appear to be highly questionable to Week 17 against a Jets secondary that ranks among the worst in the league. If Boutte is sidelined, Mack Hollins — who ranks fourth in the NFL in air yards over the past three weeks — would be an excellent flex play for Week 17. Kyle Williams, who caught a touchdown in Week 16’s win, would have some deep league appeal if Boutte is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c09-d56e-afff-eee93f6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars head coach Liam Coen said the offense has not “changed a single thing” since the summer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c23-d35e-a1bf-4de354a50000</link>
      <description>“We haven’t changed a single thing from the moment we started coaching him,” Coen said when asked by reporters if the team’s offense had been tweaked ahead of Trevor Lawrence’s recent heater, which includes 12 total touchdowns over his past three games. “Sometimes, it just takes time to click.” Lawrence, according to Coen, showed more comfort with progressions and reads around Week 10 after a somewhat shaky start to the season. The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports the acquisition of Jakobi Meyers has been a key to Lawrence’s emergence as an elite QB. Meyers’ “command over the middle of the field, coupled with tight end Brenton Strange’s return, has helped receivers like Brian Thomas Jr. and Parker Washington produce outside the numbers,” Howe said. “Beyond that, Lawrence’s footwork has also been cleaner, and he’s cut back on unnecessary off-platform throws. It’s all tied into confidence in his reads and progressions.” Lawrence will have a good shot to keep his hot streak going in Week 17 against a listless Colts defense that gave up 295 yards and five touchdowns to Brock Purdy on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c23-d35e-a1bf-4de354a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said DK Metcalf will appeal his two-game suspension on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c38-d35e-a1bf-4dfa1a770000</link>
      <description>Metcalf’s appeal comes one day after the NFL suspended him for two games following an altercation with a fan during the Steelers’ Week 16 win against the Lions. Metcalf said the fan, Ryan Kennedy, used a racial slur — an accusation Kennedy has denied through a lawyer. Metcalf had reported Kennedy to Seahawks team security in a previous trip to Detroit to play the Lions before he was traded to the Steelers. “He did explain to me why he did what he did,” Tomlin said of Metcalf. “I certainly don’t condone the behavior, but I support DK.” Metcalf would miss the team’s final two regular season games and return for the playoffs if the two-game punishment stands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c38-d35e-a1bf-4dfa1a770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said WR Roman Wilson could see more opportunities if DK Metcalf misses the regular season’s final two games.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c4d-d56e-afff-eeedf4b10000</link>
      <description>It’s a strange thing to say about a wideout who has been a healthy scratch for three straight weeks as veteran journeyman Adam Thielen plays ahead of him. Tomlin said if Metcalf’s two-game suspension is upheld this week, Wilson — who has 166 yards and two touchdowns this season — will have a chance “to show his professionalism and his readiness and how he’s been sharpening his sword for battle.” Calvin Austin III and Thielen could also see an increase in routes and targets if Metcalf if out in Week 17 against the Browns. The Steelers are likely to revert to a run-heavy offense without their top receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c4d-d56e-afff-eeedf4b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice (concussion) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c5c-d968-a19b-5cfdffb50000</link>
      <description>It’s not a great sign for Rice’s Christmas Day availability against the Broncos. Rice was sidelined last week against the Titans with the head injury, and the Chiefs have little reason to rush him back into game action with their season lost. Xavier Worthy will continue operating as the Chiefs’ de facto WR1 while Rice is out, though Worthy remains a deep league-online option for Week 17 against Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c5c-d968-a19b-5cfdffb50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
