<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:29:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (chest) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36e6-d1e7-a1fa-7eee03a10000</link>
      <description>Darnold should be good to go, following the Seahawks’ Week 8 bye. The Seahawks’ passing offense is averaging a league-best 9.03 yards per play and can be expected to keep the momentum going against the Commanders on Sunday. Darnold is playing extremely well in his first season with the Seahawks and can be treated as a borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36e6-d1e7-a1fa-7eee03a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp (heel/hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36e7-d673-a39e-b6f71f350000</link>
      <description>Kupp was a full participant coming out of the Seahawks’ Week 8 bye yesterday, though he was only listed only with the heel injury. Thursday’s injury report suggests Kupp injured his hamstring in practice today, which jeopardizes his availability for the Seahawks’ Week 9 game against the Commanders. Anything is possible, but Kupp is sitting on the wrong side of questionable as of Thursday afternoon. Seahawks No. 4 WR Jake Bobo was also added to the injury report with an Achilles injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36e7-d673-a39e-b6f71f350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe that Lamar Jackson (hamstring) will have no “limitations” in Week 9 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3765-d713-ad9e-7f759a080000</link>
      <description>Well, well, well. Lookout, Russell Wilson. There’s a new Mr. Unlimited in town. Jackson reportedly wanted to wait until he was 100.0 percent healthy before returning. He does so tonight against a fantasy-friendly Dolphins defense allowing the fourth-most yards per carry (4.0) in the NFL. Jackson should be started as an elite, dual-threat QB1 tonight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3765-d713-ad9e-7f759a080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Jayden Daniels (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-376a-d713-ad9e-7f7e14a40000</link>
      <description>Daniels has now practiced in full twice this week, putting him firmly on track to play in Week 9 against the Seahawks. Daniels’ participation levels indicate fantasy managers can expect him to operate as his typically efficient dual-threat self this weekend. He should return to fantasy lineups as an elite QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-376a-d713-ad9e-7f7e14a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Puka Nacua (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-376b-d1e7-a1fa-7feb3b7f0000</link>
      <description>Nacua is firmly on track to play in Week 9 against the Saints. Players coming off multi-week injuries carry re-injury risk, but Nauca also possesses one of the highest ceilings in fantasy football. Assuming he is good to go, he should be locked into starting lineups against a fantasy-friendly Saints defense. He is an elite WR1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-376b-d1e7-a1fa-7feb3b7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Titans WR Calvin Ridley and OLB Arden Key could be traded before the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3774-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe23a60000</link>
      <description>Rapoport kept the segment brief, simply listing the two players as trade candidates in the coming days. The Titans are looking ahead to 2026, and their young receiving corps, featuring WRs Chimere Dike and Elic Ayomanor, along with TE Gunnar Helm, has shown promise. Unfortunately, Ridley (hamstring) and Key (quadricep) are both hurt, but if the team is set on acquiring future assets, they could be willing to send them packing cheaply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3774-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe23a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Jets RB Breece Hall and DL Quinnen Williams are “drawing interest” from other teams ahead of the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3774-d45b-affe-77f671600000</link>
      <description>Reports on Hall’s availability and outside interest have swirled for weeks now, with reports most recently indicating that the Jets could re-sign him for 2026. Williams, 24, is a three-time defending Pro Bowl player, so his price is unlikely to be cheap. He currently leads all Jets defenders with 19 quarterback pressures and could instantly star on any defensive line. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3774-d45b-affe-77f671600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel is “on the hot seat.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-375d-d673-a39e-b7ddfc500000</link>
      <description>Rapoport adds that Dolphins owner Stephen Ross “likes” and “believes in” McDaniel, but that only counts for so much. McDaniel’s job status will reportedly depend on the players’ response to McDaniel’s leadership from here on out. Rapoport lists locker room demeanor and player effort among the top factors in Ross’ continued assessments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-375d-d673-a39e-b7ddfc500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that CB Riq Woolen is “more likely that not to remain” with the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3743-d673-a39e-b7d31d740000</link>
      <description>Woolen has been the subject of trade rumors for roughly one month, but the Seahawks are choosing to preserve their defensive back depth. The unit has been banged up quite a bit this season and Seattle has playoff aspirations. While Woolen’s play has been up and down, he remains a capable starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3743-d673-a39e-b7d31d740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Ben Baby reports that Bengals DT McKinnley Jackson has requested a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-379c-d45b-affe-779e97370000</link>
      <description>Jackson’s 2024 rookie season was negatively impacted by a knee injury suffered in training camp, but he returned in time to play in 13 games, notching 15 tackles, one sack and one forced fumble. Jackson is frustrated with his role, having been a healthy scratch for six of the team’s first eight games this season. Jackson joins a long line of disgruntled Bengals defenders who have taken issue with everything from salary to playing time. EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) remains a trade candidate after battling the front office for a new deal this offseason. LB Logan Wilson has requested a trade after losing his job to a pair of rookies, and earlier this week, the team reached a noninjury settlement with DT Mike Pennel, granting him a release. He signed with the Chiefs shortly thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-379c-d45b-affe-779e97370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
