<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said Kenneth Walker is “showing that he’s earning more opportunities to get the ball.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</link>
      <description>Walker out-snapped Zach Charbonnet on Sunday, playing 43 snaps to Charbonnet’s 36. Over the last three weeks, he has 99 snaps to Charbonnet’s 77. Macdonald’s comments create the possibility that there’s more ceiling to Walker going forward this season, perhaps something closer to 70-30 than 60-40 with Charbonnet. “I think you really felt Ken (Sunday),” Macdonald said. “And just, even in the pass game, too, on check-downs, finding him late in the play. Just shows you that he’s such an explosive player with the ball in his hands.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9851-d713-ad9e-fc55a9290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said “I wanted to get the ball to Brock a bunch and see what he could do. ... I’m responsible for that,” when asked about the Raiders’ pass-heavy approach in Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9859-d45b-affe-dddf3b1a0000</link>
      <description>He added, in words that are a dagger to Ashton Jeanty owners: “I don’t really care about pleasing people with our run/pass mix. I’m trying to move the football.” And as bad as Geno Smith has been this year, it’s hard to argue with the fact that Jeanty had nowhere to go on Sunday with just seven yards on his six carries. It’s possible the Raiders will lean into being a pass-first offense down the stretch, something that would be music to the ears of Bowers-reliant managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9859-d45b-affe-dddf3b1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Khalil Shakir (personal) was excused from practice for personal reasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9861-d673-a39e-bcf18cbb0000</link>
      <description>He also did not participate in Monday’s practice for personal reasons. If this were a non-TNF game, we probably wouldn’t post about this, but zero practices two days in to the week is mildly concerning even if Shakir isn’t hurt. It’s at least in the range of outcomes that he misses this game and further throws the Bills receiving corps into chaos in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9861-d673-a39e-bcf18cbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said C.J. Stroud (concussion) will not play in Houston’s Week 12 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</link>
      <description>This did seem to the way it was going for most of the week, even with Stroud returning to practice today. The good news is that a return against the Colts in Week 13 seems plausible for Stroud, who has now missed three full games with this concussion suffered against the Broncos in Week 9. Davis Mills will shepherd the Texans through Thursday Night Football against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-987f-d673-a39e-bcffebd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said he’s “optimistic” about Jaylen Warren (ankle) playing in Week 12 but said he’ll be limited early in the week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</link>
      <description>He added that Warren was cleared to return to the game by trainers, but that the Steelers opted not to chance anything. The story here seems to be the Steelers just taking it easy on their best back. We’ll probably see him limited on Wednesday, possibly Thursday as well, but we’re expecting him to play in Week 12 based on everything we’ve seen to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-988a-d1e7-a1fa-daeab6fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said “we’ll see where the week goes” when asked about Will Howard getting first-team reps in practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-989d-d45b-affe-dd9fa7f40000</link>
      <description>Howard missed the entire preseason thanks to a fractured pinkie finger, so the Steelers probably would like to evaluate him to some extent with the extra time that Aaron Rodgers (wrist) vacates in practice. There’s no indication that Mason Rudolph won’t be the starter in Week 12 if Rodgers is ruled out, but it probably says something about how the Steelers feel about Howard’s long-term projection that there’s discussion about him seeing some first-team reps in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-989d-d45b-affe-dd9fa7f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions activated LB Malcolm Rodriguez (knee) from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98cb-d45b-affe-dddf2f760000</link>
      <description>His 21-day window was up, so Rodriguez had to be activated today or lost for the season. Rodriguez practiced in full all last week on the injury report and should be a good bet to be active right away in Week 12 for the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98cb-d45b-affe-dddf2f760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (ankle) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98d2-d1e7-a1fa-dafae1240000</link>
      <description>He’ll more than likely be good to go for the Texans on Thursday night. Collins was limited on Monday. He’ll be on the WR1/WR2 borderline against the Bills after being the target on 36 Davis Mills passes over the last three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98d2-d1e7-a1fa-dafae1240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (shoulder) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e7-d713-ad9e-fcf7e7880000</link>
      <description>He’ll likely be removed from the injury report on Wednesday. Schultz was limited on Monday and has been managed for most of the last three weeks with shoulder soreness. He’ll be in line for a low-end fantasy TE1 role against the Bills on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e7-d713-ad9e-fcf7e7880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans G Ed Ingram (knee) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e9-d713-ad9e-fcfd26760000</link>
      <description>After missing each of the last two games with a knee injury, Ingram looks likely to go on Thursday night. Ingram has posted back-to-back full practices this week. Tytus Howard (ankle/knee) and Trent Brown (hand/knee) were both limited participants on Monday and Tuesday and also look to be trending towards playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-98e9-d713-ad9e-fcfd26760000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
