<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 01:30:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Rams and Steelers have requested an interview with Browns special teams coordinator Bubba Ventrone.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05b9-d452-afdd-f7bbcd800000</link>
      <description>Pelissero said Ventrone, widely seen as one of the NFL’s best special teams coaches, is not expected to stay on with new Cleveland head coach Todd Monken, who will presumably clean house and bring in his own coaches for 2026. The Rams in 2025 had what was by most measures the worst special teams unit while the Steelers were mostly middle of the pack in special teams metrics. Ventrone’s Browns allowed the seventh most yards per kickoff return and the fifth most yards per punt return in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05b9-d452-afdd-f7bbcd800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers hired former Bills defensive coordinator Bobby Babich as their defensive pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05ca-d452-afdd-f7fbd74c0000</link>
      <description>Babich will also hold the title of secondary coach. He joins the Packers after serving two years as the Bills’ DC. Babich previously interviewed for the Packers’ DC opening but chose to stay in Buffalo for a promotion. He will work under Jonathan Gannon in Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05ca-d452-afdd-f7fbd74c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Gardner Minshew did not suffer a torn ACL and “already is back to full strength.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05ed-db99-adfc-27fff1890000</link>
      <description>Minshew was initially believed to have suffered a torn ACL in Week 16. The issue would have sidelined him for much of 2026, if not the entire season. Per Schefter, it was just a bone bruise that did not require surgery. Minshew did not suffer any long-term damage from the injury. Minshew will head into free agency with a clean bill of health. At just 29 years old, Minshew should have no issues finding another backup gig in the spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-05ed-db99-adfc-27fff1890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sports’ Greg Auman reports the Bucs talked to former Bills head coach Sean McDermott about joining the team’s staff.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0611-df77-a39d-4751937b0000</link>
      <description>McDermott crossed paths with Bucs GM Jason Licht nearly two decades ago when both men were with the Eagles. It’s unclear what role the Bucs had in mind for McDermott, but it’s a moot point. He is expected to take the year off and evaluate potential openings in 2027. We fully expect him to find another job as a head coach at that time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0611-df77-a39d-4751937b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns hired former Ravens offensive line coach George Warhop for the same position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0670-d452-afdd-f773c9fb0000</link>
      <description>Warhop will follow new Browns head coach Todd Monken from Baltimore to Cleveland. He has held the role of OL coach for three decades across nine teams. He previously coached in Cleveland from 2009 to 2013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0670-d452-afdd-f773c9fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans hired Giants quarterbacks coach Shea Tierney to the same role.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-06f8-d452-afdd-f7fbe2b30000</link>
      <description>Tierney has spent much of his career with new Titans offensive coordinator Brian Daboll. Starting as an offensive analyst under Daboll at Alabama, Tierney followed him to the Bills as offensive assistant, and then the Giants as quarterbacks coach. He now arrives in Tennessee to partner with Daboll again to develop 2025 No. 1 overall pick Cam Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-06f8-d452-afdd-f7fbe2b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Eagles interviewed Colts offensive coordinator Jim Bob Cooter for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0700-db99-adfc-27d24f2d0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles are still searching for their next offensive coordinator, now having interviewed the Colts’ Jim Bob Cooter both virtually and in-person. Cooter is offensive coordinator of the Colts, coaching offenses with rotating quarterbacks and Jonathan Taylor as the constant since 2023. The Eagles bringing him in for a second interview indicates Cooter is a finalist for the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0700-db99-adfc-27d24f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler said he expects the Browns to “shake up” the quarterback room this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0708-d452-afdd-f73bff550000</link>
      <description>In an appearance for ESPN Cleveland radio, Fowler said he would “expect the Browns to add” to the quarterback room in the offseason. Fowler mentioned Alabama draft prospect Ty Simpson and impending free agent Malik Willis as options to “shake up” the quarterback situation under new head coach Todd Monken. Shedeur Sanders and Dillon Gabriel were underwhelming as rookies while Deshaun Watson is still in Cleveland coming off an Achilles injury and still holding a large cap hit. If Fowler’s words are any indication, we could see another name or two added to the mix this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0708-d452-afdd-f73bff550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0748-d452-afdd-f77b28440000</link>
      <description>It is still the week before Super Bowl week, but teams still must release practice report estimations on Wednesday. The Seahawks had Darnold listed as limited due to his oblique injury, no different than his last week of practice. The oblique has not visibly hampered him and a limited listing this early before the Super Bowl indicates Darnold is still good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0748-d452-afdd-f77b28440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots QB Drake Maye (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-074e-d927-a99f-af6ed9a30000</link>
      <description>Maye seemingly injured his right shoulder in the AFC Championship victory over the Broncos, though it does not look to be a major issue. Teams need to release practice reports on Wednesday despite it being the week before the Super Bowl, so the early injury listings should be taken with a grain of salt. However, it is encouraging news that Maye was listed as limited. The 23-year-old is not yet in jeopardy of missing the Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-074e-d927-a99f-af6ed9a30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
