<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (groin) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2be-d90e-a9da-dfbfa90d0000</link>
      <description>Barkley was listed as a limited practice participant for the second straight day. On a short week ahead of a Friday game against the Bears, it is possible the Eagles are keeping Barkley’s reps limited to keep him healthy. Still, fantasy managers should keep an eye on tomorrow’s final practice report to see if Barkley is good to go, or if Tank Bigsby will get a shot at starting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2be-d90e-a9da-dfbfa90d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Kenneth Walker (glute) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c0-db57-afda-d6f285ed0000</link>
      <description>Walker was dealing with the glute issue last week, but played to the tune of 14 touches in Week 12. He starts out the week limited and is still trending to play Week 13. RB George Holani (hamstring) did not practice. The running back injuries have led the Seahawks to add Cam Akers; Holani may be out an extended period of time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c0-db57-afda-d6f285ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c4-d90e-a9da-dfcfb29b0000</link>
      <description>Nwosu pops up with a new ankle issue that keeps him out of Wednesday’s practice. Also not practicing was S Ty Okada (oblique), who suffered the injury in Week 12. Both defensive players will need to log some practice time later in the week to have a shot at playing in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c4-d90e-a9da-dfcfb29b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Devin Neal (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c8-d90e-a9da-dfcf69140000</link>
      <description>Neal pops up with an ankle issue in a week he is slated to start for the Saints. With Alvin Kamara (MCL) leaving hurt, Neal got the bulk of backfield carries in Week 12 and is in line to start ahead of Audric Estime in Week 13. However, the ankle injury bears monitoring as ankle injuries can bloom into larger issues. Given he was a limited participant, Neal is still slated to play Week 13 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2c8-d90e-a9da-dfcf69140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (shoulder) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d4-db57-afda-d6f6cc170000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon was placed on injured reserve after Week 2 with a shoulder injury. He revealed on Wednesday it was a scapula injury and the Rams activated the 30-year-old off injured reserve this week. Witherspoon is trending to play Week 13 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d4-db57-afda-d6f6cc170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn (concussion) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d7-d82c-a79a-f3d781120000</link>
      <description>Horn and LB Claudin Cherelus both did not practice due to concussions suffered in Week 12. It will be a tall task to pass protocol to play in Week 13. Also not practicing was LB Christian Rozeboom (hip/hamstring). The Panthers will enter Week 13 against the Rams banged up defensively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d7-d82c-a79a-f3d781120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers OG Chandler Zavala (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d9-d90e-a9da-dfdfc71d0000</link>
      <description>Zavala suffered the calf injury in Panthers’ Week 12 loss to the 49ers and starts out the week not practicing. Also out was C Cade Mays (ankle). Jake Curhan and Austin Corbett are in line to start for Zavala and Mays, respectively, if neither can play in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2d9-d90e-a9da-dfdfc71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams EDGE Byron Young (knee) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2dc-db57-afda-d6fe56d10000</link>
      <description>Rams S Kamren Kinchens (shoulder) also did not practice. Both Young and Kinchens are starters and key contributors to the Rams defense, so losing both would leave the team short-handed against the Panthers in Week 13. They will need to log practice time in order to have a chance at playing on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2dc-db57-afda-d6fe56d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing officer Derrick Brooks upheld Panthers S Tre’von Moehrig’s one-game suspension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2df-d6c4-abfb-d6df307e0000</link>
      <description>Moehrig was suspended for punching 49ers WR Jauan Jennings in the groin in the Panthers’ loss to the 49ers on Monday night. He appealed the suspension, but hearing officer Derrick Brooks, jointly appointed by the NFL and NFLPA, denied his appeal and upheld the suspension. Moehrig will now miss Week 13 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c2df-d6c4-abfb-d6df307e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs (knee) feels “pretty close to 100 percent” for Week 13’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5b8-d82c-a79a-f7bcb7900000</link>
      <description>If true, fantasy managers can expect Jacobs to see his full assortment of touches. After missing Week 12’s game against the Vikings, Jacobs will suit up for a Thanksgiving tilt with the Lions, who rank 11th in total rushing yards allowed but sixth in yards per carry allowed (3.9). Despite the Lions profiling as a tough matchup, Jacobs will be a near must-start for those rostering him this week. Backup Emanuel Wilson isn’t expected to have much standalone value, but remains a high-upside stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c5b8-d82c-a79a-f7bcb7900000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
