<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 22:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa48d80000</link>
      <description>Samuel and Terry McLaurin (quad) have both practiced in full over the last two days, putting them on track to play in Week 8 against the Chiefs on Monday Night Football. Samuel will be a WR3 in fantasy, with McLaurin expectedly back in the fold. The wide receiver duo will be catching passes from capable backup QB Marcus Mariota, with QB Jayden Daniels (hamstring) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa48d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (hamstrings) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17df-d5d8-a3ff-ffff3c380000</link>
      <description>Waddle will play in Week 8 despite injuring both hamstrings this week. While he technically can be started as a WR2, there are obvious re-injury concerns at play. Waddle should command a healthy target share for as long as he is out there, operating as the Dolphins’ No. 1 wide receiver, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17df-d5d8-a3ff-ffff3c380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (oblique) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1803-dab4-a3fb-9b7372a50000</link>
      <description>Kincaid is firmly in the questionable camp this week. The Bills’ No. 1 tight end sat out his team’s Week 6 game against the Falcons and spent Week 7 rehabbing the injury on bye. He remained limited through all three practices this week. While he may be able to tough it out this weekend, it would be unsurprising to see the Bills rest their talented receiving tight end to ensure good health for their Week 9 game against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1803-dab4-a3fb-9b7372a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out QB Brock Purdy (toe) for Week 8 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180a-dab4-a3fb-9b7a9c070000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know Purdy’s Friday participation level, but he remained limited through Wednesday and Thursday, and we assume Friday was no different. The 49ers are seemingly set on keeping their franchise quarterback protected from re-injury for as long as possible. Mac Jones will start again in his stead, and can be treated as a borderline QB1/2 against the Texans. The 49ers also ruled out C Jake Brendel (hamstring), EDGE Bryce Huff (hamstring) and EDGE Yetur Gross-Matos (hamstring).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180a-dab4-a3fb-9b7a9c070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers ruled out WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) for Week 8 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180c-d5d8-a3ff-f96d51a60000</link>
      <description>Pearsall was not seen practicing during the portion of practice open to the media today, likely marking his third DNP of the week. Pearsall will now miss his fourth straight game. Fantasy managers must continue exercising patience with the talented, young wide receiver. Hopefully, he can return for the 49ers’ Week 9 game against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180c-d5d8-a3ff-f96d51a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said the team could open WR Brandon Aiyuk’s (knee) 21-day practice window next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180e-d245-adfb-9d5f99da0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan adds that the team is in “week-to-week” territory for opening Aiyuk’s practice window. Aiyuk can be stashed on fantasy benches at this time, but the 49ers could still delay the practice window by a week or two, and then there is the matter of whether Aiyuk actually uses up most of said window. While this report is positive, there is still a wide range of potential outcomes at play here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180e-d245-adfb-9d5f99da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived RB Velus Jones Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-181d-dab4-a3fb-9b7dbf240000</link>
      <description>Jones was waived to make room for recent signee, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, formerly of the Ravens. Mitchell-Paden caught 1-of-2 targets for three yards this year. He entered the league as a 2022 undrafted free agent but had not taken any live receiving snaps until now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-181d-dab4-a3fb-9b7dbf240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pectoral) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182e-d5d8-a3ff-f96ff6bb0000</link>
      <description>Fellow Bills’ LB Terrel Bernard (ankle) is also questionable, as is rookie CB Maxwell Hairston (knee). DT DaQuan Jones (calf) and S Taylor Rapp (knee) have both been ruled out. The injuries should allow the Panthers to continue running ball efficiently with RBs Rico Dowdle and Chuba Hubbard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182e-d5d8-a3ff-f96ff6bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
