<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said QB Deshaun Watson (Achilles/PUP) won’t be activated from the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cd1-d35e-a1bf-4dd3bac60000</link>
      <description>This has been expected all along. It’s unknown how Watson factors into next year’s plan at quarterback for the Browns — CBS’ Jonathan Jones suggested he could compete for the job in training camp with Dillon Gabriel and Shedeur Sanders. But his anvil of a contract is untradeable and releasing him with a post-June 1 cap hit would not save the Browns a single dollar currently after they restructured it yet again in 2025 to keep the roster in some semblance of order. It’s possible they could restructure it again in 2026 and continue kicking the can down the road so they can put a functional offensive line on the field next year. Watson’s current 2026 cap hit is $80,716,514.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cd1-d35e-a1bf-4dd3bac60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (foot) won’t practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ce8-d35e-a1bf-4dea46230000</link>
      <description>McDermott said that “nothing has changed” from yesterday and that Allen is expected to be available on Sunday. It’s an earlier-than-normal walkthrough practice from Buffalo as they try to give their players some semblance of a Christmas break, so we’re inclined to believe McDermott here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ce8-d35e-a1bf-4dea46230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) is not practicing on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cea-dc7a-af9b-cfff82b80000</link>
      <description>This has been the new norm for Kincaid, who actually didn’t practice in either of the first two sessions of last week en route to being removed from the injury report. It’s clear he’s struggling through this injury and only managed one target against the Browns last week. We’d exercise caution on him being a sure-fire TE1 against the Eagles in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cea-dc7a-af9b-cfff82b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings activated Ty Chandler (knee) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cf5-dc7a-af9b-cfff82570000</link>
      <description>With Jordan Mason likely out and Aaron Jones also ailing, it’s possible that Chandler could find himself in for some real work in Week 17. Unfortunately it comes with Max Brosmer under center, but volume is volume in the fantasy world and teams that lost backs and need waiver-wire help should certainly consider dialing up Chandler tonight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cf5-dc7a-af9b-cfff82570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed K Joshua Karty off the Rams’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d0d-d968-a19b-5dfd44ce0000</link>
      <description>Will we get a Chad Ryland release move here, or will the 2025 Cardinals create some sort of two-kicker abomination scenario with their remaining time? There are so many questions to ask, and so little that we know. And so little of it that feels like it matters. Someone will kick and be a decent option against the Bengals in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d0d-d968-a19b-5dfd44ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed RB Elijah Mitchell to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d0f-d35e-a1bf-4dcfe4d30000</link>
      <description>The signing doesn’t seem like great news for TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) in Week 17. Mitchell had been with the Chiefs all year and was cast aside for Dameon Pierce last week in what we’d call a “mercy” waiver. It’s possible he’ll be elevated for Week 17 if Henderson isn’t able to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d0f-d35e-a1bf-4dcfe4d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Marcus Mariota (hand/quad) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d15-d56e-afff-effdec750000</link>
      <description>It would seem exceedingly likely that Josh Johnson will get the start on Christmas against the Cowboys. The Commanders are seven-point underdogs at home and Johnson (wincing) could be a viable superflex QB2 against one of the worst defenses in the NFL this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d15-d56e-afff-effdec750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings claimed QB Brett Rypien off waivers from the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d18-dc7a-af9b-cfbf17390000</link>
      <description>Rypien was with the Vikings in training camp and arguably would be as deserving of a start as anybody in Minnesota given how Max Brosmer has played so far. Perhaps that’s a Week 18 possibility. For now, he’ll serve as a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d18-dc7a-af9b-cfbf17390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d30-d35e-a1bf-4df2feca0000</link>
      <description>Without additional context, this looks bad for Flournoy’s chances of playing on Christmas. He got in a limited session Monday, but this could be a situation where he re-aggravated his knee by pushing it too fast. Or the Cowboys may simply have seen what they wanted to see and wanted to keep him sidelined on Tuesday to rest him. We’ve presented you the narratives and leave you with: It will be interesting to see which narrative will win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d30-d35e-a1bf-4df2feca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (neck) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d35-dc7a-af9b-cfbf74a90000</link>
      <description>Two limited practices would seem to have Williams well in line to play on Christmas. Will we get a full dose of Williams, or will the backfield continue to trend more towards a split with Malik Davis as the season winds down and the Cowboys are eliminated? The answer will probably tell us a lot about what on paper seems to be an RB2 smash spot against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d35-dc7a-af9b-cfbf74a90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
