<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released WR Tyreek Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6748-d990-a1de-6f4e45f30000</link>
      <description>Hill is one of several Dolphins players who have been informed of their release. The soon-to-be 32-year-old receiver saw his 2025 season come to an end in Week 4 when he suffered a dislocated knee and torn ACL against the Jets, but put together a respectable 21-265-1 line before going down. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero notes “it’s unclear when or if” Hill will play next season, but if he does, Hill will be a free agent for the first time in his career. The eight-time Pro Bowler should have plenty of suitors once he can prove he’s fully recovered from his injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6748-d990-a1de-6f4e45f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released WR Nick Westbrook-Ikhine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-674c-d89c-a1be-efdfc62b0000</link>
      <description>Westbrook-Ikhine caught 11 passes for 89 scoreless yards in his lone season with the Dolphins. The 28-year-old vet joined the team fresh off a 32-497-9 season with the Titans, but will now be free to sign with any team. Westbrook-Ikhine’s value as a field stretcher should be enough to find him a new home in 2026, but he’s unlikely to ever be a focal point of whatever offense he’s in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-674c-d89c-a1be-efdfc62b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Dolphins don’t want their decision to move on from Tua Tagovailoa “to drag too long.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6755-d89c-a1be-efdfec600000</link>
      <description>This report comes on the heels of the Dolphins making several cost-cutting moves to their roster on Presidents’ Day. As Schultz notes, the team would prefer to trade Tagovailoa, but “a cut is possible in the end” if they are unable to find a suitor. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported last week that the Dolphins are willing to take on a portion of Tagovailoa’s contract to trade him to another team, but given the $54 million he’s guaranteed to earn this season, the team may be forced to release him and designate him as a post-June 1 cut. Tagovailoa threw for 2,660-20-15 in 14 games last season, struggling to adjust to life without Tyreek Hill (knee) who was injured in Week 4. While he could still be a serviceable starter in the right system, he’ll need to turn in a strong performance next season if he hopes to prove he can be a franchise QB elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6755-d89c-a1be-efdfec600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Doug Haller believes James Conner could be a potential cap casualty for the Cardinals this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6769-d042-afbc-7ffb40fa0000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Conner will be 31 at the start of next season and missed most of 2025 with a season-ending foot/ankle injury he suffered in Week 3. Releasing Conner would save the Cardinals $8 million against the cap in 2026, and would carry a dead cap hit of just $2.250 million if he’s released as a pre-June 1 cut. Conner rushed 32 times for 95 yards and a touchdown last season while also catching eight passes for 38 yards and another score. With his best days likely behind him, Conner would be an uninspiring fantasy lead back wherever he plays next season. It is possible he finds a situation good enough to land in the Zero RB ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6769-d042-afbc-7ffb40fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns hired Falcons defensive pass game coordinator Mike Rutenberg as defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6771-d990-a1de-6f7f62f70000</link>
      <description>Rutenberg was one of three finalists for the job and now lands his first defensive coordinator role in the NFL. The longtime coach had previous stints with the 49ers (2020) and Jets (2021-2024), and helped lead a secondary that ranked 13th in passing yards allowed and 13th in net yards per attempt, while also ranking sixth in interceptions. Rutenberg will have big shoes to fill taking over for Jim Schwartz, who resigned after being passed over for the Browns’ head coaching job earlier this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6771-d990-a1de-6f7f62f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns S Ronnie Hickman suffered minor injuries in an assault on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6824-d042-afbc-7df674660000</link>
      <description>According to an article published by the New York Post, Hickman was jumped by a group of four men in the lobby of a Manhattan hotel early Monday. The safety was reportedly taken to the hospital and has since been released, with no arrests made in the incident yet. This doesn’t sound like something that will affect Hickman moving into next season. In 2025, the third-year safety totaled 103 tackles, seven pass breakups, and two interceptions with the Browns after being named a full-time starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6824-d042-afbc-7df674660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill’s agent, Drew Rosenhaus, said Hill wants to continue playing once he is fully recovered from his knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6854-d89c-a1be-efdfdd1a0000</link>
      <description>Speaking onSports Extrawith Josh Moser, Rosenhaus said Hill is “progressing well” in his recovery and intends continue his playing career. Hill, 31, was released by the Dolphins after four seasons with the team, and still has a lot to overcome after suffering a dislocated knee and torn ACL last season, and is not a lock to be ready to go come training camp. If he does intend to play, teams could opt to bring him in and continue to work with him through rehab until he is up to speed, but it seems unlikely Hill would get more than a one-year deal given his age and current injury status. When healthy, Hill still has plenty to offer a team in need of an explosive playmaker, and could see several contenders line up for his services in the coming months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6854-d89c-a1be-efdfdd1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JoeBucsFan.com reports Bucky Irving underwent offseason shoulder surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-685b-d990-a1de-6c5f90ae0000</link>
      <description>According to the site, Irving’s “recovery and rehab are not expected to significantly impact his offseason preparation.” Irving missed multiple games due to a foot and shoulder injury last season, but it was the shoulder injury that kept him sidelined until his return in Week 13. With Rachaad White likely leaving via free agency, Irving could be in line for a bell cow role for the Bucs in 2026. The third-year back rushed for 173-588-1 last season but averaged 20.3 touches per game when active. Hopefully a full offseason to recover will have him back to his rookie form after his efficiency numbers dwindled late last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-685b-d990-a1de-6c5f90ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired former Titans run game coordinator Travis Smith to be their next defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-692b-d89c-a1be-efffda6e0000</link>
      <description>The Raiders continue to round out their new-look coaching ranks as they bring in former Titans run game coordinator Travis Smith to serve as their defensive line coach. Smith coached with the Raiders from 2012 to 2021 in multiple capacities, most recently serving as their assistant defensive line coach before stints with the Bears and Titans. Most notably, Smith served as the defensive line coach for the Bears between 2022 and 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-692b-d89c-a1be-efffda6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Seahawks are “unlikely” to use the franchise tag on RB Ken Walker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6bd9-d990-a1de-6fdf650f0000</link>
      <description>Retaining other free agents and signing Jaxon Smith-Njigba to a new mega-deal are the Seattle’s priorities this offseason. They’ll likely let Walker, Super Bowl MVP who propelled the Seahawks to a championship this season, explore free agency in the coming months. Walker will have a range of suitors, including teams that will surely be willing to make him a clearcut lead back after Walker shared the workload with the ultra-inefficient Zach Charbonnet in 2024 and 2025. Look for Walker to get a huge deal — as far as running back contracts go — from a team ready to make him the centerpiece of their offense. Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio said the Seahawks front office might “believe that Walker won’t get what he’s looking for on the open market” and make a run at bringing him back to Seattle on a short-term deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6bd9-d990-a1de-6fdf650f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
