<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 04:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (ankle) left San Francisco’s Week 18 game against the Seahawks and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-86cd-dc7a-af9b-cfffb2440000</link>
      <description>He was stepped on by Seahawks OL Josh Jones. Winters had two tackles before leaving. He spent some time in the medical tent and walked to the locker room with trainers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-86cd-dc7a-af9b-cfffb2440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Tatum Bethune (groin) left San Francisco’s Week 18 game against the Seahawks and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8710-dc7a-af9b-cfbf9cd90000</link>
      <description>It was the second time he left the game. Bethune had seven tackles, a sack, and a pass defensed before leaving. His absence leaves Eric Kendricks and Garret Wallow manning the middle for the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8710-dc7a-af9b-cfbf9cd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy completed 19-of-27 passes for 127 yards and an interception in the 49ers’ 13-3, Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8712-d56e-afff-e7fa34f90000</link>
      <description>Purdy only managed one real drive of any consequence. Leading off the fourth quarter, Purdy had the 49ers in goal-to-go only to watch a double-tipped (by the defensive lineman and Christian McCaffrey) pass land in Drake Thomas’ arms. The 49ers missed Trent Williams, but this was also a case of Kyle Shanahan getting schematically pantsed by Mike MacDonald. Purdy had just 77 yards before that fourth-quarter drive, and was left with a bloodied throwing thumb while taking some huge hits on San Francisco’s final drive. The 49ers will be either the No. 5 seed in the NFC if the Rams lose to Arizona on Sunday or, more likely, the No. 6 seed if the Rams win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8712-d56e-afff-e7fa34f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Darnold completed 20-of-26 passes for 198 yards in the Seahawks’ 13-3, Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8721-dc7a-af9b-cfbf058d0000</link>
      <description>Darnold took a rough sack on Seattle’s first drive to push them out of easy goal-to-go range, but was able to come up with big plays whenever Seattle found third-and-long and authored a 16-play, 89-yard drive to crush the life out of the game despite it ending with an unsatisfying field goal off the uprights. Darnold just sneaks over 4,000 yards with this performance and finished with a 25:14 touchdown-to-interception ratio in his first year in Seattle, becoming one of only five quarterbacks to win 13 or more games in back-to-back seasons. He’ll get next week off as this win cemented the bye for the Seahawks in the NFC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8721-dc7a-af9b-cfbf058d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker rushed 16 times for 97 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 18 win over the 49ers, adding four catches for 36 yards on four targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8729-d35e-a1bf-c7eb6c7c0000</link>
      <description>Naturally, he lost the game’s only touchdown to Zach Charbonnet despite running more effectively and getting the bulk of the carries. That’s the tale of Walker’s season, as he finished with just five scores to Charbonnnet’s 12. Walker’s best play in this one was a toss on third-and-17 that he managed to weave between defenders on and convert a miraculous first down. He’ll get the week off as Seattle preps to host the lowest remaining seed in the Divisional Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8729-d35e-a1bf-c7eb6c7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet rushed 17 times for 74 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks Week 18 win over the 49ers, adding three catches for 23 yards on four targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-872b-d56e-afff-e7ebc7b80000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet scooted past a defensive back on the edge after an impressive seal block by A.J. Barner got him to free space in the first quarter. It wound up being the game’s only touchdown. He finishes the regular season with 12 scores and will get the week off ahead of Seattle’s Divisional Round game against the lowest remaining NFC seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-872b-d56e-afff-e7ebc7b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey rushed eight times for 23 yards in the 49ers’ Week 18 loss to the Seahawks, adding six catches for 34 yards on seven targets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-872e-d35e-a1bf-c7eeb7780000</link>
      <description>He was the target on Brock Purdy’s one pick, a double-tipped ball that both Boye Mafe and McCaffrey combined to bat into Drake Thomas’ arms. The 49ers surprisingly couldn’t find much easy here, needing to resort to flea flickers to even get McCaffrey shallow zone looks. McCaffrey finishes the regular season with 2,126 total yards from scrimmage and 17 total touchdowns. The 49ers will look to get him more involved on the road in the NFC Wild Card round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-872e-d35e-a1bf-c7eeb7780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Robinson Jr. rushed twice for nine yards in the 49ers’ Week 18 win over the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8732-d56e-afff-e7fa0eb70000</link>
      <description>It’s Robinson’s lowest touch total since Week 8’s loss to Houston where he bageled. Robinson will see out the final days of his rookie contract in the NFC Wild Card round as a pure backup to Christian McCaffrey. He finishes the regular season with 92 carries for 400 yards and two touchdowns on the ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8732-d56e-afff-e7fa0eb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 6-of-8 targets for 84 yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8734-d56e-afff-e7fc764f0000</link>
      <description>A floor game for the third-year star. Smith-Njigba managed no red zone targets as the Seahawks played very run-heavy, and his one near-catch out of that area was heavily contested in double coverage. Smith-Njigba will get next week off as the Seahawks await the Wild Card round results as the NFC’s No. 1 seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8734-d56e-afff-e7fc764f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 2-of-3 targets for 29 yards in Seattle’s Week 18 win over the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8737-d968-a19b-dff770d50000</link>
      <description>Kupp was the target on a fourth-and-goal end zone chuck from Sam Darnold, but the ball wasn’t even close enough for him to make a play on it. The veteran did manage to convert two first downs on his only two catches, including a 24-yarder in the fourth quarter where Darnold was drifting towards the line on the move. Kupp didn’t crack 600 yards and managed just two touchdowns in his first year in Seattle. They can probably do better going forward if they want to move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8737-d968-a19b-dff770d50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
