<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Tyrell Shavers (knee) is questionable to return in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae7d-d56e-afff-eefde4f70000</link>
      <description>Shavers injured his left knee while on punt coverage in the second quarter. He quickly left for the locker room and was listed as questionable to return. With Josh Palmer now on IR, the Bills would be forced to lean on Keon Coleman, Gabe Davis, and Brandin Cooks for wide receiver snaps if Shavers is done for the day. Bills S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) is also questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae7d-d56e-afff-eefde4f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu suffered a ruptured patellar tendon in the Wild Card Round against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae89-dc7a-af9b-efbf47840000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, Ekwonu will undergo surgery and his availability for Week 1 of the 2026 season is in doubt. It’s a brutal end to the season for him and the Panthers. Now Carolina will likely have to spend a bit more on a backup tackle in the offseason. Pro Football Focus has Ekwonu graded as a top-40 tackle this year. He had just one year left on his contract and was likely eying an extension in the spring. Ekwonu might be forced to wait until next year to ink a new deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae89-dc7a-af9b-efbf47840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrell Shavers (knee) returned to the Bills’ Wild Card Round game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae98-d968-a19b-fef9d8b60000</link>
      <description>Shavers left in the second quarter with the knee issue. He went to the locker room and the team listed him as questionable to return. Shavers was back on the field coming out of halftime, giving the Bills some extra receiver depth for the final two quarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae98-d968-a19b-fef9d8b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (hamstring) is active for the Wild Card Round against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae97-d56e-afff-eeff254a0000</link>
      <description>Getting Williams back for this game is a huge win for Brock Purdy and the San Francisco offense. He was listed as questionable on Friday after a light week of practice. Ricky Pearsall, on the other hand, is out for the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ae97-d56e-afff-eeff254a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared WR Ricky Pearsall, LB Dee Winters, Luke Gifford, CB Chase Lucas, DL Kevin Givens, WR Jordan Watkins, and RB Isaac Guerendo inactive for the Wild Card Round against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb0-d35e-a1bf-eff22a770000</link>
      <description>Pearsall was listed as questionable on Friday but did not practice once this week, meaning he was always a long-shot to suit up. Demarcus Robinson will continue to operate as the team’s No. 2 receiver opposite Jauan Jennings this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb0-d35e-a1bf-eff22a770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared RT Lane Johnson, OLB Josh Uche, QB Sam Howell, CB Jakorian Bennett, RB AJ Dillon, OL Brett Toth, and DT Ty Robinson inactive for the Wild Card Round against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aea3-d35e-a1bf-efe39ccf0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles have been optimistic that Johnson would return from the foot issue next week for over a month. It seems like the injury isn’t progressing as Johnson or the team had anticipated. Fred Johnson will remain in the starting lineup in place of Lane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aea3-d35e-a1bf-efe39ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) will not return in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeba-dc7a-af9b-efbf5a290000</link>
      <description>Poyer went down with the hamstring issue in the second quarter. He was listed as questionable to return but the team eventually ruled him out after halftime. The Bills’ secondary will be undermanned for the rest of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeba-dc7a-af9b-efbf5a290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Davis suffered a knee injury in the Wild Card Round against the Jaguars and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb3-d35e-a1bf-eff3175a0000</link>
      <description>Davis was crushed by multiple defenders while trying to bring down a pass from Josh Allen over the middle of the field. He was unable to put weight on his left and needed to be helped off by trainers before being carted to the locker room. With Josh Palmer on IR, the Bills are dangerously thin at receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aeb3-d35e-a1bf-eff3175a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Raiders and Dolphins have requested interviews with Packers defensive coordinator Jeff Hafley for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aec6-dc7a-af9b-efffb6910000</link>
      <description>Hafley is up to five head coaching interviews now. The Falcons, Cardinals, and Titans have also requested interviews with him. Hafley has held his current position in Green Bay for two seasons. The Packers ranked 11th in points allowed this year and sixth in 2024. He was Boston College’s head coach before joining the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aec6-dc7a-af9b-efffb6910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Raiders and Cardinals have requested interviews with Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed0-d968-a19b-fef1d5530000</link>
      <description>LaFleur was fired by the Jets in the midst of a dreadful 2022 season. He landed on his feet in LA and immediately oversaw a top-10 scoring offense. Things went even better in 2025. The Rams led the league in scoring this year and Matthew Stafford will likely win his first career MVP. LaFleur is well-connected with a strong resume behind him and hasn’t gotten his shot at a head coaching gig yet. In a relatively weak hiring cycle, this could be his year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-aed0-d968-a19b-fef1d5530000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
