<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 3-of-5 targets for 58 yards and a touchdown in San Francisco’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e9-d6e9-af9d-9af910450000</link>
      <description>Tonges was hurt early in the game, but would come back and be a featured target for a depleted 49ers passing attack. His touchdown came on a well-designed screen that gave him plenty of open space to operate. Tonges wound up playing 39 snaps. There’s not much TE1 upside here, but Tonges has been a respectable fill-in for the 49ers in George Kittle’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e9-d6e9-af9d-9af910450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 4-of-7 targets for 30 yards in the Raiders’ Week 4 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e8-dca3-a9fb-bff93c450000</link>
      <description>Meyers was getting open and Geno Smith wanted to get it to him. Unfortunately, Smith’s timing was terrible. Two targets intended for Meyers ended up in the hands of Bears S Kevin Byard III, who seemingly knew where the ball was going before it was snapped. The Raiders either need to help Smith with his processing or dial up more layup targets. Meyers is just a FLEX option against the Colts next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e8-dca3-a9fb-bff93c450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Tucker caught 2-of-2 targets for 13 yards in the Raiders’ Week 4 loss to the Bears, adding two rushes for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e8-d6e9-af9d-9af834070000</link>
      <description>Tucker also returned one punt for seven yards, but this was not the showing that fantasy managers were looking for. The speedy wide receiver had a 15-plus-yard end-around called back due to a holding penalty as well. Tucker was frequently sent it motion, and it is clear that OC Chip Kelly values him. Unfortunately, the opportunities just weren’t there this week. He is a volatile FLEX option against the Colts next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92e8-d6e9-af9d-9af834070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 2-of-4 targets for 24 yards in San Francisco’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92eb-deb6-a7fd-d3ffd9410000</link>
      <description>He also caught a two-point attempt, but at a cost as Andrew Wingard sandwiched him on the goal line and forced him to the blue medical tent. It was an amazing catch of a Brock Purdy cross-field hospital ball. Jennings managed to shake off injury and play down the stretch, but was mostly ineffective as Purdy had a scattershot day and Jennings was well-covered. Jennings will almost undoubtedly be on the injury report again in Week 5 ahead of Thursday Night Football. If he can survive that, he’ll be on the WR3/WR4 borderline — possibly higher if Ricky Pearsall is inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92eb-deb6-a7fd-d3ffd9410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashton Jeanty rushed 21 times for 138 yards, one touchdown and one fumble in the Raiders’ Week 4 loss to the Bears, adding two receptions for 17 yards and two touchdowns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92ef-deb6-a7fd-d3ff8f6c0000</link>
      <description>Jeanty shook off the early fumble and cleared 100 yards from scrimmage for the first time in his career. He ran particularly well on runs up the middle against the Bears’ short-staffed defensive front and Raiders OC Chip Kelly deserves credit for featuring Jeanty as a receiving weapon in scoring position. On his second receiving touchdown, which occurred with five-plus minutes remaining in the third quarter, Geno Smith snapped the ball and simply stared down Jeanty, waiting for him to get open on a route out of the backfield. The rookie running back is an RB1 against the Colts next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92ef-deb6-a7fd-d3ff8f6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught 1-of-4 targets for 17 yards in San Francisco’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f6-dca3-a9fb-bfff58050000</link>
      <description>Bourne had 38 snaps, just ahead of an injured Ricky Pearsall for second on the team, and he would manage to drop three passes on four targets while generating one yard after the catch on his completion. So uh, those are definitely numbers. Not good ones, but numbers nonetheless. Bourne could conceivably have PPR scam relevancy next week if the higher-tier members of the 49ers receiving room remain out, but there’s not much unexplored upside here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f6-dca3-a9fb-bfff58050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 1-of-2 targets for 20 yards in San Francisco’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f9-d95b-addb-faff8b2e0000</link>
      <description>The fact that Robinson was only lightly mixed in (22 snaps) despite injuries ahead of him on the depth chart is pretty telling about his standing at the moment. Until we see signs of fantasy relevance, we’d avoid Robinson even if Ricky Pearsall and Juaun Jennings wind up missing more time in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f9-d95b-addb-faff8b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco had seven rushes for 35 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding two catches for 13 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92fd-d6e9-af9d-9afd23550000</link>
      <description>It was a prime matchup for Pacheco and he couldn’t take advantage outside of a short touchdown grab. Kareem Hunt led the Chiefs with 13 rushes (for a mere 34 yards) while splitting the pass routes out of the KC backfield. Pacheco, who had 67 combined rushing yards over his previous two games, dropped a pass in this one and missed another blitz pick up — mistakes that could cost him valuable playing time in the coming weeks. Breshard Smith, meanwhile, saw four targets on just ten routes and could be carving out a role in the team’s passing attack. Appearing unconfident and unsure of his role in the offense, Pacheco probably shouldn’t be played in 12-team leagues next week against a stellar Jaguars rush defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92fd-d6e9-af9d-9afd23550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua said he had X-rays on his thumb in the third quarter of the Rams’ Week 4 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9300-d6e9-af9d-9b909a310000</link>
      <description>We’ll assume this is a non-issue for the time being. Nacua said he was “rolled up on” during a run play, but returned to the game after his X-rays came back clear. Nacua posted a career-high 170 receiving yards on 13 receptions in Sunday’s victory. Barring an unexpected turn of events, it sounds like he will be good to go when the Rams return in Week 5 to play the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9300-d6e9-af9d-9b909a310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 25-of-37 attempts for 270 yards and four touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding four rushes for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9306-d95b-addb-fb461ab60000</link>
      <description>Mahomes made quick work on an injury-ravaged Baltimore defense missing six starters by the second half. Mahomes did his regular dink and dunk routine while mixing in a few deeper shots, mostly to Tyquan Thorton and Xavier Worthy, who returned from this Week 1 shoulder injury. Mahomes connected with four pass catchers for scores — Thornton, JuJu Smith-Schuster, Hollywood Brown, and Isiah Pacheco — on his way to a solid fantasy outing. He had not had more than one touchdown toss in any of his past three games, heading into Week 4 as one of the league’s most obvious regression candidates. Mahomes will be a borderline QB1 in Week 5 against a surprisingly solid Jacksonville defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9306-d95b-addb-fb461ab60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
