<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said S Jordan Poyer (hamstring) is “week to week” and will not play against the Broncos on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b41d-d56e-afff-f6fdc9330000</link>
      <description>2025 fifth-round pick Jordan Hancock replaced Poyer at safety and will likely be asked to do so going forward. The Bills don’t have much star-level talent on defense this year, so they’re asking a lot out of McDermott’s coaching to help them spring a road upset of the No. 1 seeded Broncos on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b41d-d56e-afff-f6fdc9330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Dalton Kincaid being in a walking boot after the game was “precautionary.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b420-dc7a-af9b-ffbf33030000</link>
      <description>Kincaid appeared to struggle to get up after his fourth-quarter touchdown catch and will likely be spotted on the injury report this week. That’s nothing unusual for Kincaid, who has been on it with a knee for weeks now. It’s possible Dawson Knox becomes a bigger part of the game plan this week, though practice reports will tell more of that story than we know right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b420-dc7a-af9b-ffbf33030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Ed Oliver (biceps) will be designated to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b422-d35e-a1bf-f5e26c0c0000</link>
      <description>The Bills will see if they can get him healthy enough to play against the Broncos in the divisional round. The 21-day window will open for Oliver when Buffalo next practices. McDermott gave the same update for Curtis Samuel, who somehow feels desperately needed with Gabe Davis lost to a torn ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b422-d35e-a1bf-f5e26c0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys scheduled an interview with former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b425-d35e-a1bf-f5e7df930000</link>
      <description>Finally a big name in this search. Gannon was more quirky than good as Eagles defensive coordinator, something he carried over with him in the desert as the unit spit out a 21st-place finish in defensive DVOA in 2025 after a ton of offseason investments in players like Josh Sweat and Will Johnson. Gannon would at least have more time to focus on calling a defense as a coordinator again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b425-d35e-a1bf-f5e7df930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys will interview former Ravens DC Zach Orr for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b429-d35e-a1bf-f5ebda8e0000</link>
      <description>Orr’s defining trait as a defensive coordinator in his two seasons in Baltimore was figuring out where Kyle Hamilton would play after a poor month, then letting him do that. With John Harbaugh fired, Orr’s job is obviously up in the air while the Ravens wait for a new head coach. Orr wouldn’t necessarily be a superb pivot for the Cowboys, but as we have often noted, it would be hard to do worse than Matt Eberflus did last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b429-d35e-a1bf-f5ebda8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers signed K Lucas Havrisik, OT Brant Banks, DL Dante Barnett, OG Karsen Barnhart, DL Anthony Campbell, TE McCallan Castles, OT Dalton Cooper, TE Drake Dabney, DL James Ester, CB Tyron Herring, LB Jamon Johnson, RB Damien Martinez, S Mark Perry, WR Will Sheppard, RB Pierre Strong Jr. and TE Messiah Swinson to reserve/futures contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b42d-d35e-a1bf-f5ef65e00000</link>
      <description>Havrisik hit 4-of-4 field goals and 7-of-9 extra points this year, and the Packers seemed to be developing him as kicker of the future — whatever that means in the NFL — while letting him stay on the practice squad. With Brandon McManus’ job officially under scrutiny, it’s possible he eventually gets the Packers kicker gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b42d-d35e-a1bf-f5ef65e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Braxton Berrios, QB Graham Mertz, LB Christian Harris, G Juice Scruggs, RB Jawhar Jordan, and CB Alijah Huzzie inactive for their Wildcard game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b49a-d968-a19b-fcfbf40b0000</link>
      <description>Jordan’s absence likely brings veteran Nick Chubb back into the fold in the backfield pecking order, although rookie Woody Marks appears to be in line for a hefty workload against the Steelers. There are no real surprises with the remainder of the inactives list out of Houston as they look to topple the Steelers on the road in the first week of the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b49a-d968-a19b-fcfbf40b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Roman Wilson, RB Kaleb Johnson, OL Jack Driscoll, DL Logan Lee, OLB Jeremiah Moon, and CB Tre Flowers inactive for their Wildcard game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b49b-d968-a19b-fcfbf5d90000</link>
      <description>A pair of rookies draw inactivity as both Wilson and Johnson are not active for the team’s Wildcard game against the Texans. The Steelers aim to avoid a one-and-done after backing into the postseason in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b49b-d968-a19b-fcfbf5d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks HC Mike Macdonald said TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) has a chance to play in the Divisional Round against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b4ae-d968-a19b-fcff59860000</link>
      <description>Speaking to media Monday evening, Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters that rookie tight end Elijah Arroyo “looked good” in his return to practice last week, his first time on the field since seeing his 21-day practice window opened as he attempts to return from injured reserve. Macdonald added that there is a chance Arroyo makes it back in time for their Divisional Round game against the 49ers after the team enjoyed a bye week following securing the No. 1 seed out of the NFC. While not necessarily likely to contribute elite counting stats, Arroyo could return to 40-50% of the team’s offensive snaps as a pass-catching specialist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b4ae-d968-a19b-fcff59860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (head) was carted to the locker room at the end of the third quarter in the team’s Wildcard game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b4ed-dc7a-af9b-fffff8b20000</link>
      <description>Collins was unable to brace himself as he went to the ground on a catch attempt at the end of the third quarter, appearing to contact the frozen ground with the forehead area of his helmet. Clearly disoriented following the play, Collins had to be redirected towards the sideline after attempting to rejoin the huddle. He would then be seen hunched over on the sideline before even making it into the medical tent. Collins was eventually carted to the locker room with a towel over his head for further evaluation. It certainly appears as if his night is over after catching just 3-of-7 targets for 21 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b4ed-dc7a-af9b-fffff8b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
