<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Simmons (personal) hs returned to the Chiefs after four weeks away.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</link>
      <description>Simmons was away from the Chiefs for four weeks to tend to a family issue. We don’t know the specifics beyond that, but the rookie tackle who started the first five games of the season is now set to return following his absence, and should immediately slot in as the team’s left tackle when the team returns from its Week 10 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4adc-d1e7-a1fa-5afe06190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Kayshon Boutte is day-to-day with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aec-d1e7-a1fa-5aee37140000</link>
      <description>It’s an encouraging sign for Boutte following his early exit from Sunday’s win over the Falcons, although Vrabel did add that he doesn’t expect Boutte to practice “early in the week.” His practice status will be one to monitor when the Patriots release their first injury report on Wednesday, but as of now, Boutte does have a chance to play in Week 10 in a game that could feature plenty of scoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4aec-d1e7-a1fa-5aee37140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ribs) would undergo a scan but that he feels “optimistic ... in regard to where we’re potentially heading.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b12-d45b-affe-5f9682ad0000</link>
      <description>A scan means we’re not completely out of the woods yet, but Nacua has bled on the field this year and we doubt a small-scale fractured rib would keep him out. (Easy for us to say.) Nacua’s status will be worth tracking, but we’d enter Week 10 expecting him to play based on the rhetoric so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b12-d45b-affe-5f9682ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Commanders are open to dealing OLs Andrew Wylie and Nick Allegretti.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b0e-d45b-affe-5f9e4b710000</link>
      <description>According to Schultz, Wylie and Allegretti are one of “several players” the 3-6 Commanders are open to dealing. Wylie first joined the Commanders in 2023 and has started four games this season at right guard, while Allegretti, who started the first two games at right guard, hasn’t taken an offensive snap since Week 4. Wylie is on an expiring contract, and Allegretti’s deal ends after the 2026 season. Both players have plenty of starting experience and could serve as stopgaps for contenders looking to improve along the offensive line before the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b0e-d45b-affe-5f9e4b710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Dolphins are open to trading S Minkah Fitzpatrick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b14-d713-ad9e-6f54ea9f0000</link>
      <description>Fitzpatrick was acquired earlier in the offseason in the trade that sent Jonnu Smith and Jalen Ramsey to Pittsburgh. According to Schultz, the Dolphins have received “interest from multiple teams” for Fitzpatrick, who is under contract through 2026. Fitzpatrick has appeared in all nine games for the Dolphins this season, totaling 50 tackles, five pass breakups, and one interception, while also recovering one fumble. Fitzpatrick, 28, has been named as a Pro Bowler for each of the last three years and would immediately improve whatever secondary he lands with.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b14-d713-ad9e-6f54ea9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Kyle Williams has “settled down” and that he’s excited Williams will “get a greater opportunity here moving forward.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b1e-d713-ad9e-6f5eb43b0000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear whether Vrabel is advocating for Williams getting more of a role in the absence of Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) or just in general, but Williams saw a season-high 31 offensive snaps against the Falcons in Week 9. Williams has just two catches all season and does not need to be pre-emptively picked up based on this news, but he’s someone to monitor down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b1e-d713-ad9e-6f5eb43b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated C Cooper Beebe (ankle) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b22-d713-ad9e-6f769f620000</link>
      <description>He took most of the 21-day window. Beebe will resume his role as starting center for the Cowboys going forward, with Brock Hoffman sent back to the bench.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b22-d713-ad9e-6f769f620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed LB Jack Sanborn (groin) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b22-d713-ad9e-6f76799b0000</link>
      <description>Sanborn was a late scratch for Week 8’s game against the Broncos and will now miss at least the team’s next four games. Sandborn was injured in practice prior to last week’s game and has totaled 16 tackles, one TFL, and one pass breakup in the six games he’s appeared in this season. Sandborn will be eligible to return in Week 14 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b22-d713-ad9e-6f76799b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said RT Taliese Fuaga (ankle) has a high-ankle sprain and is unlikely to play this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b46-d713-ad9e-6f564ef10000</link>
      <description>Ditto Jack Stoll. Fuaga has played through multiple injuries this year, with a knee and back listing. The second-year tackle has played up to his form last year, with a 65.0 PFF rating in 473 dropbacks. Asim Richards replaced him for the final two snaps of Week 9’s loss to the Rams and would be next man up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b46-d713-ad9e-6f564ef10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Broderick Washington underwent surgery on his Achilles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b43-d713-ad9e-6f5746990000</link>
      <description>According to Harbaugh, Washington didn’t have a torn Achilles, but he was unable to provide a timeline on when the veteran defensive tackle can return. Washington was placed on injured reserve last weekend and will miss at least three more games, but it seems likely he will return well outside of the four-game minimum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4b43-d713-ad9e-6f5746990000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
