<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Drake London “is not believed to have suffered a major knee injury” in Week 11’s loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f74-d1e7-a1fa-dffe136a0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that London “could miss some time,” but we’ll learn more about that on Monday after the star receiver undergoes further tests. The Falcons could be without their top receiver and quarterback if London and Penix (knee) can’t suit up for Week 12 against the Saints, which could set the stage for both Bijan Robinson and Tyler Allgeier to see significant work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f74-d1e7-a1fa-dffe136a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Engram caught 4-of-5 targets for 33 yards in Denver’s Week 11 win over the Chiefs</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f71-d45b-affe-dff70f460000</link>
      <description>Engram only played 25 snaps to Adam Trautman’s 41. At this point it has to be said that Engram simply is only going to find TE1 usage if the Broncos are actually forced into a passing script. No team has done that since the Giants in Week 7, and even then he only returned 5/42 on eight targets. The real joker were the offseason blurbs we wrote about the joker along the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f71-d45b-affe-dff70f460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 3-of-7 targets for 23 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 11 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f8c-d713-ad9e-efdc38920000</link>
      <description>Kupp’s long-awaited revenge game against his former mates didn’t lead to much, as Jaxon Smith-Njigba continued dominating looks (12 targets) in the Seattle passing attack and AJ Barner came out of nowhere to see 11 targets against LA. It’s possible Kupp was slowed by the hamstring and wrist injuries that kept him sidelined for parts of practice last week. Kupp, who doesn’t have more than three catches in a game since Week 5, is little more than a flex option in deep fantasy formats going forward. He gets the Bucs in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f8c-d713-ad9e-efdc38920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 5-of-6 targets for 82 yards in Denver’s Week 11 win over the Chiefs</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df9608900000</link>
      <description>Career highs in catches, targets, and yards are following Bryant’s somewhat expanded role since Week 5. He’s played at least 30 snaps in every game since then, and the Chiefs let him get free for a 48-yarder that momentarily landed Bryant in concussion protocol before he returned later in the game. Heading into the bye, we don’t think Bryant is necessarily a good bet to explode on to the scene in the fantasy playoffs, but he’s building a case that it’s in the range of outcomes. He’s banished Marvin Mims (15 snaps in return from a concussion) to an ancillary gadget role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df9608900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 1-of-8 targets for one yard and one touchdown in the Rams’ Week 11 win against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df96ee380000</link>
      <description>Adams gritted it out after suffering an oblique injury in Week 10 against the 49ers and tied for the team lead with eight targets. His lone catch came on a first half one-yard touchdown. It was his tenth touchdown grab of the season, working as the Rams’ primary weapon inside the five yard line. Adams also had a brutal over-the-middle drop on a perfectly thrown ball from Matthew Stafford in the second half. Adams’ touchdown-based upside makes him a weekly top-12 fantasy option. He’ll have plenty of fantasy appeal in Week 12 against a fading Tampa defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f92-d45b-affe-df96ee380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum had eight carries for ten yards in the Rams’ Week 11 win against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f96-d713-ad9e-efd689060000</link>
      <description>Kyren Williams once again led the Rams backfield with 12 rushes for 91 yards and a touchdown. Williams also ran far more routes than Corum, who was targeted once on three routes against Seattle. Corum coming into this game had seen 38 rushing attempts over the past three games. Corum isn’t a viable fantasy option unless Williams misses time down the stretch. He should be rostered in most fantasy leagues though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8f96-d713-ad9e-efd689060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba caught 9-of-12 targets for 105 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 11 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fa1-d45b-affe-dfb7db210000</link>
      <description>It was Smith-Njigba’s seventh game this season with more than 100 receiving yards. He was targeted on 26 percent of his pass routes and had one of the best catches of the NFL season — a one-handed stab near the sideline on an off-target throw from Sam Darnold. JSN’s domination of air yards and targets in the balanced Seattle offense makes him the safest player in fantasy. He’ll be an elite option against the Titans in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fa1-d45b-affe-dfb7db210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrei Iosivas caught 3-of-4 targets for 20 yards in the Bengals’ Week 11 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fbb-d45b-affe-dfbf50d80000</link>
      <description>All three of Iosivas’ receptions came on the Bengals’ first two offensive drives. Outside of that, the third-year receiver was held in check for much of the afternoon. Iosivas has seen a slight uptick in volume since Joe Flacco took over as starter, but is far too inconsistent to warrant any fantasy consideration for Week 12 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fbb-d45b-affe-dfbf50d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Fant caught 5-of-6 targets for 36 yards in the Bengals’ Week 11 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fbe-d673-a39e-afbf38150000</link>
      <description>It was a typical receiving line for Fant, whose six targets set a new season high. Fant’s most memorable moment, unfortunately, came in the fourth quarter when he fumbled the ball late and with the game well out of reach. The fumble was then recovered by Steelers DB James Pierre, who returned it 34 yards for the Steelers’ second defensive touchdown of the day. Fant can be left on waivers ahead of Week 12’s game against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fbe-d673-a39e-afbf38150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo did not catch either of his two targets in the Seahawks’ Week 11 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fa8-d1e7-a1fa-dfea28790000</link>
      <description>Arroyo, who has more than two receptions in just one game this season, ran a route on 16 of the Seahawks’ 49 drop backs while AJ Barner was second on the team with 11 targets. He caught ten for 77 yards in a career game. It looks like Barner has taken over as the Seahawks’ top pass-catching tight end. Arroyo can be left on the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8fa8-d1e7-a1fa-dfea28790000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
