<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:01:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) is active for Week 9 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbded00000</link>
      <description>Flacco had been listed as questionable to face the Bears after sustaining a shoulder injury last week against the Jets. He’ll play through the injury against a soft Chicago defense, but presents a very real in-game injury risk. The fantasy prospects of every Bengals player rely on Flacco being under center for the pass-heavy Cincinnati offense. Bengals declared CB Marco Wilson, LB Logan Wilson, OL Dalton Risner, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, and DE Trey Hendrickson (hip) inactive against Chicago. With Hendrickson out, the Bengals defense presents an even better matchup for Caleb Williams and the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbded00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared S Jevon Holland, CB Paulson Adebo, CB Cor’Dale Flott, DL Chauncey Golston, OT Jermaine Eleumunor, and TE Daniel Bellinger inactive for Week 9 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d673-a39e-e5f159ed0000</link>
      <description>Holland tested his knee out in pre-game warmups but wasn’t cleared to play. He will look to return in Week 10 against the Bears. The Giants are down multiple starters this week, making them a strong matchup for Mac Jones, who is a solid QB2 option in Superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4571-d673-a39e-e5f159ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Scotty Miller, S Chuck Clark, S Jabrill Peppers, LB Cole Holcomb, OG Andrus Peat, and DT Logan Lee inactive for Week 9 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4570-d45b-affe-55f695a00000</link>
      <description>Both Clark and Holcomb were ruled out before the weekend, so there are no notable surprises here. The Steelers, who have dropped their last two games are hoping a home matchup against the Colts can break in their favor as they look to distance themselves from the resurgent Ravens in the AFC North.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4570-d45b-affe-55f695a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared RB D’Andre Swift, WR Luther Burden III, RB Roschon Johnson, DE Dominique Robinson, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 9 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4575-d45b-affe-55f7abb70000</link>
      <description>The Bears will be without their lead back for the first time in 2025. That leaves rookie RB Kyle Monangai as the team’s default RB1 against one of the worst rush defenses in the NFL. Monangai, who has 20 carries over his past two outings, should be in every 12-team league fantasy lineup today, facing a Bengals defense allowing 133 rushing yards per game this season. Burden’s absence should mean more routes and targets for Olamide Zaccheaus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4575-d45b-affe-55f7abb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Terry McLaurin (quad) is expected to miss Week 10 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4573-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbf31b0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport also mentioned that McLaurin could miss Week 11. The Commanders then get a Week 12 bye, giving McLaurin a month to recover from his lingering quad injury. The Commanders didn’t put him on injured reserve, which would have forced him to sit for at least four games. That means they expect him to be back with fewer than four games missed, though things have yet to go as expected for McLaurin this year. Luke McCaffrey and Chris Moore will round out the team’s starting wide receiver trio until McLaurin returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4573-d1e7-a1fa-5ffbf31b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaguars LB Devin Lloyd (calf) is not expected to play in Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-457c-d45b-affe-55fee18a0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd had a chance to return to action this week after being listed as questionable on Friday. He was limited in practice throughout the week. Holding him out for one more game should ensure Lloyd doesn’t re-aggravate the issue. He will eye a Week 10 return against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-457c-d45b-affe-55fee18a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence is dealing with an illness but will play in Week 9 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4583-d713-ad9e-6dd7e4af0000</link>
      <description>The news comes directly from the team. The Jags are just doing their due diligence with their injury report by adding Lawrence without changing his game-day designation. He should be good to go for the team’s Week 9 date with Vegas. With Travis Hunter out and Brian Thomas Jr. struggling in his sophomore season, Lawrence is stuck in the QB2 ranks this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-4583-d713-ad9e-6dd7e4af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Chiefs will “split carries” between Brashard Smith and Isiah Pacheco.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45ad-d45b-affe-55bfb3e40000</link>
      <description>Anything close to a 50/50 split would be a massive win for Smith. The rookie has been largely relegated to designed targets this year. He has seen more than four carries just once, a blowout win over the Raiders in which he handled mop-up duties. Hunt should still have the slight edge in carries, but Smith is firmly in the RB3 ranks with Isiah Pacheco on the sidelines. Rapoport also noted that the Chiefs could be in the market for an explosive running back ahead of the trade deadline. Breece Hall is the biggest name potentially available, though it’s rare for stars as big as Hall to get moved in the middle of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45ad-d45b-affe-55bfb3e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns “do not sound inclined” to trade David Njoku.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45b9-d45b-affe-55bf4b400000</link>
      <description>Schefter reports that instead of being sellers at the deadline, the Browns are “still looking to add quality young players to their roster.” If the price is right, the Browns could potentially buy low ahead of the deadline despite being largely out of the playoff race. We don’t, however, expect any splashy moves from the team. Njoku will continue to split snaps with rookie Harold Fannin Jr. down the stretch, though it wouldn’t be surprising for the latter to see more work as the season wears on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45b9-d45b-affe-55bf4b400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans QB C.J. Stroud (concussion evaluation) left Houston’s Week 9 game against the Broncos and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45e2-d713-ad9e-6df65ac10000</link>
      <description>A late sliding Stroud was hit in the shoulder by Kris Abrams-Draine, and the back of his helmet hit the turf hard. Stroud hit the medical tent to be checked after lying on the turf for a few minutes. He then retreated back into the locker room with trainers. Davis Mills will take over as Texans quarterback until Stroud returns. Stroud was 6-for-10 for 79 yards before leaving, leading the Texans to two field-goal attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-45e2-d713-ad9e-6df65ac10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
