<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze caught 2-of-5 targets for 32 yards in the Bears’ Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</link>
      <description>Odunze nearly had his fantasy day saved with an 11-yard touchdown, but that was negated by a penalty. It was a quiet day for the second-year wideout in a contest where the Bears relied heavily on D’Andre Swift in the run game. Expect Odunze to bounce back with more touches — and a potential trip to the end zone — against the Saints in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0cf-dd4c-afb9-e7cfcc670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said the team’s running backs might be focusing too much on ball security.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e29b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdd1e0000</link>
      <description>That focus on not fumbling, Vrabel said, is limiting some rushing plays in the Patriots offense. His comments come after a rash of fumbles and miscues from New England running backs during the first month of the regular season. Against a middling Saints defense in Week 6, Rhamondre Stevenson and TreVeyon Henderson combined for 45 yards on 22 carries in another pass-first game plan. It’s hard to say when — or if — the team’s backs will pay a proper amount of focus on not fumbling and costing the team points and themselves playing time. For now, Stevenson appears to be the nominal lead runner for the Patriots, who this week take on a Titans defense allowing 4.6 yards per rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e29b-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdd1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said he’s helping J.J. McCarthy (ankle) on “building that foundation back up.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e2ed-db72-a199-faefa11f0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell has reportedly spent the bye week working with McCarthy on improving his mechanics, especially his footwork, an area of concern over the season’s first two games before McCarthy apparently sustained a serious ankle injury that has kept him sidelined for more than a month. Concerns about McCarthy’s unrefined mechanics stretch back to the offseason, when the second-year QB would miss easy throws and held the ball long enough for the pass rush to get home in practices. O’Connell and the Vikings might have no choice but to turn back to McCarthy in Week 7 against the Eagles with Carson Wentz “managing a serious left shoulder injury,” according to The Athletic’s Alec Lewis. McCarthy would be a significant downgrade for all of Minnesota’s pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e2ed-db72-a199-faefa11f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (unknown) was hospitalized Monday evening following the Week 6 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e393-dd4c-afb9-e7d3de970000</link>
      <description>We’re still waiting on an update from the team after Moore finished the game against the Commanders but was mysteriously hospitalized Monday evening in the Washington area. Moore was notably seen blocking 15 yards downfield on the team’s final drive of the game, leading to the game-winning field goal. He did not travel home with the team while spending the night in a D.C. area hospital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e393-dd4c-afb9-e7d3de970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chiefs OC Matt Nagy and Steelers OC Arthur Smith are “names to watch” for the Titans head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3af-db72-a199-fbefd0660000</link>
      <description>These are both very logical fits as GM Mike Borgonzi has worked with Nagy on the Chiefs and Smith was a long-time Titans OC under Mike Vrabel. There’s familiarity with both of them in the building. Neither hire would be particularly inspiring as failed head coaches in Atlanta and Chicago, respectively. But of course it’s going to take a while for the coaching candidate cycle to truly pick up and we don’t know yet who will emerge as a new name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3af-db72-a199-fbefd0660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OL coach Bill Callahan resigned.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3be-d94a-a79d-ebbfd3500000</link>
      <description>Not a huge surprise, after all, they did fire his son from the head-coaching role. Callahan will be a coveted offseason coaching free agent and has a long history of success turning around bad offensive lines despite not delivering on that promise with the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3be-d94a-a79d-ebbfd3500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens released C.J. Gardner-Johnson from their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d0-def2-abdb-fff1eb970000</link>
      <description>The 27-year-old safety asked for his release after the Ravens traded for Alohi Gilman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d0-def2-abdb-fff1eb970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons LT Jake Matthews (ankle) left Atlanta’s Week 6 game against the Bills and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d5-d94a-a79d-ebddcec70000</link>
      <description>It’s one injury to watch ahead of Week 7, though it wasn’t like the Falcons had major problems on the offensive line without the 33-year-old veteran. Mike Jerrell played left tackle in Matthews’ absence for most of the second half on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3d5-d94a-a79d-ebddcec70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Brandon Aiyuk (knee) is getting “closer and closer” to returning to practice and mentioned Week 10 as a “rough estimate.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3dd-def2-abdb-fffd53d40000</link>
      <description>The 49ers head coach added that there’s no set date yet. Shanahan also estimated that Aiyuk would return in Week 6 in August. You may be aware that it is Week 7. While we’re sure to see some positive movement on Aiyuk over the next month, until we get word that the 49ers are going to open his 21-day return window, it’s hard to trust that he’s going to be back any time soon. We’d anticipate that Week 10 would be about the earliest he’d return based on how the 49ers have handled it thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3dd-def2-abdb-fffd53d40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said Jordan Watkins (calf) is expected to resume practicing this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3ed-dd4c-afb9-e7edbe950000</link>
      <description>We were just thinking the 49ers wideout projections needed another variable to deal with. Watkins briefly wowed in training camp before dealing with a high-ankle sprain and later this calf issue. It’s possible he cuts into some veteran playing time if the 49ers wideout room remains unsettled, but he’s not someone to rush and pick up in re-draft leagues without seeing some real signs of fantasy life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e3ed-dd4c-afb9-e7edbe950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
