<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:28:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 1-of-2 targets for 20 yards in San Francisco’s Week 4 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f9-d95b-addb-faff8b2e0000</link>
      <description>The fact that Robinson was only lightly mixed in (22 snaps) despite injuries ahead of him on the depth chart is pretty telling about his standing at the moment. Until we see signs of fantasy relevance, we’d avoid Robinson even if Ricky Pearsall and Juaun Jennings wind up missing more time in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92f9-d95b-addb-faff8b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco had seven rushes for 35 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding two catches for 13 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92fd-d6e9-af9d-9afd23550000</link>
      <description>It was a prime matchup for Pacheco and he couldn’t take advantage outside of a short touchdown grab. Kareem Hunt led the Chiefs with 13 rushes (for a mere 34 yards) while splitting the pass routes out of the KC backfield. Pacheco, who had 67 combined rushing yards over his previous two games, dropped a pass in this one and missed another blitz pick up — mistakes that could cost him valuable playing time in the coming weeks. Breshard Smith, meanwhile, saw four targets on just ten routes and could be carving out a role in the team’s passing attack. Appearing unconfident and unsure of his role in the offense, Pacheco probably shouldn’t be played in 12-team leagues next week against a stellar Jaguars rush defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-92fd-d6e9-af9d-9afd23550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua said he had X-rays on his thumb in the third quarter of the Rams’ Week 4 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9300-d6e9-af9d-9b909a310000</link>
      <description>We’ll assume this is a non-issue for the time being. Nacua said he was “rolled up on” during a run play, but returned to the game after his X-rays came back clear. Nacua posted a career-high 170 receiving yards on 13 receptions in Sunday’s victory. Barring an unexpected turn of events, it sounds like he will be good to go when the Rams return in Week 5 to play the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9300-d6e9-af9d-9b909a310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 25-of-37 attempts for 270 yards and four touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding four rushes for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9306-d95b-addb-fb461ab60000</link>
      <description>Mahomes made quick work on an injury-ravaged Baltimore defense missing six starters by the second half. Mahomes did his regular dink and dunk routine while mixing in a few deeper shots, mostly to Tyquan Thorton and Xavier Worthy, who returned from this Week 1 shoulder injury. Mahomes connected with four pass catchers for scores — Thornton, JuJu Smith-Schuster, Hollywood Brown, and Isiah Pacheco — on his way to a solid fantasy outing. He had not had more than one touchdown toss in any of his past three games, heading into Week 4 as one of the league’s most obvious regression candidates. Mahomes will be a borderline QB1 in Week 5 against a surprisingly solid Jacksonville defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9306-d95b-addb-fb461ab60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall said he felt “a little bit of instability” in his knee in Week 4’s loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9315-deb6-a7fd-d3dfaf310000</link>
      <description>Speaking after the game, Pearsall noted that he “fell pretty hard” and was in some pain while also experiencing some instability. He took the field for one more play to see if he could still go before opting to shut things down for the day, but Pearsall didn’t offer much insight as to how he thinks he could feel heading into a short week to prepare for the Rams on Thursday night. His name is one of many we will have to keep an eye out for when the Niners release their estimated injury report on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9315-deb6-a7fd-d3dfaf310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith had four rushes for nine yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding three catches for 27 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9316-d6e9-af9d-9b96b14a0000</link>
      <description>Smith is clearly the back with the most burst and elusiveness in the KC backfield, but continues to play well behind Isiah Pacheco and Kareem Hunt, who averaged two yards per carry in Week 4. The rookie’s three grabs were the first of his season, and could signal that the Chiefs are ready to use Smith more often in the passing game. Smith is an interesting roster add in deeper formats in case Hunt or Pacheco miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9316-d6e9-af9d-9b96b14a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 3-of-4 targets for nine yards in the Bucs’ Week 4 loss against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-931e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f2e370000</link>
      <description>Otton was third among Bucs pass catchers in targets while running nearly all the routes. He now has six catches over the season’s first four games and profiles as a deep league option for as long as Mike Evans is sidelined with a hamstring injury. The Bucs remains a pass-first offense, which could fuel routes and target volume for Otton next week against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-931e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f2e370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White had six rushes for 17 yards in the Bucs’ Week 4 loss against the Eagles, adding four catches for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-932b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbeb130000</link>
      <description>White had ten touches while Bucky Irving had 20 touches for 165 yards and a touchdown, fueled by a 72-yard touchdown catch from Baker Mayfield. White saw most of his involvement in the second half, and remains one of the league’s most involved RB2 options. He now has 23 rushing attempts through four weeks and has eaten into Irving’s pass-catching role enough to be concerning on days when Irving doesn’t catch a long touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-932b-dca3-a9fb-bfbbeb130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt had 13 rushes for 24 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 4 win against the Ravens, adding one catch for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933c-dca3-a9fb-bfbdb3fe0000</link>
      <description>Hunt easily led the KC backfield with 14 touches while Isiah Pacheco had seven carries and caught a short touchdown in the team’s blowout win. Hunt and Pacheco largely split route running duties against the Ravens, though rookie RB Brashad Smith mixed in with three receptions for 27 yards on four targets. Hunt, the team’s primary goal line back in the early season, is a low-ceiling weekly option in deeper leagues for as long as Smith doesn’t take on a larger role in the KC offense. Hunt has 36 rushes over the season’s first four weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933c-dca3-a9fb-bfbdb3fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Miles Sanders (ankle) is questionable to return to Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933e-dca3-a9fb-bfbf298d0000</link>
      <description>Sanders was escorted to the locker room ahead of the half with an ankle injury and was deemed questionable to return after the break. Sideline reporter Melissa Stark said he is going to try to return to the game. Sanders managed eight yards on two carries and 17 yards on two receptions prior to departing. Backfield depth is an issue if Sanders can’t make it back on the field with only Javonte Williams and fullback Hunter Luepke active for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-933e-dca3-a9fb-bfbf298d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
