<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:14:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef4d-d651-a9df-ef5d4b980000</link>
      <description>It seems like Watson may still be a week away from returning. Earlier today, Packers OC Adam Stenavich told reporters that Watson is “taking a few more reps” every day and hopes that “someday soon we’ll get him out there.” Watson can be stashed in 12-team leagues, though it may take him a few weeks to get up to speed once he is active on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef4d-d651-a9df-ef5d4b980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that there is “real concern that Terry McLaurin (quad) might miss another game this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef18-df81-ab9b-ffdf69110000</link>
      <description>McLaurin practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday before sitting out on Thursday. We do not yet have details on what changed. A setback is possible, though McLaurin may have simply realized his quad is not yet ready to play after giving it a go on Wednesday. Hopefully, WR Deebo Samuel (heel) can practice tomorrow. He has not yet practiced this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef18-df81-ab9b-ffdf69110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef56-df81-ab9b-ffd7bec90000</link>
      <description>Atwell could have a FLEX-worthy role in Week 7 against the Jaguars with Puka Nacua (ankle) likely sidelined. Atwell was limited yesterday, so his progression is promising. As long as Atwell makes it through Friday’s practice without re-injury, he should be good to go. Fellow WR Jordan Whittington will also likely mix in as a passing game contributor this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef56-df81-ab9b-ffd7bec90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams RB Blake Corum (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5b-d99b-a1dd-ff5f40980000</link>
      <description>Corum’s return to practice puts him on track to play, and likely pours cold water on Jarquez Hunter’s stash value. Corum was not involved enough to warrant weekly standalone value pre-injury, but he remains a valuable bench stash, given Kyren Williams’ high-end workloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5b-d99b-a1dd-ff5f40980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Jerry Jeudy (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5ddf560000</link>
      <description>The Browns’ No. 1 wide receiver was already playing inefficiently. Although he faces the Dolphins’ fantasy-friendly defense in Week 7, his knee injury adds another negative variable to his range of potential outcomes. Assuming Jeudy is good to go, he can only be viewed as a boom-bust FLEX option. Weather forecasts will be worth monitoring for those who are considering Jeudy as a starter this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5ddf560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Bengals QB Joe Burrow (toe) is on track to return in mid-December.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef61-df81-ab9b-ffe767e80000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that Burrow is currently just one month into his three-month recovery, but this is good news nonetheless. Although the Bengals are currently 2-4, they trail only the Steelers (4-1) in the AFC North standings. As long as they can remain in the hunt for a playoff spot, Bengals fans have a chance to see Burrow retake the field later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef61-df81-ab9b-ffe767e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is expected to be back for the Ravens’ Week 8 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5de5d50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s report backs up what Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said earlier this week. Both the Ravens and fantasy managers can expect to have their elite QB1 back in the lineup against the Bears’ welcoming defense next week. Credit to the Ravens for handling Jackson’s soft tissue strain smartly by allowing him to take the requisite time off for it to heal despite falling to a 1-5 record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5de5d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6ff0b80000</link>
      <description>Johnston has not yet graduated to full practice participation, so fantasy managers must view him as questionable to play in the Chargers’ Week 7 game against the Colts this week. Were he to sit, rookie WR Tre’ Harris would get another chance to carve out a role in the offense. He caught 4-of-5 targets for just 24 yards with Johnston sidelined last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6ff0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Brashard Smith (illness) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6f-da18-a39b-ff7f06c90000</link>
      <description>Smith was back at it on Thursday after taking the day off on Wednesday, so he should be good to go for the Chiefs’ Week 7 game against the Raiders. The intriguing rookie remains a high-upside bench stash, having logged seven touches on 12 snaps over the last two weeks. The coaching staff currently trusts Isiah Pacheco and Kareem Hunt despite their inefficient play, but Smith’s involvement remains promising.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6f-da18-a39b-ff7f06c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Riq Woolen (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 7 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef73-d651-a9df-ef776b5c0000</link>
      <description>Woolen is also the subject of trade rumors after up-and-down early-season performances. Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and S Julian Love (hamstring) remain limited, while LB Derick Hall (oblique) remains sidelined. The Seahawks are tasked with containing Nico Collins on Monday night. Getting Witherspoon and Love back would be a big boost in that regard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef73-d651-a9df-ef776b5c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
