<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions requested an interview with Steelers offensive coordinator Arthur Smith for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c1ff-d968-a19b-d9ff70f40000</link>
      <description>The Lions are in need of a new OC after firing John Morton. Morton lasted one season on the job and was stripped of play-calling duties late in the year. Head coach Dan Campbell took over that responsibility from Week 10 onward. The offense got more aggressive under Campebll but wasn’t that much more successful. Campbell is expected to give over play-calling duties to his next coordinator. Smith would likely get a lot out of Jahmyr Gibbs and David Montgomery, but his history of run-first football would not bode well for Jared Goff and the rest of the passing attack. For a team chasing the loss of offensive guru Ben Johnson, Smith would be a markedly underwhelming hire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c1ff-d968-a19b-d9ff70f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Panthers defensive coordinator Ejiro Evero for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c21c-d35e-a1bf-c7dea9800000</link>
      <description>Evero has been one of the more highly-regarded defensive coordinators in the league for a while. He has been with the Panthers as their DC for three years and previously spent a year in Denver with the same role. The Panthers just finished in the top half of the league in yards and points allowed, though they were a below-average unit by EPA per play. Evero has head coaching interviews with the Raiders, Falcons, and Steelers. He also received head coaching looks last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c21c-d35e-a1bf-c7dea9800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Maxwell Hairston (ankle) will not play in the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c283-d35e-a1bf-c7c3d2fb0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Poyer will also miss this game with a hamstring issue. Neither player was able to practice before today. The Bills will be undermanned in the secondary as they travel to take on the Broncos in Denver. Per usual, it will be up to Josh Allen to put the team on his bcak this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c283-d35e-a1bf-c7c3d2fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT Ed Oliver (bicep) is questionable for the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c296-dc7a-af9b-cfbff3a60000</link>
      <description>Oliver and Curtis Samuel, also questionable, are on injured reserve. The Bills have to activate them from injured reserve tomorrow if they are going to play, so we will get more information on them soon. Oliver is the bigger name between the two, but even Samuel could be an important piece in the offense. Tyrell Shavers and Gabe Davis suffered season-ending injuries last week and Josh Palmer was placed on IR ahead of the playoffs. Oliver has only appeared in three games this year. He has a sack in each game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c296-dc7a-af9b-cfbff3a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers requested an interview with Packers defensive coordinator Jeff Hafley for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2a4-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb5e80000</link>
      <description>The Steelers are now up to seven interview requests for the opening left by Mike Tomlin. Six of them are with defensive coordinators. Without a young quarterback in need of an offensive mind at the helm, it looks like Pittsburgh will attack the other side of the ball with its head coaching hire. Hafley has been contacted by six teams for head coaching interviews. He has held the role of defensive coordinator in Green Bay for two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2a4-dc7a-af9b-cfbfb5e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Nico Collins (concussion) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2d9-d35e-a1bf-c7db7c5f0000</link>
      <description>The Houston Chronicle’s Jonathan M. Alexander believes Collins is “a long shot” to play on Sunday against the Patriots, given “the steps he must clear.” Unfortunately, he might be right. Collins still has time to advance through the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol, but another absence at tomorrow’s practice would be discouraging. Veteran slot WR Christian Kirk stepped up last week, catching 8-of-9 targets for 144 yards and one touchdown in the Texans’ Wild Card win over the Steelers. We expect him to operate as the team’s top target earner if Collins cannot play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2d9-d35e-a1bf-c7db7c5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed an interview with Packers DC Jeff Hafley for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2d8-d968-a19b-daf9b64f0000</link>
      <description>NBC Sports’ Pro Football Talk notes that Hafley has already interviewed with the Dolphins and Titans. The Raiders, Cardinals and Steelers hope to do the same. The Packers’ defensive coordinator will continue to be a busy interviewee, unless one of the prior teams makes him an offer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2d8-d968-a19b-daf9b64f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2df-d56e-afff-e6ff70fe0000</link>
      <description>Minter interviewed with the Ravens yesterday. Assuming he accepts the remaining requests, he has six reported interviews left, unless one of these teams makes him an offer he cannot refuse. The Raiders are searching for their identity after rolling with a well-seasoned coaching staff in 2024. Minter, 42, could bring a fresh perspective.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2df-d56e-afff-e6ff70fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders completed an interview with Panthers DC Ejiro Evero for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ea-dc7a-af9b-cfff33fe0000</link>
      <description>This is Evero’s first reported interview. He has also received interview requests from the Steelers and Falcons this week. Evero’s defenses have delivered volatile results over the last three seasons, but the 45-year-old coach evidently remains a respected figure in league circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ea-dc7a-af9b-cfff33fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers promoted assistant QB coach and pass game specialist Mike Bercovici to pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e80000</link>
      <description>Bercovici recently interviewed for the Commanders’ offensive coordinator vacancy, but the Panthers opt not to let Bercovici walk. Bercovici, 32, began his coaching career at Arizona State as a graduate assistant in 2019. He signed on with the Cardinals in 2020 as a coaching assistant before being promoted to offensive assistant in 2022. He joined the Panthers’ coaching staff in 2023 and has been there ever since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c2ef-dc7a-af9b-cfff69e80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
