<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 18 times for 169 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills, adding 13 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2787-db7b-a5dd-a787027f0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens completely controlled the game on the legs of Henry and quarterback Lamar Jackson, with Henry amassing a ridiculous 123 yards and a score on nine first half carries. Henry also managed 86 yards after contact on the team’s first three possessions alone in what appeared to be a convincing road victory. Things sputtered in the second half for the Ravens even though Henry added another score from 46 yards out, punctuated by a fumble while nursing an eight point lead with just over three minutes remaining. Even with the disappointing loss, Henry reminded us all that Father Time has yet to catch up to his massive frame. He started his 2025 season on track to challenge 2,000 yards yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2787-db7b-a5dd-a787027f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 7-of-9 targets for 143 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills, adding eight yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278c-de13-afdd-67cf0f9a0000</link>
      <description>After a quiet first half that was dominated by Derrick Henry and Lamar Jackson, Flowers erupted for catches of 39 yards, 23 yards, and 36 yards to set a new career high in receiving with 143 yards. His touchdown came on his 23-yard grab in the third quarter that pushed Baltimore’s lead to 14 points. The nine targets also accounted for a robust 47.4 percent team target market share on just 19 Jackson pass attempts, with no other pass-catcher on the team seeing more than a modest four looks. Flowers and the Ravens draw another difficult matchup against the Jets on the road in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278c-de13-afdd-67cf0f9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught his only target for four yards in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278f-d332-a1fd-b7bffdc90000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Lamar Jackson attempted only 19 passes in a game the team controlled until the final kick, losing in spectacular fashion via a Matt Prater walk-off field goal after leading by 15 points twice in the fourth quarter. The fantasy returns from the veteran tight end were particularly disappointing considering fellow tight end Isaiah Likely was unable to suit up. Andrews is never overly likely to see immense target volume considering his advanced age and the run-focused nature of the offense, gaining most of his value from his robust red zone role. It was veteran wide receiver DeAndre Hopkins that cashed in on a touchdown from just outside the red zone in this one, but it is worth noting that only one of the team’s five touchdowns came from within 20 yards. We should see better fantasy days ahead for Andrews, with managers hoping that start in Week 2 on the road against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278f-d332-a1fd-b7bffdc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught both targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2795-dbe3-a9bb-37d746bc0000</link>
      <description>Hopkins made a spectacular, one-handed grab through two defenders for a touchdown in the third quarter, giving the Ravens their second 15-point lead of the final frame. Two three-and-outs and a Derrick Henry fumble allowed the Bills to score 16 unanswered points in the final four minutes to snatch the victory away. Hopkins was not in a route enough to return consistent fantasy production, something likely to remain the case throughout the season as the aging veteran adapts to a reduced role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2795-dbe3-a9bb-37d746bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 2-of-4 targets for 10 yards in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2798-db7b-a5dd-a79c80210000</link>
      <description>Bateman was an afterthought in the offensive game plan as the Ravens played with a lead for most of the game. His four targets ranked second on the team behind only Zay Flowers, but were not enough to return any fantasy value on just 19 Lamar Jackson pass attempts. Bateman remains a touchdown-dependent fantasy asset on a run-heavy offense in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2798-db7b-a5dd-a79c80210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed RT Colton McKivitz to a three-year, $45 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-294e-dbe3-a9bb-395faaab0000</link>
      <description>McKivitz was in the final year of his deal and is now tied to the Niners through the 2028 season. The sixth-year tackle cemented himself as a starter in 2023 and has started all 35 regular-season games he’s appeared in since then. McKivitz allowed just two sacks on 36 pressures last season, turning in arguably the best year while earning a PFF blocking grade of 72.2. His solid performances and availability over the years make McKivitz an easy player to invest in for the foreseeable future, and should solidify the Niners’ right side of the line for three more years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-294e-dbe3-a9bb-395faaab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Eagles are hosting free agent CB Mike Hilton for a visit.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-298c-d332-a1fd-bfbe5ed20000</link>
      <description>Hilton has spent the last four seasons with the Bengals. He appeared in 16 games for them last season, totaling 73 tackles and one interception while also breaking up five passes. The Eagles’ corners struggled at times in the team’s Week 1 win over the Cowboys and could benefit from adding a veteran like Hilton to shore up a secondary that C.J. Gardner-Johnson and Darius Slay this offseason. If signed, Hilton shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a depth player who can contribute in nickel and dime packages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-298c-d332-a1fd-bfbe5ed20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Christian Darrisaw’s (knee) “status is murky” for Week 1’s game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2998-db7b-a5dd-a99c16820000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw was listed as questionable entering the weekend but may be trending toward missing Monday night’s Week 1 game against the Bears. Darrisaw suffered a season-ending knee injury in Week 8 of last season. Rapoport suggests that even if Darrisaw does play, the team may opt to take it easy on him in his return, which could lead to backup Justin Skule seeing more snaps than initially expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2998-db7b-a5dd-a99c16820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Allen Lazard was inactive for Week 1 due to the two weeks of camp he missed.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29ad-db7b-a5dd-a9ad52d90000</link>
      <description>Glenn didn’t say if Lazard would be active for Week 2’s game against the Bills, but said the decision to scratch him for Week 1 was made because they want to make sure he’s up to speed with the offense. Garrett Wilson led the Jets with 7-95-1 through the air in Sunday’s loss, but fellow receivers Tyler Johnson and Josh Reynolds combined for just four receptions for 49 additional yards. Lazard won’t make for a huge upgrade at the position, but he should provide a bit more than Johnson and Reynolds did if he’s active next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29ad-db7b-a5dd-a9ad52d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE Harold Fannin played 55 snaps in Week 1’s loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29b6-d332-a1fd-bfb66d850000</link>
      <description>The snap total comes courtesy of PFF. Fannin, who surprised with a receiving line of 7-63-0 on a team-high nine targets, saw the fourth-most snaps of any Browns offensive position player in Week 1, and found himself lining up all over the formations. In addition to playing 41.7 percent of his snaps in the slot, Fannin also lined up 29 times as an inline tight end and took three snaps out of the backfield. It’s only one week, but Fannin’s usage was no fluke. He’s a priority add in all formats for fantasy managers looking to improve at tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-29b6-d332-a1fd-bfb66d850000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
