<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (finger) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a858-d82c-a79a-bbdcf80a0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t even miss a practice after being sidelined ahead of Week 11’s game with the Browns. Humphrey will return and help limit the Jets’ new-look passing game in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a858-d82c-a79a-bbdcf80a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (calf) is not on Baltimore’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a85a-db57-afda-fe7aff6b0000</link>
      <description>Back to the TE2 mines for Likely, a good player stuck behind Mark Andrews in the pecking order. He’s not a must-play against the Jets in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a85a-db57-afda-fe7aff6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) is questionable to play in Week 12 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a84b-d90e-a9da-bf4f66670000</link>
      <description>Johnson has a chance to return this week, after practicing in a limited fashion on Thursday and Friday. Cardinals LB Baron Browning (concussion) has, unfortunately, been ruled out once more. He was unable to resume practicing as he works through his brain injury. Fellow CB Garrett Williams (ankle) is also questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a84b-d90e-a9da-bf4f66670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said RT Spencer Brown (shoulder) could go on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a862-d90e-a9da-bf6f19d50000</link>
      <description>Brown left Week 12’s loss to the Texans twice and came back with a sling towards the end of the fourth quarter. While doctors are still evaluating him, it doesn’t sound like good news. Ryan Van Demark came on for Brown towards the end of the game and would likely be his replacement going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a862-d90e-a9da-bf6f19d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said LB Terrel Bernard (shoulder) could possibly land on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a865-db57-afda-fe7794360000</link>
      <description>Bernard was spotted on the sideline in a sling during the game after his injury. We’d be surprised if he was able to go in Week 13, but it’s still theoretically possible he avoids IR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a865-db57-afda-fe7794360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Sterling Shepard (shoulder) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a867-d413-ad9f-bdffbf020000</link>
      <description>He got in full sessions on both Thursday and Friday. Shepard would retain some low-end PPR scam juice if Chris Godwin remains sidelined this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a867-d413-ad9f-bdffbf020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said CB Maxwell Hairston is in the NFL’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a863-d90e-a9da-bf6fc93d0000</link>
      <description>Hairston suffered a concussion in the Bills’ Week 12 loss to the Texans on Thursday Night Football. The rookie cornerback has forced one incompletion and notched two interceptions since taking the field in Week 8, following a training camp knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a863-d90e-a9da-bf6fc93d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (illness) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a869-db57-afda-fe7b7c290000</link>
      <description>Neither is Emeka Egbuka. Whatever was going around in Tampa Bay earlier this week has dissipated, as all six players listed with illness recovered and are not on the final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a869-db57-afda-fe7b7c290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) is questionable for Week 12.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a86b-d90e-a9da-bf6f016a0000</link>
      <description>Todd Bowles said that Godwin is “trending toward playing” earlier today. He went limited-full-limited in his three practice sessions this week and seems to be on the optimistic side of questionable. Godwin will probably be more of a FLEX than a WR3 in Week 13 due to a tough opponent (Rams) and the re-injury risk, but he could be startable in the playoffs if everything breaks right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a86b-d90e-a9da-bf6f016a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 12 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a88b-d82c-a79a-bb9f16910000</link>
      <description>Crosby practiced fully on Friday, restoring faith in the Raiders D/ST unit. Browns rookie QB Shedeur Sanders will make his first career start and Crosby and Co. this weekend. Sanders notched a 20.0 percent pressure-to-sack rate on 21 dropbacks in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a88b-d82c-a79a-bb9f16910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
