<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said he’d “watch” Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb as a potential candidate for the Bills head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7eb-d35e-a1bf-d7ebd7070000</link>
      <description>“He’s really close to Josh Allen,” Pelissero says while noting the Bills are focusing on a more offensive-minded coach. Apparently multiple teams are waiting for the Broncos to be eliminated to get Webb in for a second interview per Pelissero’s reporting. Based on that, it sure seems likely that the 30-year-old former NFL quarterback stands a good chance of leaving the cycle with a head-coaching gig. The NFL Network reporter also says that Joe Brady is “a candidate, but I don’t know if he isthecandidate” in Buffalo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d7eb-d35e-a1bf-d7ebd7070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero says “the teams to watch” for former Bills head coach Sean McDermott are Pittsburgh, Baltimore, and Tennessee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d804-d968-a19b-d8f52a8b0000</link>
      <description>“It doesn’t make a ton of sense for him to go into a total rebuild” per Pelissero, who rules out Arizona and Las Vegas as landing spots for McDermott. Pelissero mentions that McDermott would be outside of the normal bucket the Steelers hire from, and says Baltimore “makes a lot of sense” while the Titans brass has mutual ties to McDermott from his work with Andy Reid. Seeing McDermott coach Lamar Jackson might be the funniest idea we’ve ever heard of, so of course we’re for it. The Titans also seem like a reasonable landing spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d804-d968-a19b-d8f52a8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Vikings DC Brian Flores will interview with the Steelers on Tuesday for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d807-d35e-a1bf-ddc7d3780000</link>
      <description>Flores has long been considered a potential replacement for Mike Tomlin, and will now have a chance to meet with the team he spent the 2022 season with under Tomlin. The former Dolphins head coach has spent the last three seasons as the Vikings’ defensive coordinator, and over that span, elevated the defense from one of the worst in the league to being a top-10 unit. In addition to fielding head coaching requests from the Steelers and Ravens, Flores has also met with the Commanders to discuss their defensive coordinator vacancy. If he’s unable to land a head coaching job, the option to return to Minnesota remains on the table, but Flores is in high demand after turning in one of his strongest years as a coordinator to date.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d807-d35e-a1bf-ddc7d3780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Raiders DC Patrick Graham for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d810-d968-a19b-d8f1de370000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are the first team to meet with Graham as a potential head coaching fit this cycle. The long-time defensive coordinator was in the same role with the Dolphins during the 2019 season, but has spent the last four seasons as the Raiders’ defensive coordinator despite the team going through three head coaching changes over that span. Graham’s defense allowed the fourth-lowest yards per carry on the ground last season, but ranked 25th in points allowed and 14th in total yards allowed. Graham becomes the eighth coach to interview with the Fins for their head coach opening. We’ll see if he’s one of the few called back for a second interview in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d810-d968-a19b-d8f1de370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers EDGE Mykel Williams (knee) said he “should be” ready to go right around training camp.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d81c-d968-a19b-d8fdb5760000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Williams, who tore his ACL in early November, should be ready for the start of the season based on that timeline. He’ll be penciled in next to fellow injury returner Nick Bosa as the 49ers two starting EDGE players next year. Williams managed one sack in nine starts during his rookie season, adding 20 tackles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d81c-d968-a19b-d8fdb5760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs hired Bears RB coach Eric Bieniemy as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d81f-d968-a19b-d8ff695e0000</link>
      <description>Apparently, there wasn’t much to think about when deciding whether Andy Reid would be interested in running things back with Bieniemy. Bieniemy was a member of Reid’s coaching staff from 2013 to 2022 and served as offensive coordinator beginning in 2018 until leaving for the Commanders during the 2023 offseason. During Bieniemy’s time as OC, the Chiefs never finished worse than sixth in scoring, although some of that could also be a direct reflection of the team having Tyreek Hill in his prime to stretch the field and make defenders miss. Last year’s offensive coordinator, Matt Nagy, saw his contract expire at the end of this season and he is in the mix for multiple head coaching opening across the league. The Chiefs had their worst offensive season of the Patrick Mahomes era in 2025. Hopefully, an infusion of young talent this offseason coupled with the return if Bieniemy can lead to a bounce-back for an offense that was among the league’s best the last time he coached the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d81f-d968-a19b-d8ff695e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TitansInsider’s Terry McCormick believes it “sure feels like” Matt Nagy is the frontrunner for the Titans head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d836-d56e-afff-fefef1e30000</link>
      <description>49ers DC Robert Saleh is meeting with the Titans this afternoon and giving his final sales pitch. McCormick adds that Packers DC Jeff Hafley may get “full-court press[ed]” by the Dolphins this afternoon before he can get to Tennessee. Nagy and the Titans have been a rumored pair for a long time — it was one of the first names to emerge after the firing of Brian Callahan. Perhaps the sudden availability of Sean McDermott will get the Titans to keep things cool for a bit — it sure doesn’t feel like anyone else is as imminently interested in hiring Nagy as they are, as the Titans are the only place so far we have with a reported second interview for the former Chiefs OC. Or perhaps this is going to wrap up in short order. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d836-d56e-afff-fefef1e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins to hire Packers DC Jeff Hafley as their next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d848-d968-a19b-d8f9fe7f0000</link>
      <description>This news comes via NFL Network’s The Insiders, as Hafley is expected to sign a deal to become the next head coach of the Dolphins in the very near future. Ian Rapoport notes that while a deal still needs to be worked out, Hafley and the Dolphins are highly motivated to get a deal done. The move to Miami will reunite Hafley with new Dolphins GM Jon-Eric Sullivan, who worked with Hafley in Green Bay over the last two seasons. Hafley re-joined the NFL ranks in 2024 after spending five seasons in the college ranks, and helped lead the Packers defense to top-12 finishes in both of his seasons. He’ll now look to round out his first coaching staff in the coming days as he prepares to lead a Dolphins team that finished 7-10 last season while ranking 24th or worst in scoring on both sides of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d848-d968-a19b-d8f9fe7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports 49ers DC Robert Saleh is meeting in person with the Titans on Monday for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d856-d56e-afff-fefe65ec0000</link>
      <description>Saleh was initially set to meet with the Titans virtually on Sunday, but instead pushed his interview to Monday so he could hold an in-person meeting with the team. His interview comes shortly after the team wrapped things up with former Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy, who is believed by some to be the front runner to land the position. Schultz reported earlier that Saleh, Nagy, and Jeff Hafley were believed to be the top three choices for the Titans, who recently saw Hafley get taken off the market by the Dolphins. If there’s any truth to Saleh and Nagy being the Titans’ top options, they’ll likely move quickly to close the deal with their preferred candidate as they look to find the coach best fit to lead the franchise and No. 1 overall pick Cam Ward into the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d856-d56e-afff-fefe65ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Cardinals have scheduled a second interview on Tuesday with 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d867-dc7a-af9b-dfff00470000</link>
      <description>Saleh is currently interviewing with the Titans for their head coaching vacancy. If he lives without a deal, he will be on his way to Arizona for a second meeting with the Cardinals on Tuesday. Saleh has made the rounds this coaching cycle, meeting with four different teams to discuss their head-coaching vacancies, with the Cardinals being the first team to put in a second request. The former Jets head coach returned to the Bay Area in 2025 to lead the Niners defense to a 13th-ranked finish in points allowed, and is clearly a valued candidate on the coaching market despite going 20-36 in his first try as a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-d867-dc7a-af9b-dfff00470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
