<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:44:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Courtland Sutton caught 1-of-2 targets for five yards in the Broncos’ Week 18 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bcb-d35e-a1bf-cfcbb7790000</link>
      <description>Sutton simply ran cardio in this one. The Broncos’ No. 1 wide receiver led the receiving corps with 46 offensive snaps, yet earned just two targets. His lone reception occurred with roughly six minutes left in the third quarter. To Sutton’s credit, he successfully forced a missed tackle after QB Bo Nix dumped off to him on 3rd-and-8. Unfortunately, Sutton was unable to pick up the first down. He goes on bye next week with the Broncos having secured the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bcb-d35e-a1bf-cfcbb7790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 2-of-5 targets for 20 yards in the Commanders’ Week 18 win over the Eagles, adding one yard on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8be0-dc7a-af9b-cfffac3a0000</link>
      <description>Samuel joined Washington in the offseason and operated as the Commanders’ No. 1 wide receiver with Terry McLaurin holding out before the season and dealing with a quad injury during the season. He is primarily a slot receiver that sees rushing opportunities out of the backfield. The 29-year-old finished the year with 72 receptions for 727 yards and five touchdowns, rushing 17 times for 75 yards and a touchdown. He failed to hit 100 yards receiving in any games this season, the first time that has happened in his career. Samuel was off to a fast start with at least six receptions in four out of the first five games of the season, but had only one such game the rest of the way. He finishes a 71.0 PFF receiving grade, good for No. 40 among wide receivers. Samuel is slated to enter free agency in the offseason and will find a role as a veteran slot receiver, whether for the Commanders or another team next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8be0-dc7a-af9b-cfffac3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treylon Burks caught 2-of-4 targets for 12 yards in the Commanders’ Week 18 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bea-d35e-a1bf-cfeac4f70000</link>
      <description>Burks signed to the Commanders’ practice squad in October after the Titans released him. He finished his year with the Commanders totaling 10 receptions for 130 yards and a touchdown. Burks is a candidate for catch of the year, making a highlight-reel five-yard touchdown grab with one hand in Week 13 against the Broncos. With Luke McCaffrey and Jaylin Lane out towards the end of the season, Burks became the team’s WR3, seeing a variety of targets as an outside receiver opposite Terry McLaurin. He is certainly an option to return to Washington next season, though he is likely to be a depth piece on whichever team employs him for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bea-d35e-a1bf-cfeac4f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports that Matt Ryan “is being strongly considered for a high-profile front office role with the Falcons.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bde-d35e-a1bf-cfde6a210000</link>
      <description>Per Schultz, the role would be similar to the one currently occupied by the Lions’ Chris Spielman, who serves as the special assistant to the owner and CEO. Schultz closes the report by saying, “we’ll see what happens with” Falcons CEO Rich McKay, “but ownership has been frustrated with how things have been run, and changes are happening at all levels.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bde-d35e-a1bf-cfde6a210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Sinnott caught both of his targets for three yards in the Commanders’ Week 18 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bef-d968-a19b-dbff164e0000</link>
      <description>Sinnott spent his second year seldom-used, sitting behind veteran Zach Ertz for much of the season. He started seeing double-digit passing-down snaps from Week 15 onwards, after Ertz tore his ACL. Sinnott only caught 11 total passes for 114 yards and a touchdown. The 23-year-old will enter his third season in 2026 and may finally be in line for the starting tight end role with Ertz unlikely to return. Sinnott is a former second-round pick who deserves TE2 consideration in Dynasty leagues due to his high draft capital and no elite veterans under contract next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bef-d968-a19b-dbff164e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Bates caught both of his targets for 13 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 18 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf5-d35e-a1bf-cff71c0b0000</link>
      <description>Predominantly used as a run blocker, Bates ran more routes after Zach Ertz tore his ACL in Week 14. He scored his first touchdown since 2022 in Week 18 against the Eagles, totaling 11 receptions for 103 yards and a score on the season. Bates’ contract is guaranteed for 2026, making it likely he returns for next season, though he will not be on fantasy radars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf5-d35e-a1bf-cff71c0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt had five rushes for 14 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 18 loss against the Raiders, adding three catches 21 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf8-dc7a-af9b-cfffe6180000</link>
      <description>With Isiah Pacheco inactive, Pacheco was a distant second to Breshard Smith (12 rushes, two receptions) in backfield touches. Hunt finishes the 2025 season with 611 yards on 158 rushes over 16 games, mostly functioning as the Chiefs’ short yardage and goal line back. He also had 15 catches for 122 yards and a touchdown in the pass-heavy Chiefs offense. Hunt, 30, heads into the offseason as an unrestricted free agent, though he could end up with the Chiefs again as he remains a favorite of head coach Andy Reid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf8-dc7a-af9b-cfffe6180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Moody converted 1-of-2 field goal attempts in the Commanders’ Week 18 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf7-d56e-afff-efffd64e0000</link>
      <description>Moody missed a chip shot 24-yard field goal in Week 18, but subsequently made a 56-yard field goal later. He spent the 2025 season bouncing between the 49ers, Bears, and Commanders. The 49ers cut him after missing a pair of field goals in Week 1, after which he signed to the Bears’ practice squad. The Commanders signed him off the Bears’ practice squad after he made eight field goals in two games for Chicago. Moody spent the final six games of the season with the Commanders; it remains to be seen if he will return to Washington or sign elsewhere for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf7-d56e-afff-efffd64e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant caught 4-of-5 targets for 31 yards in the Broncos’ Week 18 over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8be7-d56e-afff-efef51c40000</link>
      <description>Bryant’s team-high five targets accurately depict the Broncos’ offensive successes and failures today. Although they came away with a win, and the AFC’s No. 1 playoff seed, it was an underwhelming outing. Broncos head coach Sean Payton tried to get Bryant into the end zone on the team’s first drive by calling a screen pass for him from the Chargers’ five-yard line. He was stopped just two yards past the line of scrimmage. Bryant is on bye next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8be7-d56e-afff-efef51c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams rushed 12 times for 60 yards in the Rams’ Week 18 win over the Cardinals, adding three catches for 21 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf7-d968-a19b-dbf75c840000</link>
      <description>Williams was stuffed on his only goal line carry of the day, missing out on the opportunity to score his 11th rushing touchdown of the year. He ends the season with 1,252 yards and 10 scores on 259 attempts. Williams was out-carried by Blake Corum 13-12 in this contest, though Corum tallied five drives on LA’s final drive compared to just one for Williams. The two will continue to split work in the Wild Card Round versus the Panthers, making Williams a high-risk fantasy option next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8bf7-d968-a19b-dbf75c840000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
