<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said G Kevin Dotson (ankle) is “doubtful” for Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38aa-d35e-a1bf-7dea51140000</link>
      <description>He suffered an ankle sprain, and the fact that McVay is already grim on his chances to play in Week 17 doesn’t color his rest of season output with a rosy picture. Justin Dedich took over in the first quarter and seems likely to be Los Angeles’ starter in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38aa-d35e-a1bf-7dea51140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) is not on Las Vegas’ final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38b8-da28-afbb-fcfd9a990000</link>
      <description>Crosby, as usual, will be Las Vegas’ main defensive weapon against the Texans. IDP leaguers should note that he stands a good chance of wrecking shop against a weak Texans offensive line. Crosby continues to be given days off ahead of games as this going-nowhere season winds down for the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38b8-da28-afbb-fcfd9a990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) is questionable for Houston’s Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38ba-da28-afbb-fcffc0fe0000</link>
      <description>It’s an aggressive listing based on one limited practice, one that perhaps augurs that the Texans are just managing Marks through some existing injuries that they know are going to be tough to overcome in-season. If Marks starts, he’ll be a high-end RB2 against the Raiders. If not, Jawhar Jordan will be a worthwhile plug-and-play starter in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38ba-da28-afbb-fcffc0fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) is questionable for Houston’s Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38bc-d35e-a1bf-7dfe5b320000</link>
      <description>It’s a curious questionable tag since Chubb got in two full sessions on Thursday and Friday — several backs with that workload would be off the injury report entirely. Chubb could be a worthwhile FLEX play against the Raiders depending on who is active at 3 ET, but odds are he’ll probably split the workload with Jawhar Jordan if he is up and Woody Marks (ankle) is down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38bc-d35e-a1bf-7dfe5b320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (oblique) is questionable for Houston’s Week 16 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38be-d35e-a1bf-7dfe1b830000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session to get on to the questionable line after missing Wednesday and Thursday practice. Azeez Al-Shaair was limited on Thursday, but did not participate in Wednesday or Friday practice for the Texans. Both players should be considered true question marks for Week 16’s action against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38be-d35e-a1bf-7dfe1b830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) did not practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e4-da28-afbb-fcfd96780000</link>
      <description>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan initially said he expects Pearsall “to be alright.” He followed that statement up on Monday by saying “there is a concern” about Pearsall’s injuries. On Thursday, he said there is a “possibility” Pearsall plays on Monday night. This is nothing new. Return timelines have been all over the place with this team. Even if he does play, he will do so at less than 100.0 percent. Make a backup plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e4-da28-afbb-fcfd96780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Bears plan to activate LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) from injured reserve before Week 16 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3928-d35e-a1bf-7dea71d00000</link>
      <description>That’s great. Edmunds has not played since Week 11, but he still leads the team with 67 tackles. He has also recorded eight quarterback pressures, two sacks, two pass breakups and four interceptions. Getting him back is a big deal. The Packers (9-4-1) face the Bears (10-4) on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3928-d35e-a1bf-7dea71d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs TE Travis Kelce “plans to play in each of the final three games this season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e0-d087-addf-b9f08d460000</link>
      <description>We assumed this would be the case, but it is good to know nonetheless. The Chiefs are eliminated from playoff contention and Kelce’s “best friend on the roster,” QB Patrick Mahomes (knee),” is out for the year. The 36-year-old tight end needs just 203 receiving yards to “become the oldest tight end in the NFL’s history to record 1,000 yards in a season.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-38e0-d087-addf-b9f08d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Cowboys CB Trevon Diggs (knee) is likely to be activated for Week 16’s game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c6e-da28-afbb-fc7f57b30000</link>
      <description>This report comes on the heels of Diggs himself telling reporters earlier this week that he was healthy. The 27-year-old cornerback seemed miffed about not being activated from injured reserve earlier. If Diggs isn’t activated Saturday, he’ll be ineligible to return at all this year. While Rapoport reports an activation is likely, the final decision will come Saturday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3c6e-da28-afbb-fc7f57b30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
