<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Will Campbell (knee) will “probably be [out] more than a week or two.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b5fb-d90e-a9da-bfff9acc0000</link>
      <description>Campbell suffered his knee injury in Week 12’s win over the Bengals and is expected to undergo an MRI. We’ll likely learn more about the rookie’s status later in the day, but the star rookie has been solid in his first season, allowing five sacks and 25 pressures while earning a PFF pass blocking grade of 75.0. The Patriots were dealt multiple injuries to their OL in Sunday’s win, and could be looking at a patchwork group in Week 13 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b5fb-d90e-a9da-bfff9acc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) is in concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b600-db57-afda-f632b1730000</link>
      <description>With the Bengals playing on Thursday night against the Ravens, Higgins is up against a short turnaround time to clear protocol if he hopes to play in Week 13. Higgins caught five passes for 31 yards in the Bengals’ Week 12 loss to the Patriots, but entered the week with a four-game touchdown streak. His likely absence in Week 13 should free up more targets for Ja’Marr Chase against a Ravens secondary that’s ranked 24th in receiving yards allowed this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b600-db57-afda-f632b1730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots LT Will Campbell is believed to have suffered a torn MCL in Week 12’s win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b60d-d413-ad9f-b7dd2c560000</link>
      <description>An MRI will confirm Campbell’s injury and how much time he could miss, but the rookie tackle is likely facing a multi-week absence that could include a stint on the injured reserve. Backup Vederian Lowe is listed behind Campbell on the depth chart and will presumably draw the start after playing on 30 snaps in Week 12’s win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b60d-d413-ad9f-b7dd2c560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants fired DC Shane Bowen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b62b-d413-ad9f-b7ff0c880000</link>
      <description>The dismissal of Bowen has felt like a foregone conclusion for weeks, especially after losses to the Broncos and Bears in which they held double-digit leads with less than six minutes left. The Giants blew their fifth 10-point, fourth quarter lead of the season in Week 12’s loss to the Lions to tie an NFL record. The blown leads compounded with a defense that ranks 30th in both yards and points allowed simply became too much for a Giants team that is finishing out eight’s eighth losing season of the last nine years. Interim head coach Mike Kafka had the Giants in position to pull off an upset road win over the Lions but were outscored 17-0 after grabbing a 27-17 lead. Kafka has been a hot name in coaching circles over the last few offseasons, and is auditioning to become the next coach of the Giants over the final six weeks of the season, and needs all the help he can get from the staff in place. Kafka is expected to name an interim defensive coordinator in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b62b-d413-ad9f-b7ff0c880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants named OLB coach Charlie Bullen as interim DC.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b63b-d82c-a79a-b7bfce6c0000</link>
      <description>Bullen, 41, will call the plays on the defensive side of the ball for the Giants for the rest of the season. Boasting 12 years of NFL coaching experience, Bullen got his start with the Dolphins as a defensive assistant in 2012, and rose through the ranks in Miami before taking a job with the Cardinals as their assistant linebackers coach in 2019. Bullen has never held a role as a defensive coordinator and will now have five games to show his chops for a team in need of help at defensive play-calling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b63b-d82c-a79a-b7bfce6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Elliott missed his only field goal attempt and made all three of his extra point attempts in the Eagles’ Week 12 loss against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b655-d90e-a9da-bf5f69190000</link>
      <description>Elliott narrowly missed on a 52-yard attempt in the second half as the Eagles choked away a big lead to the Cowboys. He’s now missed three of his 14 field goal tries on the season. The Eagles’ red zone aggressiveness and use of the tush push near the goal line makes Elliott a dicey weekly bet for fantasy purposes. Elliott has one or zero field goal attempts in eight games this season. He should remain on waiver wires in Week 13 against Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b655-d90e-a9da-bf5f69190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Saints will host free agent K Justin Tucker for a tryout this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b68f-d413-ad9f-b7df8b2c0000</link>
      <description>Tucker’s 10-game suspension for violating the league’s personal conduct policy due to his involvement in sexually inappropriate behavior was lifted two weeks ago. Now, the 36-year-old kicker will have a chance to try out for the Saints, who are looking for a potential upgrade over Blake Grupe after his two missed field goals in Week 12’s loss to the Falcons. Tucker had his worst season as a pro in 2024, converting on a career-low 73.3 percent of his field goal attempts while going 11-for-19 from 40-plus yards. Among other participants in the tryout will be Cade York, who last kicked for the Commanders in 2024, going 0-for-2 on his attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b68f-d413-ad9f-b7df8b2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots LG Jared Wilson suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 12’s win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b69e-d90e-a9da-bf9fe9860000</link>
      <description>Rapoport reports the Patriots hope Wilson’s recovery time “is on the shorter side” of a 4-6 week recovery window, but the team will be without the rookie for the next few weeks. Wilson is one of two Patriots rookies to suffer multi-week injuries in Sunday’s win, as left tackle Will Campbell is feared to have suffered a torn MCL in the same game. The Patriots will have some work to do to figure out their offensive line entering Week 13 against the Giants, but backup Caedan Wallace figures to be first in line to replace Wilson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b69e-d90e-a9da-bf9fe9860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said the team will open Darren Waller’s (pec) 21-day return window this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6a4-d90e-a9da-bfafcabc0000</link>
      <description>Waller has appeared in just four games for the Dolphins this season, but the veteran receiver caught 10 passes for 117 yards and four touchdowns in those games, and was quickly developing into a key player for the offense. The Dolphins will have 21 days to either activate Waller or rule him out for the season. With matchups against the Saints and Jets on tap, Waller’s return could come at just the right time as the Dolphins hope to make a postseason push over the final month of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6a4-d90e-a9da-bfafcabc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chiefs RG Trey Smith “is dealing with both high- and low-ankle sprains.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc41720000</link>
      <description>The sprain is too low to be high, but too high to be low. According to Rapoport, Smith “is expected to miss some time,” which would include Thursday’s game against the Cowboys. The fifth-year guard has played in all 11 games for the Chiefs this season, earning a PFF grade of 71.4 on 577 snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b6ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc41720000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
