<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (neck) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d35-dc7a-af9b-cfbf74a90000</link>
      <description>Two limited practices would seem to have Williams well in line to play on Christmas. Will we get a full dose of Williams, or will the backfield continue to trend more towards a split with Malik Davis as the season winds down and the Cowboys are eliminated? The answer will probably tell us a lot about what on paper seems to be an RB2 smash spot against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d35-dc7a-af9b-cfbf74a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RB David Montgomery (illness) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d39-d968-a19b-5df9b8a90000</link>
      <description>We’d write that this increases the chances of Jahymr Gibbs consolidating the backfield touches, but he’s already done that since Dan Campbell started calling plays. Montgomery might get a little extra run on Thursday if the Lions manage to blow out the Max Brosmer-led Vikings, so he does perhaps have a little more FLEX upside than in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d39-d968-a19b-5df9b8a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets place QB Justin Fields (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d3d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf45a30000</link>
      <description>Fields looked downright unplayable for much of 2025, struggling to complete 10 passes at times and crossing 200 yards passing in just four of nine starts. The Jets also failed to really utilize his legs on designed plays for much of the season, leaving him with the worst of both worlds as a fantasy contributor. Still somehow only 26, Fields is no guarantee to see out the second year of his two-year contract with the Jets. A post-June 1 release would save the Jets $10 million in cap space. He also is a trade possibility. The knee injury is not incredibly significant, with Fields telling reporters in the locker room last week that he felt “week to week,” so he should be healthy for the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d3d-dc7a-af9b-cfbf45a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that George Kittle (ankle) is dealing with a “mid-to-low ankle sprain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d42-d968-a19b-5df345ff0000</link>
      <description>Kittle’s Week 17 status could be in jeopardy with the 49ers having already clinched a playoff berth, but we’ll keep the light on for the practice report since the 49ers are (miraculously) alive for the No. 1 seed in a must-win game against the Bears. Some are calling it the middest ankle sprain they’ve ever seen, the rare “Jeff Fisher 7-9" ankle sprain. We’ll check back in on Kittle on Wednesday, but fantasy managers should probably start preparing backup plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d42-d968-a19b-5df345ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans LT Aireontae Ersery (hand) had surgery and will miss an indefinite amount of time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d45-d968-a19b-5df58f540000</link>
      <description>He’ll presumably miss the rest of the regular season at the very least. Ersery finishes the campaign with a 58.7 PFF grade — decent, but nothing outstanding — and a surprisingly low 52.9 PFF run block grade as a rookie second-round starter on C.J. Stroud’s blind side. Blake Fisher replaced Ersery on Sunday when he left the game, but the Texans have enough versatility that it wouldn’t be a surprise if they lined up someone else there against the Chargers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d45-d968-a19b-5df58f540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE T.J. Hockenson (shoulder) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d4d-d56e-afff-efed20e80000</link>
      <description>You don’t need to wait for the rule out on Wednesday — with Max Brosmer under center, it’s a run-don’t-walk to the waiver wire to replace Hockenson in your Week 17 lineup. If you somehow made it to the championship with Hockenson in your lineup, we’re impressed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d4d-d56e-afff-efed20e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (ankle) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d4f-d968-a19b-5dff6cd50000</link>
      <description>He appears on track to start and play the main role on Thursday against the Lions, perhaps with Ty Chandler backing him up as it seems Jordan Mason won’t be able to make it active. Jones will probably be more of an RB3 with Max Brosmer under center against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d4f-d968-a19b-5dff6cd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d60-d968-a19b-5df1668b0000</link>
      <description>Very rare that we see a player clear the concussion protocol to play on a short-week Thursday. Even rarer that we see a player who was actually stretchered off the field play on a short-week Thursday. We expect plenty of Marvin Mims and Lil’Jordan Humphrey against the Chiefs on Thursday, is what we’re saying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d60-d968-a19b-5df1668b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring) is not practicing Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d62-d56e-afff-efea2b820000</link>
      <description>He left Denver’s Week 16 game against the Jaguars with a non-contact hamstring injury and currently has no timetable for a return. It definitely sounds like he won’t be suiting up against the Chiefs on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d62-d56e-afff-efea2b820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d6d-d968-a19b-5dfd82010000</link>
      <description>He was “day-to-day” per Ian Rapoport’s reporting, but the Chargers signed RB Jarret Patterson back to the active roster earlier today. It’s probably more likely than not that Vidal misses Week 17’s game against the Texans based on this practice status and that transaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4d6d-d968-a19b-5dfd82010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
