<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Colts QB Philip Rivers will start against the Seahawks in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</link>
      <description>Schefter reports that the Colts are signing Rivers to the active roster. The quarterback who turned 44 earlier this week and ranks seventh in all-time passing yards entering Week 15 was a semifinalist for this year’s Pro Football Hall of Fame class. Rivers will now have to wait another five years before he’s eligible again, assuming he retires again after this season. Fantasy managers considering using the signal caller who was in the same draft class as Eli Manning, who last played in 2019, in the fantasy playoffs have lost the plot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers added RB Emanuel Wilson (illness) to the injury report Saturday with a questionable designation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-18e8-d8cf-affb-bceae9f40000</link>
      <description>The team elevated RB Pierre Strong from the practice squad in an associated move, which comes as both Josh Jacobs and Wilson are listed as questionable. Stay tuned ahead of the team’s inactives Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-18e8-d8cf-affb-bceae9f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed TE Eric Saubert to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d8cf-affb-bd6e12030000</link>
      <description>Saubert played 2025 on a one-year contract, with the extension tying him to the Seahawks through the 2026 season. Largely lauded for his run-blocking and pass-blocking abilities, Saubert should return to contributing primarily from 12-personnel once he makes his way back from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d8cf-affb-bd6e12030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers downgraded RB Christian McCaffrey (back) to questionable for Week 15 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196e-d8cf-affb-bd6efae90000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey dealt with an illness that limited his practice participation this week. He was removed from the injury report Friday before being added back and listed as questionable Saturday with a bak injury. It is unclear when the new ailment surfaced. Late-week additions to the injury report are never something fantasy managers want to see, also leading to a significant decision in the first week of fantasy playoffs considering the 49ers don’t play until the afternoon Sunday. McCaffrey will remain a top tier RB1 if active against the Titans. Fantasy managers might want to hedge by grabbing Brian Robinson off of waivers, if available. ESPN’s Adam Schefter later followed up the report by saying McCaffrey will go “good to go” Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196e-d8cf-affb-bd6efae90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Daniel Jones (Achilles) underwent successful surgery Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1997-d8cf-affb-bdbf5d620000</link>
      <description>The veteran quarterback was in the midst of a career year before it was halted due to a torn Achilles. The six-to-eight month recovery window gives him the potential to be ready for preseason camp ahead of the 2026 regular season, which is sure to figure into the team’s plans moving forward. That will likely be a point of continuous discussion surrounding the Colts considering Jones was playing the 2025 season on a one-year, “prove-it” deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1997-d8cf-affb-bdbf5d620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed WR Brandon Aiyuk on the reserve/left squad list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-199f-d8cf-affb-bdbfdac20000</link>
      <description>If you’re not familiar with the reserve/left squad list, that’s okay, it is something typically reserved for players about to retire. The awkward saga between Aiyuk and the 49ers appears to be ending in a messy divorce, with the recent move by the team all but ensuring the two sides split in the coming offseason. The transaction also officially ends Aiyuk’s 2025 season before it began. Stay tuned through the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-199f-d8cf-affb-bdbfdac20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) is likely to return to practice next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d005-a9bf-d97c3d560000</link>
      <description>Johnson is set to miss his fourth consecutive game in Week 15 against the Raiders, which was his original target for return. The 35-year-old right tackle is dealing with a Lisfranc sprain, but Rapoport passes along that Johnson will likely return to practice next week and depending on how that goes he could be active against the Commanders in Week 16 or Bills in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d005-a9bf-d97c3d560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Packers RB Emanuel Wilson (illness) plans to play against the Broncos in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d55-d1bc-a3fb-9d75362a0000</link>
      <description>With Josh Jacobs (knee) expected to play, Wilson’s availability doesn’t appear to be crucial for the first round of the fantasy playoffs. He’s still listed as questionable. The team already elevated Pierre Strong from the practice squad and he could fill in as the backup if either of the Packers’ top two backs are ultimately ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d55-d1bc-a3fb-9d75362a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) is expected to play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5a-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e1c2a0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs is still listed as questionable with a knee injury. He’s missed one game already this season because of his balky knee, but is expected to play against the Broncos in Week 15. Jacobs’ backup Emanuel Wilson is also questionable with an illness, though he plans to play. In a tough matchup at less than 100 percent, Jacobs is a midrange RB2 in the first round of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1d5a-d1bc-a3fb-9d7e1c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
