<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott has not decided if he will let Josh Allen play in the Bills’ second preseason game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae9e-d90d-a5bd-aedfee8e0000</link>
      <description>McDermott beat around the bush regarding his MVP quarterback and whether or not we would see him on Sunday night against the Bears. Speaking Friday, McDermott said his team is using the joint practice against the Bears “to see where (Allen is) at and how he feels” and will decide later in the weekend if Allen will suit up. If Allen doesn’t play, we would expect Mitch Trubisky to draw the start and see plenty of work. Last week, Trubisky started against the Giants, throwing for 138 yards and a touchdown on 9-of-13 passing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ae9e-d90d-a5bd-aedfee8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars HC Liam Coen said Travis Hunter (upper body) may miss the team’s second preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aeb9-d45c-a7fc-aebba9ff0000</link>
      <description>Coen said the decision to sit Hunter would be out of precaution, seemingly downplaying whatever upper-body injury the two-way star is dealing with. Hunter played on 11-of-12 offensive snaps with the starters last week, and was expected to see a little more work in his second tune-up as he prepares for his rookie season. The Jaguars don’t play until Sunday, which could give Coen some extra time to consider Hunter’s status for the weekend, but it wouldn’t be too surprising if the team opted not to push things with the season just weeks away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aeb9-d45c-a7fc-aebba9ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case Keenum is considered day-to-day with a leg injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aed3-df63-a199-fffb56f40000</link>
      <description>The injury could cost Keenum his shot at earning the Bears’ No. 2 quarterback job. He currently sits behind fellow backup QB Tyson Bagent, and backup snaps will be harder to come by this weekend, with the starters slated to get some work early on against the Bills. Details on Keenum’s leg injury, suffered yesterday, have not yet been released. He spent the 2024 season on injured reserve with a foot injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aed3-df63-a199-fffb56f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts EDGE Samson Ebukam left Thursday’s practice early after suffering a back injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aefa-df63-a199-fffbe9c20000</link>
      <description>Ebukam spent the 2024 season on injured reserve after rupturing his Achilles tendon in training camp. The Colts have not yet provided an update on his back injury. Ebukam posted career highs in tackles (34), quarterback pressures (48) and sacks (10) in his first season with the Colts, back in 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-aefa-df63-a199-fffbe9c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released TE Ross Dwelley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-af86-df63-a199-ffaf47240000</link>
      <description>Dwelley has evidently lost the battle for the 49ers’ No. 3 tight end role. Dwelley spent the first six seasons of his career with the 49ers before venturing to Atlanta for a one-off season with the Falcons last year. He re-signed with the 49ers in May. He turned 30 in January. The 49ers correspondingly signed DT Shakel Brown, with three of their defensive linemen currently working through injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-af86-df63-a199-ffaf47240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice “has received clearance to travel with the team and be permitted to enter Brazil” for the Chiefs’ Week 1 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afbb-d90d-a5bd-affb72810000</link>
      <description>Rice pleaded guilty to a pair of felonies in relation to a multi-car crash last month. Per the Washington Post’s Mark Maske, “there had been questions among some familiar with the case” whether Brazil’s immigration policies would complicate Rice’s entry into the country. The Chiefs’ No. 1 wide receiver is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afbb-d90d-a5bd-affb72810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports Houston’s Aaron Wilson reports, Joe Mixon (foot, ankle) “is not considered a lock to be ready for” the Texans’ Week 1 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-af8e-d90d-a5bd-afdf0ca30000</link>
      <description>Wilson adds that “the Texans will take their time with managing his recovery and will not rush him back onto the field.” Mixon missed the entire offseason and remains out indefinitely, weeks into Texans training camp. Earlier today, Texans OC Nick Caley praised Dameon Pierce for his physical, violent playing style. Observing the backfield rotation in the Texans’ preseason Week 2 game against the Vikings tomorrow will be worthwhile for fantasy managers. In the same report, Wilson quotes Texans owner Cal McNair waxing poetic about his love of old school football: Playing tight defense and fielding a good rushing attack. The Texans’ backfield will be fantasy-relevant in Week 1, whether Mixon is active or inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-af8e-d90d-a5bd-afdf0ca30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that Kirk Cousins is “finally healthy again and has impressed in training camp.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afdf-d45c-a7fc-afdfa8d50000</link>
      <description>Cousins dealt with a throwing arm injury in-season last year, but in the video segment, Pelissero curiously references Cousins’ 2023 Achilles tendon rupture, with regard to Cousins’ current health. The comment seemingly acknowledges that Cousins’ ability to plant and drive off of his surgically repaired right leg was compromised last year. The good news is Cousins’ zip has apparently returned. Pelissero names the Rams as a potential trade partner, given Matthew Stafford’s back injury and Cousins’ familiarity with head coach Sean McVay’s scheme via Falcons’ OC Zac Robinson, McVay’s former understudy. Cousins will not play in the Falcons’ preseason Week 2 game against the Titans tonight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afdf-d45c-a7fc-afdfa8d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that “there is still a possibility” for the NFL and Rashee Rice to “agree to a settlement on a suspension, that would allow Rice to be suspended at the start of the season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afe2-d05a-adda-afe2a0950000</link>
      <description>Per Pelissero, the NFL initially proposed a suspension lasting 10-plus games. Rice’s representatives argued for a far shorter suspension, in part because “there is no precedent for suspending someone for over half of the season.” With the two sides reaching an impasse, it was determined Rice’s case would be presented before Judge Sue L. Robinson, which could put Rice’s late-season availability at risk. Losing Rice early in the year would sting as well, with high-profile opponents like the Chargers, Eagles and Ravens on tap in Weeks 1-4. Both the team and the league are incentivized to get this issue sorted out as quickly as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-afe2-d05a-adda-afe2a0950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Browns are “cautiously optimistic” that Shedeur Sanders (oblique) can return to practice next week and play in the team’s preseason Week 3 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01b-df63-a199-f93b0a5f0000</link>
      <description>Sanders will not play in the Browns’ preseason Week 2 game against the Eagles tomorrow. Kenny Pickett is rehabbing a hamstring injury and will not play either, though the team is “hoping” that Dillon Gabriel will “wake up feeling good enough” to play on Saturday, after rehabbing a hamstring injury of his own this week. Tyler Huntley will take most reps, if not. Joe Flacco has been bubble-wrapped as the lone healthy, proven player in the room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b01b-df63-a199-f93b0a5f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
