<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints LG Trevor Penning (toe) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1161-dbe3-a9bb-3173ac1c0000</link>
      <description>Penning suffered a turf toe injury during training camp and was spotted in a boot for a few weeks. He shed the boot last week but has yet to resume practice, all but ruling him out for Week 1 already. Penning was set to start at left guard this year after switching from tackle to guard in the offseason. Dillon Radunz will likely take his place in the lineup for Week 1 versus the Cardinals. Penning was the only Saint unable to practice in some capacity on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1161-dbe3-a9bb-3173ac1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints head coach Kellen Moore said Alvin Kamara will get the bulk of the work in the run game.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1168-de13-afdd-57ebf6180000</link>
      <description>Moore has talked up Kamara all offseason so this shouldn’t come as much of a surprise. His backups are currently rookie Devin Neal and third-year back Kendre Miller. Neither back generated much buzz in training camp and fantasy managers should expect both to be used sparingly to start the year. Kamara will likely open the year as a top-five fantasy back. Whether he can sustain that production down the stretch is another question, but that’s a problem for another week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1168-de13-afdd-57ebf6180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers DT Vita Vea (foot) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-116d-dbe3-a9bb-317fd39f0000</link>
      <description>Vea, 30, has built an extension lower-body injury record over the last two years. He dealt with a recurring calf issue in 2023, a worked through both knee (MCL) and hamstring issues last year. The towering (6'4/347) nose tackle remains a game changer whenever he’s on the field and he regularly plays through injuries. Buccaneers S Christian Izien (oblique) was also sidelined Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-116d-dbe3-a9bb-317fd39f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said EDGE Chase Young suffered a calf injury in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-116d-dbe3-a9bb-317f9c080000</link>
      <description>Young was officially listed as limited for the first practice of the year, though that’s presumably because he left the session early. Moore downplayed the severity of the injury after practice, but Young’s status on Thursday will be more revealing. Young totaled 5.5 sacks and one forced fumble in his first year as a Saint in 2024. He was looking to build on that momentum after re-signing with the team during the offseason, though this calf issue could throw a wrench in those plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-116d-dbe3-a9bb-317f9c080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (groin) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-115a-dbe3-a9bb-315bec830000</link>
      <description>Otton is on track to suit up against the Falcons on Sunday, but practicing in full on Friday would go a long way toward solidifying his status as a TE2 with touchdown-based upside in what could be a back-and-forth game script. The Buccaneers will be without Chris Godwin (ankle) and Jalen McMillan (neck).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-115a-dbe3-a9bb-315bec830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed S J.T. Gray, formerly of the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1179-de13-afdd-57fb8a060000</link>
      <description>Gray rarely sees the field on defense but is a special teams ace. He logged over 300 special teams snaps for five consecutive seasons with the Saints before being a surprise cut at the end of training camp this year. Gray’s 14 special teams tackles were second-most in the league last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1179-de13-afdd-57fb8a060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Sean Tucker (hand) fully practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-db7b-a5dd-b176b89a0000</link>
      <description>Tucker is good to go for Week 1. The 23-year-old running back has flashed intriguing traits at times, though he remains stuck in the Buccaneers’ No. 3 role. If Bucky Irving were to miss time, Tucker would be flex-viable, serving as the likely lead rusher in Tampa Bay’s potent offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-db7b-a5dd-b176b89a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions worked out free agent QB C.J. Beathard on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-dbe3-a9bb-317727680000</link>
      <description>The Lions also worked out free agent QB Nathan Peterman. Ironically, the Jets worked out the same duo on August 14th. The Lions currently have just two quarterbacks between their active roster and practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1176-dbe3-a9bb-317727680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquise Brown (ankle) practiced in full on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-118a-dbe3-a9bb-31db0cd70000</link>
      <description>Brown’s ankle is holding up nicely. The veteran wide receiver should have a role in both two- and three-wide receiver sets, though he will likely be stuck behind Xavier Worthy and Travis Kelce in the pecking order. Brown draws FLEX consideration for the matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-118a-dbe3-a9bb-31db0cd70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Kristian Fulton (knee) practiced in full on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1191-dbe3-a9bb-31d3a1330000</link>
      <description>Fulton spent a little over two weeks on the active/physically unable to perform list this summer. He’s been practicing with the team since August 7th, though. Fulton notched five pass breakups and one interception, playing for the Chargers last year. He should be available for his new team’s bout with the Bolts on Friday night. Chiefs OT Jawaan Taylor (knee) is practicing in full this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1191-dbe3-a9bb-31d3a1330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
