<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 16:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 3-of-4 targets for 55 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs struggled to move the football throughout against the league’s top defense, with quarterback Patrick Mahomes setting a career high in consecutive incompletions with 10 in the second half. The one good aspect of Worthy’s game was that he failed to account for any drops, which both Travis Kelce and Rashee Rice could not say leaving the game. Worthy continues to see modest volume with both primary options healthy, a trend likely to hold ahead of a Week 15 showdown with the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc6a-d77b-adfa-feebe0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 4-of-8 targets for 34 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</link>
      <description>Not only did Rice fail to return a usable fantasy outing, but two of Patrick Mahomes’ four incompletions when targeting Rice went down as drops. The worst instance came on fourth down half way through the fourth quarter when Rice saw the pass go straight through his hands. The poor outing can be viewed as a slight blip for fantasy’s overall WR1 in fantasy points per game ahead of a must-win game against the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc72-d8cf-affb-fc7afd990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 1-of-5 targets for eight yards in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</link>
      <description>Kelce’s night looks bad enough on paper before you realize two of Patrick Mahomes’ incompletions when targeting the veteran tight end were drops. Additionally, Kelce bobbled a pass on the team’s penultimate possession that was picked off by Azeez Al-Shaair with under four minutes remaining and down by a touchdown. That would allow the Texans to run down the clock to under 30 seconds after kicking a field goal to go up by 10. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-7 with only a 16% chance of making the playoffs. Kelce will be needed in a must-win showdown with the Chargers in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7a-d77b-adfa-fefb939a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Butker went 1-for-2 in field goal attempts in the Chiefs’ Week 14 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</link>
      <description>He connected from 36 yards and made his only point after attempt, missing from 43 yards at the end of the second quarter when his kick hit off the left upright. That missed field goal contributed to the Chiefs being shutout in the first half for only the third time in quarterback Patrick Mahomes’ career, making the failed conversion slightly more meaningful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fc7d-da9b-a9bf-fe7de1f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Mevis converted his lone field goal attempt and al six of his extra point attempts in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</link>
      <description>Mevis has proven a fine weekly fantasy play thanks to the high-powered Rams offense and the positive game script it creates. He’s made all three of his field goals this season and has yet to miss an extra point. He should be in fantasy lineups next week against the Lions in what should be a high-scoring affair. The Lions have allowed 1.7 field goal tries per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Loop converted all three of his field goal and one of his two extra point attempts in the Ravens’ Week 14 loss against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</link>
      <description>Loop has been excellent all season, making 25 of his 27 field goal tries. He hasn’t missed a field goal since Week 5 against the Texans. Loop will be a top-10 fantasy option in Week 15 against the Bengals. The Ravens are averaging 2.1 field goal tries per game, the 11th highest mark in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports DK Metcalf (stomach) will rejoin the Steelers on Monday after staying the night in a Baltimore hospital on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, Metcalf experienced stomach pain on the team flight and stayed the night in the hospital “out of an abundance of caution.” Given the brief stay and the fact he’s rejoining the team on Monday, we’ll assume this is a minor issue until we hear otherwise. With the Steelers playing on Monday Night Football in Week 15, Metcalf will have some extra time to rest up before his next game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed TE Brevin Jordan to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe40-d77b-adfa-fec3bb0f0000</link>
      <description>Jordan was set to be a free agent next offseason, but will now remain under contract through the 2026 season. The fifth-year tight end missed all of this season after suffering a torn patellar tendon in training camp, and has appeared in just two games since 2024 after a torn ACL also ended his season last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe40-d77b-adfa-fec3bb0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chad Ryland converted one of two field goal attempts in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe5d-d77b-adfa-fedf0dec0000</link>
      <description>Ryland has now missed one field goal in four straight games. On the season he has missed six of his 25 field goal tries while making all 29 of his extra points. Attached to an Arizona offense that rarely has the benefit of neutral and positive game script — allowing for field goal attempts throughout the game — Ryland is not a reliable fantasy play. He should not be rostered in Week 15 against Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe5d-d77b-adfa-fedf0dec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said the “guy that’s gonna give us the best chance to win” will have the most first-team reps ahead of Week 15’s game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe90-d77b-adfa-fe93c2f80000</link>
      <description>Justin Fields (knee) was ruled out last Friday ahead of Week 14’s game against the Dolphins, and Tyrod Taylor exited the game with a groin injury and did not return to the field. Glenn said he still has to talk to the team doctors to see where things stand as far as the health of his players is concerned, but we could be looking at rookie UDFA Brady Cook making his first career start if both Taylor and Fields are unable to go in Week 15. Cook threw for 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions while completing 46.7 percent of his passes against the Dolphins. What little upside Jets positions players still have will be capped if Cook is under center next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe90-d77b-adfa-fe93c2f80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
