<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed QB Davis Mills to a one-year, $7 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bf7-db7b-a5dd-abf723c50000</link>
      <description>Big news for fans of the 2022 Texans. Mills played extensively in the team’s Week 18 win over the Titans last year, culminating in a second-and-goal dive where Mills landed helmet mask first short of the goal line and a narrow win. Mills hasn’t exactly played poorly when given a chance, but he’s probably not one of the best 10 backups in the league either.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0bf7-db7b-a5dd-abf723c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders listed Jacory Croskey-Merritt fourth on their unofficial depth chart at running back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c11-d332-a1fd-9e37a0170000</link>
      <description>Sure, whatever you say guys. Austin Ekeler is the starter in name on this depth chart. We tentatively expect Croskey-Merritt and Chris Rodriguez to have major roles on the early downs while Ekeler is in charge of passing downs this year. We’re sure this will generate questions for Dan Quinn and Kliff Kingsbury later. For now, let’s enjoy being engaged by some bait.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c11-d332-a1fd-9e37a0170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne Jr. and Tank Bigsby are listed as co-starters on Jacksonville’s unofficial depth chart for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c22-de13-afdd-4eebad8f0000</link>
      <description>A confusing situation remains confusing. Worst of all, correctly figuring out which Jaguars running back will get the majority of the run against a Panthers defense coming off one of the worst seasons defending the run in NFL history could mean a lot for fantasy football in Week 1. We’re going to have to hit the press conference tape hard to figure this one out. Either player is startable in Week 1 as a FLEX play until we hear something stronger from the coaching staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c22-de13-afdd-4eebad8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints re-signed QB Jake Haener.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c2c-d332-a1fd-9e3e8a100000</link>
      <description>The 26-year-old remains a longshot to find playing time this year behind Spencer Rattler and Tyler Shough. Haener was cut at last cuts, signed to the Saints practice squad, and didn’t appear to have any other interest around the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c2c-d332-a1fd-9e3e8a100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Najee Harris (eye) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c55-db7b-a5dd-ac550eed0000</link>
      <description>While Jim Harbaugh has been careful to lower expectations when asked about Harris, it certainly seems like he’s good if perhaps not in complete football shape yet. This listing definitely puts Harris in line to play against the Chiefs on Friday in Sao Paolo. He’d probably only qualify as a FLEX play while splitting snaps with Omarion Hampton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c55-db7b-a5dd-ac550eed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released Russell Gage.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c57-de13-afdd-4edf2b100000</link>
      <description>Gage was released at last cuts, brought back on a one-year deal on August 28th, and now is being released again to be brought back on the practice squad and get promoted to the active roster for Week 1, saving the 49ers a few dollars. It’s clever (derogatory) accounting of a roster spot, and if you include signing Gage to a future contract in the first place, all it took was five different transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c57-de13-afdd-4edf2b100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent RB Deuce Vaughn visited the Broncos on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c5d-de13-afdd-4edfdc800000</link>
      <description>Vaughn was waived by the Cowboys at last cuts and went unclaimed. The Broncos kept four running backs but don’t have one on their practice squad, so it’s possible Vaughn will get signed to help remedy that problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c5d-de13-afdd-4edfdc800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent RB Boston Scott visited with the Colts on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c60-db7b-a5dd-ac64f34c0000</link>
      <description>Scott had a workout with the Ravens in August, but has otherwise gone unsigned and taken no official visits this offseason. The Colts have two backs on the practice squad in Khalil Herbert and Ulysses Bentley IV. We’re rooting for Bentley but if the Colts do sign Scott, he seems likely to be the corresponding p-squad cut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c60-db7b-a5dd-ac64f34c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed RT Luke Goedeke to a four-year, $90 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c86-dbe3-a9bb-3cd7ed000000</link>
      <description>Goedeke was selected in the second round of the 2022 NFL Draft by the Bucs, becoming a key part of the offensive line. He started all 30 games that he played over the last two seasons and finished 2024 with a 76.4 PFF run-blocking grade, No. 18 amongst offensive tackles. Entering the final year of his rookie deal, Goedeke now gets an extension done and the Bucs get to keep a key piece of the offensive line for the foreseeable future.ESPN’s Jeremy Fowlerreports the deal is worth $90 million over four years, with $50 million guaranteed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c86-dbe3-a9bb-3cd7ed000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins is listed as the starter on Denver’s unofficial Week 1 depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c9a-dbe3-a9bb-3cdbb4e20000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is notably ahead of rookie R.J. Harvey as the starter. This is just an unofficial depth chart that ultimately does not mean much when games start, but signifies that Dobbins is at least a significant part of the Broncos’ plans this season. Harvey should also split snaps out of the backfield and his fantasy outlook for this season should not change. Tyler Badie is listed as RB3, while Jaleel McLaughlin is RB4, indicating Sean Payton would like to utilize Badie in passing-down situations more often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0c9a-dbe3-a9bb-3cdbb4e20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
