<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers GM Jason Licht said Chris Godwin (ankle) is likely to return in Week 5 or later.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f22d-db7b-a5dd-f22d161e0000</link>
      <description>This tracks with prior reporting that suggested Godwin is expected to return sometime in October. Although we would love to have him on the field in Week 1, he appears to be on schedule, as far as the team is concerned. Licht also said OT Tristan Wirfs’ (knee) return “might be a little sooner.” It sounds like Baker Mayfield may be without his left tackle for the first 3-4 weeks, in which the Bucs face the Falcons, Texans, Jets and Eagles. All four teams are expected to field capable pass-rush units. Getting Wirfs back in time to face the Eagles’ vaunted group could be the goal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f22d-db7b-a5dd-f22d161e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers GM Dan Morgan said Jalen Coker “is going to step into the slot” role this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c9-db7b-a5dd-f1cd3a360000</link>
      <description>The Panthers traded last year’s slot-snap leader, Adam Thielen, to the Vikings yesterday and released fellow veteran slot receiver Hunter Renfrow one day prior. Enter Coker, who sporadically produced WR4, WR3 and WR1 finishes while averaging 1.72 yards per route run as an undrafted rookie last year. The Panthers’ No. 2 WR Xavier Legette could prevent Coker from playing in two-WR sets, but Coker now firmly warrants flex consideration, having won a starting role in an expectedly ascending offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f1c9-db7b-a5dd-f1cd3a360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed WR Devin Duvernay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f248-de13-afdc-f6cb28180000</link>
      <description>Duvernay provides wide receiver depth and will likely compete for a special teams role as a returner. He is not fantasy-relevant. The Bears also signed LS Scott Daly, placed DL Austin Booker on injured reserve with a designation to return, waived LB Carl Jones Jr., signed TE Nikola Kalinic, DB Dontae Manning and S Gervarrius Owens to the practice squad while releasing LS Luke Elkin and DB Mekhi Garner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f248-de13-afdc-f6cb28180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent K Eddy Pineiro worked out for the Bills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f258-de13-afdc-f6db93ee0000</link>
      <description>Fellow free agent kickers Zane Gonzalez and Greg Joseph also worked out for the Bills. Incumbent K Tyler Bass struggled last season and dealt with a pelvis injury in training camp. The Bills are likely just covering their bases, but Bass could be a risky fantasy pick at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f258-de13-afdc-f6db93ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers acquired Micah Parsons from the Cowboys in exchange for two first-round picks and DT Kenny Clark, and signed him to a four-year, $188 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f230-dbe3-a9bb-f273b7d60000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the extension “includes $120 million fully guaranteed at signing and makes Parsons the highest-paid non-QB in NFL history.” The Packers now field a formidable EDGE rush, with Parsons bookended by DL Rashan Gary. Clark, meanwhile, will line up next to DT Osa Odighizuwa, providing the Cowboys a solid, if unexciting, defensive tackle unit. The development undeniably downgrades the Cowboys’ ability to rush the passer, though, which puts the onus on the offense to keep the team in games. The Cowboys’ passing offense just became even more fantasy-friendly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f230-dbe3-a9bb-f273b7d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed OG Trevor Keegan, formerly of the Eagles, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f27f-dbe3-a9bb-f27f71390000</link>
      <description>Keegan appeared in one game for the Eagles last year and earned a 65.3 PFF run-blocking grade for his efforts. He will likely compete for a backup role with the Cowboys, who correspondingly waived WR Ryan Flournoy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f27f-dbe3-a9bb-f27f71390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Kendrick Bourne will visit the 49ers on Monday and the Commanders on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2b9-db7b-a5dd-f2bda4260000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that “the framework of a deal is in place for both.” The veteran wide receiver makes sense for both teams. Bourne is intimately familiar with 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan’s system, having spent 2017-2020 with them. Should he end up with the Commanders, he would serve as a fine rotational player who can be counted on to run routes on time. He is unlikely to return flex value with either team, though he could be relevant in 14-team leagues if Jauan Jennings (calf, contract) joins Brandon Aiyuk (knee) and Demarcus Robinson (suspension) on the sidelines early in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2b9-db7b-a5dd-f2bda4260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed CB Ambry Thomas, formerly of the 49ers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2cc-db7b-a5dd-f2cce8b10000</link>
      <description>Thomas broke his arm in August 2024 before bouncing from the 49ers’ active roster to the Colts’ and Vikings’ practice squads. In 2023, he recorded six pass breakups, one interception and 37 tackles with the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2cc-db7b-a5dd-f2cce8b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed LB Chazz Surratt, formerly of the 49ers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2f4-d332-a1fd-f6f62f7f0000</link>
      <description>Surratt will likely contribute on special teams. The Seahawks also waived S D’Anthony Bell, signed rookie LB Chris Paul Jr. and WR/RS Courtney Jackson to the practice squad and released RB Anthony Tyus III and OLB Jalen Gaines from the practice squad in corresponding moves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2f4-d332-a1fd-f6f62f7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ ProFootballTalk reports that Vikings S Harrison Smith “is dealing with a personal health issue and is expected to make a full recovery.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</link>
      <description>Smith has reportedly been dealing with the issue throughout August. Details on the matter have not yet been disclosed but the team will continue to evaluate him on a weekly basis. Smith, 36, remains an impactful player in the Vikings’ secondary. Hopefully, he is good to go for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f2fd-de13-afdc-f6ff68260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
