<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions and Commanders scheduled interviews with Ravens QB coach Tee Martin for their offensive coordinator vacancies next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</link>
      <description>Per Jordan Schultz, “has done extensive work for Baltimore’s passing game as a whole” over the last three seasons, “helping propel Lamar Jackson to the 2023 NFL MVP.” Martin coach the Ravens’ wide receivers in the two prior seasons. These are the first reported interviews scheduled for Martin this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ee-d968-a19b-fcffa3640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders hired David Blough as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</link>
      <description>The former NFL quarterback was on the Lions’ practice squad as recently as 2023. Blough, 30, has just two years of coaching experience, both with the Commanders as their assistant quarterbacks coach. The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala notes that Blough “helped fill in when QBs coach Tavita Pritchard left for Stanford” in November. The Commanders were evidently impressed with Blough’s ability to rise to the occasion. The Lions had requested an interview with Blough for their vacant offensive coordinator role earlier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a526-d35e-a1bf-e5e6cebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers are expected to interview Falcons OC Zac Robinson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a507-d35e-a1bf-e5c778da0000</link>
      <description>The Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud notes that Robinson spent five seasons with the Rams, “rising from assistant quarterbacks coach to passing game coordinator/QB coach” under head coach Sean McVay. Robinson served as the Falcons’ offensive coordinator from 2024-2025. The Falcons notably denied the Cowboys’ request to interview DC Jeff Ulbrich for their defensive coordinator vacancy. Perhaps, things will work out differently for Robinson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a507-d35e-a1bf-e5c778da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys completed their interview with Browns S coach Ephraim Banda for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a542-dc7a-af9b-efff54f50000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys completed two defensive coordinator interviews today, having met with Vikings defensive pass game coordinator and DB coach Daronte Jones earlier on. Tomorrow, they are set to speak with Broncos assistant head coach and defensive passing game coordinator Jim Leonhard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a542-dc7a-af9b-efff54f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State S Caleb Downs declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a566-d35e-a1bf-e5e661770000</link>
      <description>Downs began his college career at Alabama in 2023. He transferred to Ohio State the following season and helped the Buckeyes win the 2024 College Football Playoff Championship. In 2023, he was a second-team All-American, the SEC Freshman of the Year and first-team All-SEC. In both 2024 and 2025, Downs was a Unanimous All-American, the Big Ten Defensive Back of the Year and earned first-team All-Big Ten honors. In 2025 alone, he won the Lott Trophy and Jim Thorpe Award. The Athletic’s James Boyd notes Downs is Colts WR Josh Downs’ younger brother and “is widely considered to be a potential top-10 pick.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a566-d35e-a1bf-e5e661770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports’ Pro Football Talk reports that the arraignment in Patriots WR Stefon Diggs’ criminal case “has been delayed from January 23 until February 13.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a58d-dc7a-af9b-efbf16370000</link>
      <description>The arraignment will now occur five days after Super Bowl LX, making it “virtually certain,” per Mike Florio, that the NFL will not place Diggs on the commissioner exempt list before the Super Bowl. Diggs is “the subject of a criminal complaint” that accuses him of “felony strangulation or suffocation and misdemeanor assault and battery.” Nothing is guaranteed, but it appears as though Diggs will be available for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a58d-dc7a-af9b-efbf16370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed their interview with Matt Ryan for their president of football vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a5de-dc7a-af9b-efffaefa0000</link>
      <description>ESPN previously reported that “many believe” the position was “created” for Ryan. It is safe to say he is the favorite to land the role. Per team owner Arthur Blank, the president of football will lead the interview process as the team searches for its new head coach and general manager. Both positions will report directly to the president of football, who reports directly to Blank. The trio “will work collaboratively as a football leadership team on all football decisions.” While the head coach and general manager “remain the primary decision-makers” in their respective roles, “final decision-making authority will rest with the president of football.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a5de-dc7a-af9b-efffaefa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Packers plan to discuss a contract extension with head coach Matt LaFleur after the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a67e-d968-a19b-feffb23c0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur’s current contract runs through the 2026 season, but the Packers aren’t going to have him coach next season on an expiring deal. Green Bay intends to extend the 46-year-old coach’s contract whenever the Packers’ season ends. LaFleur is 76-40-1 and has taken the Packers to the playoffs six times in seven years, though he’s yet to make it to the Super Bowl. Recent reports that LaFleur might not be safe in this round of the NFL coaching carousel never passed the smell test. Rapoport couldn’t be clearer in his reporting, explicitly stating that LaFleur isn’t coaching for his job in the first round of the playoffs, according to sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a67e-d968-a19b-feffb23c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons hired Matt Ryan as President of Football.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a84d-d35e-a1bf-edcfcb010000</link>
      <description>Ryan spent 14 of his 15 years in the NFL as a player with the Falcons, winning the MVP in 2016 and making four Pro Bowls. He signed a one-day contract to retire with the organization and was inducted into the Falcons’ ring of honor in 2024. Ryan is putting his reputation on the line in taking a job many believe was created specifically for him as the Falcons’ President of Football. He’s been granted full control with final say over all football decisions, including leading the search for the team’s next head coach and general manager. Ryan will pause his broadcasting career at CBS while he takes over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a84d-d35e-a1bf-edcfcb010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Panthers are expected to pick up QB Bryce Young’s fifth-year option this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a87a-d56e-afff-eefa9d500000</link>
      <description>Young improved a lot in his third year after a rough first two seasons with the Panthers. The 24-year-old quarterback led Carolina to eight wins, a division championship and the playoffs. Young orchestrated four fourth quarter comebacks and six game-winning drives. He threw for over 20 touchdowns for the first time without increasing his interceptions and lowered his sack percentage. Young led the league in deep ball accuracy with a catchable percentage of 75 percent on passes that traveled at least 20 yards in the air. While Young still has work to do to be a top-15 fantasy quarterback, the Panthers are committed to him for at least the next two years now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a87a-d56e-afff-eefa9d500000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
