<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears coach Ben Johnson said Rome Odunze (foot) is “going to be able to help us this year” but didn’t offer a timeline for his return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c88-d35e-a1bf-4dca2fba0000</link>
      <description>Considering there are only two weeks left in the season, if we don’t see any kind of improvement from Odunze in practices this week, there’s a real chance that the Bears have nothing to play for in Week 18. Odunze may be mothballed until the playoffs. The fact that Johnson wouldn’t put a timetable on it arguably tells us Week 17 will be a stretch for an Odunze return, but the practice report on Wednesday will speak louder than his statement today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c88-d35e-a1bf-4dca2fba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed OL Ben Brown to a two-year extension worth “up to” $6.6 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c8a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd4800000</link>
      <description>The UDFA center will be a rotational cog along the middle of the Patriots line, probably mostly as a backup, for the two years to come. Brown has started just two games this year, but had a 10-game stretch as a starter in 2024. He qualifies as competent depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c8a-dc7a-af9b-cfbfd4800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots DT Khyiris Tonga (foot) will miss 1-2 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c8d-d968-a19b-5cfd20900000</link>
      <description>Ian Rapoport’s sourced timeline on Tonga’s recovery should have him ready for New England’s first playoff game. New England will be desperately trying to get him, Robert Spillane, and Milton Williams as ready as they can be for the playoffs after the run defense has sprung a leak over the last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c8d-d968-a19b-5cfd20900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) is practicing on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c90-dc7a-af9b-cfbfbdca0000</link>
      <description>This should put him in line to reclaim a major role in the Texans backfield in Week 17 against the Chargers. Marks would be more of a low-end RB2 play against a good defense in what is projected to be a lower-scoring game, but volume should be on his side if he’s able to be active for the contest. Assuming he actually stays on the field, anyway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c90-dc7a-af9b-cfbfbdca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (hand) has a hairline fracture and will be out for Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c96-d968-a19b-5cf78d010000</link>
      <description>No surprise on a short week. McCarthy apparently has a chance to play in Week 18 based on Ian Rapoport’s reporting, but we can’t exactly circle that for a fact just yet. Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said McCarthy will not need surgery for the “very small” fracture, perhaps the smallest we’ve ever heard of. It’s been an injury-plagued, disastrous year for the 2024 tenth overall pick. The Vikings almost have to bring in real competition for him in 2026 based on what we’ve seen so far. Max Brosmer should be in line for a Week 17 start and can be started in superflex leagues by sadomasochistic managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c96-d968-a19b-5cf78d010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said Max Brosmer will start Minnesota’s Week 17 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c9e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf0c210000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks dud was understandable — they have arguably the best defense in the NFL this year. But Brosmer didn’t exactly light it up against the Giants in relief in Week 16, and the Lions play aggressive coverage. Brosmer is yet another governor on the fantasy prospects of players like Aaron Jones, Justin Jefferson, and Jordan Addison in Week 17. “Boy, we wish Carson Wentz was still healthy,” we unbelievably thought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4c9e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf0c210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) will not play in Week 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ca6-dc7a-af9b-cfbfff6b0000</link>
      <description>When a man who has already spent time on IR for concussions suffers another concussion in Week 16, and said man is 32 years old, the thoughts tend to be more towards “is it time for him to retire” than “can he go Week 17?” We would be surprised if Kelly played again this season. We would not be surprised if this was it for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ca6-dc7a-af9b-cfbfff6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Amon-Ra St. Brown (knee) still has “a little irritation” but news was positive on his injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ca8-d968-a19b-5cf9efc40000</link>
      <description>That makes it sound like it’s preparing us for another practice DNP today, but otherwise it all sounds like good news for St. Brown and fantasy managers who will want him available for Week 17’s game against the Vikings. St. Brown would be an easy WR1 as long as he makes it to the active line, but there is probably a non-zero chance that he gets extra rest in this one, especially if the Lions are able to put Max Brosmer to bed early.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4ca8-d968-a19b-5cf9efc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that Jordan Mason (ankle) is “a long shot” for Week 17’s game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cab-dc7a-af9b-cfbff6140000</link>
      <description>Already with one DNP and a locker room carting under his belt in the last two days, the source here isn’t telling us anything that we shouldn’t already have been thinking. The good news for Mason is that the way Fowler’s source and Kevin O’Connell (who refused to rule him out today) have been talking about him says this isn’t a major injury and that he has a chance to play in Week 18. He’s droppable for those of you with championship games in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cab-dc7a-af9b-cfbff6140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Jordan Love (concussion) and Malik Willis (shoulder) will be limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cb6-d35e-a1bf-4df6171f0000</link>
      <description>It’s good news for both of them, as Love appears to be going through the concussion protocol just fine and with a chance to play in Week 17. If he doesn’t, Willis will get a chance to start. If neither of them are available, we’ll watch Clayton Tune do his thing against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4cb6-d35e-a1bf-4df6171f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
