<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Keon Coleman (groin) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1130-de13-afdd-57fb43570000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Joe Buscaglia commented on the matter, saying, Coleman “pops up on the injury report unexpectedly.” It gives the impression that Coleman may have strained his groin in practice today. That’s a bad sign for his Week 1 availability. Coleman and the Bills are hoping he can make a second-year leap after a disappointing, injury-impacted rookie season. He should not be in starting lineups at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1130-de13-afdd-57fb43570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (hamstring) is not on the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-113f-db7b-a5dd-b13f4ebd0000</link>
      <description>Downs suffered a hamstring injury during a practice in mid-August and missed multiple weeks. He returned to practice last week and is good to go after avoiding the Week 1 injury report entirely. With Daniel Jones drawing the start versus Miami, there should be plenty of check-downs to go around in the Colts offense to start the year. Downs will be a strong FLEX option for his first action of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-113f-db7b-a5dd-b13f4ebd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (groin) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1141-dbe3-a9bb-31538e470000</link>
      <description>Bills CB Tre’Davious White was limited by a groin strain as well. That makes both of the Bills’ starting perimeter cornerbacks who are now questionable to play in Week 1 against the Ravens. Zay Flowers and Rashod Bateman could have fruitful outings if neither coverage defender can go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1141-dbe3-a9bb-31538e470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1141-db7b-a5dd-b14596380000</link>
      <description>We expect Parsons to be on the field when the Packers host the Lions in Week 1, but it’s possible they limit his snap count. Parsons joins a talented Packers defensive unit that will thoroughly test new Lions OC John Morton’s mettle. The Packers have notably officially switched Parsons to a generic defensive line positional designation. Packers CB Nate Hobbs (knee) did not practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1141-db7b-a5dd-b14596380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Denzel Ward (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1146-de13-afdd-57cfce470000</link>
      <description>The Browns have a lengthy injury report ahead of Week 1, though only one player actually missed Wednesday’s practice entirely. That was defensive tackle Mike Hall, who is still recovering from the season-ending knee injury he suffered in Week 18 of last year. Hall avoided the PUP list, meaning he shouldn’t be out for long, even if he misses Week 1. The remainder of the Browns, including Ward, don’t appear to be at risk of missing the team’s opener versus Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1146-de13-afdd-57cfce470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill (oblique/calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-114d-dbe3-a9bb-315f10ac0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Mike McDaniel said last week that Hill “looks great” for Week 1. Though it’s not ideal to see him start the season with a pair of injuries, Hill will be on the field when Miami kicks off versus the Colts. Hill is looking for a rebound campaign following a disastrous 2024 that saw him fall below 1,000 receiving yards for the first time since 2019. Week 1 will give fantasy managers loads of info on how to view the Dolphins for the remainder of the season. Hill will look like one of the best fantasy values of the summer if Mike McDaniel can recreate his Greatest Show on Turf tribute band from 2023. On the other hand, Hill will stand little chance at living up to his third-round pricetag if Miami remains stuck in first gear like they were for most of 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-114d-dbe3-a9bb-315f10ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers QB Jordan Love (left thumb) was a full participant in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1146-db7b-a5dd-b146e95e0000</link>
      <description>Love is on track to suit up for the Packers’ Week 1 game against the Lions, in what could be a high-scoring affair. Thankfully, Love’s injury is to his non-throwing hand, so it will not impact his throwing motion. Love spent the early portion of 2024 playing through a knee injury. It is possible the Packers increase their passing volume a tad this season, with Love’s mobility no longer impacted. He’s a borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1146-db7b-a5dd-b146e95e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1153-d332-a1fd-9777d6f80000</link>
      <description>Achane went down with the calf injury a few weeks ago, but his absence from practice was always said to be precautionary. A limited session to open Week 1’s practices backs that up and puts him on track to play on Sunday versus the Colts. With Jaylen Wright not expected to suit up, Achane will be spelled by rookie Ollie Gordon. Though Gordon should see a handful of carries, Achane is in line to handle the bulk of the backfield touches to start the year, putting him firmly in the RB1 ranks for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1153-d332-a1fd-9777d6f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1154-db7b-a5dd-b1541abe0000</link>
      <description>Wicks appears to be truly questionable for the Packers’ Week 1 game against the Lions. He picked up the injury at the end of July and was allowed to return after just two days off. The issue again forced him from practice in mid-August, and it apparently remains an issue heading into the season’s opening weekend. The Packers could be thin at wide receiver this weekend, clearing the way for rookie Matthew Golden to secure a starting role. Christian Watson (knee) is sidelined for at least four weeks and Jayden Reed (foot) was unable to practice today. Third-round rookie WR Savion Williams (hamstring) was limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1154-db7b-a5dd-b1541abe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1156-db7b-a5dd-b156cadc0000</link>
      <description>Waller came out of retirement to play for the Dolphins after they traded away Jonnu Smith early in the offseason. the age-32 tight end was initially placed on the PUP list to allow him to get back into football shape before practicing. Now it appears as though he is dealing with an actual injury, though head coach Mike McDaniel said earlier this week that Waller is on track to play in Week 1. Still, the lack of practice and Waller’s lack of live reps over the past year make him a clear stay-away for fantasy purposes. He will hang out at the bottom of the TE2 ranks until we see what his role looks like versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1156-db7b-a5dd-b156cadc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
