<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker rushed 11 times for 100 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams while adding three catches for 64 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34ec-d087-addf-b5fc1bb10000</link>
      <description>Walker set up the first score for Seattle with a 46-yard screen pass. He showed off his wheels again in the third quarter with a 55-yard score for his first rushing touchdown since November 16; also against the Rams. He finished with two more carries than Zack Charbonnet, and while both found the end zone, he was the much more effective option during Thursday’s overtime win. Walker will be a RB2 with a wide variety of potential outcomes against the Panthers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34ec-d087-addf-b5fc1bb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams rushed 23 times for 70 yards in the Rams’ Week 16 overtime loss to the Seahawks while adding three catches for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fb-dc7a-af9b-ffff3c9b0000</link>
      <description>Williams ran hard against the stout Seahawks’ front, but there wasn’t much in terms of explosive plays. He also wasn’t able to find the end zone while Blake Corum was able to take advantage of a late opportunity. The yardage was decent, but no touchdown here makes for a relatively disappointing game, even considering the opponent and TNF situation. He’ll be a RB2 for Week 17 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fb-dc7a-af9b-ffff3c9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Charbonnet rushed 9 times for 31 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams while adding four catches for 22 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fc-dc7a-af9b-ffff34aa0000</link>
      <description>Charbonnet vultured a touchdown away from Kenneth Walker after Walker got the Seahawks inside the red zone on a long screen pass. He also was the recipient of one of the flukiest two-point conversions ever, as a backwards pass that went off the dome of Jared Verse was recovered by Charbonnet on a play where neither team knew the ball was live. Still counts. The 24-year-old was a checkdown target for Sam Darnold as Darnold was under duress for most of the game, but he didn’t do much with those opportunities. Charbonnet will be a touchdown-dependent FLEX option for Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fc-dc7a-af9b-ffff34aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed 14 times for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 16 overtime loss to the Seahawks while adding one catch for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fd-dc7a-af9b-ffff32cf0000</link>
      <description>Corum was heavily involved in the game plan, even with Kyren Williams getting 23 carries for 70 yards in the overtime defeat. The 25-year-old tailback has scored in each of the last four games, and it’s certainly helped make up for the fact that he’s a non-factor in the Rams’ passing attack. Corum should see a similar amount of touches in Week 17 against the Falcons, but expect a better yardage total against a front that isn’t nearly as good as Seattle’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fd-dc7a-af9b-ffff32cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Smith caught both of his targets for 57 yards in the Rams’ Week 16 overtime loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fd-da28-afbb-f4fdc1850000</link>
      <description>Smith was wide open for a 48-yard connection with Matt Stafford to set up a score. The 28-year-old certainly has some speed, but even with Davante Adams not available, there just aren’t enough targets to make him fantasy relevant at this stage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fd-da28-afbb-f4fdc1850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konata Mumpfield caught 3-of-8 targets for 40 yards in the Rams’ Week 16 overtime loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fe-d087-addf-b5feabce0000</link>
      <description>With Davante Adams out due to a hamstring injury, Mumpfield was given a chance to make some plays. He didn’t make enough of them, as Matthew Stafford just missed on a few connections with the seventh-round pick of this year’s draft. If Adams can’t go in Week 17 against the Falcons, Mumpfield will be in the conversation for fantasy relevance in that contest. If Adams can go, there’s not enough upside for consideration in redraft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34fe-d087-addf-b5feabce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrance Ferguson caught 3-of-4 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 16 overtime loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34ff-dc7a-af9b-ffff8ddf0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson should have had a second touchdown, but an (incorrectly called) illegal downfield lineman wiped away a terrific catch in the back of the end zone on the Rams’ second drive. He was able to find the end zone late in the fourth for the rookies’ second career touchdown. Ferguson has long-term upside and finished with more catches than both Coby Parkinson (2/21) and Davis Allen (2/34), but he’s off the radar for the remainder of the regular season, including Week 17 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-34ff-dc7a-af9b-ffff8ddf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 3-of-4 targets for 39 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3500-da28-afbb-f57d788e0000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks tried to get Kupp a touchdown early against his former team on a gadget pass that had no shot of working. Late in the second quarter, Sam Darnold found him for what should have been a play to set up a score, but he fumbled the football for what ended up being a touchback for the Rams. He did catch a low throw from Darnold for a two-point conversion, and the 32-year-old showed he’s still capable of getting it done on a beautiful sideline catch for 21 yards in overtime to help set up the winning score. Kupp remains a desperation FLEX going forward, with his next chance to contribute coming against the Panthers in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3500-da28-afbb-f57d788e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rasheed Shaheed didn’t catch his lone target while adding one rush for 31 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3501-da28-afbb-f57d9fea0000</link>
      <description>Shaheed didn’t make much of a contribution outside of an end-around to set up a score late in the game on offense, but he showed off his sensational returning skills by returning a punt for 58 yards for a score in the middle of the fourth quarter. It’s a disappointing receiving day after Shaheed had made real progress over the previous two contests, but at least the trip to the end zone helps compensate. Shaheed should be more involved in Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3501-da28-afbb-f57d9fea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 4-of-6 targets for 49 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 16 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3502-da28-afbb-f57f53e60000</link>
      <description>Barner — not exactly known for his elite athleticism — made Kam Kitchens look silly on a wide-open touchdown connection with Sam Darnold in the fourth. The 23-year-old is the clear top tight end in the passing game with Elijah Arroyo unavailable, but it was the case even with Arroyo healthy. Barner will again be on the TE1 cusp for Week 17 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3502-da28-afbb-f57f53e60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
