<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 21:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) is questionable for Green Bay’s Week 8 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cd-deb1-a39b-37cf13030000</link>
      <description>Watson said earlier this week that his plan is to play this week. Matt LaFleur noted that there might be a re-acclimation period today, saying “you’re talking about a long layoff without football. Just trying to build him up so he can handle the demands of what will be placed upon him on game day.” It sounds like Watson could be on a snap count. He’s best left on fantasy benches even in a bye week squeeze this week, but it does feel like he has a real chance to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cd-deb1-a39b-37cf13030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (glute) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cb-d5d8-a3ff-ffebc8940000</link>
      <description>Cowboys C Cooper Beebe (ankle) has been designated to return from injured reserve, yet remains questionable against the Broncos. He was limited all week. Guyton evidently injured his glute on Thursday, logging consecutive limited sessions to close the week. Hopefully, at least one of them can play. QB Dak Prescott faces the Broncos’ top-tier pass rush this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17cb-d5d8-a3ff-ffebc8940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) will not play in Green Bay’s Week 8 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d0-deb1-a39b-37de2d210000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week with a calf injury that he picked up in Week 8. Wicks’ absence will put a lot on Romeo Doubs’ plate against the Steelers in Week 8. Doubs feels like a WR3 candidate in a bye week crunch without much competition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d0-deb1-a39b-37de2d210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (hamstring) won’t play in Philadelphia’s Week 8 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d2-d5d8-a3ff-fff36dae0000</link>
      <description>Brown didn’t practice all week and, despite Nick Sirianni saying that he could play without practicing, will officially be down against the Giants. DeVonta Smith is in for a huge workload, and some of Philadelphia’s secondary receiving options could step up in Brown’s place. Brown will enter Week 9 as a question mark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d2-d5d8-a3ff-fff36dae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles C Cam Jurgens (knee) won’t play in Philadelphia’s Week 8 game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d5-deb1-a39b-37df3f140000</link>
      <description>Neither will Adoree Jackson (concussion) and Azeez Ojulari (hamstring), three of the four injuries the Eagles announced that they suffered against the Vikings in Week 8. (A.J. Brown never was given a status in that game.) LB Jeremiah Trotter (ankle) got in a full practice on Friday and isn’t on the final injury report for the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d5-deb1-a39b-37df3f140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (calf) is not on Philadelphia’s final Week 8 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d7-d245-adfb-97df24a50000</link>
      <description>He got in a second-straight full practice and may have a bigger role than usual against the Giants in Week 8 with A.J. Brown ruled out. Goedert’s red zone usage already made him a locked-in TE1. The Brown injury should give him a solid floor to pair with it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d7-d245-adfb-97df24a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Terry McLaurin (quad) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d5-deb1-a39b-37df87ad0000</link>
      <description>Great news. McLaurin has now logged consecutive full sessions, putting him firmly on track to play in Week 8 against the Chiefs on Monday night. The fact that his injured quad responded positively to Thursday’s practice is positive. Although McLaurin will be without QB Jayden Daniels (hamstring), he can be started as a WR2 in what should be a favorable game environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17d5-deb1-a39b-37df87ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Josh Reynolds (hip) is questionable for New York’s Week 8 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-deb1-a39b-37de811d0000</link>
      <description>He did not practice on Friday with the hip injury, which is a concerningly quick downgrade. We’re not entirely sure who else to recommend in New York’s pass-catcher room if Reynolds is down — Arian Smith played 91.8 percent of the snaps last week but turned them into just a three-target sacrificial X showing. Tyler Johnson led the team in receiving yardage and might be the play, but only played 25 percent of the snaps in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-deb1-a39b-37de811d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WR Deebo Samuel (heel) practiced in full on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa48d80000</link>
      <description>Samuel and Terry McLaurin (quad) have both practiced in full over the last two days, putting them on track to play in Week 8 against the Chiefs on Monday Night Football. Samuel will be a WR3 in fantasy, with McLaurin expectedly back in the fold. The wide receiver duo will be catching passes from capable backup QB Marcus Mariota, with QB Jayden Daniels (hamstring) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17da-dab4-a3fb-9ffa48d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (hamstrings) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 8 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17df-d5d8-a3ff-ffff3c380000</link>
      <description>Waddle will play in Week 8 despite injuring both hamstrings this week. While he technically can be started as a WR2, there are obvious re-injury concerns at play. Waddle should command a healthy target share for as long as he is out there, operating as the Dolphins’ No. 1 wide receiver, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-17df-d5d8-a3ff-ffff3c380000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
