<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 03:29:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the franchise tag is “potentially” in play for Falcons TE Kyle Pitts at the end of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</link>
      <description>Pitts is in the fifth and final year of his rookie contract. Last night, he caught 11-of-12 targets for 166 yards and three touchdowns in the Falcons’ Thursday Night Football victory over the Buccaneers. Before the game, Falcons owner Arthur Blank reportedly visited the NFL Network’s pre-game broadcast set. Rapoport followed up the visit with a televised report saying Blank will “evaluate” all football operations after the season. Although head coach Raheem Morris and general manager Terry Fontenot may end up being let go, Pitts may have played his way into a new contract, or at least a one-year deal on the lucrative franchise tag. Rapoport notes, though, that Pitts’ agent, David Mulugheta, “hates the franchise tag” and could play hardball in pursuit of a long-term deal. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Bears are optimistic WR Rome Odunze (foot) will play in Week 15’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10e6-d77b-adfb-dae7ae440000</link>
      <description>Odunze is listed as questionable with a foot injury after missing last week’s Bears loss in Green Bay. The 23-year-old wide receiver practiced all week in a limited fashion. Odunze had just two catches and eight yards in his last game action against the Eagles in Week 13. If active, he’ll be a risky FLEX option for desperate teams in the first round of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10e6-d77b-adfb-dae7ae440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186a-d8cf-affb-bc6a4e990000</link>
      <description>Jennings was already ruled out for Week 15’s matchup with the Bills, but now he’s set to miss the next four games after being placed on injured reserve. Jennings had already seen his role in the offense evaporate with the return of Rhamondre Stevenson. D’Ernest Johnson will serve as the Patriots’ third running back in Jennings’ absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186a-d8cf-affb-bc6a4e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Colts QB Philip Rivers is “trending towards” starting against the Seahawks in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186e-d77b-adfb-daef29180000</link>
      <description>While Rivers hasn’t officially been named the starter, reports that lean towards him starting against the Seahawks continue to pile up. Riley Leonard (knee) practiced in full all week and has no injury designation, but the Colts seem convinced after last week’s loss to the Jaguars that Rivers, who has a wealth of experience that includes familiarity with Shane Steichen’s offense from his Chargers days, gives them the best chance to win. Rivers isn’t a recommended fantasy option in his first game action since January 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186e-d77b-adfb-daef29180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Colts QB Philip Rivers will start against the Seahawks in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</link>
      <description>Schefter reports that the Colts are signing Rivers to the active roster. The quarterback who turned 44 earlier this week and ranks seventh in all-time passing yards entering Week 15 was a semifinalist for this year’s Pro Football Hall of Fame class. Rivers will now have to wait another five years before he’s eligible again, assuming he retires again after this season. Fantasy managers considering using the signal caller who was in the same draft class as Eli Manning, who last played in 2019, in the fantasy playoffs have lost the plot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers added RB Emanuel Wilson (illness) to the injury report Saturday with a questionable designation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-18e8-d8cf-affb-bceae9f40000</link>
      <description>The team elevated RB Pierre Strong from the practice squad in an associated move, which comes as both Josh Jacobs and Wilson are listed as questionable. Stay tuned ahead of the team’s inactives Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-18e8-d8cf-affb-bceae9f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed TE Eric Saubert to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d8cf-affb-bd6e12030000</link>
      <description>Saubert played 2025 on a one-year contract, with the extension tying him to the Seahawks through the 2026 season. Largely lauded for his run-blocking and pass-blocking abilities, Saubert should return to contributing primarily from 12-personnel once he makes his way back from injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196c-d8cf-affb-bd6e12030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers downgraded RB Christian McCaffrey (back) to questionable for Week 15 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196e-d8cf-affb-bd6efae90000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey dealt with an illness that limited his practice participation this week. He was removed from the injury report Friday before being added back and listed as questionable Saturday with a bak injury. It is unclear when the new ailment surfaced. Late-week additions to the injury report are never something fantasy managers want to see, also leading to a significant decision in the first week of fantasy playoffs considering the 49ers don’t play until the afternoon Sunday. McCaffrey will remain a top tier RB1 if active against the Titans. Fantasy managers might want to hedge by grabbing Brian Robinson off of waivers, if available. ESPN’s Adam Schefter later followed up the report by saying McCaffrey will go “good to go” Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-196e-d8cf-affb-bd6efae90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Daniel Jones (Achilles) underwent successful surgery Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1997-d8cf-affb-bdbf5d620000</link>
      <description>The veteran quarterback was in the midst of a career year before it was halted due to a torn Achilles. The six-to-eight month recovery window gives him the potential to be ready for preseason camp ahead of the 2026 regular season, which is sure to figure into the team’s plans moving forward. That will likely be a point of continuous discussion surrounding the Colts considering Jones was playing the 2025 season on a one-year, “prove-it” deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1997-d8cf-affb-bdbf5d620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed WR Brandon Aiyuk on the reserve/left squad list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-199f-d8cf-affb-bdbfdac20000</link>
      <description>If you’re not familiar with the reserve/left squad list, that’s okay, it is something typically reserved for players about to retire. The awkward saga between Aiyuk and the 49ers appears to be ending in a messy divorce, with the recent move by the team all but ensuring the two sides split in the coming offseason. The transaction also officially ends Aiyuk’s 2025 season before it began. Stay tuned through the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-199f-d8cf-affb-bdbfdac20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
