<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 15 times for 33 yards in the Falcons’ Week 18 win over the Saints, adding three receptions for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b18-d56e-afff-eff858460000</link>
      <description>Coming off a monumental Week 17, Robinson finishes the season with his fewest yards from scrimmage at 43. Disappointing, though Robinson still easily secured the league’s overall yardage crown at 2,298, which also goes down as a new personal best. We already knew Robinson was one of the league’s best overall offensive players, but now he has a strong claim to the title of *the* best, especially with Christian McCaffrey slowing down between the tackles. 26 days shy of his 24th birthday, Robinson is eligible for a contract extension, though the Falcons will probably simply exercise his fifth-year team option first. Despite the Falcons’ coach and quarterback question marks, Robinson profiles as probably your best overall bet at the No. 1 spot in offseason drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b18-d56e-afff-eff858460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenny Pickett was benched in favor of Aidan O’Connell in Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b14-d35e-a1bf-cfd64b120000</link>
      <description>Pickett appeared to be benched after throwing a first quarter interception on an intermediate pass attempt. His day ends after three pass attempts. O’Connell, who has missed most of the season with injury, will finish out a disastrous season for Vegas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b14-d35e-a1bf-cfd64b120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn “is expected back for the 2026 season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aef-d35e-a1bf-cfef64c40000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Dianni Russini adds that “changes to the offense and the defense remain possible.” Quinn took over defensive play-calling in November. Replacing DC Joe Whitt seems plausible. The team has also reportedly “had conversations about potentially moving on from [OC Kliff] Kingsbury even if he doesn’t get a head-coaching job.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aef-d35e-a1bf-cfef64c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Gesicki caught both of his targets for 13 yards in the Bengals’ Week 18 loss to the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b19-d968-a19b-dbf9625f0000</link>
      <description>Hot off a rebound 2024 season, Gesicki inked a three-year, $25.5 million contract to stay in Cincinnati in the offseason. It became apparent early in the year that Gesicki would not be giving Bengals fans an encore in 2025. He was held under 20 receiving yards in each of his first six games before a pec injury sent him to injured reserve. Gesicki started to turn things around after coming off IR, totaling 35 yards on four grabs in Week 12. At the time, it was his best game of the year. He eventually popped for a few other meaningful games, though he ultimately topped 50 yards just once on the year. He posted a 28/307/2 receiving line in total. The Bengals could save $3.3 million in cap space with a $4.3 million dead cap hit if they move on from him after the year. Either way, we don’t expect him to be on the fantasy radar in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b19-d968-a19b-dbf9625f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 4-of-8 targets for 78 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 18 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b25-d968-a19b-dbf5d3d10000</link>
      <description>London finishes his injury-abbreviated season just 81 yards shy of 1,000 despite missing five games. His 76.6 yards per game go down as a new career high despite the Falcons having to switch quarterbacks from Michael Penix Jr. to Kirk Cousins mid-season. London also dealt with a revived Kyle Pitts, but he simply did what an alpha No. 1 wideout does. Now headed into the final year of his rookie contract, London will spend the offseason negotiating an extension. The Falcons also have Pitts to worry about, but London could end up the priority even though he’s not a free agent like Pitts. For 2026, London will remain a safe WR1 with top-five upside depending on how things shake out at quarterback in Atlanta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b25-d968-a19b-dbf5d3d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson rushed 10 times for 32 yards in the Browns’ Week 18 win over the Bengals, adding two catches for 12 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b1e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf32090000</link>
      <description>Sampson led the Browns in carries but still ceded six attempts to his backups and another five to Cleveland’s wide receivers. Sampson was ultimately doomed to committee duties the moment he was drafted by the Browns in the fourth round. The team had already taken Quinshon Judkins two rounds earlier and Jerome Ford was in the mix as a competent backup. Even when he got the opportunity for more work, Sampson wasn’t particularly impressive. He posted a The rookie averaged a dismal 2.7 yards per carry en route to a just 175 rushing yards. Sampson wasn’t the only back to struggle in the Browns’ horrendous offensive environment, but he did play notably worse than his backfield compatriots. Browns fans and dynasty managers will hope that Sampson can take over as the team’s top option on passing downs next year. He caught 33 passes for 271 yards and two scores this year while averaging a stellar 1.9 yards per route run. With Ford headed into free agency during the offseason, his role should be Sampson’s for the taking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b1e-dc7a-af9b-cfbf32090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 2-of-6 targets for 17 yards in the Browns’ Week 18 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b2f-d35e-a1bf-cfef05ea0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy labored through inconsistent and downright awful quarterback play for the better part of the 2025 season. Coming off a 1,200-yard campaign in 2024, his yardage was cut in half this time around. He finished the season with 50 catches for 602 yards and two touchdowns. Jeudy was also credited with nine drops on the year, which nearly led the league. All in, Jeudy averaged a career-low 1.02 yards per route run. He finished outside the top 75 wideouts in that metric. Jeudy is miscast as a No. 1 receiver and the Browns’ quarterback woes compounded that issue into a catastrophic season. With the Browns looking at quarterback and head coaching changes in the offseason, Jeudy’s fantasy outlook could shift drastically by the time early drafts roll around. For now, he looks like a low-wattage WR5 heading into 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b2f-d35e-a1bf-cfef05ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheim Sanders rushed five times for 26 yards in the Browns’ Week 18 win over the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b36-d968-a19b-dbf7c5560000</link>
      <description>Sanders signed with the Chargers after going undrafted in April. He didn’t make their final roster, but the Browns scooped him up and gave him some short-yardage work in Week 1 with Quinshon Judkins unavailable. He scored a short touchdown and didn’t touch the ball again until Week 16, after Judkins went down with a season-ending injury. Sanders split work with fellow rookie Dylan Sampson over the final three weeks of the year. Judkins is locked in as the high-volume runner in Cleveland and Sampson can be penciled in for most of the work on passing downs in 2026. That doesn’t leave much room for Sanders, but he has made progress toward earning a roster spot next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b36-d968-a19b-dbf7c5560000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
