<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) is believed to have suffered “a bad sprain” in Week 15’s loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22be-d8cf-affb-bebe23b30000</link>
      <description>Knight is expected to undergo an MRI on Monday to confirm the diagnosis, but the belief is that he did not break anything. Knight is highly unlikely to play in Week 16’s game against the Falcons, and depending on the severity of his injury, it wouldn’t be surprising if this proved to be season-ending. We’ll check back in with an update when the team provides one, but an already thin Cardinals backfield could be looking at Emari Demercado and Michael Carter as it’s top two options down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22be-d8cf-affb-bebe23b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers added RB Jaylen Warren (illness, questionable) to the injury report for Week 15 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22c3-d005-a9bf-faf760f70000</link>
      <description>Players typically play through any illness-related issues, but Warren’s addition to the injury report just hours before kickoff is concerning. NFL Network’sTom Pelissero reportsWarren “woke up sick and is getting fluids” and that he is “optimistic” about playing on Monday night. His status will be one to watch for when inactives are announced 90 minutes before kickoff, but if he is unable to go, Kenneth Gainwell would be primed for a large role on Monday night against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-22c3-d005-a9bf-faf760f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans DT Mario Edwards (pectoral) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-230f-d005-a9bf-fb3f68570000</link>
      <description>Edwards has appeared in 14 games for the Texans this season, tallying 13 tackles, 1.5 sacks, and two TFLs in a supporting role. Naquan Jones, who the Texans recently claimed off waivers, took over in Edwards’ absence on Sunday and will presumably be tasked with filling his role for the remainder of the season. Edwards signed a two-year deal with the Texans this offseason and should be back in time for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-230f-d005-a9bf-fb3f68570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryans HC DeMeco Ryans said Woody Marks (ankle) should be fine after being injured in Week 15’s win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2314-d8cf-affb-bf3e6a070000</link>
      <description>Ryans said the team will monitor Marks’ injury this week, but this doesn’t appear to be too big of an issue. Ryans said after Sunday’s game that Marks could have returned against the Cardinals if needed, so his comments on Monday aren’t too surprising. Fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on his practice status throughout the week, but Marks has a nice Week 16 matchup against the Raiders on tap if he is able to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2314-d8cf-affb-bf3e6a070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports an MRI revealed a torn ACL for Micah Parsons, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2329-d77b-adfb-ebab69cf0000</link>
      <description>The worst was confirmed on Monday, as the Packers will now be without their star pass rusher for the remainder of the season. Parsons suffered a non-contact knee injury in the third quarter of Sunday’s loss to the Broncos and remained down for several minutes before being helped off the field by trainers. Head coach Matt LaFleur said after the game that things “didn’t look good,” for Parsons, with reports later coming out that the team feared a torn ACL. There isn’t much to explain here. Parsons is one of the premier pass rushers in the league. He totaled 12.5 sacks in 14 games this season while also posting 41 tackles, 12 TFLs, and forcing two fumbles. The Packers now have to find a way to get by in the regular and postseason without their best player, who has accounted for 37.9 percent of their sacks this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2329-d77b-adfb-ebab69cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Anthony Richardson (eye/IR) has been medically cleared to return to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2335-d1bc-a3fb-a735f7d00000</link>
      <description>Could a healthy Richardson start for the Colts at some point in the next three weeks? It’s not impossible to imagine. Of course, Philip Rivers didn’t join this team to sit. We’d expect Richardson to be designated to return from injured reserve in the near future. Richardson probably would be the team’s backup over Riley Leonard if both were fully healthy, but anything beyond that comes down to ego and what the Colts have left to play for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2335-d1bc-a3fb-a735f7d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs HC Andy Reid said Patrick Mahomes is getting a second opinion on the surgery that is required to repair the torn ACL in his left knee.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2344-d1bc-a3fb-a764349b0000</link>
      <description>We are not injury experts here at Rotoworld, so we don’t have much to offer regarding what this second opinion could mean for Mahomes. The Chiefs’ star quarterback was confirmed to have suffered a torn ACL in Week 15’s loss to the Chargers and is expected to miss the rest of the season. Gardner Minshew, who has backed up Mahomes all season, is expected to draw the start as the now-eliminated Chiefs look to finish out the final three games of their 2025 schedule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2344-d1bc-a3fb-a764349b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said he’s “very hopeful” Drake London (knee) will return for Week 16’s game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234a-d77b-adfb-ebcb0c3c0000</link>
      <description>“Obviously got to get to the practice week. I’m very hopeful he can go out there and play for us,” Morris said while labeling him “day to day, but more hopeful.” London looks like a true question mark for Week 16 based on this update from Morris. We still wouldn’t be surprised if he only tested the knee in practice later in the week. A cleared London would be a must-play against the Cardinals, obviously.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234a-d77b-adfb-ebcb0c3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers placed CB Zyon McCollum (hip) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234c-d8cf-affb-bf6e80d20000</link>
      <description>Assuming the Buccaneers do not advance out of the wild card round, this will be a season-ender for McCollum. He started 13 games for the Bucs after signing a three-year extension ahead of the 2025 season. McCollum ends the regular season with a 61.9 PFF coverage grade in 766 defensive snaps, playing roughly equivalent to his 2024 numbers by the same metric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-234c-d8cf-affb-bf6e80d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he will have an answer on his Week 16 QB by Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2349-d8cf-affb-bf6b90aa0000</link>
      <description>Glenn’s delayed decision to name a starter could be due to injuries, as Justin Fields (knee) and Tyrod Taylor (groin) were both unable to play in Week 15, or he just wants more time to evaluate his QB room full of backups. Brady Cook threw for 176-1-3 in his first career start against the Jaguars in Week 15, and would get the Saints in Week 16 if he were to be named the starter. The situation is a clear: ¯\_(ツ)_/¯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2349-d8cf-affb-bf6b90aa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
