<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:29:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Carlton Davis (concussion) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</link>
      <description>Davis still has a chance to clear the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol, but he will probably need to upgrade to full participation tomorrow. Davis leads the team with 12 pass breakups this season. It would be great to have him on the field for New England’s AFC Championship Game against the Broncos, though Denver may opt for a run-heavy approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e5-dc7a-af9b-efff13a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB TreVeyon Henderson (shoulder) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</link>
      <description>Henderson is practicing fully this week, so his availability for the Patriots’ AFC Championship Game against the Broncos’ top-tier defense is not in jeopardy. He will continue sharing the backfield workload with veteran RB Rhamondre Stevenson, who is playing very well at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e7-d35e-a1bf-e7e79c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</link>
      <description>Landry still has a chance to play, though it would be nice to see him resume practicing tomorrow. The veteran pass rusher ranks third on the team in quarterback pressures (50), second in sacks (nine) and 10th in tackles (28). Patriots LB Marte Mapu (hip) was also absent on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7e9-d56e-afff-e7e9a3520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7ce-d968-a19b-ffff1c710000</link>
      <description>Great news. The Broncos’ third-round rookie is on track to play in the AFC Championship Game against the Patriots as long as he remains setback-free. Bryant caught three passes for 32 yards on the Broncos’ opening drive last week. He should handle a featured role in the offense once again this week, though head coach Sean Payton may opt for a run-heavy approach with backup QB Jarrett Stidham under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e7ce-d968-a19b-ffff1c710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e817-d968-a19b-f8f7f2f30000</link>
      <description>Dobbins is in the questionable camp at this time. The 27-year-old rusher is attempting to return from a Lisfranc injury suffered during an illegal hip-drop tackle in Week 10 against the Raiders. Ideally, he upgrades to full participation tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e817-d968-a19b-f8f7f2f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Troy Franklin (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e81d-dc7a-af9b-efbf6ed30000</link>
      <description>Franklin has a chance to play this week, but hamstring injuries can be finicky. The young wide receiver was forced from last week’s Divisional Round win over the Bills after suffering the injury in-game. He earned zero targets before departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e81d-dc7a-af9b-efbf6ed30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed and interview with Steelers assistant general manager Andy Weidl for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e824-d35e-a1bf-ede6b1230000</link>
      <description>Weidl spent the last four seasons in his current role. He previously served as the Eagles’ vice president of player personnel and has worked in the NFL for 27 years. This is Weidl’s first interview in the current hiring cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e824-d35e-a1bf-ede6b1230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams EDGE Byron Young (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e82b-d968-a19b-f8fb1c310000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters that keeping Young sidelined thus far is a precautionary measure. The Rams’ sack leader (13) is still expected to play. Young ranks second on the team in quarterback pressures (74) and fifth in tackles (56). Rams S Quentin Lake (illness) resumed practicing fully today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e82b-d968-a19b-f8fb1c310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e83a-d968-a19b-f8fb81a70000</link>
      <description>We fully expect Darnold to play in the Seahawks’ NFC Championship Game against the division-rival Rams. The Seahawks’ quarterback was able to throw at practice today, which is great to hear. The two teams faced each other twice this season, both squads coming away with one win. The Rams’ defense has held Darnold to less than 280 passing yards in both outings, while intercepting six passes and allowing just two passing touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e83a-d968-a19b-f8fb81a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e82d-d968-a19b-f8fd5df50000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters earlier today that they are “optimistic” about Cross’ availability this week. Cross’ top-two backups, OT Josh Jones (knee/ankle) and OT Amari Kight (knee), were also absent again on Thursday and are considered “day-to-day,” per Macdonald.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e82d-d968-a19b-f8fd5df50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
