<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (concussion) is not on New England’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88c-d35e-a1bf-cdceac290000</link>
      <description>Mike Vrabel said Gonzalez would be questionable before practice, but he cleared protocol and will officially suit up against the Texans on Sunday. The star cornerback is one of New England’s best players and it’s great news for their defense that he’ll not miss any time after leaving Sunday’s win over the Chargers with a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88c-d35e-a1bf-cdceac290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots EDGE Harold Landry (knee) is questionable for New England’s Divisional Round game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeea6eb0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice today. Landry played 26 snaps against the Chargers last week and would figure to be part of a rotation at EDGE if he were able to go — the Pats have managed him through practices so we’re not surprised to see him on the injury report, but a DNP on Friday is different than the norm for him. Backup RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) is questionable after two full practices on Thursday and Friday and could come off injured reserve tomorrow. Khyiris Tonga (foot) is not on the injury report at all after two full sessions. His return is great news for the New England run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeea6eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said he is “really optimistic” QB Sam Darnold (oblique) “is going to be able to play” in the Divisional Round against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeeca8d0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald adds that there is “a possibility the injury limits [Darnold] physically,” while adding that Darnold “is confident he’ll be able to operate normally.” Per The Athletic’s Mike Dugar, Macdonald “gave a non-answer” when asked if Darnold “threw during the walkthrough.” Macdonald’s obfuscatory responses make it difficult to assess the severity of Darnold’s injury, but we believe Darnold will play even if the oblique injury is bothering him on Saturday. The Seahawks enter their matchup with the 49ers averaging a below-average 62.5 plays per game, methodically picking up yardage while running out the clock. If they can control the game’s pace, they may be able to keep Darnold’s workload at a manageable, moderate level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c88e-d56e-afff-eeeeca8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (knee) is not on New England’s final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c891-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcad40000</link>
      <description>As expected, Henry will play his usual role. He hooked up with Drake Maye for Maye’s lone touchdown last week against the Chargers and should be in DFS consideration this weekend despite playing in a game with the lowest scoring total on the slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c891-dc7a-af9b-cfbfcad40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills activated DT Ed Oliver (biceps) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8a2-dc7a-af9b-cfbfc2030000</link>
      <description>Oliver and WR Curtis Samuel (elbow/neck) are both being activated today. Samuel cannot reasonably be viewed as a reliable contributor, but the Bills’ wide receiver room is thin. Oliver’s return should have a larger impact on the game. Despite missing much of the season, he ties for third on the team with three sacks. The Bills are also elevating WR Mecole Hardman and RB Frank Gore Jr. from the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8a2-dc7a-af9b-cfbfc2030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets interviewed Michigan DC Wink Martindale for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf868e0000</link>
      <description>It was part of an announcement of eight names that the Jets had preliminary interviews with, those other names are: Browns safeties coach Ephraim Banda, Packers defensive run game coordinator DeMarcus Covington, Vikings defensive passing game coordinator and cornerbacks coach Daronte Jones, Broncos assistant head coach and defensive passing game coordinator Jim Leonhard, internal Jets DB coach and defensive pass game coordinator Chris Harris, and Lions safeties coach Jim O’Neil. (Mathieu Araujo, the Dolphins cornerbacks coach, was also revealed earlier today.) Martindale hasn’t had any outside interest since last offseason, when he interviewed for the Falcons and Colts defensive coordinator roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8af-dc7a-af9b-cfbf868e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins completed an interview with Jaguars DC Anthony Campanile for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8b6-d56e-afff-eefe124e0000</link>
      <description>Surprisingly the Dolphins are the only team so far to interview or request an interview with the Jaguars defensive coordinator who oversaw a breakout season where the Jags finished sixth in defensive DVOA. Campanile might be a name to file away for next year, much like Jesse Minter was in 2025 after his initial breakout success as Chargers defensive coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8b6-d56e-afff-eefe124e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Cowboys “plan to bring in” Eagles defensive passing game coordinator and DBs coach Christian Parker for an in-person interview.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8b9-d35e-a1bf-cdfb0e5d0000</link>
      <description>It looks like the Cowboys are gearing up for the second phase of their defensive coordinator interviews, this time in-person. They requested Parker a few days ago initially. Parker with join Jonathan Gannon and Daronte Jones as in-person interviews with the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8b9-d35e-a1bf-cdfb0e5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) is not on Los Angeles’ final Divisional Round injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c3-d35e-a1bf-cdc3d5c80000</link>
      <description>Ferguson practiced in full all three days this week and will return to the Rams’ 13-personnel sets after being inactive against the Panthers. His role was growing towards the end of the season, but with all of Davis Allen, Colby Parkinson, and Tyler Higbee also active, Ferguson will just be a DFS punt dart throw on this slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c8c3-d35e-a1bf-cdc3d5c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike Silver reports that the Eagles “might draft a quarterback this spring.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84b-dc7a-af9b-cfffa81b0000</link>
      <description>Silver adds that Eagles backup QB Tanner McKee “is also highly regarded within the building.” Hurts reportedly “fashions himself” as the NFL’s Michael Jordan, chasing excellence with a “hyper-focus that can come off as aloofness.” He has reportedly “been the source of much internal frustration, including from teammates other than” WR A.J. Brown. That said, Hurts “likely isn’t going anywhere anytime soon.” There is “a sense inside the locker room” that head coach Nick Sirianni, general manager Howie Roseman and owner Jeffrey Lurie “are reluctant to criticize Hurts,” and Lurie “remains confident that an offseason reset can thrust Philly back into Super Bowl contention.” Hurts, 27, did not have a good year, but he led the team to a Super Bowl victory one year ago and has three years left on the five-year, $255 million extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-c84b-dc7a-af9b-cfffa81b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
