<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:29:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is questionable to return to Week 3 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ed4-d6a5-adff-fed563660000</link>
      <description>Tracy had nine touches on the first two drives for the Giants but took a stinger to the shoulder late in the first quarter. He managed to gain 29 yards on seven carries and seven yards on two receptions prior to departing. Tracy was hit along the sideline by Chiefs linebacker Nick Bolton. He remained motionless on the field until New York’s medical staff arrived, eventually walking to the locker room under his own power. Rookie Cam Skattebo could be in for a large workload if Tracy is unable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ed4-d6a5-adff-fed563660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Jones said he re-aggravated the PCL injury he dealt with during training camp in the 49ers’ Week 3 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ef1-dfde-a1bd-7efd76800000</link>
      <description>Jones went down with a PCL sprain in a preseason match with the Raiders but was ready to go by Week 1. He was knocked to the ground in the first half versus Arizona and landed directly on the same knee. Jones returned from the locker room after halftime with a brace on his knee and appeared hobbled at multiple points, though he gutted it out and even led a game-winning drive to defeat Arizona. Brock Purdy is expected to be back for Week 4 after missing the past two games with knee and shoulder issues. With Jones banged up, there will be even more urgency for Purdy to get back on the field. Adrian Martinez will make his NFL debut versus the Jags if neither quarterback is ready for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ef1-dfde-a1bd-7efd76800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston caught 6-of-10 targets for 89 yards in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ef3-dfde-a1bd-7eff4e7f0000</link>
      <description>His 89 yards led the Chargers. Johnston again piled up air yards in the pass-heavy LA offense. He took in 36 percent of the team’s air yards and was one target behind team leader Keenan Allen on the day. Justin Herbert barely overthrew Johnston in the fourth quarter on what would have been a long touchdown, as Johnston had beaten the Denver secondary. Johnston’s role is more fantasy friendly than Ladd McConkey’s, though he remains a somewhat volatile WR3 option week to week. Johnston should serve as a usable flex in Week 4 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ef3-dfde-a1bd-7eff4e7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Benson rushed 10 times for 42 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 3 loss to the 49ers, adding three catches for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ecc-d1b3-a5dd-6ffd9c1e0000</link>
      <description>Benson was already splitting reps with James Conner before this game. Then, at the top of the third quarter, Conner’s leg was bent backward at the ankle, immediately knocking him out of the game. Conner rode the cart to the locker room and the Cardinals’ bench cleared so players could console him on his way off the field. The best-case scenario for Conner would be a severe high-ankle sprain, which would still sideline him multiple weeks. It’s possible the issue is season-ending. Either way, Benson is in line for a massive role in Week 4 versus the Jags. He should be rostered in all formats and is set for an RB2 fantasy ranking next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ecc-d1b3-a5dd-6ffd9c1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 7-of-11 targets for 65 yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efe-d93f-ad9d-7eff36690000</link>
      <description>Allen continues running as Justin Herbert’s clear No. 1 wideout. His touchdown against Denver was his third of the season (one in each game) as he now has 28 targets on the season. The pass-heavy Chargers offense could quite easily keep Allen afloat as a top-20 weekly option based on volume alone. In Week 3 he was working the intermediate areas, averaging 9.5 air yards per target. Allen should be in all fantasy lineups in Week 4 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efe-d93f-ad9d-7eff36690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Josh Weinfuss reports the Cardinals “assume James Conner’s right ankle injury is severe enough to end his season.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efc-d93f-ad9d-7eff26750000</link>
      <description>Weinfuss notes that an official prognosis hasn’t been made, but the team clearly fears the worst. Conner suffered a brutal injury in Sunday’s loss and had to be carted from the field. While he hasn’t officially been ruled out for any length of time, it sounds like the team is preparing to be without him for the rest of the season if tests confirm the worst. It’s a tough blow for Conner, 30, who has rushed for 1,000-plus yards in back-to-back seasons. If he is lost for the season, Trey Benson could be forced into a decent bell cow role while Emari Demercado gets elevated to RB2 duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efc-d93f-ad9d-7eff26750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 3-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 3 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efd-d6a5-adff-fefd51560000</link>
      <description>It was another frustrating day for Cardinals fans and fantasy managers alike. MHJ led Arizona in yards on the back of a 32-yard catch, but also committed an egregious drop on a deep shot from Kyler Murray. Harrison Jr. was open on a deep crossing route and Murray heaved the ball to him. The pass floated to MHJ like a punt and he muffed it like a struggling return man. Harrison Jr. also dropped a diving end zone grab late in the game. He was bailed out by pass interference from a defender dragging Zay Jones to the ground in the end zone. It would have been a highlight-reel play from Harrison Jr., but you expect the No. 5 overall pick to make the show-stopping grabs. MHJ and Murray’s struggles from last year have fully carried over into 2025. After a strong Week 1, Harrison Jr. has just five catches for 71 yards over the past two weeks. MHJ is nothing more than a boom/bust WR3 heading into Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6efd-d6a5-adff-fefd51560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports James Conner “did in fact suffer a season-ending injury to his right ankle” in the Cardinals’ Week 3 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f0d-d6a5-adff-ffcd88b60000</link>
      <description>Things were already trending in this direction given the gruesome nature of the injury. The Cardinals still don’t know the full extent of Conner’s injury, which will require surgery, but the veteran running back is likely looking at a long road to recovery. Conner signed a two-year contract extension last offseason and is officially under contract through 2026. However, he also carries alow dead cap hit of just $2.250 millionand given his age (31), and the latest injury, it’s fair to wonder if the his time with the Cardinals could be coming to an end. Conner’s season ends with a rushing line of 32-95-1. Second-year running back Trey Benson is expected to takeover the lead role in Conner’s absence and profiles as a strong RB2 going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f0d-d6a5-adff-ffcd88b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Conklin did not catch either of his targets in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f37-d6a5-adff-fff738ff0000</link>
      <description>It was rookie TE Oronde Gadsden II, not Conklin, who filled in for Will Dissly (knee) against Denver. Gadsden was second on the team with seven targets on the day despite running just 17 pass routes. It would appear Conklin — who has two receptions on the season — is unplayable in all fantasy formats even with Dissly sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f37-d6a5-adff-fff738ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 28-of-47 attempts for 301 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos, adding two rushes for six yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f3a-d1b3-a5dd-6f7b06d90000</link>
      <description>Herbert led the Chargers back from a fourth quarter deficit on a relatively inefficient outing. Herbert’s 54 percent completion rate ranked 27th out of 31 qualifying quarterbacks in Week 4. Still, he hit his main pass catchers when it counted, including Keenan Allen for a red zone touchdown, beating tight coverage from an elite Broncos secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f3a-d1b3-a5dd-6f7b06d90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
