<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars released LB Chad Muma.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69a-d332-a1fd-f6be87970000</link>
      <description>Quite the surprise for the former No. 70 overall pick in the 2022 NFL Draft. Muma started just seven games across 50 appearances for the Jaguars since being drafted but shouldn’t wait long to resurface on a professional roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e69a-d332-a1fd-f6be87970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers released LB/S Isaiah Simmons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6a4-d332-a1fd-f6b6a22a0000</link>
      <description>Simmons signed with the Packers in April after the Giants let him walk in free agency but was unable to crack the final 53 in Green Bay. His unique athletic profile allows him to play multiple positions in the middle of the field, something that could help him catch on with another team via waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6a4-d332-a1fd-f6b6a22a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints released DE Isaiah Foskey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6ac-de13-afdc-e6eff5f00000</link>
      <description>Foskey was selected at No. 40 overall in the 2023 NFL Draft after setting the all-time record for sacks at Notre Dame. He appeared in 27 games but did not make any starts for the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6ac-de13-afdc-e6eff5f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released OT Trent Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6bf-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff0c3f0000</link>
      <description>Brown joined the Texans on a one-year, $3 million deal in March but was unable to crack the 53-man roster while recovering from a season-ending knee injury suffered in September. The 10-year veteran most recently played for the Bengals and will need to prove his health before another team takes a risk on his services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6bf-dbe3-a9bb-f6ff0c3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Aaron Wilson reports Irv Smith Jr. (ankle) could be headed for injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6c8-dbe3-a9bb-f6db5d810000</link>
      <description>A former second-round pick of the Vikings, Smith signed a one-year deal with the Texans this offseason. The 27-year-old tight end is dealing with a sprained ankle and could be headed to injured reserve, according to Wilson. When healthy, Smith is merely a depth tight end without fantasy value at this point of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6c8-dbe3-a9bb-f6db5d810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released TE Greg Dulcich.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6cd-d332-a1fd-f6ffedeb0000</link>
      <description>Dulcich was claimed off waivers by the Giants last year after the Broncos decided to move on from the former third-round tight end. The 25-year-old had seven catches for 53 yards and three touchdowns in the preseason, but it still wasn’t enough to crack the Giants’ tight end room. Expect him to catch on with another organization either on waivers or via the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6cd-d332-a1fd-f6ffedeb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets released WR Malachi Corley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6ca-d332-a1fd-f6fe41c60000</link>
      <description>The Jets moved up in the 2024 NFL Draft to select Corley at No. 65 overall. Corley made just three grabs for 16 yards in his rookie season and the new brass in New York now move on from him after just one season with the organization. He’ll have an opportunity for a change of scenery via waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6ca-d332-a1fd-f6fe41c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts released TE Jelani Woods.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6d3-db7b-a5dd-e6d75c040000</link>
      <description>No surprise here. Due to injury problems, Woods hasn’t appeared in a game for the Colts since the 2022 season. At the time, Woods was a third-round rookie who shared tight end duties with Mo Allie-Cox and Kylen Granson. The Colts’ tight end rotation is long gone with the addition of first-round Tyler Warren and Woods is also on his way out of Indianapolis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6d3-db7b-a5dd-e6d75c040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals released QB Desmond Ridder.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6d1-dbe3-a9bb-f6d3cba50000</link>
      <description>The release leaves just Jake Browning behind starter Joe Burrow on the active roster. Ridder didn’t pan out with the Falcons or Raiders but could get another chance to stick on an NFL roster through waivers. A career 16-to-14 touchdown-to-interception ratio in three professional seasons is the clear downside to Ridder’s profile, but plus athleticism and an above average arm are valuable traits in the current state of the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e6d1-dbe3-a9bb-f6d3cba50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
