<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Hunter caught all three targets for 64 yards in the Jagaurs’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcea-db72-a199-feebfb470000</link>
      <description>Hunter continued to play both ways against the Chiefs, notably matching up with Kansas City tight end Travis Kelce on multiple occasions on the defensive side of the ball. He made a ridiculous 44-yard catch in the second half after briefly exiting with injury in which he elevated enough to rest on the shoulder of a defender before coming down with the ball, something head coach Liam Coen hinted at this week with talks of getting the electric rookie involved more down the field. Volume has not yet erupted in an offense built behind the run, but Hunter could continue his surge in production against the Seahawks in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcea-db72-a199-feebfb470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington caught 2-of-3 targets for 16 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bced-db72-a199-feefdc010000</link>
      <description>Washington played sparingly behind both Dyami Brown and Tim Patrick, but made the most of his opportunity with a touchdown grab from three yards out in the second quarter for the team’s first points of the game. Washington can safely be returned to the waiver wire barring an injury ahead of him on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bced-db72-a199-feefdc010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown caught 2-of-4 targets for 15 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 5 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcf0-db72-a199-fefbec5e0000</link>
      <description>Brown’s four targets tied for second on the team on a night quarterback Trevor Lawrence attempted only 25 passes, keeping him on the fringes of fantasy consideration moving forward. He likely remains a touchdown-dependent potential FLEX option unless, or until, the team starts utilizing rookie Travis Hunter on offense for heavier rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bcf0-db72-a199-fefbec5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner Jr. believes Brett Rypien, Sean Clifford, and Mike White “are not in consideration to replace” Jake Browning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bee2-d94a-a79d-bfeff7b60000</link>
      <description>Rypien is on the 53-man roster as Browning’s backup while Clifford and White are currently on the team’s practice squad. Dehner Jr. put it bluntly, “Any options left open to, theoretically, replace Browning in Green Bay would have to come from outside the building.” With no outside additions made yet, Browning will get at least one more week as the starter. It is, however, clear that his leash is shrinking by the weak. Bengals head coach Zac Taylor said earlier this week that the team is evaluating the quarterback position like any other heading into Week 6. The Giants have two backup quarterbacks, Russell Wilson and Jameis Winston, who could both be moved now that Jaxson Dart is the starter. Kirk Cousins is also sitting on the Falcons bench waiting for an opportunity of his own, though his bloated contract makes a trade difficult to swing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bee2-d94a-a79d-bfeff7b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals released QB Mike White from their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bef2-def2-abdb-bff3fb070000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner Jr. wrote this morning that the Bengals’ replacement for Jake Browning wasn’t on the roster. That could mean White was released to clear space for a new addition at quarterback. Browning will likely get at least one more start, but he will need to turn things around on Sunday versus the Packers if he wants to hold the job beyond Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bef2-def2-abdb-bff3fb070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Lions CB Terrion Arnold (shoulder) is likely to miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf19-db72-a199-ff5be2fe0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Dan Campbell already told reporters that Arnold is expected to be out for a long time. Now Pelissero is all but confirming that Arnold is done for the year. Pelissero notes that Arnold still has some testing to undergo, though we suspect they will affirm his shoulder injury as season-ending. Arnold was dealing with the shoulder injury heading into Week 5 and aggravated the issue versus Cincinnati. Much like last year, the injuries are piling up on the defensive side of the ball for Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf19-db72-a199-ff5be2fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans GM Nick Caserio said Joe Mixon (foot) is “making progress” and the team will have a better idea of his availability for the year “in a few weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf30-def2-abdb-bf71c6e30000</link>
      <description>Caserio declined to put a timetable on a potential return for Mixon, but it sounds like he at least has a chance to play at some point this year. Mixon popped up with a mysterious foot injury early in the offseason, but beat reporters insisted it was a minor issue, likely hearing that from Mixon’s camp. Training camp came and went and Mixon never took the field once. The team then put him on the NFI list and updates on his status have been few and far between. The fact that he hasn’t been ruled out for the year yet is at least a modestly positive sign, though it’s unlikely he has any impact on the fantasy landscape in 2025. Woody Marks and Nick Chubb will continue to split the backfield for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf30-def2-abdb-bf71c6e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Lions CB Terrion Arnold’s shoulder injury “is not as bad as feared” and he could return “sooner than expected.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf69-def2-abdb-bf693f4a0000</link>
      <description>Arnold underwent testing on his shoulder earlier today. He was expected to be done for the year, but the Lions received good injury news seemingly for the first time in over a year. Now Arnold could return before the end of the month, according to Schefter. Detroit will still be severely undermanned for the next few weeks, but this is as good of news as Lions fans could have hoped for, given the expectation for Arnold heading into Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf69-def2-abdb-bf693f4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf91-def2-abdb-bff1b1990000</link>
      <description>The Giants held another walkthrough today. Head coach Brian Daboll told reporters Slayton would not have been able to practice if it were a live session. With two DNPs to start the week, Slayton is looking unlikely to play on Thursday versus the Eagles. Beaux Collins and Jalin Hyatt will likely see more work in his absence, though neither wideout is on the fantasy radar for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf91-def2-abdb-bff1b1990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart (hamstring) “will be ok” for Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf96-dd4c-afb9-ffd74e330000</link>
      <description>Dart tweaked his hamstring in his first start back in Week 4. He played through the injury on Sunday without any issues. The Giants then listed him as limited for the team’s Monday walkthrough. Dart may continue to have his reps monitored in practice, but he’s at no risk of missing Thursday’s game against the Eagles. His rushing output will keep him in the QB2 ranks despite a tough matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-bf96-dd4c-afb9-ffd74e330000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
