<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught all four targets for 45 yards and two touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb7-d94a-a79d-dbbfcb690000</link>
      <description>It was the first multi-touchdown game since the 2021 season for Brown, who shook free on two crossers near the end zone for easy scores in this one. Brown’s role is almost assuredly set to change with Rashee Rice due back to the field in Week 7 after serving his six-game suspension. Brown could be relegated to prayer FLEX status moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbb7-d94a-a79d-dbbfcb690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 2-of-4 targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 6 win over the Lions, adding six yards on one carry.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbbb-def2-abdb-dffb24a90000</link>
      <description>Worthy continues to gut out multiple injuries after playing through a dislocated shoulder and ankle injury for the previous three games, this time finding the end zone early in the first quarter to put the Chiefs on the board. It will be interesting to see how the team handles the return of Rashee Rice in Week 7 considering the state of the pass-catching corps at present. Worthy sees a slight bump down to WR4 range with the return of Rice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dbbb-def2-abdb-dffb24a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimere Dike caught 2-of-3 targets for eight yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd7f-dd4c-afb9-ffff1c590000</link>
      <description>Dike, who has primarily played as a kicker returner this season, saw his playing time spike with Calvin Ridley (hamstring) sidelined against the Raiders. He ran a route on 31 of Cam Ward’s 46 drop backs. The speedy Dike — who’s been targeted on a strong 23 percent of his routes this season — could see more opportunity in the coming weeks if Ridley remains sidelined. He’s someone to monitor on deep league waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd7f-dd4c-afb9-ffff1c590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Lockett caught 1-of-3 targets for zero yards in the Titans’ Week 6 loss against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd88-d94a-a79d-dd8dd6080000</link>
      <description>That gives Locket a grand total of three receptions over his past four games. With Calvin Ridley possibly missing time with a hamstring injury, look for Chimere Dike and Van Jefferson to see an increase in playing time and targets. Lockett has seen a target on a paltry 12 percent of his routes in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd88-d94a-a79d-dd8dd6080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice is eligible to return from suspension in Week 7 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd8a-dd4c-afb9-ffcbddb20000</link>
      <description>Rice served a six-game suspension after violating the league’s personal conduct policy. Rice pleaded guilty to two felonies relating to a multi car crash he was involved with last year. It will be Rice’s first taste of game action since Week 4 of last season, but the third-year receiver was on a tear before his season-ending knee injury. In what amounted to essentially three games played, Rice caught 24 passes for 288 yards and two touchdowns on 29 targets. Rice was involved with the team throughout training camp and should be up to full speed or close to it. We’ll conservatively project him as a WR2/WR3 in his first return to action against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dd8a-dd4c-afb9-ffcbddb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Buccaneers WR Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) will undergo an MRI on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddad-db72-a199-ffef8cff0000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, the hope is Egbuka’s hamstring injury isn’t as significant as the one Mike Evans suffered in Week 3 against the Jets, but the star rookie is still likely to miss some time. It’s yet another blow to a Buccaneers receiving corps that has now seen its top three receivers go down during the first month and a half of the season, which could give way to Kam Johnson and Tez Johnson serving as the top two wide outs in Week 7 when the Bucs take on the Lions. We should know more on Egbuka’s status after his MRI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddad-db72-a199-ffef8cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he will not bench Justin Fields after Week 6’s loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddb1-dd4c-afb9-fff1fbba0000</link>
      <description>Glenn, who said that Fields “did some pretty good things” in his first four games of the season, said it will take more than one bad game to bench Fields. A quick glance at Fields’ second-half splits may change Glenn’s tune on his QB1, as the majority of Fields’ production has come in garbage time for the now 0-6 Jets. He’s also now thrown for less than 50 yards in two of the games he’s appeared in this season. Among 34 qualified quarterbacks this season, Fields ranks 30th in EPA/play and 23rd in dropback success rate. There’s plenty of blame to go around for the Jets disastrous start, but Fields deserves a good chunk of it, as the offense has consistently gotten off to a slow start. It wouldn’t be surprising if Glenn eventually made the switch to veteran Tyrod Taylor, but it will again be Fields under center in Week 7 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddb1-dd4c-afb9-fff1fbba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Puka Nacua suffered a sprained ankle in Week 6’s win over the Ravens “that will likely cause him to miss time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddea-d94a-a79d-ddef38d90000</link>
      <description>The Rams get the Jaguars in Week 7 and then have a Week 8 bye. It wouldn’t be surprising to see Nacua sit out next week, giving him two weeks to recover while hopefully avoiding a stint on injured reserve. We’ll hopefully get more clarity on his Week 7 availability once Sean McVay speaks to the media, but fantasy managers should prepare to be without Nacua for at least the next two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ddea-d94a-a79d-ddef38d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said Puka Nacua (ankle) is day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de38-def2-abdb-df79baa20000</link>
      <description>This could be an overly optimistic take by McVay, but the real proof will be in the injury report. McVay did note that Nacua’s availability for next week is uncertain, but if he can get on the practice field in any capacity he could have a chance to suit up in Week 7 against the Jaguars. Still, it wouldn’t be surprising if he missed at least one game with the Rams having a Week 8 bye coming up. Nacua played through the injury in Sunday’s win over the Ravens, but played primarily a decoy role. Keep an eye out for Wednesday’s injury report, which will give us a better sense of where things could stand for next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de38-def2-abdb-df79baa20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles EDGE Za’Darius Smith retired from the NFL after 11 seasons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de43-def2-abdb-df637c210000</link>
      <description>This one comes as a bit of a surprise after Smith signed a one-year contract with the Eagles shortly before Week 1, and played in the team’s Week 6 loss to the Giants on Thursday night. The former fourth-round pick who first entered the league with the Ravens in 2015 walks away from the game with 70.5 career sacks on his resumé to go with 87 TFLs and 10 forced fumbles. Smith’s most productive seasons came with the Packers, who he signed a four-year contract with during the 2019 offseason. He earned back-to-back Pro Bowl nods during his first two years in Green Bay, racking up 26 sacks over that span and also received Second-Team All-Pro honors in 2020. Smith’s decision to walk away leaves an already banged up Eagles defense another man short. They will likely look to bring on another veteran pass rusher in the coming days to make up for his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-de43-def2-abdb-df637c210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
