<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jordon Riley (Achilles) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 18 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6280-d56e-afff-e6e8befa0000</link>
      <description>Riley was roled up on Derrick Henry’s touchdown run and needed a cart. The 27-year-old is obviously in danger of missing Week 18 against the Vikings as well as the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6280-d56e-afff-e6e8befa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oronde Gadsden caught 3-of-6 targets for 32 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62ab-d968-a19b-7afba3630000</link>
      <description>Gadsden had quite the volatile day. He first chipped in a six-yard gain on a checkdown pass during the Chargers’ fourth drive. Two drives later, Gadsden got open at the Texans’ five-yard line against Texans LB Azeez Al-Shaair. Instead of securing the target and powering in for the score, Gadsden swiped at an albeit high, fast pass, bobbling it behind him and into Al-Shaair’s hands for the interception. He dropped his next target, two drives later. He earned a 13-yard end zone target two drives after that, but Texans CB Kamari Lasster broke up the pass. Chargers QB Justin Herbert stuck with the young tight end, though, connecting with him for a one-yard touchdown via a delayed post route for Herbert’s lone passing touchdown of the day. Gadsden remains a TE1 in re-draft against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62ab-d968-a19b-7afba3630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarion Hampton rushed 14 times for 29 yards and one touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans, adding eight receptions for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62af-d35e-a1bf-67ef2c5d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans’ defense dominated the trenches in this one. Hampton’s five-yard rushing touchdown, late in the fourth quarter, was his longest run of the day. Fortunately, he is a talented three-down player, which allows him to remain on the field in passing situations, either as a checkdown weapon or as a reliable pass protector. He played well in both phases. Hampton is a low-end RB1 against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62af-d35e-a1bf-67ef2c5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 1-of-1 targets for eight yards in the Chargers’ Week 17 loss to the Texans, rushing once for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b5-dc7a-af9b-efbfdbd30000</link>
      <description>Harris sure looks speedy. Unfortunately, the Texans’ defense kept the Chargers’ offense in check for much of the day. The rookie wide receiver was given the ball on an end-around from the Texans’ 15-yard line. Although he failed to score a touchdown, seeing the youngster get a red zone touch was heartening. He is a boom-bust FLEX against the Broncos next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b5-dc7a-af9b-efbfdbd30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) has been ruled out for the remainder of Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b4-d56e-afff-e6fca6b70000</link>
      <description>Wicks picked up the concussion during the third quarter. The 24-year-old will miss the remainder of Week 17, and his status for the finale against the Vikings next week will be dependent on how he recovers and if he can exit the protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-62b4-d56e-afff-e6fca6b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Willis (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 17 against the Ravens. He completed 18-of-21 passes for 288 yards with a touchdown while rushing for 60 yards and two scores before exiting.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6309-dc7a-af9b-efbfc7ab0000</link>
      <description>Willis appeared to aggravate the shoulder injury that he suffered in Week 16 against the Bears. The signal-caller was playing exceptionally well prior to the injury, but looked to be in significant pain after stretching the arm on a throw to the outside. Clayton Tune has taken over at quarterback. It did appear that Willis was set to return to this contest, but with the game out of hand, Tune remained in the game. He could start in Week 18 against the Vikings with that game having no meaning, but it’ll be at least somewhat dependent on Jordan Love (concussion) and his health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6309-dc7a-af9b-efbfc7ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Huntley completed 16-of-20 passes for 107 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ 41-24, Week 17 win over the Ravens, adding eight rushes for 60 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631a-d56e-afff-e7faa9d30000</link>
      <description>Huntley got the start with Lamar Jackson’s back contusion keeping him from playing, and his main goal was handing the football to Derrick Henry (36/216/4) and getting out of the way. Mission accomplished. He did do a nice job connecting on his short-yardage passes, and was rewarded with a touchdown pass to Zay Flowers late in the contest. Huntley will be tasked with being a game manager in Week 18 against the Steelers if Jackson can’t go, and there’s a smidgen of upside because of his ability to make some plays as as a runner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631a-d56e-afff-e7faa9d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 36 times for 216 yards and four touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-630f-d56e-afff-e7effa670000</link>
      <description>Henry now has more 200 yard rushing games (7) than any player in NFL history. He wasn’t targeted in the passing game, because why would you need to? Three of his touchdowns came in the first half, and he routinely ran over completely overmatched Green Bay defenders in yet another impressive effort for the 31-year-old. Keaton Mitchell was somehow able to get nine carries for 31 yards as his (beyond) clear backup on a day where Baltimore rushed for 307 total yards in Lambeau Field. Even if Lamar Jackson (back) returns for Week 18 against the Steelers, Henry is going to be the focal point of the Ravens’ offense for that contest. He has to be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-630f-d56e-afff-e7effa670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 4-of-5 targets for 30 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 17 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</link>
      <description>Flowers was just able to get across the pylon on a connection with Tyler Huntley in the fourth quarter. The 25-year-old was a bit of an afterthought during Saturday’s contest, but that was true for every Raven not named Drrick Henry. He should again be the top option in the passing attack whether it’s Huntley or Lamar Jackson (back) throwing him the ball in Week 18 against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-631f-d35e-a1bf-67dfab500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 4-of-4 targets for 28 yards in the Ravens’ Week 17 win over the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</link>
      <description>Andrews’ biggest play was drawing the Packers offsides while lining up under center on a fourth-and-inches play late in the contest. The Ravens only threw the ball for 107 yards in this contest, so there wasn’t much chance for Andrews, Isaiah Likely (3/27) or any of the Baltimore receivers in this one. He’ll be back in Week 18 against the Steelers in a game that’s meaning will be determined by what happens in Week 17 between Pittsburgh and the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-6327-d968-a19b-7bf7df190000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
