<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught all four of his targets for 37 yards in the Rams’ Week 2 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9a-da67-a99f-ceffea9b0000</link>
      <description>Higbee was held without a counting stat in Week 1, so a four-catch outing represents a massive improvement compared to last week. He did, however, watch backup tight end Davis Allen score an eight-yard touchdown on his only grab of the day. Higbee is still the Rams’ starting tight end, but he isn’t much of a target-earner and is splitting snaps with his backups. Higbee isn’t worth rostering in most fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9a-da67-a99f-ceffea9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 5-of-5 targets for 30 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 2 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9b-d294-a19b-eefbab970000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs went into Week 1’s game hoping to feature Xavier Worthy, then turned Brown loose into his role in the game plan. In Week 2, they looked at what Brown had done with those targets and said “nah, let’s spread the ball around.” If Worthy doesn’t play in Week 3, Brown has a decent PPR scam case against the Giants, but that’s about all he has at the moment. It was a pretty disappointing performance after Week 1 and you could argue Brown is droppable if Worthy returns to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9b-d294-a19b-eefbab970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed five times for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 2 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9d-dc44-a9d9-4fff91c10000</link>
      <description>Corum picked up his first career touchdown on a goal line plunge in the fourth quarter. The Rams were up two scores late in the fourth quarter, but their starters were still on the field, so it wasn’t a true garbage-time touchdown. Corum isn’t going to be a short-yardage back anytime soon, but he ran with power versus the Titans and did what was asked of him at the goal line. He could wind up being a bit of a nuisance for Kyren Williams drafters this year after barely playing as a rookie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9d-dc44-a9d9-4fff91c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman Jr. caught 4-of-5 targets for 40 yards in the Colts’ Week 2 win over the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a99-da67-a99f-cefd9d0b0000</link>
      <description>Pittman earned just one target before halftime, which he efficiently secured for a 10-yard gain. Pittman got going a bit in the second half, though, tying for a team-high four targets in quarters three and four as the Colts successfully pulled off the comeback win. Pittman should have a much easier time returning WR3 value against the Titans in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a99-da67-a99f-cefd9d0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 4-of-6 targets for 61 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 2 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9e-da67-a99f-ceffa14a0000</link>
      <description>One of his incompletions was a drop at the goal line that turned into a Patrick Mahomes interception by Andrew Mukuba and all but sealed the game. Kelce has yet to show any whiff of the ceiling case we saw last year in ideal circumstances without Rashee Rice and Xavier Worthy. Through two weeks, we’re more at “What if Brenton Strange married Taylor Swift?” That’s not to say Kelce needs to be dropped in shallow leagues, but we’re running out of weeks to believe he can turn back the clock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9e-da67-a99f-ceffa14a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 2-of-5 targets for 59 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 2 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa2-d86f-abdd-4fbf80dd0000</link>
      <description>Thornton had another shot play earlier on the drive with his touchdown catch where he was wide-open deep after an Eagles defender fell, but Mahomes simply missed him. What can we say? The whole Chiefs deep offense relies on Tyquan Thornton, and Matt Nagy has proven to be a Tyquan Thornton merchant through two weeks. He’s a low-end FLEX dart throw against the Giants in Week 3. Good on the Chiefs for making a successful reclamation project out of Thornton, but it sure doesn’t feel good that the state of the offense in Week 2 is “Tyquan Thornton better win some sideline one-on-ones.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa2-d86f-abdd-4fbf80dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. caught 2-of-5 targets for 27 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 2 win against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa3-d86f-abdd-4fbf64660000</link>
      <description>Harrison wasn’t involved in the second half, as the Cardinals went run heavy to protect a hefty lead that they almost blew to Bryce Young and the Carolina offense. MHJ caught a red zone pass and stiff armed a defender before being tackled inside the five yard line. Harrison, who had five grabs for 71 yards and a touchdown in Week 1 against the Saints, saw 23 percent of the team’s air yards against the Panthers, trailing Trey McBride (33 percent). Harrison is set up to be something of a frustrating fantasy option if he can’t command targets at a higher clip in the coming weeks. Harrison faces the Niners in Week 3 and should remain in all fantasy rosters for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa3-d86f-abdd-4fbf64660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 25 times for 165 yards in the Colts’ Week 2 win over the Broncos, adding two receptions for 50 yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9b-da67-a99f-ceff309e0000</link>
      <description>Taylor was involved non-stop against the Broncos, and remained astonishingly efficient (6.6 YPC) despite the monstrous workload. His 68-yard run on the Colts’ first drive after halftime was the longest run of the game, and his 43-yard reception was the game’s second longest. Taylor’s receiving touchdown was an easy catch-and-run into the end zone during the second quarter, when Daniel Jones found him wide open in the flats. Taylor is an elite RB1 against the Titans next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4a9b-da67-a99f-ceff309e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Hurts completed 15-of-22 passes for 101 yards in the Eagles’ 20-17, Week 2 win against the Chiefs, adding nine carries for 16 yards and a touchdown on the ground.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa7-d294-a19b-eef743370000</link>
      <description>The Eagles passing offense has disintegrated into something that looks incapable of moving the ball, something where A.J. Brown needs to make a spectacular four-yard catch to come even close to the first down. Kellen Moore is doing his strongest “Miss Me Yet?” in the background of this blurb. Hurts salvaged his overall line with a late rushing score to put the Eagles up 20-10, but if not for a 28-yard chuck-and-hope to DeVonta Smith on the outside, this was shaping up to go sub-100 yards. The Chiefs defense is good and all, butcome on. Hurts’ rushing upside will keep him on the QB1 line but there’s already a case to be made that this Eagles pass offense needs to be better for him to be in the elite tier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4aa7-d294-a19b-eef743370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
