<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Tolbert caught his only target for eight yards in Dallas’ Week 6 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2f-dd4c-afb9-ffef30b10000</link>
      <description>Tolbert started, played 50 of 55 snaps, and managed just one target. Last week, he played 46 offensive snaps and managed ... one target. It’s been a magical run of sacrificial X receiver play. Tolbert does not need to be rostered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2f-dd4c-afb9-ffef30b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 21 times for 123 yards and a touchdown in the Colts’ Week 6 win over the Cardinals, adding four receptions for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da28-db72-a199-fa6bc9b90000</link>
      <description>Taylor remains one of the most consistent workhorse backs in the league, gashing the Cardinals for 5.9 yards per carry. He was constantly turning short gains into long ones and was available as Daniel Jones’ outlet pass-catching option. Taylor scored the go-ahead touchdown on a toss play from the one-yard line in the fourth quarter and sealed the game with a 16-yard rush on the Colts’ last drive. The 26-year-old handles nearly all of the Colts’ backfield touches and scores touchdowns, despite Daniel Jones’ rushing ability vulturing some of that opportunity. Taylor is a definitive RB1 for Week 7 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da28-db72-a199-fa6bc9b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 4-of-6 targets for 24 yards in the Ravens’ Week 6 loss to the Rams, adding three carries for two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2a-def2-abdb-df6bb1670000</link>
      <description>Two of Andrews’ three “carries” were goal-line tush pushes where, as you can see, he did not reach the end zone. The dreadful play-calling led to a Derrick Henry fourth down stop and left the game tied at three at halftime. The Rams then quickly made it 17-3 early in the third frame. Although he’s had Lamar Jackson’s absence as an alibi the past two weeks, Andrews has now been held to 30 receiving yards or fewer every game but one this season. Already hurting for ceiling, it just hasn’t been possible with L-Jax on the shelf. Jackson is expected to return against the Bears following the Ravens’ Week 7 bye, probably keeping Andrews on the TE1/2 borderline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2a-def2-abdb-df6bb1670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin caught 7-of-10 targets for 81 yards in the Browns’ Week 6 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2d-db72-a199-fa6f23b80000</link>
      <description>Fannin’s 10 targets were second only to Jerry Jeudy (13). The rookie tight end had his best game since breaking out for 9-63-0 in Week 1, and did a significant amount of his damage in the fourth quarter. Fannin saw five of his targets come in the fourth quarter after David Njoku exited with an apparent knee injury, and turned one of those receptions into a 24-yard gain on a long catch-and-run. Fannin has been involved in the offense all season long, but hasn’t lived up to the hype he generated following his Week 1 performance. With that said, he would be firmly on the TE1 radar in Week 7 against the Dolphins if Njoku is unable to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2d-db72-a199-fa6f23b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara rushed 10 times for 31 yards in the Saints’ Week 6 loss to the Patriots, adding five catches for 45 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2e-dd4c-afb9-ffefbb400000</link>
      <description>Kamara again did nothing on the ground, but he finally got things going through the air with a season-high in receiving yards on the back of a 22-yard reception in the third quarter. It was his longest play of the year, catch or carry. However, he still ceded eight carries and one catch to backup Kendre Miller. Miller’s increasing role and Kamara’s declining efficiency have dropped him from a volume-based RB2 to an RB3 in most weeks. A date with a putrid Chicago defense might be enough to keep him in the RB2 ranks one more time in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da2e-dd4c-afb9-ffefbb400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Fred Warner (ankle) was carted away from Week 6’s game against the Buccaneers and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da31-dd4c-afb9-fff109320000</link>
      <description>Warner’s foot went a way that a foot should not go after he was rolled up on defending against a Rachaad White run in the first quarter. It was a brutal injury, likely one that will end his season, and the last thing the 49ers needed for a defense without any other impact pieces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da31-dd4c-afb9-fff109320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 3-of-5 targets for 29 yards and two touchdowns in the Panthers’ Week 6 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da34-db72-a199-fa7fb3950000</link>
      <description>They weren’t pretty catches — it looked like a pair of busted coverages where no Cowboys defender was near McMillan — but they count for fantasy managers that had seen plenty of beautiful catch attempts go nowhere for McMillan. He’ll be in the WR2 ranks for Week 7’s game against the Jets, though it doesn’t look like the Panthers are going to be a good enough passing attack for him to have a 10-plus target ceiling any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da34-db72-a199-fa7fb3950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) is questionable to return in Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da35-d94a-a79d-db3dfca80000</link>
      <description>Ridley limped off the field in the second quarter and went straight into the blue medical tent. He doesn’t have the look of a player who expects to re-tenter the ball game. Ridley had one catch for 18 yards before sustaining the injury. Elic Ayomanor should operate as the Titans’ No. 1 wideout with Ridley sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da35-d94a-a79d-db3dfca80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
