<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:20:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons general manager Ian Cunningham said the team will release QB Kirk Cousins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</link>
      <description>The move will be made on the first day of the 2026 NFL calendar year, according to Cunningham. This was all but confirmed last month when Cousins and the Falcons agreed to a contract modification that guaranteed he’d be gone ahead of the 2026 season. Cousins, 37, should see some interest from quarterback-needy teams in the coming months. Last year Cousins had a career-low 6.3 adjusted yards per attempt and 44.3 percent drop back success rate in five appearances (three starts) for the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9033-d89c-a1be-bfff62730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens general manager Eric DeCosta said the team has offered C Tyler Linderbaum a “market setting” deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9040-d629-a1bc-b05dd4a80000</link>
      <description>DeCosta was clear about the team’s intent to keep Linderbaum as he’s expected to have several suitors in free agency this spring. The All-Pro center, perhaps the best in the league, could see interest from the Chargers and Giants, as both teams are coached by Harbaugh brothers, and John Harbaugh — Baltimore’s former head coach — is trying his best to get the band back together in New York. Pro Football Focus graded Linderbaum 23rd among centers in pass blocking last year and third in run blocking. Linderbaum has been durable, missing just two regular season games over his first four NFL seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9040-d629-a1bc-b05dd4a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears general manager Ryan Poles said teams have expressed interest in acquiring QB Tyson Bagent.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9046-d629-a1bc-b05fd5090000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals are among the teams reportedly interested in trading for Bagent this offseason after he showed flashes in preseason games and during four starts back in 2023. Bagent, if he lands with another team in the coming weeks or months, will likely have to compete for a starting job but could have a decent shot at landing one in a QB-hungry league. Bagent, entering his age-26 season, played at Division II Shepard in college, throwing for 94 touchdowns and 21 interceptions over his final two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9046-d629-a1bc-b05fd5090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Zach Ertz (ACL) intends to return for a 14th season in 2026, and that he hopes to be cleared “right around” Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904a-d57c-a1dd-944ae2360000</link>
      <description>The 35-year-old was injured in early December. Ertz had already become a catch-and-fall specialist even before his injury, but he has maintained a route-running savvy and strong pair of hands. His injury timeline makes him a tricky bet early in free agency, perhaps making it more likely he holds out for more guaranteed money on the eve of training camp. By then, teams will have a better idea of his health, as well as their own needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904a-d57c-a1dd-944ae2360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan said the team is not “actively” shopping De’Von Achane or Jaylen Waddle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904e-d042-afbc-fdde5e4e0000</link>
      <description>Sullivan spoke with reporters at the NFL Combine and didn’t exactly quash rumors that the Dolphins could part with one or both of their best players in a potential tear-down rebuild of the team. That rebuild — whatever it looks like — will certainly include parting ways with QB Tua Tagovailoa. One of the most explosive, efficient backs in the NFL, Achane could fetch a haul of draft picks if Miami moves on from him in the coming months. Waddle, meanwhile, profiles as a solid No. 2 receiver with a long history of injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-904e-d042-afbc-fdde5e4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers general manager Omar Khan said he had not set a deadline for when Aaron Rodgers can decide on whether to return to the team in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9055-d89c-a1be-bfdf3d1f0000</link>
      <description>Khan told reporters at the NFL Combine on Tuesday that he has been in touch with Rodgers, 42, and doesn’t “foresee this going like it did last year,” when Rodgers drew out his decision to play for the Steelers well into the spring. ESPN reported on February 13 that Rodgers is “more likely than not” to return to Pittsburgh and play for his former Packers coach Mike McCarthy. Rodgers in 2025 showed some improvement over his play with the Jets in 2024. He ranked 23rd out of 36 qualifying quarterbacks last season in drop back EPA and 33rd in drop back success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9055-d89c-a1be-bfdf3d1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens general manager Eric DeCosta said he’s confident the team can reach a contract extension with Lamar Jackson this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9086-d89c-a1be-bfdf9f6b0000</link>
      <description>Jackson, slated to be a free agent after the 2027 NFL season, could re-up with the Ravens after being involved in the coaching search that ended with former Chargers defensive coordinator Jesse Minter as Baltimore’s new head coach. During a press conference at the NFL Combine on Tuesday, DeCosta declined to discuss any details of a potential extension for Jackson, who in 2023 signed a five-year deal worth $260 million, with $185 million guaranteed. Jackson, 29, is looking to bounce back in 2026 after an injury-marred 2025 campaign in which the Ravens missed the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9086-d89c-a1be-bfdf9f6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs general manager Brett Veach said “hopefully” Travis Kelce will return to the team in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-908f-d629-a1bc-b09f728e0000</link>
      <description>Kelce has reportedly been in touch with Andy Reid and the Chiefs in recent weeks after the Chiefs inexplicably missed the postseason. Kelce, 36, has mulled retirement in each of the past three offseasons and seems more serious about the prospect of hanging it up following the disappointment of 2025. “We are prepared for either scenario,” Veach said Tuesday. Kelce caught 76 passes for 851 yards and five touchdowns in 2025. Only five tight ends had more receptions than Kelce and a mere three tight ends had more receiving yards. Kelce ranked 22nd in tight end yards per route run and 14th in yards after the catch per reception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-908f-d629-a1bc-b09f728e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Browns hired longtime NFL coach Dom Capers as the team’s senior defensive assistant coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9098-d042-afbc-fddae6dc0000</link>
      <description>Capers, 75, has been head coach twice during his long run in the NFL. He most recently served as a senior defensive assistant coach for the Panthers. In Cleveland, Capers will join new head coach Todd Monken — formerly of the Ravens — in trying to maintain top-tier status for Cleveland’s defense. In 2025 the Browns — led by Myles Garret — allowed the league’s fourth lowest offensive success rate and third lowest EPA per play. Only the Texans gave up a lower drop back EPA than the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9098-d042-afbc-fddae6dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans general manager Nick Caserio said talk of the team trading QB C.J. Stroud this offseason is “moronic.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-909e-d042-afbc-fdde70130000</link>
      <description>“He’s not going anywhere,” Caserio added. Well, that settles that. Caserio shut down loose talk of the Texans parting with their franchise quarterback after Stroud’s nationally televised Divisional Round meltdown against the Patriots in which he threw for 212 yards, one score, and four interceptions. Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans said in late January that he would not talk about a contract extension for Stroud “right now,” fueling social media speculation that the team was not fully committed to Stroud as their long-term starter. Stroud’s sometimes massive struggles over the past two seasons likely means he won’t get a top-tier extension, though it would be a shock if the Texans parted ways with him. Since the start of the 2024 regular season Stroud ranks 23rd out of 34 qualifying QBs in EPA per drop back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-909e-d042-afbc-fdde70130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
