<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Detroit plans to use WR Isaac TeSlaa “more on offense moving forward.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9d-dbe3-a9bb-3adfa56c0000</link>
      <description>Campbell explained away TeSlaa’s lack of involvement in Week 1 by noting his illness and missing practice kept them from wanting to load him up too much. TeSlaa caught a touchdown on his only target, playing just three snaps. What “more” is could be anything, but we’d start expectations for Week 2 at maybe 20-30 snaps as TeSlaa works to dislodge Kalif Raymond from the WR3 role. He’s by no means a must-start, but a worthy bench stash as waivers open this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2a9d-dbe3-a9bb-3adfa56c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said he hopes to have more clarity on OT JC Latham (hip) by Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aa6-de13-afdd-6eef593b0000</link>
      <description>Latham left Week 1’s game after playing 45 of 57 snaps, giving way to Olisaemeka Udoh at right tackle. It would be a huge loss for the Titans if Latham was sent to injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aa6-de13-afdd-6eef593b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Bengals RG Lucas Patrick will miss a “couple of weeks” with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ab3-de13-afdd-6efbbf220000</link>
      <description>Patrick played on 16 snaps in Week 1’s game against the Browns before going down and was replaced by Dalton Risner. Risner, who signed with the Bengals on a one-year contract this offseason, earned a PFF blocking grade of 43.6 in his debut performance with the Bengals and played on 611 snaps for the Vikings last season. A strong performance by Risner in the coming weeks may be enough to unseat Patrick, who has been on three different teams over the last four seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2ab3-de13-afdd-6efbbf220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said Brock Bowers (knee) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2abd-db7b-a5dd-aabda54a0000</link>
      <description>Carroll admitting that anything is wrong should be a warning sign for fantasy managers, as he’s always supremely optimistic on injuries. Bowers’ practice status will be a major news story for the week ahead. We wouldn’t be surprised if he missed Week 2, but at the very least we expect the Raiders to take it easy on him in practice ahead of their game against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2abd-db7b-a5dd-aabda54a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans restructured S C.J. Gardner-Johnson’s contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</link>
      <description>According to KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson, the Texans are converting $7.75 million of Gardner-Johnson’s base salary into a $6.58 million signing bonus that will free up just over $3.086 million in cap space. Gardner-Johnson is in the second year of a three-year deal he originally signed with the Eagles in 2024, but can be released with no dead cap hit if the team opts to move on from him at the end of this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acf-d332-a1fd-befff7af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys placed DL Perrion Winfrey (back) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aeb-de13-afdd-6eeb77300000</link>
      <description>Winfrey will miss at least the next four games due to the injury. The veteran lineman, who was injured in practice last week, didn’t play in the team’s Week 1 contest against the Eagles due to his injury. He will now have some additional time away to rehab the injury. Winfrey last took a regular-season snap in 2023 and caught on with the Cowboys after a stint in the UFL earlier this spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aeb-de13-afdd-6eeb77300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals coach Jonathan Gannon said Kyler Murray scrambling was “a point of emphasis for us.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acc-de13-afdd-6ecfb13d0000</link>
      <description>“I did think there were some high-leverage snaps in that game where he used his legs for our advantage and that’s what you want to see,” Gannon continued. Murray scrambled four times for 31 yards against the Saints in Week 1, last year he averaged just 2.4 scrambles per game per PFF data. It sounds like Murray is getting the green light to run more when he sees an opportunity and, per Theo Mackie, the Cardinals “tweaked some of their pass protection schematics in an attempt to open up more scrambling lanes for Murray up the middle.” It’s possible we see more running production out of Murray this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2acc-de13-afdd-6ecfb13d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman suffered a high-ankle sprain in the team’s Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aff-d332-a1fd-beff4caf0000</link>
      <description>Perryman is considered week-to-week with the injury, per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. While we don’t know how much time the long-time vet could miss, whether or not he’s placed on injured reserve in the coming days will give us some clue as to how long the team expects his recovery to be. Perryman totaled 55 tackles and one sack with the Chargers last season, appearing in 11 games over that span. He has played in 12 or fewer games in every season dating back to 2022 and will almost certainly be facing a multi-game absence with this latest injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2aff-d332-a1fd-beff4caf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said “I’ve got to be better there” when asked about running the ball only three times against 17 passes in the first quarter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b04-dbe3-a9bb-3b5745db0000</link>
      <description>“It’s one of those day-afters where you look back and say, ‘Alright, let’s look at how we really wanted to start that game and get those two runners going,’ because we think we’ve really improved in that area,” Payton continued. Bo Nix didn’t do much with the added volume and Denver eventually wound up rushing for five yards a carry against the Titans. It sounds like the Broncos could employ a more run-heavy approach against the Colts in Week 2, which should help J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b04-dbe3-a9bb-3b5745db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers DT Tershawn Wharton (hamstring) will miss 2-4 weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b18-dbe3-a9bb-3b5bc8700000</link>
      <description>With four weeks in play, the Panthers might consider placing Wharton on injured reserve. “He was having a fantastic game,’' Panthers coach Dave Canales said of Wharton. “He had four tackles early on, and was really doing a good job of getting of blocks and making opportunities.’' The Panthers figure to remain easy to run on in Week 2, which is good news for James Conner and Trey Benson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2b18-dbe3-a9bb-3b5bc8700000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
