<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:05:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport expects the Bucs to hire Falcons senior offensive assistant Ken Zampese and passing game coordinator TJ Yates.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5e1-d56e-afff-e7e9accc0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a done deal yet, but both coaches should make it to Tampa Bay sooner rather than later. The Bucs are finalizing a deal to bring on Falcons OC Zac Robinson in the same role. As most coaches do, he will bring along some of his lieutenants. Zampese has been coaching in the NFL for over 20 years. Yates joined the coaching ranks almost immediately after his playing career ended in 2017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5e1-d56e-afff-e7e9accc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Ravens assistant head coach Willie Taggart for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5f1-dc7a-af9b-efffe6ec0000</link>
      <description>Taggart also holds the title of running backs coach. He joined the Ravens in 2023 after a lengthy career coaching college football. After a quiet first year on the job, Taggart got to work with Derrick Henry for his next two seasons in Baltimore. Henry exploded with the Ravens, running for 3,516 yards over the past two years. As expected, John Harbaugh plans on bringing as many of his former staffers to New York as possible. Both Taggart and Ravens OC Todd Monken are reportedly in consideration for the OC vacancy in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5f1-dc7a-af9b-efffe6ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles requested an interview with Bears offensive coordinator Declan Doyle for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5ff-d35e-a1bf-e5ff49020000</link>
      <description>While it’s a lateral move on the surface, Doyle doesn’t call plays in Chicago and would do so in Philly. That also means that the Bears can’t turn down the Eagles’ request to interview Doyle. Chicago finished the year ninth in points per game and made their deepest playoff run since 2010. Most importantly, Caleb Williams showed drastic improvement in his second season after Ben Johnson and Doyle took over the offense. The Eagles would hope to get a similar turnaround from Jalen Hurts, who is coming off a career-low in yards per attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e5ff-d35e-a1bf-e5ff49020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Texans quarterbacks coach Jerrod Johnson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e61f-d35e-a1bf-e7df55470000</link>
      <description>Johnson received several offensive coordinator interviews following C.J. Stroud’s breakout rookie season. That was all the way back at the end of the 2023 season. Stroud regressed in 2024 and the Texans fired OC Bobby Slowik. Johnson was a candidate to replace him, but the team ultimately chose an outside voice in Nick Caley. With Stroud playing better this year, there is again some interest in Johnson as an OC. Johnson would join a Miami team without any answers at quarterback. Tua Tagovailoa is expected to be released and the team doesn’t have a high enough pick in the draft to land a premier rookie quarterback. It wouldn’t be surprising to see Johnson stick in Houston for another year in search of better opportunities next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e61f-d35e-a1bf-e7df55470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons signed Browns offensive coordinator Tommy Rees for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e665-dc7a-af9b-efff97910000</link>
      <description>Rees interviewed for the Browns’ vacant head coaching job but did not receive a second meeting with the team. His days in Cleveland were numbered after the team chose to go in a different direction at head coach. The good news for Rees is that his former boss, Kevin Stefanski, just so happened to be looking for an offensive coordinator for his new job as Atlanta’s head coach. As expected, Stefanski is bringing several Browns staffers with him to the Falcons. It’s unclear who will call plays for Atlanta in 2026. Stefanski initially called plays for the Browns but eventually handed those duties off to Rees late in the 2025 season. Neither play-caller found much success, though Cleveland’s abhorrent quarterback room played a major part in that failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e665-dc7a-af9b-efff97910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills interviewed former Giants head coach Brian Daboll for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6ca-dc7a-af9b-efff779a0000</link>
      <description>Daboll previously interviewed for the Titans’ head coach opening, but that job has been taken by Robert Saleh. The Bills’ job is now the only head coaching gig for which Daboll is still in the running. He has, however, received plenty of interest as an offensive coordinator. The Athletic’s Dianna Russini recently reported that he could still land in Tennessee as their OC. The Eagles are also interested in Daboll as an OC, meaning he should get to at least call plays for a team in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6ca-dc7a-af9b-efff779a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers DC Jesse Minter canceled today’s interview for the Browns’ head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6de-d35e-a1bf-e7de1e490000</link>
      <description>In a span of three days, Minter and former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel have withdrawn from the Browns’ head-coaching sweepstakes. Both individuals had advanced to the second round of interviews. Shortly after Minter canceled today’s meeting, former Browns head coach and current Falcons head coach Kevin Stefanski rehired former Browns offensive coordinator Tommy Rees. Collectively, all three moves reflect poorly on the Browns’ organization in an “it’s not me, it’s you” type of way. NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports that Minter is believed to be in serious consideration for other head-coaching jobs. He interviewed with the Ravens for a second time yesterday, which reportedly “went very well.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6de-d35e-a1bf-e7de1e490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots head coach Mike Vrabel said he does not expect Denver’s altitude to limit DT Christian Barmore, who has a history of blood clots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2a9-d56e-afff-e6e952be0000</link>
      <description>The Broncos’ Empower Field at Mile High is located one mile above sea level, which can present problems for certain individuals. Barmore has previously been placed on the reserve non-football illness list and been limited at practice due to blood clots. The disruptive interior defender ranks second on the team with 56 quarterback pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e2a9-d56e-afff-e6e952be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys are working to hire Eagles DB coach and pass game coordinator Christian Parker for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6f8-d35e-a1bf-e7fa93930000</link>
      <description>The deal has not yet been finalized, but multiple national and local reporters are saying the Cowboys want to bring him aboard, so we expect it to be finalized soon enough. Parker, 34, has studied under Eagles DC Vic Fangio, in his current roles, for the past two seasons. He spent the 2022-2023 seasons as the Broncos’ defensive backs coach, notably working under Broncos DC Vance Joseph in his second season with the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e6f8-d35e-a1bf-e7fa93930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans fired DC Dennard Wilson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e70f-d35e-a1bf-e7cff9010000</link>
      <description>The Titans recently hired defensive-minded head coach Robert Saleh, who will implement his own defensive scheme. Wilson held the Titans’ defensive coordinator role for the past two seasons. He has coached in the NFL since 2012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-e70f-d35e-a1bf-e7cff9010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
