<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 17:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0e1-dd4c-afb9-e7e1b36b0000</link>
      <description>Barkley was listed as DNP on Monday but gets a limited designation on Tuesday. He is still expected to play Thursday against the Giants as his knee issue seems to be a minor injury. Another limited or full designation on Wednesday would give fantasy managers more confidence, but expect Barkley to suit up Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0e1-dd4c-afb9-e7e1b36b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints hosted WRs K.J. Osborn, Mecole Hardman, and Ronnie Bell for workouts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c10a-dd4c-afb9-e7cb96fb0000</link>
      <description>The Saints are looking to add receiver depth and hosted a trio of wideouts for tryouts Tuesday. Osborn was cut by the Commanders prior to the start of the season while the Packers let Hardman go last month. Bell was also released by the Lions last month. Between the three, the Saints signed Bell to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c10a-dd4c-afb9-e7cb96fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes the Bengals will “lean on” Joe Flacco until Joe Burrow (toe) returns to action.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3be-db72-a199-fbff69440000</link>
      <description>It’s a bold strategy. Let’s see it it works. The Bengals on Tuesday acquired Flacco and a 2026 sixth-round draft pick from the Browns in exchange for a 2026 fifth round draft pick. The Bengals are apparently pulling the plug on Jake Browning after three of the worst quarterback performances in recent memory. They’re replacing Browning — whose chance of landing a starting job in the NFL surely vanished over the past month — with Flacco, the NFL’s worst starting QB this season. Flacco in four games with the Browns ranked dead last in adjusted yards per attempt (3.6), second to last in touchdown rate (1.2 percent), and second to last in completion rate (58 percent). Rapoport said the hope is Flacco can keep the Bengals afloat until Burrow is ready to return to the field. It’s a long shot, at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3be-db72-a199-fbff69440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe believes Jaguars WR Travis Hunter will see more downfield opportunities in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3d4-db72-a199-fbdf7f100000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said Jaguars coaches and players felt the listless offense was “unlocked” during Monday night’s win over the Chiefs. Trevor Lawrence finally connected with Hunter, the second overall selection in the 2025 NFL Draft, on a deep ball into double coverage — one of the highlights of the game and Hunter’s first big play in the league. Hunter, coming into Week 5 against KC, had averaged 7.2 air yards per target. Against the Chiefs he averaged 15.5 air yards per target. More deep looks for Hunter would give him some kind of weekly ceiling in fantasy. For now, he’s a borderline flex in 12-team formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3d4-db72-a199-fbdf7f100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Lamar Jackson (hamstring) faces an “uphill battle” to play in Week 6 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3ed-def2-abdb-dfed84700000</link>
      <description>There’s almost no chance Jackson will suit up this week against LA with the Ravens’ bye week looming in Week 7. The plan could be for Jackson to get to full health — or something close to it — and try to run the table to sneak into the postseason after a catastrophic start to the season. The Ravens are a non-competitive team with Cooper Rush under center, as they showed in their humiliating Week 5 blowout loss to the Texans. Rush, a career journeyman check-down artist, threw for 179 scoreless yards along with three interceptions against Houston. He’ll have no chance against a stout Rams defense in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3ed-def2-abdb-dfed84700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) is out for Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3f3-d94a-a79d-cbff7f1c0000</link>
      <description>Slayton never had a real chance to suit up for the Giants on Thursday night after he was seen with a pronounced limp in the locker room following New York’s Week 5 loss against the Saints. ESPN’s Jordan Raanan said Lil’Jordan Humphrey will likely take Slayton’s spot in the Giants offense on Thursday. Slayton had seen 14 targets over the past three games as the team’s primary downfield threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3f3-d94a-a79d-cbff7f1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts head coach Shane Steichen said Alec Pierce (concussion) will practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c477-dd4c-afb9-e7f707d30000</link>
      <description>Pierce practiced late last week but was ruled out for the Colts’ Week 5 game against the Raiders. He’s recovering from a head injury he sustained two weeks ago. If he’s able to play this week against the Cardinals, Pierce will be a volatile WR3/4 option in 12-team leagues. Pierce has 179 yards on nine catches over three games this season as a full-time player in the Colts offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c477-dd4c-afb9-e7f707d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said he’s not ready to name Shedeur Sanders as the team’s No. 2 quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c496-dd4c-afb9-e7d7a7e80000</link>
      <description>With Joe Flacco shipped to the Bengals this week, the Browns were widely expected to bump Sanders to to the backup spot behind Dillon Gabriel, who got his first NFL start in Week 5 against the Vikings. Bailey Zappe could be called up from the practice squad to function as the Browns’ QB2 if Sanders doesn’t get the role. NFL Network reported Sunday that Sanders is expected to get snaps at some point in 2025, as the Browns enter evaluation mode in another lost season. For now, Stefanski seems reticent to name Sanders as Gabriel’s backup, perhaps due to the media attention it will surely create.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c496-dd4c-afb9-e7d7a7e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers opened the 21-day practice window for WR Jalen Coker (quad).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4be-d94a-a79d-cdbf1e800000</link>
      <description>Coker will now have three weeks before the team must activate him to the game day roster. He could play as soon as Week 6 against the Cowboys, a good matchup against one of the league’s worst coverage units. Coker, who had 32 catches for 478 yards and two touchdowns in 2024, would immediately function as Carolina’s WR2 when he’s activated. He should be rostered in deeper leagues as a viable flex option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4be-d94a-a79d-cdbf1e800000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
