<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e8-def2-abdb-dde956f40000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Jackson is reportedly facing “an uphill battle” to play in Week 6. A DNP on Wednesday confirms that report and all but rules Jackson out for Sunday’s game. Barring a surprise, Cooper Rush should make his second start as a Raven, though Tyler Huntley is also an option for the team. Rush imploded in his first start, throwing for 179 yards and three interceptions in a blowout loss to the Texans. We don’t have high hopes for the offense no matter who draws the start versus the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e8-def2-abdb-dde956f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f0-dd4c-afb9-e7f167bd0000</link>
      <description>Linebacker Roquan Smith and fellow corner Chidobe Awuzie both missed Wednesday’s practice with hamstring injuries. With Lamar Jackson unlikely to play this week, the Ravens may ultimately choose to sit the bulk of their injured players for a likely loss to the Rams on Sunday. They then get their bye week, allowing them to return close to full strength for Week 8 versus the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f0-dd4c-afb9-e7f167bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f6-db72-a199-feff541a0000</link>
      <description>It’s presumably a limited session for Sanders, but that’s still a step in the right direction as he works his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. Mitchell Evans and Tommy Tremble have combined for three touchdowns over the past two weeks. It’s possible all three see the field once Sanders is healthy. This is largely a situation to avoid for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f6-db72-a199-feff541a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said QB Kyler Murray (foot) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4fd-d94a-a79d-cdfd6edd0000</link>
      <description>When asked if Murray would resume practicing later this week, Gannon simply said, “we’ll see.” Fantasy managers should treat Murray as being truly questionable to play in Week 6 against the Colts. If active, it stands to reason that the dual-threat quarterback’s rushing ability would be compromised. He can only be viewed as a QB2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4fd-d94a-a79d-cdfd6edd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard (calf) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c503-d94a-a79d-cd0f6d6f0000</link>
      <description>The Charlotte Observer’s Mike Kaye didn’t spot him during the portion of practice open to the media. Hubbard could return for some light work later in the session, but this is typically what is reported before a player is listed as a DNP. With Rico Dowdle erupting for 206 rushing yards in Week 5, the Panthers don’t need to rush Hubbard back. Assuming he remains sidelined for Week 6, Dowdle will move to the top of the RB2 ranks for his date with Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c503-d94a-a79d-cd0f6d6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks placed OG Shane Lemieux on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c50c-def2-abdb-dd6d3ca80000</link>
      <description>Lemieux’s injury has not yet been disclosed. The Seahawks signed the former Saint on September 18th. He has logged zero offensive snaps since then. The team correspondingly signed S Maxen Hook to the practice squad. Hook previously signed with the Eagles as an undrafted free agent earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c50c-def2-abdb-dd6d3ca80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c507-db72-a199-ff4f1fa10000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation, but it’s still good to see Barkley get in a full practice and be cleared from the injury report entirely. His injury was described as “general soreness’ by NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport earlier this week. We don’t expect it to limit him in any capacity versus the Giants. Barkley is off to a slow start this year, but a date with the lowly G-Men should give him a chance to rack up touches and chunk plays. He remains an RB1 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c507-db72-a199-ff4f1fa10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (ankle) will not play in Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c513-def2-abdb-dd7369840000</link>
      <description>Dickerson suffered the ankle injury in Week 5 and was always expected to miss at least one game. He could be out another week or two as well. Brett Toth replaced Dickerson in the lineup last week and is presumably in line to do so again versus the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c513-def2-abdb-dd7369840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (heel) is questionable for Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c515-d94a-a79d-cd1d28170000</link>
      <description>Linebacker Nakobe Dean (knee) is also listed as questionable. Carter was added to the injury report on Wednesday as a limited participant before being listed as questionable. A surprise addition to the injury report this late in the week is typically a bad sign, and the fact that the Eagles have a short turnaround to Thursday’s game will only compound the issue. Philly will still be favored by at least a touchdown with or without Carter, but his absence would make life a little easier for Jaxson Dart in his third NFL start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c515-d94a-a79d-cd1d28170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed Kimani Vidal from their practice squad to the active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c51b-dd4c-afb9-e7db262b0000</link>
      <description>The team also signed Nyheim Miller-Hines to their practice squad. Both running backs were cut at the end of training camp. Vidal re-signed to the team’s pratice squad and is now being called up permanently with both Najee Harris and Omarion Hampton on injured reserve. Vidal will split work with Hassan Haskins this week. Haskins should handle more work on early downs, making him the priority off waivers this week. Vidal will be a high-risk RB4 for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c51b-dd4c-afb9-e7db262b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
