<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:04:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95f4-d968-a19b-ddf5a5320000</link>
      <description>Tate is projected to be one of the draft’s top wide receiver prospects, foregoing his final season of eligibility to declare early out of Ohio State. He accomplished a sophomore year of 52 receptions for 733 yards and four touchdowns, following it up with a 51/875/9 line his junior year. Tate crossed the 100-yard mark in four games in 2025 as the Buckeyes’ No. 2 wide receiver and will now enter the draft early to first-round buzz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-95f4-d968-a19b-ddf5a5320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Raiders requested to interview Broncos quarterbacks coach Davis Webb for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-963a-dc7a-af9b-dfbff1060000</link>
      <description>Webb is a former 2017 third-round pick who started one game in 2022 before the Broncos hired him as quarterbacks coach in 2023 under Sean Payton. He also held the role of passing game coordinator for the 2025 season. Webb’s role in developing Bo Nix through the first two years of his career explain the Raiders’ interest in him; Vegas has a quarterback likely on the way with the No. 1 overall pick. The Raiders await the opportunity to interview Webb for their head coaching job amidst the Broncos’ playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-963a-dc7a-af9b-dfbff1060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants will interview former Cowboys head coach Mike McCarthy for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9881-d968-a19b-d8f1f8580000</link>
      <description>McCarthy last coached the Cowboys in 2024 and has made the postseason in 12 of 18 seasons as an NFL head coach in Dallas and Green Bay. With a history of quarterback development and a QB-friendly offensive system, McCarthy would be a natural choice to develop Jaxson Dart as he enters his second NFL season. McCarthy, who has won 61 percent of his games as an NFL head coach along with 11 postseason contests, would likely be a short-term option for the Giants, one who could stabilize the situation around Dart and give him a chance to establish himself as a high-end NFL starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9881-d968-a19b-d8f1f8580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Baltimore Sun’s Brian Wacker reports former Commanders OC Kliff Kingsbury and Chargers DC Jesse Minter are among the candidates to be the Ravens’ next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-989a-d56e-afff-fefa9d1d0000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury, who mutually parted ways with the Commanders on Tuesday, will apparently have his choice of head coaching gigs, with the Titans and Giants lining up to interview him. Kingsbury would be an interesting fit with Lamar Jackson; he has plenty of experience coaching dual-threat QBs over his years in Arizona and Washington. Minter, meanwhile, would be the natural choice if the team is committed to getting back to its tough-nosed defensive roots. Wacker also mentioned Rams defensive coordinator Chris Shula, who would seem to be a long shot for the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-989a-d56e-afff-fefa9d1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Chiefs offensive coordinator Matt Nagy will interview with the Titans, Cardinals, and Raiders for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-98e3-d35e-a1bf-dde377d70000</link>
      <description>Nagy for some reason could have his choice of head coaching spots in the coming weeks. The Chiefs offense under his control became strikingly ordinary and uncreative. The former Bears head coach has deep connections around the league, however. Sometimes that’s all that matters in a head coaching search. Nagy would be tasked with a total rebuild of the Cardinals, Titans, or Raiders. Only the Titans have a potential franchise QB in 2025’s first overall draft pick Cam Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-98e3-d35e-a1bf-dde377d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Ravens are looking for a head coach to “invigorate” QB Lamar Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9913-d35e-a1bf-ddd309d20000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added that a new Baltimore head coach would ideally “reach” Jackson and “get the absolute most” out of the two-time NFL MVP. Jackson, who appeared checked out and low-effort at time in 2025, will remain the centerpiece of the Ravens offense in the aftermath of John Harbaugh’s firing after 18 years at the helm. There was reportedly a rift between Jackson and Harbaugh in the months leading up to Harbaugh’s dismissal. Jackson in 2025 saw a significant statistical drop off from his wildly efficient 2024 season. His passing success rate (46 percent) was the third lowest of his NFL career and he took a sack on 10.3 percent of his drop backs, the highest rate of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9913-d35e-a1bf-ddd309d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed DT Jordan Phillips (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9933-d35e-a1bf-ddf39b150000</link>
      <description>The Bills will enter the postseason without one of their main run stoppers. It’s a tough break for a Buffalo front seven that has been one of the softest against the run throughout the 2025 season, allowing the third highest yards per carry and the most rushing touchdowns. It sets up well for Travis Etienne in the Wild Card round against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9933-d35e-a1bf-ddf39b150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY TV’s Connor Hughes reports the Giants are “all in” on hiring former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9942-dc7a-af9b-dfff285e0000</link>
      <description>Though they’ll likely interview a few head coaching candidates, it looks like the Giants are ready to do what it takes to land Harbaugh after he was fired by the Ravens following 18 years at the helm. “Just about every team has interest in him (obviously), but the other that I heard is increasingly interested is the Falcons,” Hughes said. Harabugh would be tasked with making the right hires to develop Jaxson Dart, particularly as a passer. Even with Dart, Harbaugh would be entering a rebuild of a Giants team with major roster holes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9942-dc7a-af9b-dfff285e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Falcons head coach Raheem Morris will interview with the Titans, Cardinals, and Giants for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</link>
      <description>Morris, fired by the Falcons after going 20-25 over three seasons, will join a bevy of former head coaches and coordinators in interviewing with the Cardinals, Titans, and Giants, who are reportedly “all in” on hiring former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh. Morris, 49, struggled with in-game decision making and was among the league’s most conservative fourth down decision makers during his three years in Atlanta. His defensive background would be appealing to any of these three teams after their defenses collapsed in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Bengals offensive coordinator Dan Pitcher for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</link>
      <description>Pitcher, 39, has garnered some head coaching interest in previous hiring cycles but has never been considered a leading candidate for any job. He would be a long shot to land the Browns head coaching job, though the team could fall back on Pitcher if other, more experienced candidates turn down one of the most thankless jobs in football. Pitcher is known for his work with quarterbacks — a key qualification for anyone who gets the head coaching gig in Cleveland. Pitcher once worked for the Colts scouting department alongside Browns general manager Andrew Berry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
