<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:09:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed RB Nyheim Hines to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c061-db72-a199-fa6bffb70000</link>
      <description>Hines has a chance to play immediately with the Chargers running back position in shambles following the Omarion Hampton injury. He’d certainly make some sense as a passing-downs caddy for Hassan Haskins. We’ll likely need some coach quotes to verify how likely it is that Hines will be active. Haskins is probably the favorite for early-down duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c061-db72-a199-fa6bffb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said he reduced Pat Freiermuth’s role in Week 4 because he wanted bigger bodies to block Minnesota’s 4-3 front.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c06e-dd4c-afb9-e7efd9750000</link>
      <description>“You can’t play 4-3 teams with 250-pound tight ends,” Tomlin said. Not that fantasy managers needed another variable to keep track of after Freiermuth had just 65 yards over his first four games — Freiermuth should be long gone on most rosters — but if the Steelers are going to limit his snaps in some situations, he stands to be hard to start in even deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c06e-dd4c-afb9-e7efd9750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived RB Velus Jones Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c074-dd4c-afb9-e7f510ab0000</link>
      <description>Jones received two offensive snaps in five games with the Saints, operating as a returner. He’ll likely look to continue his career on a practice squad elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c074-dd4c-afb9-e7f510ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed CB Mike Hilton on practice squad injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0be-def2-abdb-ddff6f610000</link>
      <description>Hilton signed with the Colts after Week 3 and started two games for the team. The 31-year-old tallied five combined tackles and a forced fumble as he helped cover for slot cornerback Kenny Moore’s absence due to a calf injury. Hilton was technically on the practice squad, so he goes on the injured reserve there. The Colts signed Troy Pride to the practice squad in a corresponding move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0be-def2-abdb-ddff6f610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cardinals fined head coach Jonathan Gannon $100,000 for a sideline altercation with RB Emari Demercado.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0de-d94a-a79d-c9df6fe30000</link>
      <description>The altercation happened during the Cardinals’ Week 5 loss to the Titans after Demercado dropped the ball before crossing the goal line on a would-be 72-yard score. The NFL will not discipline Gannon further. The Cardinals are 2-3 and Gannon is 14-25 over the course of his coaching tenure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0de-d94a-a79d-c9df6fe30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0e1-dd4c-afb9-e7e1b36b0000</link>
      <description>Barkley was listed as DNP on Monday but gets a limited designation on Tuesday. He is still expected to play Thursday against the Giants as his knee issue seems to be a minor injury. Another limited or full designation on Wednesday would give fantasy managers more confidence, but expect Barkley to suit up Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c0e1-dd4c-afb9-e7e1b36b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints hosted WRs K.J. Osborn, Mecole Hardman, and Ronnie Bell for workouts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c10a-dd4c-afb9-e7cb96fb0000</link>
      <description>The Saints are looking to add receiver depth and hosted a trio of wideouts for tryouts Tuesday. Osborn was cut by the Commanders prior to the start of the season while the Packers let Hardman go last month. Bell was also released by the Lions last month. Between the three, the Saints signed Bell to their practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c10a-dd4c-afb9-e7cb96fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes the Bengals will “lean on” Joe Flacco until Joe Burrow (toe) returns to action.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3be-db72-a199-fbff69440000</link>
      <description>It’s a bold strategy. Let’s see it it works. The Bengals on Tuesday acquired Flacco and a 2026 sixth-round draft pick from the Browns in exchange for a 2026 fifth round draft pick. The Bengals are apparently pulling the plug on Jake Browning after three of the worst quarterback performances in recent memory. They’re replacing Browning — whose chance of landing a starting job in the NFL surely vanished over the past month — with Flacco, the NFL’s worst starting QB this season. Flacco in four games with the Browns ranked dead last in adjusted yards per attempt (3.6), second to last in touchdown rate (1.2 percent), and second to last in completion rate (58 percent). Rapoport said the hope is Flacco can keep the Bengals afloat until Burrow is ready to return to the field. It’s a long shot, at best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3be-db72-a199-fbff69440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Cameron Wolfe believes Jaguars WR Travis Hunter will see more downfield opportunities in the coming weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3d4-db72-a199-fbdf7f100000</link>
      <description>Wolfe said Jaguars coaches and players felt the listless offense was “unlocked” during Monday night’s win over the Chiefs. Trevor Lawrence finally connected with Hunter, the second overall selection in the 2025 NFL Draft, on a deep ball into double coverage — one of the highlights of the game and Hunter’s first big play in the league. Hunter, coming into Week 5 against KC, had averaged 7.2 air yards per target. Against the Chiefs he averaged 15.5 air yards per target. More deep looks for Hunter would give him some kind of weekly ceiling in fantasy. For now, he’s a borderline flex in 12-team formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c3d4-db72-a199-fbdf7f100000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
