<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said DL Bryce Huff (hamstring) will miss two weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03ce-d651-a9df-6bdf61e90000</link>
      <description>Huff suffered a hamstring strain in the team’s Week 7 win over the Falcons and will miss the next two games. The 49ers continue to struggle through injuries up and down their roster, yet still remain tied with the Rams atop the NFC West.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-03ce-d651-a9df-6bdf61e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out WR Mike Evans (concussion, shoulder) in the second quarter of Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0425-d651-a9df-6d35362f0000</link>
      <description>Evans appeared to come down with a long reception late in the second quarter but went limp after hitting the ground, adding insult to injury as the pass fell incomplete and the receiver on the turf. Evans was returning from three missed contests with a hamstring injury. He also reportedly suffered a shoulder injury that left him in clear agony. Evans could be looking at another extended absence. He failed to catch any of his four targets prior to departing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0425-d651-a9df-6d35362f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LB Derick Hall, LB Jared Ivey, TE Nick Kallerup, DB Devon Witherspoon, OT Mason Richman, S Julian Love, and QB Jalen Milroe inactive for Week 7 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0428-df81-ab9b-7eef21cd0000</link>
      <description>Seattle will be slightly shorthanded in the secondary after both Witherspoon and Love were unable to go in Week 7. That could become an issue considering the defensive struggle we expect in the final game of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0428-df81-ab9b-7eef21cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared WR Christian Kirk, RB Dameon Pierce, DE Darrell Taylor, QB Graham Mertz, OG Jarrett Kingston, and OT Trent Brown inactive for Week 7 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-042e-d99b-a1df-3e2e5ef30000</link>
      <description>Kirk made it all of two-and-a-half games before suffering another injury after starting the season as an inactive. His absence should allow for more opportunities for rookie Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel. Dameon Pierce remains inactive as the team has shifted their focus towards rookie Woody Marks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-042e-d99b-a1df-3e2e5ef30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield completed 28-of-50 passes for 228 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Buccaneers’ 24-9, Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0432-d99b-a1df-3e3e49130000</link>
      <description>As has been the case for most of the Buccaneers’ games this season, Mayfield was forced into late-game heroics once more, although this time he could not replicate the magic he managed through the first six weeks of the season. He lost Mike Evans in the second quarter to a concussion and shoulder injury while rookie Emeka Egbuka played through a hamstring injury, leaving Mayfield heavily reliant on Cade Otton, Tex Johnson, and Sterling Shepard. The Buccaneers were unable to crack a Lions defense playing with zero members of their starting secondary, but defensive coordinator Kelvin Sheppard seemed to have all the right answers, limiting the Bucs to just 251 yards of total offense after holding them to 52 yards in the first half. Baker and the Buccaneers fall to 5-2 ahead of a divisional meeting with the Saints in Week 8, a contest they could once again be forced to play without their top pass-catcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0432-d99b-a1df-3e3e49130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White rushed 10 times for 38 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 8 loss to the Lions, adding six yards on four receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0499-d651-a9df-6d9dca6a0000</link>
      <description>Detroit defensive coordinator Kelvin Sheppard had all the answers in this one, holding the Buccaneers to only 52 yards of total offense in the first half and 252 total. The macro matchup on the ground for White was a difficult one against a Lions team near the top of the league in opposing pass rate over expectation forced, which combined with negative game script to limit White to a modest 10 carries on the evening. White’s days of consistent fantasy production could be nearing an end with lead back Bucky Irving inching closer to a return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0499-d651-a9df-6d9dca6a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 7-of-9 targets for 65 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-df81-ab9b-7edfbc7c0000</link>
      <description>Otton and the rest of the Tampa Bay offense struggled in the first half, managing only 52 yards of total offense before the break. They would then be thrust into a negative game environment following a 78-yard rushing score from Jahmyr Gibbs, which led to Otton seeing a boost in targets in the second half against the prevent defense of the Lions. Alpha wide receiver Mike Evans also departed in the second quarter, forcing the secondary options through the air to step up as Mayfield was tasked with 50 pass attempts. Otton won’t return meaningful volume in most weeks and he remains nothing more than a TE2 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-df81-ab9b-7edfbc7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans is expected to miss “most of the year” after suffering a broken collarbone in Week 7 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-d99b-a1df-3e9c7b750000</link>
      <description>Evans entered the 2025 season hoping to record his 12th straight 1,000-yard season. It appears as though achieving that goal is no longer possible. Evans became the first NFL wide receiver to total 1,000 receiving yards in each of his first seven seasons, back in 2020. He continued extending that record every year through 2024. Despite another 1,000-yard season potentially being out of reach, phrasing regarding the injury suggests Evans has a chance to return later this season. The Buccaneers (5-2) should still be in the playoff hunt when early-to-mid December rolls around, which NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports is in line with the “regular” recovery timeline for a broken collarbone. Evans will likely be placed on injured reserve in the short term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049c-d99b-a1df-3e9c7b750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-12 targets for 58 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049f-df81-ab9b-7edf822d0000</link>
      <description>Egbuka saw his snap rate monitored in the first half but a second quarter injury to Mike Evans forced him into increased snaps and routes after the break. Quarterback Baker Mayfield continually missed Egbuka high, part of the reason he managed only four receptions on a team-leading 12 targets. Even so, fantasy managers can take solace in the fact he once again led the team in targets, this time while playing through a hamstring strain suffered in Week 6. Egbuka could once again function as the otp option through the air when the Buccaneers travel to New Orleans to face the Saints in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-049f-df81-ab9b-7edf822d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tez Johnson caught 4-of-9 targets for 58 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 7 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04a1-df81-ab9b-7ee7f8660000</link>
      <description>Johnson saw an increased snap rate throughout due to the team managing the workload of fellow rookie Emeka Egbuka in the first half and veteran receiver Mike Evans’ departure in the second quarter. He appears to be worthy of a waiver addition considering the state of the wide receiver corps, with Evans likely to miss the team’s Week 8 meeting with the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-04a1-df81-ab9b-7ee7f8660000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
