<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Hunter Renfrow is listed as a starting wide receiver on the team’s unofficial Week 1 depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ca1-dbe3-a9bb-3cf390c80000</link>
      <description>Renfrow was cut and re-signed to the Panthers’ active roster after Jalen Coker was placed on injured reserve. The 29-year-old is the only player listed in a slot wide receiver role on the team’s depth chart. Coker was expected to play the slot frequently this season, but now that he is sidelined, Renfrow will be in the slot role. He will still trail Tetairoa McMillan and Xavier Legette in the pecking order but could earn his way to fantasy viability early on in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0ca1-dbe3-a9bb-3cf390c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars listed Travis Hunter as a starting wide receiver and backup cornerback on their Week 1 depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0d66-dbe3-a9bb-3d77d89e0000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars had initially listed Hunter as a starting wide receiver and backup cornerback at the beginning of preseason and continue to do so ahead of Week 1. Though not much stock should go into these early depth charts, camp usage indicates Hunter will be primarily an offensive player, with secondary usage on defense. Head coach Liam Coen said the Jaguars are evaluating Hunter’s Week 1 usage due to missed time for an upper body injury. The rookie No. 2 overall pick is still slated for versatility, but fantasy managers can expect to get his offensive production at the WR3 level to start with.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0d66-dbe3-a9bb-3d77d89e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed FB Hunter Luepke to a two-year extension worth up to $7.5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0f6b-d332-a1fd-9f7f39870000</link>
      <description>Luepke’s new deal includes $5 million guaranteed. He had been set to make $1 million in 2025. Pro Football Focus graded Luepka as last year’s eighth best pass-protecting back. He was graded 32nd out of 36 qualifying backs in run blocking grade. Last season he had 38 yards on 12 rushing attempts. He’ll be on the field often this season blocking for Javonte Williams and the rest of the Dallas running backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0f6b-d332-a1fd-9f7f39870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee) did not travel with the team to Brazil.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0faa-d332-a1fd-9fbe22870000</link>
      <description>Royals will miss at least the first game of the season as he works through knee tendinitis that flared up in late August. The rookie was expected to be a rotational wideout and a special teams player to start the season. With Royals sidelined, look for JuJu Smith-Schuster and Hollywood Brown to see significant snaps in Week 1 against the Chargers. Both receivers will be borderline options in deeper fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0faa-d332-a1fd-9fbe22870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Jets LG Alijah Vera-Tucker “suffered a potentially serious [arm] injury and could miss significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0fd0-d332-a1fd-9ff6b2f80000</link>
      <description>Vera-Tucker’s 2025 season could be over before it begins after sustaining an arm injury days before the Jets’ Week 1 opener against the Steelers. Vera-Tucker missed the entire 2022 and 2023 seasons due to injury before returning and playing 15 games for the Jets in 2024. The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt said Vera-Tucker “was a standout in camp, dominant in the run game and appeared to be finally fully healthy” headed into the regular season. His injury is a massive blow to the Jets offense, expected to be predicated on the run. Pro Football Focus graded Vera-Tucker as the 33rd best run blocking offensive lineman in the NFL last season out of 148 qualifying players. This news is certainly a blow to Breece Hall and Braelon Allen, and perhaps the whole New York offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0fd0-d332-a1fd-9ff6b2f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Vic Tarfur suggested the “hype” surrounding WR Ricky Pearsall this offseason was “premature.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1001-d332-a1fd-9637b0d60000</link>
      <description>This comes as unpleasant news to the Pearsall truthers who months ago crowned the second-year wideout as the Niners’ unquestioned No. 1 receiver. Jauan Jennings’ return to action, 49ers beat writers have said, should take the shine off Pearsall. “He was out there at practice every day and did look good, but — sorry, fantasy football people — it sure seemed like the hype and jump to No. 1 receiver status was premature,” Tarfur said. “Pearsall is very quick and will still catch a fair number of passes, but physical corners will have some success against him, and Jennings’ return allows the 49ers to not put too much on Pearsall’s plate after all.” Pearsall should still see a good number of looks in Week 1 against the Seahawks, and certainly has top-30 in his range of fantasy outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1001-d332-a1fd-9637b0d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said Jaylen Warren will be the team’s “featured runner” to start the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1012-de13-afdd-56db07ab0000</link>
      <description>Tomlin’s comments come after Warren on Tuesday signed a two-year contract extension with the Steelers. “His progress has been very evident and he’s to be congratulated,” Tomlin said of Warren, who in 2024 had 821 total yards and one touchdown, sharing the backfield with Najee Harris. “Certainly he’ll be our featured runner. Certainly you’ll see [Kaleb Johnson/Kenneth Gainwell], but at what time and at what degree [will depend week-to-week].” Warren is listed as the team’s RB1 on their Week 1 depth chart. Gainwell is listed as RB2, and Johnson as RB3. Warren could see a solid workload both as a rusher and a pass catcher in Week 1 against the Jets. He’s flex worthy in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1012-de13-afdd-56db07ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Jerome Ford is listed as the starter on the team’s Week 1 depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1028-dbe3-a9bb-307b81400000</link>
      <description>The veteran will get the nod as the top back on the Cleveland depth chart for Week 1 against the Bengals. That might mean Ford will simply play the team’s first offensive drive, or it could mean he’ll operate as a workhorse over rookie RB Dylan Sampson. Ford over the past two seasons has 81 catchers for 544 yards and could suffice as a PPR flex option with check-down artist Joe Flacco under center for the Browns. The team’s backfield will be throwing into further chaos if Quinshon Judkins signs with the team in the coming days or weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1028-dbe3-a9bb-307b81400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (ankle) was limited during Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1062-de13-afdd-56eb29120000</link>
      <description>Shakir appears on schedule to play Week 1 against the Ravens after sitting out for nearly a month with a severe high ankle sprain. He resumed practicing last week, and team is sure to be careful with their de facto No. 1 wideout ahead of the season opener. Shakir proved to be a reliable middle-of-the-field target commander in 2024, catching 76 passes for 821 yards and four touchdowns as Josh Allen’s main slot receiver. He’ll be a top-36 PPR option in Week 1 against Baltimore barring any setbacks to his ankle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1062-de13-afdd-56eb29120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt Lafleur said he’s “hopeful” Micah Parsons (back) can play in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-106f-dbe3-a9bb-307f5fbc0000</link>
      <description>Parsons, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, is “uncertain” to suit up for the Packers after being traded from the Cowboys last week. “We’ll see,” LaFleur said when asked if Parsons will be ready for opening day. “He’s doing everything in his power. Got to get through a couple practices to see how he responds, but certainly hopeful.” The injury doesn’t sound like one that will keep the star EDGE rusher sidelined for very long, even if he does miss Week 1. Parsons is set to join a Packers front seven that pressured the quarterback at the league’s 13th highest rate in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-106f-dbe3-a9bb-307f5fbc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
