<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31c5-d321-a5bf-b3d77ba90000</link>
      <description>Hip left the Saints’ Week 8 loss to the Bucs late because of the hip issue. He hit the ground hard on a tackle in the fourth quarter and eventually walked off the field after being checked out by trainers. A limited practice this early in the week bodes well for his odds of suiting up on Sunday. He will be a boom/bust WR4 in Tyler Shough’s first start as a pro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31c5-d321-a5bf-b3d77ba90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31c8-de12-a19e-37e8bb730000</link>
      <description>Olave missed practice last Wednesday because of the ankle issue. He returned on Thursday and was good to go for Sunday’s game. A full practice today suggests he is getting healthier. The same is true of Juwan Johnson, who was listed with a neck injury but practiced in full. Olave will stay in the WR2 ranks for Week 9 while Johnson is a volume-based TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31c8-de12-a19e-37e8bb730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31cd-d4ed-a9de-77cf9c1c0000</link>
      <description>London was a late addition to the injury report last week. The team listed him as a limited participant on Friday but didn’t assign him a game-day status. On Saturday, the team downgraded him to questionable, foreshadowing his eventual absence. Head coach Raheem Morris called him “day to day” earlier this week. London can once again be considered questionable, though we will get more info on his status as the week progresses. Kyle Pitts would be in line for de facto WR1 duties if London is unable to suit up once again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31cd-d4ed-a9de-77cf9c1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d1-d48c-ad9f-fddd075a0000</link>
      <description>Pitts racked up a team-high nine catches with Drake London out last week. His limited status today is likely maintenance after a heavy workload on Sunday. Barring a setback, we assume he will be good to go versus the Patriots this week. If London remains out, Pitts will sit comfortably in the TE1 ranks. London’s returns, however, would put him on the TE1/2 border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d1-d48c-ad9f-fddd075a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (hamstring) was limited in practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d3-d4ed-a9de-77dfcb470000</link>
      <description>Mooney has been playing through the hamstring issue for a few weeks. He was modestly successful in Week 7 with three grabs for 68 yards. Mooney couldn’t replicate that production with Kirk Cousins under center, catching just one pass for 11 yards. His fantasy outlook will get a bump with Michael Penix expected to return this week, but Drake London could also be back on the field, slashing Mooney’s target ceiling. Fantasy managers should treat Mooney as a high-risk WR4 versus the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d3-d4ed-a9de-77dfcb470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 9 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d9-d4ed-a9de-77dfd9c80000</link>
      <description>Brashard Smith was listed with a toe issue. He also practiced in full. The same can’t be said of Isiah Pacheco, who suffered an MCL sprain in Week 8 and is considered week-to-week. He did not practice today and will likely miss Week 9’s game against the Bills. With extra carries to go around, Hunt, who was already handling the goal line work, will move into the RB3 ranks. Smith should also see a few extra carries and his receiving role will be amplified in a potential shootout. Smith is a high-upside RB4 for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31d9-d4ed-a9de-77dfd9c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Palmer (ankle/knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31de-d321-a5bf-b3df8c700000</link>
      <description>It looks like Palmer will miss another game because of the injury he suffered versus the Falcons in Week 6. Elijah Moore will operate as the team’s WR3 versus the Chiefs. Moore only ran half of the routes last week and caught just one pass. He is not on the fantasy radar for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31de-d321-a5bf-b3df8c700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31e1-d4ed-a9de-77efa8380000</link>
      <description>According to PennLive.com’s Nick Farabaugh, Freiermuth is dealing with a bruised quad. It shouldn’t result in an extended absence, but it is possible that Freiermuth misses Week 9. That would likely allow Jonnu Smith to play a full-time role. Smith hasn’t done much this year while playing a limited number of snaps. He would become an interesting streaming option if Freiermuth is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31e1-d4ed-a9de-77efa8380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas Jr. (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f5-d4ed-a9de-77ffa8a50000</link>
      <description>Thomas Jr. went down to a light push from a Rams corner late in the team’s Week 7 loss to LA. The shove almost certainly aggravated a preexisting issue. The good news is that players tend to suit up after opening the week with a limited practice, though we suspect BTJ is nowhere near fully healthy. The shoulder issue could cause the Jags to lean on Travis Hunter more coming out of the bye. BTJ will get another week in the WR1 ranks, but his usage will be worth monitoring versus the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f5-d4ed-a9de-77ffa8a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f8-d321-a5bf-b3ffb4c50000</link>
      <description>Tim Patrick, the Jags’ No. 5 receiver, was also limited in practice. With Travis Hunter’s role expected to grow this week, Brown and Parker Washington will be fighting for the WR3 role in Jacksonville. Brown has run more routes this year but Washington has the edge in targets and most receiving stats. Washington will be a low-ceiling WR5 for the team’s Week 9 date with the Raiders. Brown is barely on the fantasy radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-31f8-d321-a5bf-b3ffb4c50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
