<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3726-d1e7-a1fa-7feed3a30000</link>
      <description>Thomas was surprisingly joined in the limited column by rookie WR/CB Travis Hunter today, who evidently suffered a knee injury in practice. The news leaves WR Dyami Brown as the team’s lone starting wide receiver to practice in full, though Brown is nursing a shoulder injury of his own. If active, Thomas can once again be treated as a theoretical WR1 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3726-d1e7-a1fa-7feed3a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-370e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee75a60000</link>
      <description>Brown was the only starting Jaguars wide receiver to practice fully today. No. 1 WR Brian Thomas Jr. (shoulder) remains limited and No. 2 WR/CB Travis Hunter (knee) was added to the injury report. While Brown is hardly a top-tier talent, he could earn enough targets to warrant FLEX consideration against the Raiders this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-370e-d1e7-a1fa-7fee75a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3734-d713-ad9e-7f74b3ed0000</link>
      <description>Demercado evidently suffered a rough ankle injury, given his continued limitations following the Cardinals’ Week 8 bye. The Cardinals face the Cowboys’ fantasy-friendly defense this week. If Demercado can play, he could retake the passing game role from RB Michael Carter, though he would only be a PPR scam, type of player in the FLEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3734-d713-ad9e-7f74b3ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Zay Jones (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3737-d45b-affe-77b7f1b60000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals face the Cowboys in Week 9’s Monday Night Football game, so Jones should have plenty of time to get his knee game-ready. The volatile downfield wide receiver is a boom-bust FLEX option, given the matchup. His odds of catching another deep pass could increase if QB Kyler Murray (foot) misses another game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3737-d45b-affe-77b7f1b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-373a-d713-ad9e-7f7e8ba50000</link>
      <description>Purdy remains limited while Mac Jones (knee) continues to practice in full. The 49ers have made clear that they will not let Purdy take the field on game day if his toe injury is still an issue. It appears as though Jones will make yet another start this week, this time against the Giants. Jones is a high-end QB2 for the occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-373a-d713-ad9e-7f7e8ba50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (oblique) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3739-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbe52b0000</link>
      <description>Kittle caught 4-of-5 targets for 43 yards and a touchdown last week, evidently picking up an oblique injury along the way. His continued practice participation puts him firmly on track to face the Giants in Week 9. Kittle can be safely lodged in fantasy lineups for the occasion, once again sitting in the elite TE1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3739-d1e7-a1fa-7ffbe52b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the Raiders have not yet found a trade partner for WR Jakobi Meyers, but said he “wouldn’t give up hope on this one just yet.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3741-d713-ad9e-7f55981b0000</link>
      <description>Garafolo’s phrasing suggests the Raiders are indeed shopping Meyers, which should be music to Meyers’ ears. The veteran wide receiver has reportedly requested a trade “multiple times.” The Raiders brought in veteran WR Tyler Lockett as a depth option in case another NFL does come calling for Meyers prior to the trade deadline. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3741-d713-ad9e-7f55981b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that the Giants “have no interest” in trading LB Kayvon Thibodeaux.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3743-d673-a39e-b7d31f090000</link>
      <description>It appears as though the 24-year-old pass rusher will remain a Giant. The team picked up Thibodeaux’s fifth-year option in the offseason, keeping him under contract through 2026. Thibodeaux is third on the team in quarterback pressures (25) and second in NFL sacks (2.5). Keeping him in-house allows the Giants to preserve their defensive strength.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3743-d673-a39e-b7d31f090000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
