<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Mevis converted his lone field goal attempt and al six of his extra point attempts in the Rams’ Week 14 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</link>
      <description>Mevis has proven a fine weekly fantasy play thanks to the high-powered Rams offense and the positive game script it creates. He’s made all three of his field goals this season and has yet to miss an extra point. He should be in fantasy lineups next week against the Lions in what should be a high-scoring affair. The Lions have allowed 1.7 field goal tries per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d005-a9bf-fe3f39780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Loop converted all three of his field goal and one of his two extra point attempts in the Ravens’ Week 14 loss against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</link>
      <description>Loop has been excellent all season, making 25 of his 27 field goal tries. He hasn’t missed a field goal since Week 5 against the Texans. Loop will be a top-10 fantasy option in Week 15 against the Bengals. The Ravens are averaging 2.1 field goal tries per game, the 11th highest mark in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe32-d77b-adfa-feb35cf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports DK Metcalf (stomach) will rejoin the Steelers on Monday after staying the night in a Baltimore hospital on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, Metcalf experienced stomach pain on the team flight and stayed the night in the hospital “out of an abundance of caution.” Given the brief stay and the fact he’s rejoining the team on Monday, we’ll assume this is a minor issue until we hear otherwise. With the Steelers playing on Monday Night Football in Week 15, Metcalf will have some extra time to rest up before his next game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe2f-d8cf-affb-fe2fef540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed TE Brevin Jordan to a one-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe40-d77b-adfa-fec3bb0f0000</link>
      <description>Jordan was set to be a free agent next offseason, but will now remain under contract through the 2026 season. The fifth-year tight end missed all of this season after suffering a torn patellar tendon in training camp, and has appeared in just two games since 2024 after a torn ACL also ended his season last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe40-d77b-adfa-fec3bb0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chad Ryland converted one of two field goal attempts in the Cardinals’ Week 14 loss against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe5d-d77b-adfa-fedf0dec0000</link>
      <description>Ryland has now missed one field goal in four straight games. On the season he has missed six of his 25 field goal tries while making all 29 of his extra points. Attached to an Arizona offense that rarely has the benefit of neutral and positive game script — allowing for field goal attempts throughout the game — Ryland is not a reliable fantasy play. He should not be rostered in Week 15 against Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe5d-d77b-adfa-fedf0dec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said the “guy that’s gonna give us the best chance to win” will have the most first-team reps ahead of Week 15’s game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe90-d77b-adfa-fe93c2f80000</link>
      <description>Justin Fields (knee) was ruled out last Friday ahead of Week 14’s game against the Dolphins, and Tyrod Taylor exited the game with a groin injury and did not return to the field. Glenn said he still has to talk to the team doctors to see where things stand as far as the health of his players is concerned, but we could be looking at rookie UDFA Brady Cook making his first career start if both Taylor and Fields are unable to go in Week 15. Cook threw for 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions while completing 46.7 percent of his passes against the Dolphins. What little upside Jets positions players still have will be capped if Cook is under center next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fe90-d77b-adfa-fe93c2f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he did not have an update on Garrett Wilson (knee) possibly returning from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feb0-da9b-a9bf-febd17590000</link>
      <description>Wilson is eligible to be activated off injured reserve this week, but Glenn declined to comment on whether or not that would happen. The Jets’ head coach said any decision to activate Wilson would be a medical decision that’s made by Wilson and the team doctors. The Jets are 3-10 and in the process of wrapping up another lost season. Given the nature of his knee injury and the fact that it was a re-aggravation that landed him on injured reserve, it would seem there’s little reason for the Jets to risk the health of their top receiver at this point in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feb0-da9b-a9bf-febd17590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer said CeeDee Lamb is “progressing nicely” through the league’s concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fedc-da9b-a9bf-fedd68b50000</link>
      <description>It’s encouraging news for Lamb, who exited the Cowboys’ Thursday night game against the Lions in the first half with a concussion. With some extra time to recover, Lamb could have a chance at suiting up for Week 15’s game against the Vikings, but the only way he’ll get on the field is if he clears protocol. His status will be one to watch throughout the week, but if he can’t go against the Vikings, both George Pickens and Ryan Flournoy would see slight boosts to their fantasy stocks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fedc-da9b-a9bf-fedd68b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFootballTalk’s Mike Florio reports the Colts “don’t know when or if Anthony Richardson (eye) will be cleared at any point” to return this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fee8-da9b-a9bf-feedff900000</link>
      <description>The Colts are waiting to receive official word on Daniel Jones’ Achilles injury, but it’s a widely held belief that Jones will miss the remainder of the season with a torn Achilles. Richardson suffered an orbital fracture ahead of Week 6’s game against the Cardinals and has been on injured reserve ever since, leaving Riley Leonard as the primary backup to Jones. Leonard is currently positioned to be the Colts’ starting quarterback for the remainder of the season, but Richardson could step into the role if he is cleared to return. The former No. 4 overall pick has shown flashes as a starter and is an imposing presence on the ground when he takes off to run. That said, it doesn’t sound like anyone is expecting a return any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fee8-da9b-a9bf-feedff900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers waived DT Naquan Jones.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feff-da9b-a9bf-feff89590000</link>
      <description>Jones appeared in eight games for the Chargers this season, tallying 10 tackles and one TFL while playing in a backup role. The decision to waive Jones likely has to do with rookie RB Omarion Hampton being activated ahead of Monday night’s game against the Eagles. If he clears waivers, Jones will be free to sign with any team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-feff-da9b-a9bf-feff89590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
