<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:06:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua caught 10-of-12 targets for 85 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 5 overtime loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a846-deb6-a7fd-fbdfb9990000</link>
      <description>The PPR superstar and all-around dynamo has now caught at least 10 passes in 4-of-5 2025 performances. Unbelievable. Nacua is sitting on 52 catches for 588 yards receiving. This evening’s score came on a strange goal line dive play where Matthew Stafford feathered the ball to Nacua on the ground. Nacua has simply been unstoppable while Davante Adams does an admittedly admirable job of occupying defensive attention. Nacua will remain the WR1 overall for Week 6 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a846-deb6-a7fd-fbdfb9990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught 10-of-11 targets for 142 yards in the 49ers’ Week 5 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a84a-d6e9-af9d-aada777b0000</link>
      <description>30-year-old Patriots castoff Bourne entered this evening with exactly one career 100-yard performance, hitting 100 on the dot in Dec. 2022 for the Pats. He also had only one prior 10-catch outing. His missed connection was a third down drop, but it was an otherwise flawless performance over the middle of the field as Bourne filled in for George Kittle, Ricky Pearsall and Jauan Jennings. The Niners now have 10 days to get (much) healthier for Week 6 against the Bucs, but Bourne could end up maintaining some WR4 fill-in appeal for that one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a84a-d6e9-af9d-aada777b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davante Adams caught 5-of-11 targets for 88 yards in the Rams’ Week 5 overtime loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a84f-d6e9-af9d-aadfbbdd0000</link>
      <description>The catches, yards and targets were all Adams’ second most in five games as a Ram. Solid, though that speaks to what has been a lower floor than fantasy managers have become accustomed to from Adams. For what it’s worth, Adams still seems to be occupying a ton of defensive attention. That doesn’t change the fact that it’s Puka Nacua posting absolutely nuclear box scores. Still doing enough to keep himself in the WR2 ranks, Adams has a plus Week 6 matchup in the Ravens’ injury-ruined defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a84f-d6e9-af9d-aadfbbdd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutu Atwell caught 2-of-4 targets for 72 yards in the Rams’ Week 5 overtime loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a852-d6e9-af9d-aad264800000</link>
      <description>Atwell has now cleared 70 yards in back-to-back starts after totaling four in Weeks 1-3. His biggest play was a 38-yard grab in the bonus frame on an absurd deep-crossing shot from Matthew Stafford. Atwell is a valuable real-life role player, but his path to WR4 relevance is blocked by Puka Nacua and Davante Adams’ target dominance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a852-d6e9-af9d-aad264800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 3-of-7 targets for 39 yards in the 49ers’ Week 5 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a854-d6e9-af9d-aad4cf590000</link>
      <description>Active for just the second time this season after serving a three-game suspension to begin the year, D-Rob was the fill-in No. 2 wideout behind fill-in No. 1 Kendrick Bourne. With Ricky Pearsall and Jauan Jennings both sidelined, it was Bourne who did the stat-sheet stuffing, turning his 11 targets into 10/142. Jake Tonges also commanded 11 looks at tight end. Coaches love Robinson and his gritty game, but it is not promising he posted this quiet of a box score on an evening where Mac Jones attempted 49 passes. Robinson can be left on waiver wires in all 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a854-d6e9-af9d-aad4cf590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Tonges caught 7-of-11 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the 49ers’ Week 5 overtime win over the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a857-d95b-addb-e857667f0000</link>
      <description>Aside from the yards, it was an evening of new career highs across the board, while the touchdown was Tonges’ third in five 2025 appearances. This, after he entered the season with one career target and zero catches. Tonges has exceeded the wildest expectations for his George Kittle caretaking, but Kittle is eligible to return from his hamstring injury in Week 6, and the early reports are that he just may do so. Tonges’ time in the fantasy TE2 sun could be at an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a857-d95b-addb-e857667f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chuba Hubbard (calf) “is expected to miss” Week 5’s game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa03-dca3-a9fb-bf9b80ba0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard’s calf injury will require at least a one-game absence. The Panthers’ RB1, while not officially ruled out by the team, is expected to miss Week 5 against the Dolphins, per Rapoport, which would put Rico Dowdle in line for lead duties. Hopefully, this is only a one-week thing for Hubbard, who has struggled out of the gate. After breaking out for 250-1,195-10 on the ground last season, Hubbard has totaled just 217 scoreless yards on 53 carries this season, but has found the end zone twice through the air. Fantasy managers who add Dowdle can view him as a fringe RB2/RB3 against a Miami defense that’s allowed the third-most rushing yards per game and fourth-highest YPC (5.1) to its opponents this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa03-dca3-a9fb-bf9b80ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports free agent DE Drake Jackson is scheduled to meet with the Jets, Commanders, and Ravens in the coming days.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</link>
      <description>Jackson was waived with a failed injury designation earlier this offseason after a knee injury prematurely ended his 2023 campaign and kept him out for all of 2024. Now cleared for a return, the former second-round pick has totaled six sacks in 23 career games, but could provide help to a team in need of bolstering its pass rush.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa08-d6e9-af9d-aa98c7960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (ankle) will play in Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</link>
      <description>Garrett was a DNP to open the week and was upgraded to a limited participant in Thursday’s practice. Garrett’s injury doesn’t appear too severe at this point. We would expect him to see his normal assortment of snaps as he looks to get after Carson Wentz in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1b-d95b-addb-ea5f4aac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Newsome (hamstring) is questionable for Week 5’s game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</link>
      <description>Newsome popped up on Thursday’s injury report with a hamstring and will officially be questionable entering the week. It’s never a good sign when a player is a late addition to the injury report, and the Browns will need all hands on deck if they hope to slow the receiving duo of Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison. If he’s unable to go, backup Myles Harden appears next in line to receive snaps. In addition to Newsome, RT Jack Conklin (elbow), who hasn’t played since Week 1, is also questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-aa1e-dca3-a9fb-bf9f14350000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
