<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said DB Billy Bowman suffered an Achilles injury in practice and will not play in Week 12’s game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7d1-d413-ad9f-b7dd7dfe0000</link>
      <description>It was “not good” in Morris’ words, which probably means this is a season-ending injury. For any normal team, this would be a devastating blow. For the Falcons, it is business as usual on a Friday. Bowman had a 52.8 PFF coverage grade over 300 snaps in his rookie season while mostly playing nickel corner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7d1-d413-ad9f-b7dd7dfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 12 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3fb-d413-ad9f-b7ff9f2e0000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been an injury report mainstay since appearing on it with an ankle issue in Week 6. Despite that, he has not yet missed a game this season. The Falcons’ run defense presents whichever running back starts for the Saints with a fantasy-friendly matchup. The unit is allowing the seventh-most yards per carry (4.7) in the league. Saints rookie RB Devin Neal has failed to impress this season, but he could be worth stashing for running back-needy squads, given Kamara’s questionable listing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a3fb-d413-ad9f-b7ff9f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 12 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a40d-d413-ad9f-b5dd35f30000</link>
      <description>The Steelers have defended the run well in recent weeks, but the Bears’ rushing attack is averaging the sixth-most yards per carry (4.8) and the offensive line is generating the second-most yards per carry before contact (1.8). Swift is ready to rock as an RB2, operating as the Bears’ lead rusher in Week 12. Nos. 3 and 4 RBs Roschon Johnson (thumb) and Travis Homer (hamstring/knee) have both been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a40d-d413-ad9f-b5dd35f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons G Chris Lindstrom (foot) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 12 game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7e2-db57-afda-f7f2c60e0000</link>
      <description>So is Matthew Bergeron (ankle), who has missed the last two weeks with this ankle injury. Lindstrom is almost certain to go, but continues to be listed as questionable as they manage his injury. Bergeron is more of a true question mark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7e2-db57-afda-f7f2c60e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) for Week 12 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7df-db57-afda-f7ffb35b0000</link>
      <description>Bears LB Tremaine Edmunds (groin) has also been ruled out. This is bad news for the Bears’ defense and good news for the Steelers’ rushing attack. If RB Jaylen Warren (ankle) is cleared to play, he should be ranked as a high-end RB2 at worst. In the meantime, No. 2 RB Kenneth Gainwell should be stashed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7df-db57-afda-f7ffb35b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (hamstring) is off New York’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ea-d82c-a79a-b7fefec20000</link>
      <description>With Jameis Winston under center, Slayton has a playable FLEX case despite New York’s low projected point total for the week. He was limited on both Thursday and Friday before (surprisingly) avoiding the questionable line altogether. He wound up missing one week with his hamstring injury this time around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ea-d82c-a79a-b7fefec20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (groin) is questionable to play in Week 12 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7df-d90e-a9da-bfdfbb230000</link>
      <description>Bears slot CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) and S Jaquan Brisker (shoulder) are also questionable to play. All three players practiced fully on Friday, but the team will be cautious here. Both Johnson and Gordon were placed on injured reserve due to injuries suffered in training camp, and Johnson required core muscle surgery to correct his groin issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7df-d90e-a9da-bfdfbb230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder) won’t play in New York’s Week 12 game against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ec-d90e-a9da-bfefb1ad0000</link>
      <description>He did not practice all week and is in some danger of an IR placement on Saturday. New York also ruled out veteran CB Paulson Adebo (knee), which should help open up room in the secondary for Detroit’s receivers in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ec-d90e-a9da-bfefb1ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals activated TE Mike Gesicki (pectoral) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7f0-d413-ad9f-b7fd8ffe0000</link>
      <description>After practicing fully all week, Gesicki will resume his role as head of the Bengals TE committee. He and Noah Fant will likely cannibalize each other’s production enough to keep either from being fantasy-interesting, but if they were ever going to be interesting, playing a pass-funnel Patriots defense with Ja’Marr Chase being suspended might be the place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7f0-d413-ad9f-b7fd8ffe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (ankle) is questionable for Kansas City’s Week 12 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7f9-d82c-a79a-b7fdd9ef0000</link>
      <description>He does seem to be on the optimistic side of the line after going DNP-&gt;Limited-&gt;Full over his three practices this week, but it’s not a great sign that he’s questionable. Worthy will be a low-end WR3 or high-end FLEX candidate against the Colts, but has not returned much over the past month, cracking 40 yards just once with no touchdowns since Rashee Rice returned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7f9-d82c-a79a-b7fdd9ef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
