<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared LG Donvan Jackson, QB J.J. McCarthy, QB Desmond Ridder, OT Walter Rouse, OLB Andrew Van Ginkel, and TE Benjamin Yurosek inactive for Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9034-dca3-a9fb-bdbdd9080000</link>
      <description>Jackson missed all three practices this week with a wrist injury. He was ruled out on Friday. With McCarthy still nursing an ankle injury, Carson Wentz will make his second start of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9034-dca3-a9fb-bdbdd9080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren (knee) is inactive for Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-902f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffd2a30000</link>
      <description>It’s a nightmare scenario for fantasy managers who care about getting their nightly eight hours of sleep. Warren was reportedtly expected to play as of Saturday and was spotted going through warmups this morning. Kenneth Gainwelll figuires to be the team’s top back and should be scooped up in all formats. Warren’s absence could also give rookie Kaleb Johnson a shot at redemption after his kickoff snaffu from Week 2 got him sent to the bench.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-902f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffd2a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith (hip) is active for Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9037-d6e9-af9d-9ab787c30000</link>
      <description>Smith missed Wednesday’s practice but was upgraded to two limited sessions before being listed as questionable. He has at least three catches in every game this year but no more than 27 receiving yards. Smith is barely clinging to TE2 relevance in his current role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9037-d6e9-af9d-9ab787c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared CB Joey Porter Jr., OLB Alex Highsmith, OL Andrus Peat, DL Esezi Otomewo, and RB Jaylen Warren inactive for Week 4 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9039-dca3-a9fb-bdb9be7e0000</link>
      <description>Porter Jr. returned to practice this week and was listed as questionable on Friday. With a game in Ireland on tap for today, the Steelers have their bye next week. They are likely playing things safe and giving Porter Jr. one more week to recover from the hamstring issue he suffered in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9039-dca3-a9fb-bdb9be7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Ricky Pearsall (knee) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9042-d95b-addb-f8462b290000</link>
      <description>Jauan Jennings is also expected to suit up, though he may be on a pitch count. Pearsall broke out with Jennings inactive last week, turning 11 targets into eight catches for 117 yards. He was a chunk play machine for a team that had no other options at receiver or tight end. Even with Jennings back, Pearsall could push for WR2 numbers with a few big plays. Fantasy managers should be looking for ways to get him in their lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9042-d95b-addb-f8462b290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jauan Jennings (shoulder/ankle) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9046-d6e9-af9d-9ad60a930000</link>
      <description>Ricky Pearsall is also expected to suit up. Both receivers were listed as questionable for Week 4. Per Schefter, Jennings is “likely to be limited.” Jennings led the 49ers in targets when he was last active in Week 2. He saw 10 looks and posted a 5/89/1 receiving line. A potential pitch count, however, is a big blow to his fantasy outlook. Jennings will sit on the WR3/4 border for a week but could be even higher than Pearsall for Week 5 if his date with the Jags does well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9046-d6e9-af9d-9ad60a930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Davante Adams (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-904d-d95b-addb-f84f40ca0000</link>
      <description>Adams missed the first two practices of the week with the hamstring injury but was back for a limited session to close the week. Head coach Sean McVay told reporters that he felt good about Adams being able to play on. The team only targets those two players, meaning both can be treated as WR1s for Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-904d-d95b-addb-f84f40ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jacory Croskey-Merritt (ankle) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9052-d95b-addb-f85677c10000</link>
      <description>Bill was upgraded to a full practice on Friday after being held out of the first two practices of the week entirely. Commanders coach Dan Quinn also seemed to indicate on Friday that JCM would be good to go. Chris Rodriguez led the Commanders with 11 carries last week. Bill saw just eight. The ankle issue makes it even less likely that he sees a role change in Week 4. As nothing more than a change-of-pace back, JCM is an RB4 for heading into his date with the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9052-d95b-addb-f85677c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Vikings “at least considered” signing Aaron Rodgers in the offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9059-dca3-a9fb-bdd959140000</link>
      <description>Pelissero added, “But they pretty quickly decided and informed Rodgers that they were rolling with J.J. McCarthy.” Rodgers was likely interested in playing for Minnesota as the starter while the Vikings could only commit to a camp battle between him and their No. 10 overall pick from 2024. The team ultimately signed Carson Wentz to be McCarthy’s backup. Wentz is now the team’s starter with McCarthy sidelined because of an ankle injury. It’s a long season, but Pelissero’s report is a reminder that the Vikings were doing their due diligence on other quarterbacks even with McCarthy penciled in as the starter. If Wentz plays well during his interim gig, it’s not outlandish to think he could remain the starter even once McCarthy is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9059-dca3-a9fb-bdd959140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Isaiah Likely (foot) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9057-dca3-a9fb-bddfc2410000</link>
      <description>Likely is officially listed as questionable, but all signs point toward him making his 2025 debut. He was a full participant in Friday’s practice to close the week. Likely suffered a foot injury at the start of training camp and has been working his way back from the injury for roughly two months. His role in his first game back could be small at first, but the Ravens talked him up all summer and will likely make him an even bigger part of the offense this year once he is up to speed. For Week 4, Likely is a high-risk TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9057-dca3-a9fb-bddfc2410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
