<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos C Luke Wattenberg (shoulder) is expected to be sidelined for three weeks, “through the first two rounds of the playoffs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</link>
      <description>Wattenberg grades well as both a pass protector and run blocker, earning a 70.9 PFF offense grade. With Wattenberg sidelined, the Broncos signed C Sam Mustipher off the Chargers’ practice squad. Broncos C Alex Forsyth will operate as the starter with Wattenberg sidelined. Mustipher is his backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ca4-dc7a-af9b-dfbf09c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Kimani Vidal (neck) is questionable for Week 17 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cbc-d56e-afff-fefc26c80000</link>
      <description>The team put out an estimated practice report for Christmas Day, but gave players the day off. Vidal is surprisingly listed as a limited participant after sitting out the team’s first two practices. He would be a very risky FLEX option if active. We expect RB Omarion Hampton to hog touches against a stout Texans defense, regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cbc-d56e-afff-fefc26c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll confirmed that EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) is being “shut down.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc0-d968-a19b-5cf177ec0000</link>
      <description>Crosby is not going to like this. Hours ago, after the team ruled Crosby out for Week 17, FOX’s Jay Glazer reported that Crosby, disgruntled, had “left the building,” calling into question “his future in Vegas.” It seems likely that the decision to shut Crosby down, ostensibly for Week 18 as well, will be formalized with a move to injured reserve. Crosby leads the team with 53 quarterback pressures and 10 sacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc0-d968-a19b-5cf177ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc2-dc7a-af9b-dfff01640000</link>
      <description>Kittle did not practice this week, and reportedly told head coach Kyle Shanahan that he “should have a better answer by tomorrow” regarding his Week 17 availability. Kittle is no stranger to playing through injury, and although he is clearly less than 100.0 percent, he warrants TE1 treatment if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cc2-dc7a-af9b-dfff01640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (ankle/knee) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccb-d968-a19b-5cfb8f2d0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall has been practicing in a limited capacity this week, though we do not yet know his official participation level for Friday. If he can suit up against the Bears this weekend, he can only be viewed as a boom-bust FLEX option. Pearsall has demonstrated intriguing route running abilities this season, but knee and ankle injuries continue to slow him down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccb-d968-a19b-5cfb8f2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) was not seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccf-d35e-a1bf-5dcfd8310000</link>
      <description>We do not expect Adams to play this week. The 33-year-old wide receiver has already aggravated the multi-week injury once, and the Rams (11-4) have secured a playoff spot. On the off chance he plays, he would be a candidate to score a touchdown, operating in his featured red zone role, but he makes for a dicey play overall. Just two days ago, ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reported that the Rams may “shut down” Adams for the final two games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ccf-d35e-a1bf-5dcfd8310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders RB Raheem Mostert (knee/ankle) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-dc7a-af9b-dfffad9e0000</link>
      <description>Mostert has not been fantasy-relevant, but with the Raiders have shutting down TE Brock Bowers (knee) and EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee), we figure all skill position players are worth keeping an eye on. Mostert sits in second on the depth chart, with RB Zamir White and RB Dylan Laube behind him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-dc7a-af9b-dfffad9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Jack Bech (back) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-d56e-afff-fefeb6b50000</link>
      <description>The Raiders’ second-round rookie has not had a good season. Bech has caught 20-of-26 targets for 224 scoreless yards, while averaging 1.27 yards per route run. Hopefully, Bech can return in time for Week 18, so he can put something decent on film before the team begins evaluating its pre-draft needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5cd6-d56e-afff-fefeb6b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport believes that hiring a new offensive coordinator and play caller “could make a lot of sense” for the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ce4-dc7a-af9b-dfff43780000</link>
      <description>Lions head coach Dan Campbell took play-calling duties from OC John Morton in Week 10. The offense averaged 5.8 yards per play in Weeks 1-9 and 6.1 from Weeks 10-17. Campbell could feasibly keep play-calling duties in 2026, though he may wish to hand that responsibility off to an up-and-coming offensive mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ce4-dc7a-af9b-dfff43780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sports Bay Area’s Matt Maiocco reports that it is “possible” for LB Fred Warner (ankle) to return late in the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ddd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee5a0000</link>
      <description>Per a source, “Warner could make a push to be available for the NFC Championship Game, if the 49ers are able to advance that far in the postseason.” 49ers GM John Lynch acknowledged that “it would be well ahead of the original timeline we were given,” but it is possible for Warner to return if he can meet the “objective measurements” placed in front of him by team doctors. Per Maiocco, “Lynch sounded more optimistic” than he had been previously, when discussing whether Warner could “play again this season.” Warner’s return is far from guaranteed, as is the 49ers’ theoretical playoff run, but this is now a story worth following. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5ddd-dc7a-af9b-dfffee5a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
