<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 04:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans CB L’Jarius Sneed (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1199-db7b-a5dd-b19dc9ea0000</link>
      <description>This should be the norm for Sneed, who underwent a cleanup procedure on his ailing knee this summer. Head coach Brian Callahan said that Sneed’s knee will need to be managed “all the time” so he will likely practice in an abbreviated manner all year. Speedy wide receivers could give him fits in his age-28 season. Titans OT Dan Moore Jr. (ankle) did not practice today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1199-db7b-a5dd-b19dc9ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Jordan James (finger) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11a8-de13-afdd-57eb51a30000</link>
      <description>James underwent surgery to repair a finger fracture in early August. The backfield looks a whole lot different now, with Brian Robinson now occupying the No. 2 spot. James belongs on dynasty rosters but can be left in the free agent pool in re-draft at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11a8-de13-afdd-57eb51a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived S Jordan Poyer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119d-db7b-a5dd-b19d35190000</link>
      <description>The Bills waived Poyer, but it is likely just a formality while the team signs Gabe Davis to the practice squad. Davis will be moved to the injured list with Poyer re-joining the practice squad afterward. The 34-year-old started 16 games for the Dolphins last season after spending seven seasons in Buffalo prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-119d-db7b-a5dd-b19d35190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR/CB Travis Hunter (upper body) is not listed on the initial Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11bc-db7b-a5dd-b1bcca2f0000</link>
      <description>Hunter had been dealing with an upper body injury throughout the last couple weeks of preseason. He got back up to practice speed last week and is no longer listed on the injury report. The assumption is that Hunter is healthy and is slated to play Week 1 against the Panthers. Fantasy managers have little reason to believe the upper body injury will slow down the 22-year-old to start the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11bc-db7b-a5dd-b1bcca2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed QB C.J. Beathard to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11ce-d332-a1fd-97fe89160000</link>
      <description>Beathard joins the Lions’ practice squad as the team’s No. 3 quarterback. The 31-year-old spent the last three seasons with the Jaguars, starting one game in 2024. He has 13 career starts and has thrown for 3,886 yards, 19 touchdowns, and 14 interceptions over his six-year career. Beathard will back up Jared Goff and Kyle Allen in Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11ce-d332-a1fd-97fe89160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs (knee) is not listed on the initial Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11da-dbe3-a9bb-31db44190000</link>
      <description>Diggs has been rehabbing well from last season’s torn ACL and is slated to enter the season healthy. He participated throughout training camp and multiple reports had him looking encouragingly good to go. Head coach Mike Vrabel even said Diggs will be ready for Week 1 on Monday and his exclusion from Wednesday’s injury report shows Diggs can be fired up with WR2/3 viability against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11da-dbe3-a9bb-31db44190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11e6-d332-a1fd-97f6e97e0000</link>
      <description>Bobo entered concussion protocol after the Seahawks’ final preseason game. He is still working his way back, but a limited practice indicates he has a chance to play Week 1. Also limited at wide receiver were Cody White (shoulder) and Dareke Young (hamstring), while Tory Horton (ankle) was a full participant and is on track to play against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11e6-d332-a1fd-97f6e97e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams QB Matthew Stafford (back) is not listed on the initial Week 1 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11fe-db7b-a5dd-b1fe34d80000</link>
      <description>Rams head coach Sean McVay said on Monday that he expected Stafford to start Week 1. Stafford’s omission from Wednesday’s injury report affirms that, with the 37-year-old quarterbacksayinghe has “no issues with a physical game.” Though it seems the Rams will have no restrictions with Stafford, its hard to believe he won’t at least be popping up on the injury report every now and then. Fantasy managers can approach Stafford as a QB2 this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-11fe-db7b-a5dd-b1fe34d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1208-de13-afdd-56cb91e20000</link>
      <description>Kirk was headed for the No. 2 wide receiver role in Houston, but his Week 1 status is now in jeopardy. He popped up on the injury report with a hamstring issue and did not participate in Wednesday’s practice. Braxton Berrios (hamstring) also did not practice. With Kirk and Berrios potentially out against the Rams, rookies Jayden Higgins and Jaylin Noel will see a more immediate increase in targets Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1208-de13-afdd-56cb91e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed WR Jauan Jennings to a contract that will add $3 million in play-time incentives.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-12a8-db7b-a5dd-b2ac6e220000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jennings can earn up to $10.5 million this season, instead of the previous $7.5 million. Jennings had been in a contract dispute with the 49ers for much of the preseason while also dealing with a calf injury. He returned to practice this week and now gets a contract bump in the form of play-time incentives. The 28-year-old caught 77-of-113 targets for 975 yards and six touchdowns last season. With Brandon Aiyuk still working his way back from a torn ACL and other wide receiver injuries, Jennings is in line for a large workload beside Ricky Pearsall this season. Jennings is a fantasy WR4 heading into the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-12a8-db7b-a5dd-b2ac6e220000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
