<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns waived TE Sal Cannella.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</link>
      <description>Cannella thrived in the UFL over the last two seasons, but didn’t produce enough in the preseason to justify a roster spot; at least to the Browns. Along with Cannella, Cleveland also waived CB Chigozie Anusiem, G Javion Cohen, T Sebastian Gutierrez, DE K.J. Henry, DT Ralph Holley, CB Christian Holmes, CB Keenan Isaac, T Jason Ivey, DE Titus Le, LB Marvin Moody, CB Darius Rush, LB Charlie Thomas III, T Lorenzo Thompson, G Dartanyan Tinsley, TE Mitchell Van Vooren and C Bucky Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dda4-de13-afdc-dfef74610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots waived OL Layden Robinson with an injury designation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddb2-dbe3-a9bb-fdf356a30000</link>
      <description>Robinson was the fourth-round pick of the Patriots in 2024, but the former Texas A&amp;M standout was unable to stay on the field in his brief time with New England. He could be a candidate for the practice squad if he goes unclaimed/doesn’t find a new job on a 53-man roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddb2-dbe3-a9bb-fdf356a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears placed CB Terell Smith on injured reserve with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd94-de13-afdc-dfdf6b2e0000</link>
      <description>We already knew Smith would miss the 2025 season, but this move makes it official. It’s a terribly unfortunate development for the talented former fifth-round pick. The Bears waived LB Swayze Bozeman, OL Chris Glaser, TE Thomas Gordon, S Mark Perry and DB Jeremiah Walker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd94-de13-afdc-dfdf6b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles waived QB Dorian Thompson-Robinson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbb-de13-afdc-dffbbe710000</link>
      <description>Even with the injury to Tanner McKee (thumb), the Eagles feel confident enough in their depth at quarterback to let Thompson-Robinson hit the waiver wire. It’s certainly feasible that the team could bring back DTR on the practice squad, but it’s just as likely that he’ll be looking for a new organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbb-de13-afdc-dffbbe710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets waived QB Adrian Martinez.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</link>
      <description>Martinez is a practice squad candidate, but the Jets may choose to go with Brady Cook as the third quarterback behind Josh Fields and Tyrod Taylor. New York also waived LB Jamin Davis, DE Michael Fletcher, T Liam Forandel, T Samuel Jackson, TE Zach Kuntz, DB Tanner McCalister and RB Lawrance Toafili.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddbe-dbe3-a9bb-fdff1f8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s John Shipley believes “the Jaguars will look to unload” either Travis Etienne Jr. or Tank Bigsby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</link>
      <description>Shipley adds that if the Jaguars’ trade efforts are unsuccessful, he thinks they will carry Etienne, Bigsby and rookies Bhayshul Tuten and LeQuint Allen Jr. on the final roster and make “one of the two rookies inactive on game day.” Etienne regularly took passing down snaps during preseason play. While Tuten’s explosive traits make him an all-around breakout candidate, it’s possible Allen could sneak into a specialized passing down role if Etienne ends up being traded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddc1-d332-a1fd-dff727710000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Archer of ESPN reports that the Cowboys are releasing OT La’el Collins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</link>
      <description>Collins was signed at the start of August to add depth, but the 32-year-old didn’t do enough in his limited time with Dallas to make the 53-man roster. Collins could be of interest for a team in need of depth, but is unlikely to be more than one of the last few players on the roster as long as he’s still playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddd6-de13-afdc-dfdf061a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers waived CB Tre Avery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dde4-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7658a0000</link>
      <description>Avery signed with the Buccaneers just two days ago and racked up seven tackles in the team’s preseason Week 3 game against the Bills on Saturday. He spent the first two preseason games on the Patriots’ roster, totaling five tackles and one forced incompletion with them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dde4-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7658a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that the Bills are expected to re-sign DT Jordan Phillips later this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</link>
      <description>Phillips worked out with the Bills today, and evidently, it went well. The 32-year-old previously played for the Bills in 2019 and from 2022-2023. He spent the 2024 season with the Cowboys. He can be expected to serve as a rotational player on the Bills’ interior defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddef-de13-afdc-dfef5d460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Tomasson of the Denver Gazette reports that the Broncos waived WR Joaquin Davis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</link>
      <description>Davis caught one pass for 14 yards after being added as an undrafted free agent by the Broncos. The 6-foot-4 wideout is likely to hang around on the practice squad. Denver also waived linebacker Andrew Farmer according to Tomasson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ddf6-de13-afdc-dfff586b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
