<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said TE Noah Fant will not play in Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c24-deb6-a7fd-dffffc2c0000</link>
      <description>Fant suffered a concussion in the team’s Week 3 loss to the Vikings and did not do enough to progress through the league’s concussion protocol. His absence should boost the snap rate and route participation rate of Mike Gesicki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c24-deb6-a7fd-dffffc2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals ruled out DE Shemar Stewart (ankle) for Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c26-deb6-a7fd-dfff88380000</link>
      <description>The ankle issue will not cost Stewart his second consecutive game after the veteran defensive end missed Week 3’s loss to the Vikings. His absence was felt considering the Bengals allowed Jordan Mason to eclipse 100 yards on the ground on just 16 carries, boosting the matchup for J.K. Dobbins in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c26-deb6-a7fd-dfff88380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports WR Tetairoa McMillan is expected to play in Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c28-dca3-a9fb-bdb9a0ad0000</link>
      <description>McMillan has been adamant about taking the field when the Panthers face the Patriots on the road in Week 4, something that appears to be vindicated as Sunday approaches. It is not yet apparent whether he will see any limitations but fantasy managers are likely going to start him, assuming he dodges inactives Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c28-dca3-a9fb-bdb9a0ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2b-d6e9-af9d-8ebb0f9f0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard was limited in practices this week as he tends to a calf injury, ultimately drawing the questionable tag for the team’s Week 4 road matchup with the Patriots. It now sounds like he is in line to play and fantasy managers should assume a normal workload for the veteran back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2b-d6e9-af9d-8ebb0f9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Tyreek Hill (personal) missed practice Saturday but is expected to play Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2c-d6e9-af9d-8ebce9070000</link>
      <description>Hill was absent from team practice Saturday for personal reasons but is expected to play on Monday against the Jets. The early season returns have been less than stellar for Hill and the rest of the Dolphins’ primary skill position players. The Jets no longer present the same vaunted defense as they have in previous seasons, meaning fantasy managers will want to start Hill with confidence in Week 4, regardless of his struggles through three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2c-d6e9-af9d-8ebce9070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports TE Colston Loveland (hip) is not expected to play in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2f-deb6-a7fd-dfffa36b0000</link>
      <description>Veteran tight end Cole Kmet has played 90% or more of the offensive snaps in every game this season and ranks third on the team in route participation rate, making him a solid streaming option in a plus matchup against the Raiders. Loveland’s next opportunity to take the field comes in Week 6 when the Bears take on the Commanders following their Week 5 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2f-deb6-a7fd-dfffa36b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens placed DL Nnamdi Madubuike (neck) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c73-deb6-a7fd-dfffaed60000</link>
      <description>Madubuike had already been ruled out for Week 4 and now will miss the next four games, at minimum, for the Ravens as he tends to a neck injury. It’s a sizable loss on the defensive interior for a Ravens team struggling against the run to start the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c73-deb6-a7fd-dfffaed60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens placed DL Broderick Washington (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8cd8-d6e9-af9d-8ed86fa80000</link>
      <description>Washington joins Nnamdi Madubuike on injured reserve, meaning two of three starting defensive linemen in Baltimore’s 3-4 system will now miss the next four games, at minimum. The team has already struggled against the run to start the 2025 season, something that could get worse in the immediate future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8cd8-d6e9-af9d-8ed86fa80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants placed K Graham Gano on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8cdc-dca3-a9fb-bddd074e0000</link>
      <description>Gano has struggled through injuries the previous three seasons and will now miss the next four games, at minimum. The team signed Jude McAtamney in an associated move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8cdc-dca3-a9fb-bddd074e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Marvin Mims (hip) is questionable for Week 4 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8ce0-dca3-a9fb-bdf99a870000</link>
      <description>Mims is nursing a hip injury and draws the questionable tag for Monday Night Football against the Bengals, the team he put up career numbers against last season. Trent Sherfield and rookie Pat Bryant would be in line for a boost in opportunities should Mims be unable to go. Fantasy managers should make alternate plans considering the Broncos play in the last game of the week in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8ce0-dca3-a9fb-bdf99a870000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
