<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 17:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Justin Shorter to active roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a64-d332-a1fd-9e76103b0000</link>
      <description>Shorter was added to the Raiders’ practice squad last week after being waived during final roster cutdowns. A former fifth-round pick of the Bills back in 2023, Shorter appeared in six games for the Raiders last season while playing primarily on special teams. The decision to sign him to the active roster comes a day after Amari Cooper abruptly announced his retirement. Shorter doesn’t have any fantasy value at this time and is far from a lock to stick on the roster throughout the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a64-d332-a1fd-9e76103b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vita Vea (foot) returned to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a71-d332-a1fd-9e77299b0000</link>
      <description>It’s potentially good news for the Bucs as Vea appears set to log at least one practice before the end of the week. The veteran lineman was a DNP during the team’s first two practices to open the week, but even a limited practice would bode well for his Week 1 outlook against the Falcons. The team will release their final injury report later in the day, which should give us a good sense of whether or not Vea has a chance to suit up for the season opener.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a71-d332-a1fd-9e77299b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said he expects Sauce Gardner (fibula) to play in Week 1 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a77-d332-a1fd-9e77de560000</link>
      <description>Glenn said he expects every player to be available on Sunday, with the exception of Alijah Vera-Tucker, who has been ruled out for the season due to a triceps injury suffered earlier in the week. After being a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice, Gardner was upgraded to a full participant on Thursday and will likely be removed from the team’s injury report by the end of Friday. Gardner should see plenty of DK Metcalf in Week 1, which could severely cap the already limited upside Metcalf is expected to have in the Steelers’ run-heavy attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a77-d332-a1fd-9e77de560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said Darren Waller (hip) is doubtful for Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a86-d332-a1fd-9eb658350000</link>
      <description>Waller’s return to the league continues to go horribly. After missing nearly all of training camp to get into football shape, the veteran tight end has gone from being on track to return in Week 1 at the start of the week to being a DNP on both Wednesday and Thursday. McDaniel reports Waller suffered a setback ahead of Thursday’s practice, giving us little reason to believe he’ll be on the field on Friday. It wouldn’t be surprising if he is officially ruled out before the weekend, paving the way for Julian Hill to draw the start. It should go without saying, but there’s no reason to jam Hill into a fantasy lineup this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a86-d332-a1fd-9eb658350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said Malik Nabers’ back is a “little tight” but that he will be okay for Week 1 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a92-d332-a1fd-9eb679470000</link>
      <description>Daboll said the team will “back down on Malik” in Friday’s practice after the star receiver returned to the field earlier in the week. Nabers has not been listed on the team’s injury report this week, but it sounds like he could receive a limited designation for Friday based on Daboll’s quotes. Regardless of how the team lists him for Friday’s practice, Daboll seems confident that his WR1 will be ready to roll on Sunday against the Commanders. He’s a must-start in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a92-d332-a1fd-9eb679470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said Andrew Thomas (foot) will practice on Friday and “do some team stuff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a96-d332-a1fd-9eb66b190000</link>
      <description>It sounds like Thomas will be in a good position to play in Week 1 against the Commanders after being a DNP on Thursday. Thomas was limited in Wednesday’s practice, so it’s possible Thursday’s absence was due more to rest than further injury. We’ll have a better sense of his availability when the team releases its final injury report on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a96-d332-a1fd-9eb66b190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said he expects Jayden Reed (foot) to practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a99-de13-afdd-5edb3c0d0000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said he expects all 53 players on the roster to practice in some capacity. Reed was upgraded to a limited participant in Thursday’s practice and could have a realistic shot to play in Week 1 against the Lions. Even if Reed does play, he looks like a risky bet as far as fantasy is concerned. The third-year receiver is dealing with a fracture in his foot that he suffered less than a month ago, and with other players capable of filling his role, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Packers played him in a limited role if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1a99-de13-afdd-5edb3c0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (hip) was seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1aa7-dbe3-a9bb-3af754c50000</link>
      <description>After being a surprise DNP on Thursday, Garrett was back on the field Friday which should put him on track to play in Week 1 against the Bengals. We’ll get a good sense of his availability when the team’s final injury report is released in the coming hours, but Garrett’s return to the field is an encouraging sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1aa7-dbe3-a9bb-3af754c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mekhi Becton (illness) has been added to the injury report and is questionable for the Chargers’ Week 1 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ab3-de13-afdd-5efba22a0000</link>
      <description>With the Chargers slated to play on Friday, Becton is a game-day addition to the injury report. While it’s not often that we see players miss games due to illness, the late addition for Becton is mildly concerning. The Chargers signed Becton to a two-year, $20 million contract this offseason after his stellar first season with the Eagles, and are hoping he’ll help bolster a rushing attack that ranked 24th in yards per carry last season. If he’s unable to play on Friday, fourth-year vet Jamaree Salyer would be the presumed starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ab3-de13-afdd-5efba22a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers listed LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) as doubtful for Week 1 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ac2-de13-afdd-5ecbfb6f0000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu was listed as a limited participant in Friday’s practice after sitting out the first two days. Despite this, the team has opted to list him as doubtful, which officially puts him on the wrong side of suiting up for Week 1 against the Jaguars. Ekwonu underwent an appendectomy on August 27th and was initially viewed as “day-to-day” by the team. Barring an unexpected change between now and Sunday, fifth-year vet Brady Christensen will likely draw the start against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1ac2-de13-afdd-5ecbfb6f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
