<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton (knee) is doubtful for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09cb-da9b-a9bf-dfcfdde90000</link>
      <description>Otton failed to practice on Monday or Tuesday. He managed a limited session today, but the doubtful tag makes it highly unlikely that he suits up versus Atlatna. Payne Durham will see an uptick in routes with Otton out, though there won’t be many targets for him to handle with Mike Evans expected to make his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09cb-da9b-a9bf-dfcfdde90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen McMillan (neck) is questionable for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ce-d77b-adfb-cbcf53080000</link>
      <description>McMillan suffered a neck injury during the preseason and hasn’t played this year. He remains on injured reserve, meaning the team will have to officially activate him if he is going to suit up. With Mike Evans also expected to return, McMillan won’t have much of a role in his first game of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ce-d77b-adfb-cbcf53080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d1-d8cf-affb-bdfbe50c0000</link>
      <description>Jennings’ role has declined in recent weeks with Rhamondre Stevenson healthy once again. Jennings did not touch the ball before the Pats’ bye in Week 14. His likely absence this week will keep New England’s backfield at a two-man committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d1-d8cf-affb-bdfbe50c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RT Trey Pipkins (ankle) will not practice leading up to the team’s Week 15 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09bb-da9b-a9bf-dfbfeb6b0000</link>
      <description>Pipkins entered the Chargers’ Week 14 game against the Eagles with a back injury and exited with an ankle injury. When asked if Pipkins, along with WR Derius Davis (ankle) and S Elijah Molden (hamstring), could play after sitting out practice all week, Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said only, “we’ll see how the week goes.” Having Pipkins on the field would be extremely helpful for QB Justin Herbert (hand).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09bb-da9b-a9bf-dfbfeb6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs activated Mike Evans (collarbone) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d6-d005-a9bf-d9f6da170000</link>
      <description>Jalen McMillan was also activated. Both players are technically still listed as questionable, though the designations are largely a procedural matter. We fully expect both wideouts to suit up versus Atlanta tomorrow. Evans could be on a pitch count in his first game back, but the Bucs will make the most of the reps he is on the field for. He will be a WR3 for Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09d6-d005-a9bf-d9f6da170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers CB Jaycee Horn (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c7-d77b-adfb-cbc7c4f30000</link>
      <description>This is a step in the right direction for Horn. The Panthers’ No. 1 cornerback has been inactive on game day since suffering a concussion in Week 12. He has a chance to return for his team’s game against the division-rival Saints this week. Panthers LB Claudin Cherelus (concussion) was also limited today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09c7-d77b-adfb-cbc7c4f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Lamar Jackson was given a rest day on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09e5-d8cf-affb-bdef64570000</link>
      <description>Jackson will receive the “NIR-Rest” tag on Baltimore’s first injury report of the week. The team has routinely held him out of practice with various minor injuries over the past month. It’s a notable change for the Ravens to no longer list him with any injury designation. Jackson is also coming off his best rushing performance since September. He ran for 43 yards and a score versus the Steelers on Sunday. Hopefully this is a sign of good things to come for a quarterback who has struggled to put it all together this year. Jackson will be a low-end QB1 for his Week 15 date with the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09e5-d8cf-affb-bdef64570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Breece Hall (knee soreness) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ef-d77b-adfb-cbef2de80000</link>
      <description>Hall’s recurring knee issues can be tricky to get a read on. He played through them for a time last year and could do so again this week. His practice participation is worth watching, though. On the plus side, the “soreness” listing suggests this is more of a pain-related issue than a new injury that requires rehab. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ef-d77b-adfb-cbef2de80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said TE Elijah Arroyo (knee) is “out right now.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ef-d8cf-affb-bdef7bea0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald told reporters earlier this week that it was unlikely Arroyo would suit up on Sunday. His comments today all but confirm that. A.J. Barner will see a full complement of routes with Arroyo sidelined. Barner is a low-end TE2 heading into Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-09ef-d8cf-affb-bdef7bea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders LT Kolton Miller (ankle) resumed practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a00-d005-a9bf-da3476500000</link>
      <description>The Raiders placed their talented left tackle on injured reserve on September 30th after he suffered a high-ankle sprain and a hairline fracture in Week 4 against the Bears. The season is already lost, but Miller’s potential return would help the offense as a whole, for fantasy purposes. Raiders backup QB Kenny Pickett is expected to start in QB Geno Smith’s (shoulder) stead against the Eagles this week. Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby took the day off as he continues to manage a knee issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0a00-d005-a9bf-da3476500000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
