<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Rashid Shaheed (hip) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36be-d45b-affe-77be86f60000</link>
      <description>While he did leave Week 8’s game with the hip injury, it doesn’t look like Shaheed is in much danger of missing Week 9 after getting in back-to-back limited practices. Shaheed will likely remain a PPR WR4 dart throw against the Rams in Tyler Shough’s debut as a starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36be-d45b-affe-77be86f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons QB Michael Penix (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36bf-d1e7-a1fa-7eff378d0000</link>
      <description>Penix was expected to take the “majority” of first-team practice reps this week. It is unclear if that is indeed the case, but hopefully, he can practice in full tomorrow and this is a non-issue. Penix sat out in Week 8 after picking up a bone bruise in Week 7. If active against the Patriots this week, the Falcons’ quarterback can be treated as a high-end QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36bf-d1e7-a1fa-7eff378d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36c2-d673-a39e-b6d3e43c0000</link>
      <description>London is technically on track to play in Week 9 against the Patriots, but his continued limitations in practice indicate the Falcons’ wide receiver is still rigorously working through his rehab program. If active, London will duke it out with Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez on the perimeter. The talented wide receiver must still be treated as a WR1 in this case, though Gonzalez will undoubtedly make him work for every catch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36c2-d673-a39e-b6d3e43c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ac-d673-a39e-b6bd283d0000</link>
      <description>Pitts posted team-highs in targets (nine), receptions (nine) and receiving yards (59) against the Dolphins last week. His continued limitations are likely linked to the big workload, but he is perhaps on the fringes of questionable at this time. Fantasy managers should expect him to play in Week 9 against the Patriots, but his Friday practice participation level is worth checking up on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ac-d673-a39e-b6bd283d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes the Browns will trade away David Njoku or Jerome Ford.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ca-d45b-affe-77de52880000</link>
      <description>“Both have basically been replaced by rookies, and both are eligible for free agency next year. This is standard business, even though Njoku carries $24 million of dead money from a past contract acceleration into next year,” Jackson writes. Njoku being traded would obviously be major news for both the acquiring team and the Harold Fannin TE1 Hive. It makes plenty of sense for the Browns to move both players if they can get a real return on them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ca-d45b-affe-77de52880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons RB Tyler Allgeier (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36c9-d713-ad9e-7edda86a0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier remained limited by hip and knee injuries in all three practices last week. He suited up on game day, rushing four times for four yards and one touchdown, adding two catches for 10 yards. He practiced in full yesterday, so it is possible this is just a maintenance issue. Friday’s report should clarify his status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36c9-d713-ad9e-7edda86a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ededa340000</link>
      <description>It’s a surprise considering he went full on Wednesday, but not necessarily something that we know to be a setback. Darrisaw notably did not play all of Thursday night’s game last week because he’s simply not fully healthy from his late-2024 surgery and still requires more rest than usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ededa340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ba-d45b-affe-77beffb00000</link>
      <description>McConkey appeared on Wednesday’s injury report with a calf issue, yet managed to practice in a limited capacity. Although limited sessions early in the week are positive, new soft tissue listings are concerning. At this point, McConkey should be considered truly questionable to play in Week 9 against a Titans defense that notably just traded away starting slot CB Roger McCreary. His practice participation on Friday is critical.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ba-d45b-affe-77beffb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36d3-d1e7-a1fa-7efbcee90000</link>
      <description>Stevenson is now on the wrong side of questionable for the Patriots’ Week 9 game against the Falcons. Theoretically, rookie RB TreVeyon Henderson would be in line to start if Stevenson cannot play, though RB Terrell Jennings would likely rotate in. Hopefully, the coaching staff will provide clarity on Friday. ESPN’s Mike Reiss recently reported that the Patriots are likely to target a running back via the trade market before the NFL’s November 4th trade deadline. Stevenson’s health could be a factor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36d3-d1e7-a1fa-7efbcee90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ede91db0000</link>
      <description>The Patriots’ No. 1 pass catcher should be good to go for his team’s Week 9 game against the Falcons. His results have been a bit volatile this season, but Diggs can be started as a low-end WR2 in this one, particularly with the Falcons’ defense dealing with multiple injuries. He has finished as the WR24 and WR35 in half-PPR scoring over the last two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-36ce-d713-ad9e-7ede91db0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
