<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars declared WR Dyami Brown, RB Cody Schrader, DE Travon Walker, OL Chuma Edoga, LB Yasir Abdullah, OL Patrick Mekari, TE Hunter Long, and DT Arik Armstead inactive for Week 13 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a0-d82c-a79a-f7b41e3e0000</link>
      <description>Armstead was a late addition to the injury report with a hand issue and is now officially inactive for Week 13. With Travon Walker (knee) also ruled out, the Jaguars’ defense line is looking sparse against the Titans. Meanwhile, Dyami Brown is a healthy scratch as Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) makes his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a0-d82c-a79a-f7b41e3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared QB Stetson Bennett, RB Jarquez Hunter, CB Derion Kendrick, OL Beaux Limmer, and DE Desjuan Johnson inactive for Week 13 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a2-d90e-a9da-dfaf6d810000</link>
      <description>The Rams enter the day with a 9-2 record and are operating at nearly full strength against the Panthers. Whether by land or by air, the Rams should have no trouble moving the ball against a Panthers defense that ranks 18th in yards allowed but will be without its top corner in Jaycee Horn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5a2-d90e-a9da-dfaf6d810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Sauce Gardner (calf) left Indianapolis’ Week 13 game against the Texans and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5f6-db57-afda-d7f6e5490000</link>
      <description>Gardner could not put any weight on his left leg. He limped to the medical tent, then was helped off the field between a pair of trainers. It didn’t look good for the Colts main trade deadline acquisition, but a calf is better than it looked like it could have been.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d5f6-db57-afda-d7f6e5490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (foot) left Houston’s Week 13 game against the Colts and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d60d-d82c-a79a-f79d628b0000</link>
      <description>A Colts defender knee rolled his ankle. He had three carries for zero yards before leaving. There was no scene upon leaving, but Marks spent some time in the medical tent and jogged to the locker room with trainers. Nick Chubb has taken over as the starting running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d60d-d82c-a79a-f79d628b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (foot) has returned to Houston’s Week 13 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d627-d82c-a79a-f7b79cb90000</link>
      <description>He left with roughly two minutes left in the first quarter and missed about 10 minutes of game time in the second quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d627-d82c-a79a-f7b79cb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Parker Washington suffered an apparent hip injury and is questionable to return Week 13 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d608-db57-afda-d63a6dda0000</link>
      <description>Washington fell to the ground while fielding a punt return in the second quarter against the Titans. He was helped off the field and the Jaguars immediately listed him as questionable to return. Tim Patrick is in line for increased offensive opportunities with Washington out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d608-db57-afda-d63a6dda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (leg) exited in the second quarter of Week 13’s game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d637-d90e-a9da-df3fdd410000</link>
      <description>Williams took an awkward hit just before two minute warning and pulled himself from the game after the break according to Rams beat writer Adam Grosbard and was seen heading for the locker room. Blake Corum would come on to score a two-yard touchdown on the next play to give the Rams a 21-17 lead. Williams and Corum were already rotating before the injury, but Corum would be in line for a busy second half if Williams doesn’t return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d637-d90e-a9da-df3fdd410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 13 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d643-d6c4-abfb-d643ff970000</link>
      <description>Rams beat writer Adam Grosbard reported coming out of the half that Williams was on the field and “looked good just now on a couple of cuts.” That said, the team has officially listed him as questionable, so we’ll check back in with an official update if he returns to the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d643-d6c4-abfb-d643ff970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans S Jaylen Reed (forearm) left Houston’s Week 13 game against the Colts and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d648-d90e-a9da-df4ff1890000</link>
      <description>Definitely feels like a broken forearm for Reed, who had been starting at safety of late. He’ll probably be sent to injured reserve if that is indeed what happened here. He was hurt tackling Jonathan Taylor in the second quarter. Myles Bryant took over at safety.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d648-d90e-a9da-df4ff1890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyren Williams (ankle) returned to the field in Week 13 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d64d-d82c-a79a-f7dd57db0000</link>
      <description>Williams took the first snap and carry of the Rams’ opening possession of the third quarter. Whatever he is dealing with appears minor at this point. He should continue to split touches with Blake Corum as long as he remains healthy enough to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d64d-d82c-a79a-f7dd57db0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
