<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers released CB Trevon Diggs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd47-d968-a19b-ddf775740000</link>
      <description>A late-season cut by Dallas, the Packers added Diggs to the roster on New Year’s Eve. He played 33 defensive snaps in Week 18’s loss to the Vikings (started by Clayton Tune) and one snap in their loss to the Bears in the NFC Wild Card round. Diggs is entering his age-28 season and seems likely to be a stopgap option for some team in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd47-d968-a19b-ddf775740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Colton Pouncy believes that new OC Drew Petzing’s scheme could help make Sam LaPorta “an even bigger priority in the passing game.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd53-d968-a19b-ddf31ada0000</link>
      <description>Specifically, Petzing ran with much heavier personnel than the Lions are used to seeing and have run a lot of 13-personnel (three tight ends, one running back) since 2023. We doubt the Lions will go quite that big quite that often — that means one of Jameson Williams or Amon-Ra St. Brown is off the field — but we do think that Trey McBride’s success under Petzing generally augurs well for LaPorta in 2026. Of course, given that LaPorta (back) seems questionable for training camp after surgery, we don’t exactly know that the Lions will be able to pull this off. LaPorta seems like a boom-bust pick in Best Ball drafts from where we sit in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd53-d968-a19b-ddf31ada0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots owner Robert Kraft said the NFL wants to push to go to 18 games.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd5b-d35e-a1bf-dddb7c070000</link>
      <description>Not that this qualifies as “surprising,” but Kraft out-and-out said as much in an appearance on a Boston radio show. He also noted that owners were planning to “push like the Dickens” to make “so that every team every year will play one game overseas.” Kraft concluded by saying “as long as we can keep growing revenue we can keep long-term labor peace.” The current NFL CBA extends through the 2030 season, so we won’t have to spend too much time on this in the near future, but the specter of 18 games will continue to hover over labor negotiations as we hit the end of the decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd5b-d35e-a1bf-dddb7c070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel informed the Browns he’s withdrawing from their head coaching search.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd8a-d35e-a1bf-ddcae0040000</link>
      <description>McDaniel, who is no sure-fire shot to get a head-coaching job though he’s still a candidate with the Ravens and Raiders, is interviewing for the Chargers offensive coordinator job today. It doesn’t look great for the Browns that they couldn’t convince McDaniel to come in for a second interview given the fact that he may be looking at settling into an offensive coordinator spot. Still on the Browns list for second interviews are: Jaguars OC Grant Udinski, Rams passing-game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase, former Ravens OC Todd Monken and Chargers DC Jesse Minter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-dd8a-d35e-a1bf-ddcae0040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Falcons interviewed Cardinals pass game coordinator Drew Terrell for their open offensive coordinator position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddb0-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd8560000</link>
      <description>Terrell worked under new Lions offensive coordinator Drew Petzing in Arizona and is now interviewing at other spots with most of the coaching staff on the Cardinals experiencing turnover this offseason. The 34-year-old already interviewed with the Commanders and Chargers for their offensive coordinator roles this offseason and wrapped up another interview with the Falcons. Atlanta just completed hiring Kevin Stefanski as head coach and is now looking to round out the rest of the staff. Terrell may not call plays under Stefanski but his experience as pass game coordinator for Kyler Murray and Jacoby Brissett may be valued for the Falcons’ next starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddb0-dc7a-af9b-dfbfd8560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Ravens are blocking special teams coordinator Chris Horton from accepting a lateral position with another team.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddd2-d35e-a1bf-ddd26e170000</link>
      <description>Horton has been the Ravens’ special teams coordinator for the past six seasons and the team would like to have the option of retaining him under the impending head coaching hire. He can only leave for roles that are promotions from his current job. Garafolo reports “Assistant Anthony Levine Sr. and senior ST coach Randy Brown might also be retained, pending the new HC hire.” As Baltimore gets closer to a head coaching hire, decisions are being made about the surrounding staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddd2-d35e-a1bf-ddd26e170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Networks’ Mike Garafolo reports the Packers will interview former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddf9-dc7a-af9b-dfffd4e70000</link>
      <description>Gannon let go by the Cardinals after three underwhelming seasons as head coach. He previously spent two seasons as the Eagles’ defensive coordinator, making the Super Bowl in that time. The Cowboys have already interviewed Gannon, who will talk to Green Bay for the potential to work with Micah Parsons and the Packer defense. With Jeff Hafley leaving to coach the Dolphins, the Packers have a vacancy that could be filled by Gannon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-ddf9-dc7a-af9b-dfffd4e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel is “expected to become” the Chargers’ new offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de4a-dc7a-af9b-dfff82cb0000</link>
      <description>The Chargers have won the Mike McDaniel sweepstakes, expecting to hire the former Dolphins head coach to their open offensive coordinator role. Several teams were in on the 42-year-old, who was interviewing for both head coaching and offensive coordinator roles. According to Schefter, McDaniel is informing teams they are out and staying in Los Angeles for the evening with the expectation he is the next Chargers’ offensive coordinator. For fantasy purposes, we are in for a faster-paced offense under Justin Herbert. Omarion Hampton is in line for more opportunity in the passing game while the wide receiver room gets better opportunities in McDaniel’s offense when compared to former offensive coordinator Greg Roman’s passing game concepts. Fantasy managers can expect to be more bullish on Herbert and the Chargers offense for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de4a-dc7a-af9b-dfff82cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers beat writer Mark Kaboly reports the Falcons will interview Steelers assistant general manager Andy Weidl for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de9f-d968-a19b-deff8d2a0000</link>
      <description>Weidl spent the last four seasons as the Steelers’ assistant general manager. According to Kaboly, he “is a well-respected personnel evaluator around league circles.” Having spent 27 years in the NFL, Weidl brings experience to a Falcons front office led by President of Football Matt Ryan. The Falcons will interview Weidl for general manager after the team hired Kevin Stefanski as its new head coach. With that role filled, the general manager candidate interviews will come quicker for a potential hire soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-de9f-d968-a19b-deff8d2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Falcons are interviewing Buccaneers wide receivers coach Bryan McClendon for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-deb4-d56e-afff-fefcc0370000</link>
      <description>McClendon has been with the Bucs for the past two seasons, helping develop the likes of Jalen McMillan and Emeka Egbuka in the wide receiver room, alongside vets Mike Evans and Chris Godwin. The Falcons are conducting offensive coordinator interviews under new head coach Kevin Stefanski. McClendon will interview with the chance to develop Drake London and Bijan Robinson’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-deb4-d56e-afff-fefcc0370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
