<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate said he is only planning to run the 40-yard dash at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</link>
      <description>Tate is widely believed to be the top receiver in this year’s class and has confirmed he will run on Saturday when the receivers, quarterbacks, and running backs get their chance to shine. Tate caught 51 passes for 875 yards and nine touchdowns last season while averaging 17.2 YPR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC WR Makai Lemon will not run the 40-yard dash at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f5a-dbf6-abdd-ff5b84b10000</link>
      <description>Lemon will participate in the gauntlet and run routes, but will skip out on the 40 and all testing drills. The USC product caught 79 passes for 1,156 yards and 11 touchdowns last season and has played 65.6 percent of his snaps from the slot, per TruMedia. Lemon is expected to hear is name called in the first round of the draft and has drawn comparisons to fellow Trojan Amon-Ra St. Brown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f5a-dbf6-abdd-ff5b84b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports the Panthers have given DT A’Shawn Permission to seek a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f7b-d89c-a1be-bfff72e80000</link>
      <description>As Person points out, this was expected. Robinson is considered to be a trade/cut candidate, which would free up $10.5 million for the Panthers. The veteran lineman who will be 31 next season continues to play at a high level. Robinson totaled 65 tackles, three TFLs, and 2.5 sacks last season, and had 80 tackles, eight TFLs, and 5.5 sacks in 2024. With just one year left on his current deal, Robinson could likely be acquired for a late Day 3 pick, but given the possibility of a release, teams may just wait until he hits the open market before attempting to acquire him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f7b-d89c-a1be-bfff72e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports the Cowboys will officially place the franchise tag on George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fa1-d89c-a1be-bfff77c10000</link>
      <description>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones hinted at tagging Pickens earlier this week but didn’t entirely commit to the idea, despite things clearly heading in that direction. Now, according to Archer, the Cowboys will tag Pickens on Friday, placing him under team control through the 2026 season. While it’s possible the Cowboys will attempt to sign Pickens to a long-term extension later this offseason, they could also look to deal him for draft pick compensation in the coming weeks or force him to play out the year on the tag, which will guarantee him just over $28 million this season. Pickens finally showed his fully potential in 2025 after being traded to the Cowboys. He posted career highs in receptions (93), receiving yards (1,429), and receiving touchdowns (9), while looking every bit like a true No. 1 receiver despite playing opposite CeeDee Lamb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fa1-d89c-a1be-bfff77c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports the Giants are “seriously looking at some of the top RBs” in the draft and free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fc3-d042-afbc-ffd385ab0000</link>
      <description>Raanan reports players like Travis Etienne, Jeremiyah Love, and Kenneth Walker are among the players the Giants are reportedly interested in, while adding “there seems to be a clear focus on becoming a more physical run-heavy team.” The Giants saw last year’s rookie, Cam Skattebo, run for 101-410-5 in eight games before he suffered a season-ending ankle injury, but the team is hopeful he’ll be cleared in time for training camp. Still, the talent behind Skattebo is thin, but any big name-addition in the draft or free agency would undoubtedly limit the fantasy upside of both players in 2026. The Giants currently hold the No. 5 overall pick, but are up against a tight cap with just over $3.3 million currently available, per OverTheCap. They’ll have some work to do if they hope to land a big-name back in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fc3-d042-afbc-ffd385ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana QB Fernando Mendoza said he had a “fantastic meeting” with the Raiders at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9ff5-d629-a1bc-bffd66ca0000</link>
      <description>Mendoza also referred to newly minted head coach Klint Kubiak and his staff as a “football savvy” bunch. The 2025 Heisman Trophy winner and national champion is widely believed to heard his name called by the Raiders, who currently hold the No. 1 overall pick in this year’s draft. As far as quarterback is concerned, Mendoza isn’t facing much competition for the overall QB1 of the class, with Alabama’s Ty Simpson being viewed as a fringe first-round talent at best by most scouts and analysts. Mendoza will likely meet with other teams throughout the combine, but barring an unexpected development, he remains a virtual lock to join the Raiders come April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9ff5-d629-a1bc-bffd66ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall reports Tyler Allgeier “will be seeking a contract in the neighborhood of three-years, $22 million” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fff-d042-afbc-ffff96b70000</link>
      <description>Kendall reported earlier this month that it would be “hard to imagine” Allgeier returning to the Falcons in 2026. With that kind of money, it’s easy to understand why. The former fifth-round back is seeking starting RB money, and should have plenty of suitors after impressing during his first four years in the league. Allgeier rushed 210 times for 1,035 yards and three touchdowns as a rookie before being replaced by Bijan Robinson in 2023. He’s averaged over 4.0 YPC just once in his last three seasons, but has forced a missed tackle on 21.7 percent of his carries over that span while also converting nine of his 22 carries inside the opponent’s five-yard line into scores. While he doesn’t offer much as a pass-catcher, Allgeier can help several teams in need of an early down back who can pick up short yards and punch the ball in down near the goal line. He should have plenty of suitors when free agency opens next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fff-d042-afbc-ffff96b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall says we should “expect Kyle Pitts to play this season on the franchise tag.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a00a-d629-a1bc-b01f7aee0000</link>
      <description>The Falcons officially placed the franchise tag on Pitts on Tuesday. While the two sides could still come to terms on a long-term deal to keep Pitts in Atlanta beyond next season, Kendall says “the vibe Atlanta is giving when it comes to Pitts” suggests a new deal is unlikely. Pitts caught 88 passes for 928 yards and five touchdowns last season, turning in what was arguably the best year of his five-year career. Still only 25 years old, it’s fair to assume the Falcons will want to keep Pitts under contract for years to come if he can replicate that success again next season. That said, with a new regime in place and head coach Kevin Stefanski still getting a sense of what he can do with his roster, it’s understandable if the team would prefer to see how Pitts performs in 2026 before making any long-term commitments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a00a-d629-a1bc-b01f7aee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Broncos placed a second-round tender on CB Ja’Quan McMillian.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a011-d629-a1bc-b01d03bc0000</link>
      <description>McMillian is a restricted free agent who has quickly turned into one of the team’s top defenders after making the roster as a UDFA in 2022. The Broncos’ decision to tender McMillian means he can negotiate with other teams in free agency, but the Broncos have the right of refusal to match any offer he receives. Should the Broncos match that offer, McMillian would remain with the team, however, if they let him walk, the Broncos would receive a second-round pick as compensation. McMillian has started 16 of the 51 games he’s appeared in for the Broncos, but has played on over 700 defensive snaps each of the last two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a011-d629-a1bc-b01d03bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL announced the league salary cap will increase to $301.2 million for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a018-d629-a1bc-b01d5de30000</link>
      <description>Each club will get an additional $22 million in spending money for this season as a result of the increase. This marks the first time in league history that the cap has gone beyond $300 million, and it is a massive increase from the $208.2 million the league hit in 2022 after cutting back on cap space due to COVID in 2020/2021. This increase should put teams like the Titans, Raiders, Jets, and Chargers over $100 million in available cap space when free agency kicks off next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-a018-d629-a1bc-b01d5de30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
