<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 22:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins caught 7-of-7 targets for 89 yards in the Patriots’ Week 8 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226c-d245-adfb-b77fc1990000</link>
      <description>Hollins was the Patriots’ leading receiver on the day, getting involved early with 21-yard reception in the second quarter. He continued to get downfield usage throughout the game, catching all seven of his targets for 89 yards. Hollins saw the second-most snaps among Pats wideouts, but is behind Diggs and Boutte in the pecking order for the season. He is worth a look in the deepest of leagues, but the breakout is more likely an outlier than a long-term indicator of fantasy success.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226c-d245-adfb-b77fc1990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco completed 21-of-34 passes for 223 yards and two touchdowns in the Bengals’ 39-38, Week 8 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2268-deb1-a39b-236e49a40000</link>
      <description>Flacco also punched in a one-yard rushing touchdown, his first since 2017. The veteran passer didn;t light the Jets up, but he kept the chains moving, scored three times, and didn’t turn the ball over once. With 38 points on the board, Flacco did his job, the defense simply couldn’t stop Justin Fields and company. Flacco briefly left the game and went to the locker room in the fourth quarter, seemingly dealing with a shoulder injury. He didn’t miss any snaps on offense and threw a few passes on the team’s final drive, a failed comeback bid. Assuming the injury doesn’t linger beyond this week, Flacco will remain a solid QB2 option when he takes on the Bengals in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2268-deb1-a39b-236e49a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed four times for 43 yards in the Ravens’ Week 8 win over the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226b-deb1-a39b-236f35f90000</link>
      <description>The speedy Mitchell saw four carries to Justice Hill’s one. Mitchell ripped off a 25-yard gain on his first carry of the game and later ran for a 13-yard gain in the fourth quarter to help set up a Derrick Henry touchdown run to put the game out of reach. It was the most productive game of the season for Mitchell, who entered the day with three carries for eight yards. The explosive third-year back could see more work after an impressive showing in a small sample size, but fantasy managers shouldn’t rush to start him in Week 9 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226b-deb1-a39b-236f35f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 1-of-1 targets for 44 yards in the Patriots’ Week 8 win over the Browns, adding two carries for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226f-d245-adfb-b77f7fc60000</link>
      <description>Douglas saw just three touches against the Browns, but converted his only target into a 44-yard reception. It came in the two-minute drill at the end of the first half, shaking his defensive back, making the catch, and falling in Browns territory. The shifty slot receiver is mostly off fantasy radars for Week 9 against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-226f-d245-adfb-b77f7fc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine rushed nine times for 96 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2271-d245-adfb-b77faad30000</link>
      <description>With one catch for six yards, Perine topped 100 yards from scrimmage for the first time since 2022. The Bengals rotated their backs in this game, giving Perine multiple red zone carries over Chase Brown. Perine’s touchdown, however, came from 32 yards out. Brown was still the lead back with 12 carries and three catches, but this was the most involved Perine has been all year. Perine will be a no-floor RB5 when the Bengals take on the Bears in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2271-d245-adfb-b77faad30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins caught 1-of-2 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2278-deb1-a39b-237eefdb0000</link>
      <description>With Ja’Marr Chase soaking up 19 targets, there wasn’t much receiving volume to go around for the rest of the wideouts. The good news for fantasy managers is that Higgins did as much damage as possible on his only catch of the day. He blew by the Jets’ secondary for an easy 44-yard score in the second quarter. Higgins had 18 targets in Joe Flacco’s first two starts with the Bengals. He should see more work in Week 9 versus the Bears, keeping him in the WR2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2278-deb1-a39b-237eefdb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson rushed three times for zero yards in the Browns’ Week 8 loss to the Patriots, adding five catches for 29 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2272-dab4-a3fb-bb728c2f0000</link>
      <description>Sampson got some run against the Patriots with Quinshon Judkins (shoulder) exiting in the third quarter. He took three carries for zero yards, but was heavily utilized in the passing game, catching 5-of-6 targets for 29 yards. The Browns are heading into a Week 9 bye, but Sampson is the Browns running back to roster if Judkins misses time. Jerome ford will still be involved, but isn’t as much of a ball-carrier as the two rookies in the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2272-dab4-a3fb-bb728c2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Fant caught all three of his targets for 41 yards in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss to the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-227d-d245-adfb-b77f16500000</link>
      <description>Fant hasn’t caught more than four passes during the Joe Flacco era, but he has at least three grabs in all three of Flacco’s starts. He also has 40 yards in back-to-back games. With Ja’Marr Chase dominating targets and Tee Higgins there to clean up any looks Chase doesn’t see, there isn’t much room for a third pass-catcher in this offense. Still, Fant has established a TE2 floor, albeit without much of a ceiling. He will sit at the back of the TE2 ranks for Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-227d-d245-adfb-b77f16500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin Jr. caught 6-of-8 targets for 62 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 8 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-227d-dab4-a3fb-bb7d5c910000</link>
      <description>Fannin was the Browns’ No. 1 pass-catcher on the day, similar to how he has operated the entire season. He was utilized on several underneath crossing routes and made chunk gains to keep Cleveland drives going. Dillon Gabriel found him wide open for the Browns’ first score of the day on an 18-yard toss in the first quarter. Fannin gets diverse usage in an otherwise-anemic Browns offense and holds low-end TE1 value coming out of the Browns’ Week 9 bye for Week 10 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-227d-dab4-a3fb-bb7d5c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed nine times for 25 yards in the Falcons’ Week 8 loss to the Dolphins, adding three catches for 23 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2280-deb1-a39b-238efd770000</link>
      <description>It was a nightmare game for Robinson from start to finish. He never threatened to hit a home run, topping out at a seven-yard carry. His lowlight of the day came on a fumble where he stumbled, his knee hit the ball, and it popped out of his hands for a turnover. Robinson finished the day by watching Tyler Allgeier score a short touchdown from the sidelines. It was, by all accounts, the worst game of Robinson’s season. Better days will be ahead for the star running back, especially with a weak Patriots defense on tap in Week 9. He remains at the top of the RB1 ranks despite the quiet Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2280-deb1-a39b-238efd770000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
