<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans scheduled an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a493-dc7a-af9b-efbfe0550000</link>
      <description>Yesterday, it was reported that the Lions had reached out to McDaniel regarding their offensive coordinator vacancy. The former Dolphins’ head coach now has the chance to make a lateral move over to the AFC South, though. McDaniel could make life easier for QB Cam Ward with his creative play designs. It is an interesting potential pairing. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that there “has been significant interest in McDaniel since Miami fired him.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a493-dc7a-af9b-efbfe0550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots C Garrett Bradbury (illness) is not on New England’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a498-d35e-a1bf-e5da75970000</link>
      <description>The Patriots didn’t let Bradbury practice on Wednesday or Thursday, but he went in full today. The Patriots should have their full starting offensive line ready to go for Sunday’s Wild Card showdown against the Chargers on NBC. Guard Jared Wilson (concussion) cleared protocol today and is not on the final injury report either.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a498-d35e-a1bf-e5da75970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars OL Cole Van Lanen (knee) is questionable to play in the Wild Card Round against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a49c-d35e-a1bf-e5de44930000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars signed Van Lanen to a three-year, $51 million extension last week. The versatile blocker has taken snaps at left tackle, left guard, right guard and right tackle, most recently lining up at left tackle in each of the Jaguars’ last five games. He sat out on Wednesday and Thursday before practicing in a limited capacity on Friday. We tentatively expect him to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a49c-d35e-a1bf-e5de44930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Jawhar Jordan (ankle) did not practice Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a49f-d56e-afff-e6ffb81a0000</link>
      <description>He looks incredibly unlikely to go based on the reporting that he suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 18. Nick Chubb will probably be a pure fill-in back on a few downs for the Texans behind Woody Marks on Monday night, making Marks a high-volume play for DFS or Playoff Best Ball purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a49f-d56e-afff-e6ffb81a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (illness) practiced fully on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a9-d56e-afff-e6e9425f0000</link>
      <description>Warren should be good to go for the Steelers’ Wild Card Round game against the Texans on Monday. The Texans field a top-tier defense, so having the backfield at full strength is helpful. Warren has been splitting work with RB Kenneth Gainwell and can be safely expected to continue doing so in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a9-d56e-afff-e6e9425f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee/ankle) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ae-d968-a19b-fcff5c5b0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall did not practice at any point this week. We’d characterize Pearsall as on the pessimistic side of questionable, though we’re sure the 49ers will give him every chance to get active in a must-win playoff game. The 49ers wideout has not played since aggravating his PCL sprain in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4ae-d968-a19b-fcff5c5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Jonnu Smith (glute) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-d56e-afff-e6ee0c5c0000</link>
      <description>Mid-week appearances typically indicate that a player suffered an injury in practice. With TE Darnell Washington (arm) sidelined, the Steelers’ tight end group is suddenly looking quite thin. Steelers TE Pat Freiermuth would warrant TE1 treatment if Smith is also sidelined on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4a6-d56e-afff-e6ee0c5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LT Trent Williams (hamstring) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card matchup against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b1-d35e-a1bf-e5f399b90000</link>
      <description>He got in a limited session on Thursday and was seen practicing again today. We’d be surprised if Williams didn’t go on Sunday, though it likely wouldn’t be at 100 percent. Austen Pleasants is the reserve tackle that’d be called on if Williams faced an in-game reaggravation of his injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b1-d35e-a1bf-e5f399b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers TE George Kittle (ankle) is not on San Francisco’s final Wild Card injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b3-d56e-afff-e6fb45f00000</link>
      <description>Kittle got in limited work on Wednesday and Thursday and was spotted practicing again on Friday. He did play against the Seahawks in Week 18 so it’s not much of a surprise that he’ll be ready here. Kittle’s output will be paramount as the 49ers try to find a non-Christian McCaffrey trick over the middle against a fierce Eagles defense. He should make for a top-of-line DFS or Playoff Best Ball play at TE this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b3-d56e-afff-e6fb45f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LB Dee Winters (ankle) is questionable for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</link>
      <description>Winters did not practice Wednesday or Thursday and was not seen by media on Friday. The 49ers will give him every hour he can to be healthy as he’s the main incumbent with a chance to play this week. If not, the 49ers will have to turn to Eric Kendricks, Garret Wallow, and possibly new signing Kyzir White in the middle against the Eagles. CB Renardo Green (foot) and DE Keion White (groin/hamstring) are also questionable for the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-a4b6-d56e-afff-e6fe38770000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
