<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams elevated RB Cody Schrader from the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202d-d332-a1fd-b63f21450000</link>
      <description>It’s an interesting development considering we rarely see Sean McVay teams hold four active backs on game day, a potential hint that the team could be primed to make rookie Jarquez Hunter a healthy inactive for the team’s Week 1 contest against the Texans. Schrader enters his second year in the league and was active on two occasions late last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-202d-d332-a1fd-b63f21450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai is off the injury report and will play in Week 1 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2050-db7b-a5dd-a054fe330000</link>
      <description>Fellow running back Roschon Johnon is listed as questionable after getting in a limited session Saturday, potentially paving the way for Monangai to serve as the primary change of pace option in his first professional appearance for the Bears. Joining Johnson as questionable for Monday Night Football are DB Jaylon Johnson and DB Josh Blackwell, while LB T.J. Edwards is listed as doubtful with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2050-db7b-a5dd-a054fe330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings S Harrison Smith (illness) is doubtful for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2066-d332-a1fd-b676a94c0000</link>
      <description>Smith was absent from practice Thursday but upgraded to a limited showing Friday, ultimately drawing the doubtful tag after missing practice Saturday. LT Christian Darrisaw is listed as questionable as he works his way back from a devastating knee injury suffered in Week 8 of the 2024 season, while both RB Zavier Scott and DT Elijah Williams have both been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2066-d332-a1fd-b676a94c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived QB Jake Haener and signed DE Fadil Diggs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-206d-de13-afdd-66ef66b60000</link>
      <description>Haener was the betting favorite to win the starting quarterback job for the Saints before they went with Spencer Rattler under center. He was released by the team as they trimmed down to 53, signed to the practice squad, and then re-signed to the active roster within a week before his eventual release. The team signed DE Fadil Diggs in a corresponding move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-206d-de13-afdd-66ef66b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports 49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) is likely to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2092-de13-afdd-66db97bf0000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey popped on the team’s injury report Thursday with a calf injury, something fantasy managers remember all too well prior to the 2024 season before the veteran back eventually missed the first half of the season. He would then sit out Friday’s session entirely. “Barring a setback, it’s likely he’ll go,” Rapoport stated on X Saturday amidst mounting rumors. McCaffrey continues to insist he is fine and will suit up, stating Friday the “feels great” and that everything has been “blown out of proportion.” Even so, fantasy managers will want to monitor his situation closely and potentially line up alternative plans considering the 49ers don’t kick off until the afternoon in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2092-de13-afdd-66db97bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Patriots OT Will Campbell is “on track” to play in Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2098-dbe3-a9bb-30db9a1e0000</link>
      <description>Campbell was added to the team’s injury report Thursday with an ankle injury but signs are now pointing to him suiting up in Week 1 against the Raiders. The No. 4 overall pick in the 2025 NFL Draft is set to make an immediate impact protecting quarterback Drake Maye’s blindside as part of a retooled offensive line in New England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2098-dbe3-a9bb-30db9a1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Buccaneers NT Vita Vea (foot) is likely to play in Week 1 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-20a6-d332-a1fd-b6b6c7d50000</link>
      <description>Vea has been a stalwart defender throughout his career and is a big reason for the teams continued successes against the run, making his likely presence when the Buccaneers take the field in Week 1 against the Falcons a significant boost to their defense. It seems a full practice Friday was enough for coaches to confidently start Vea to begin the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-20a6-d332-a1fd-b6b6c7d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter Travis Hunter is expected to serve as an “every-down wide receiver and situational corner” in Sunday’s season opener against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ec-de13-afdd-46eff09d0000</link>
      <description>It has been trending this way for some time, though Schefter reports things could change going forward. “It doesn’t mean that arrangement will hold in Week 2 or further into the season, according to sources,” Schefter reported. “The Jaguars plan to mix up Hunter’s usage throughout the course of the season, sources said, but they believe there will be some weeks when the rookie can and will be deployed as a full-time wide receiver and cornerback.” The truth is that not even the Jags might not know what is ultimately in store, but it’s been clear for some time Hunter was going to see enough offensive snaps and routes to merit immediate WR3 consideration in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ec-de13-afdd-46eff09d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Steelers DL Cameron Heyward has agreed to a reworked contract ahead of Sunday’s opener against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-21d6-de13-afdd-67df77f90000</link>
      <description>Heyward had been playing coy on whether or not he would suit up Sunday. Now he will after the Steelers added “over $3 million in incentives this year.” The 36-year-old could now max out at $18 million this season. Despite his advanced age, Heyward has remained one of the very best defensive lineman in all of football. The Steelers need him more than ever as this era of Pittsburgh football continues to sunset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-21d6-de13-afdd-67df77f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed WR Jameson Williams to a three-year, $83 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-223c-dbe3-a9bb-327fcc9f0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Schultz reports the deal includes a whopping $67 million guaranteed. That’s a monster sum considering Williams’ mixed track record and seeming inherent risk, but it’s also the Lions acknowledging the inevitable. Williams had two years remaining on his rookie deal, but the team just didn’t want any drama. It’s an approach a team like the Cowboys could learn from, for instance. A 2024 breakout star, the Lions’ coaching staff has talked up the possibility Williams further breaks out in 2025. A game-breaker at every level of the field, Williams is pushing for weekly WR2 value and could force his way up the ranks as the season goes. Still somehow only 24 years old, Williams could be a fantasy stud for years to come if he can manage to avoid further suspensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-223c-dbe3-a9bb-327fcc9f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
