<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe/shoulder) will not play in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d2a-dfde-a1bd-7faf8f080000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also ruled out Jauan Jennings with ankle and shoulder injuries. Both players were reported to be out for Week 3 earlier today, so this isn’t exactly breaking news. Still, the 49ers aren’t even giving themselves the chance to do anything funny with their inactives. Mac Jones will start for the 49ers with Ricky Pearsall operating as his No. 1 receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d2a-dfde-a1bd-7faf8f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Johnson is questionable to return against the Rams in Week 3 with a neck injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d53-d1b3-a5dd-6d73824e0000</link>
      <description>Johnson is being worked on in the medical tent. The 35-year-old future Hall of Famer has been replaced on the right side by Matt Pryor. This would be a massive loss for the Eagles if Johnson was to miss significant time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d53-d1b3-a5dd-6d73824e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (rib) left Houston’s Week 3 game against the Jaguars and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d63-d6a5-adff-ffe754800000</link>
      <description>He’s been playing through some sort of injury for most of the season. Stingley’s absence should help the Jags passing attack today. Stingley had been in the blue medical tent for some of the first few drives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d63-d6a5-adff-ffe754800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (head) exited in the first quarter of Week 3’s game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d64-dfde-a1bd-7fedfb300000</link>
      <description>Mayer took a hard shot to the head late in the first quarter while playing on the punt coverage unit and remained down for several minutes. The third-year tight end waved off the cart and walked to the sideline with assistance from trainers, but it wouldn’t be surprising if his day was done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d64-dfde-a1bd-7fedfb300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jaxon Smith-Njigba (illness) is active for Week 3 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d88-dfde-a1bd-7f8d28590000</link>
      <description>The Seahawks’ target-hog is good to go after being added to the injury report on Saturday. He should be started as a WR1, per usual. The Seahawks declared RB Zach Charbonnet (foot), S Julian Love (hamstring), S Nick Emmanwori (ankle), CB Devon Witherspoon (knee), OG Mason Richman, LB Connor O’Toole and TE Nick Kallerup inactive for Week 3 against the Saints. Kenneth Walker III will handle a significant workload with Charbonnet sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d88-dfde-a1bd-7f8d28590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared RT Taliese Fuaga, EDGE Chase Young, OG Dillon Radunz, WR Devaughn Vele, WR Trey Palmer, RB Devin Neal and DT Khristian Boyd inactive for Week 3 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63ed-d1b3-a5dd-63fd928f0000</link>
      <description>Fuaga played through his knee injury last week but he picked up a back injury in-game and was unable to practice at all this week. Young (calf) has yet to suit up in 2025. Saints LG Trevor Penning (toe) was limited all week, but New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill and Mike Triplett both expressed skepticism as to whether he is healthy enough to start against the Seahawks today, so the offensive line may remain worryingly short-staffed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-63ed-d1b3-a5dd-63fd928f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders ruled out Michael Mayer (concussion) for the remainder of Week 3’s game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9d-d6a5-adff-ffdd6c0f0000</link>
      <description>Mayer exited in the first quarter with a head injury and was diagnosed with a concussion. Mayer did not log a catch in Week 3’s game, and will need to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to appear in Week 4 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9d-d6a5-adff-ffdd6c0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR Dyami Brown (shoulder) left Jacksonville’s Week 3 game against the Texans and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9d-d6a5-adff-ffddd1d50000</link>
      <description>Brown got drilled by Azeez Al-Shaair on a screen catch and was planted into the turf hard. He spent some time in the medical tent before halftime. Brown had two catches on three targets for seven yards before leaving in what has been a rock fight in Jacksonville up to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9d-d6a5-adff-ffddd1d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers declared WR Jauan Jennings, QB Brock Purdy, WR Jordan Watkins, RB Jordan James, DT Jordan Jefferson, and LB Nick Martin inactive for Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9f-dfde-a1bd-7f9f09de0000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as Jennings and Purdy were both ruled out by the earlier today. Purdy is eying a Week 4 return while Jennings’ timeline is less certain. Mac Jones will start versus the Cardinals with Adrian Martinez backing him up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d9f-dfde-a1bd-7f9f09de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quincy Williams is out for the remainder of Week 3 against the Bucs with a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da1-dfde-a1bd-7fad921e0000</link>
      <description>Williams injured his shoulder near the end of the second half and was ruled out for the remainder of the game. No word yet on the severity of the injury, but his loss is a big blow for the Jets defense in the middle of the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6da1-dfde-a1bd-7fad921e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
