<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 22:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c207-d6c4-abfb-d60778d00000</link>
      <description>Sitting out on a Wednesday makes sense, given the nature of Rodgers’ injury, but one assumes he will return on Thursday if he is to play on Sunday, as expected. Rodgers’ fractured wrist complicates everything from receiving the snap to bracing for a fall. Hopefully, rest a rehab gets the injury in a stable place before long. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c207-d6c4-abfb-d60778d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams claimed CB Derion Kendrick, formerly of the Seahawks, off waivers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c20c-d6c4-abfb-d60fca290000</link>
      <description>Kendrick spent the 2022-2024 seasons with the Rams after they drafted him in the 2022 NFL Draft’s second round. He broke out in 2023, but dealt with off-field issues that same year. He missed the 2024 season after tearing an ACL during training camp. He was waived in late August and later signed on with the Seahawks. He appeared in five games with them this season, forcing three incompletions and recording two interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c20c-d6c4-abfb-d60fca290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield (left shoulder) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c212-d90e-a9da-df1f96e80000</link>
      <description>This is hardly surprising. Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles told reporters earlier today that backup QB Teddy Bridgewater will get most of the first-team reps this week. Thus far, he has taken all of them. Mayfield has a chance to suit up and play through the pain against the Cardinals, though it would be nice to see him resume practicing soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c212-d90e-a9da-df1f96e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (toe) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c222-d82c-a79a-f3b6cd1a0000</link>
      <description>Jackson missed Monday’s practice but was back in action for the following two sessions. He could be taking off the first practice of the week for the remainder of the season as the Ravens try to keep him fresh. Jackson’s rushing numbers are down this year and his fantasy numbers have fallen as a result. A date with the horrific Bengals defense should get him on track, at least for one week. Jackson remains near the top of the QB1 ranks for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c222-d82c-a79a-f3b6cd1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c225-d6c4-abfb-d6271f920000</link>
      <description>The team is managing Godwin’s reps ahead of what is expected to be a larger workload come Sunday. Godwin totaled just four targets while playing 25-of-70 offensive snaps in Week 12. Both figures should theoretically rise this weekend against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c225-d6c4-abfb-d6271f920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c225-d82c-a79a-f3b5bfcb0000</link>
      <description>Bateman missed two weeks with what was reported to be a high-ankle sprain. He was limited in practice earlier in the week but was upgraded to a full session today. Lamar Jackson’s primary field-stretcher is good to go for a potential shootout with the Bengals. Bateman will return to the WR5 ranks this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c225-d82c-a79a-f3b5bfcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) is practicing fully for Week 13 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c215-d6c4-abfb-d61770350000</link>
      <description>Irving is expected to be eased into action on Sunday, and should be treated as a volatile RB2. The Buccaneers’ backfield is fairly deep, with RB Sean Tucker and RB Rachaad White in the fold. Irving’s early-week full participation is a great sign regarding his physical health, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c215-d6c4-abfb-d61770350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Hill (neck) will not play in Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c228-d82c-a79a-f3bc22c70000</link>
      <description>Hill was a mid-week addition to the injury report, going from a normal practice on Monday to a DNP because of the neck issue on Tuesday. He previously missed time with a toe injury. Keaton Mitchell will continue to operate as the change-of-pace back this week. Mitchell is worth a look in large-field DFS contests for the Thanksgiving slate, but redraft managers can leave him on the waiver wire for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c228-d82c-a79a-f3bc22c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chis Olave (back) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c22a-d6c4-abfb-d62bbce00000</link>
      <description>A limited session to open the week is nothing new for Olave. The bigger concern is that he left practice earlier, meaning he suffered the injury during today’s session. It could have been a precautionary measure from the Saints, but there is at least a chance this issue will force him to miss time. Devaughn Vele is the next man up for the Saints. Tight end Juwan Johnson would also see more work if Olave misses any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c22a-d6c4-abfb-d62bbce00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c229-db57-afda-d63b575e0000</link>
      <description>Benson remained limited in all three practices last week. His continued participation is good. He does not appear to have suffered any setbacks. Yet, his failure to progress to full participation keeps him firmly in the questionable camp to begin the week. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c229-db57-afda-d63b575e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
