<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Najee Harris rushed one time for five yards in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs, adding one catch for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d2e-de13-afdd-5fef8d7f0000</link>
      <description>Harris was a distant RB2 behind first-round rookie Omarion Hampton and was completely uninvolved in the offensive game plan. Hampton carried the rock 15 times and was the team’s primary back on passing downs, converting that role into a pair of receptions. Harris missed all of training camp with an eye injury that looked like it would likely force him to miss action during the regular season at one point. The lack of a normal ramp-up period and little time to learn the playbook likely affected his Week 1 role, but Hampton isn’t going anywhere anytime soon. Fantasy managers can cut ties with Harris on the next run of waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d2e-de13-afdd-5fef8d7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Conklin caught both of his targets for 50 yards in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d32-d332-a1fd-9f36a5f20000</link>
      <description>The free agent addition split time with Will Dissly in his LA debut. Though Conklin technically led the team’s tight ends in all receiving categories, a weekly diet of two targets isn’t enough to put him on the streaming radar for fantasy purposes. Conklin also coughed up a fumble on a long gain that Ladd McConkey punched out of bounds, resulting in a penalty that negated some of the yards Conklin had just picked up. Neither LA tight end is in the fantasy picture for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d32-d332-a1fd-9f36a5f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladd McConkey caught 6-of-9 targets for 74 yards in the Chargers’ Week 1 win over the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d35-db7b-a5dd-bd354ddf0000</link>
      <description>McConkey left Week 1 with a healthy target share of 26 percent, but it was Keenan Allen who led the way with 10 looks from Justin Herbert. Allen was signed after Mike Williams retired during the summer. He immediately rekindled his connection with Herbert, acting as a safety valve option for his former and current teammate. McConkey, in turn, was tasked with more downfield work. He nearly connected with Herbert on a potential long touchdown, but the throw sailed just over his hands, leaving the second-year wideout with a solid but not elite fantasy outing. McConkey should still be treated as the Chargers’ top receiver, but a resurgence from Allen could prevent McConkey from finding another gear in his second season. He will be on the WR1/2 borderline for his Week 2 date with the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d35-db7b-a5dd-bd354ddf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed five times for 25 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers, adding two receptions for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d3e-d332-a1fd-9f3eb9480000</link>
      <description>Fantasy managers who tuned in to the Chiefs’ opener to see Pacheco pull away as the team’s RB1 after a rocky 2024 campaign were sorely disappointed from the jump. Pacheco split work evenly with Kareem Hunt throughout the Week 1 loss. Hunt matched Pacheco’s carry and reception totals while taking the field over Pacheco in crucial situations. Hunt was the team’s top option on passing downs and in short-yardage situations. That makes Pacheco a between-the-20s option on a team that has little interest in running the football. Pacheco will likely out-play Hunt in the long run, giving him a shot at picking up more work as the season wears on. He will be stuck in the RB3/4 range until that happens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d3e-d332-a1fd-9f3eb9480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed five times for 16 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers, adding two catches for 10 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d44-db7b-a5dd-bd449fd90000</link>
      <description>Isiah Pacheco got the start versus the Chargers but quickly gave way to Hunt in critical situations. Hunt operated as the team’s primary short-yardage back but also subbed in for the majority of the third downs. He finished the day with exactly as many catches and carries as Pacheco. Hunt doesn’t have any big-play potential and isn’t a special pass-catcher, but he could fall in the end zone a few times this year. He will look to do so in a tough matchup versus the Eagles next week, making him an RB4 for the Super Bowl rematch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d44-db7b-a5dd-bd449fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 10-of-16 targets for 99 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d4b-d332-a1fd-9f7f642a0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs entered this game without Rashee Rice and lost Xavier Worthy on the first drive to a shoulder injury. That thrust Brown into the WR1 role for the better part of four quarters, though the results were mixed at best. Brown got off to a rocky start with an early drop and was used mostly as a check-down option until late in the game. Just when it seemed like the contest was out of reach, Patrick Mahomes uncorked a bomb to Brown on the run for a 49-yard game. The move put Kansas City deep into the red zone but only resulted in a field goal. Even that explosive play wasn’t enough to save Brown from a poor efficiency outing. There have been 66 instances of a wide receiver seeing at least 16 targets over the past five seasons. Brown is just the seventh to be held under 100 yards on that level of volume. Brown will be a PPR-merchant WR2 if Worthy remains out for Week 2, but his ceiling is severely capped as he stares down a rematch with the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d4b-d332-a1fd-9f7f642a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JuJu Smith-Schuster caught all five of his targets for 55 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d52-d332-a1fd-9f76242e0000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs lost Xavier Worthy to a shoulder injury early in this game and Rashee Rice is serving a six-week suspension, elevating Smith-Schuster to a starting role. He was open for the occasional check-down from Patrick Mahomes but wasn’t overly involved in the game plan. Hollywood Brown led the team with a staggering 16 targets. JuJu’s five looks were second-most on the squad. Smith-Schuster will have WR6 fantasy value if Worthy is sidelined for Week 2 versus the Eagles, though most fantasy managers won’t need to dig that deep this early in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d52-d332-a1fd-9f76242e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 2-of-4 targets for 41 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d55-de13-afdd-5fdfa0db0000</link>
      <description>A strong training camp showing earned Thornton a roster spot in Kansas City and he may be needed even more than expected over the next few weeks. Rashee Rice is suspended for five more games and Xavier Worthy left this game with a shoulder injury. He took a hard hit from Travis Kelce on a crossing route and was quickly ruled out after a trip to the locker room. Patrick Mahomes overthrew Thornton on a deep shot early in the game but got on the same page as his deep threat late in the second quarter. That was his final catch of the game. Thornton has taken over the Justin Watson/Marquez Valdes Scantling role in the offense, but that’s not one worth chasing for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d55-de13-afdd-5fdfa0db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 2-of-4 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 1 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d5b-de13-afdd-5fdb59640000</link>
      <description>Kelce’s night got off to a rocky start when he collided with Xavier Worthy on a shallow route, knocking the diminutive wide receiver out of the game with a shoulder injury. With Worthy out and Rashee Rice on the sidelines for the first week of his six-game suspension, the Chiefs desperately needed someone to step up. Despite this, Kelce was nowhere to be found, catching one pass for 10 yards through three quarters. He did, however, redeem himself by slipping behind the LA defense for a 37-yard touchdown early in the fourth quarter. It was his final catch of the night. The touchdown saved his outing for fantasy managers, but being out-targeted 16-4 by Hollywood Brown is a stunning indictment of his ability to earn opportunities at the age of 35. Kelce may hang around the TE1 ranks out of sheer necessity for a few weeks, but one of Worthy or Rice could send him to the TE2 range later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1d5b-de13-afdd-5fdb59640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns signed RB Quinshon Judkins to fully guaranteed deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f33-de13-afdd-5ffb7de50000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Judkins received a fully guaranteed deal. Now all draft picks are under contract for the season. Rapoport also adds that Judkins isn’t expected to play for the Browns in Week 1 against the Bengals, but could play in Week 2 against the Ravens. Expect Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford to handle the running back duties for the Browns until Judkins hits the field. While no charges remain in Judkins’ legal situation, the NFL investigation is ongoing. In the meantime, the Browns will receive a roster exemption that can last up to two weeks for Judkins and won’t have to make an additional roster move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1f33-de13-afdd-5ffb7de50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
