<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed six times for 30 yards and returned one kickoff for 22 yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 1 game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a9-d05a-adda-bfab7f440000</link>
      <description>Monangai had the first two drives all to himself and played all but one snap on the third. He rotated in and out through drives four and five. Monangai ran well, forcing two missed tackles on the ground. The No. 3 running back role behind D’Andre Swift and Roschon Johnson (foot) appears to be his.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a9-d05a-adda-bfab7f440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder said Colts CB Kenny Moore II “seemed to be in pretty intense pain” after suffering an apparent knee injury on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95b4-d90d-a5bd-b7ff97bc0000</link>
      <description>That’s bad. Moore is the secondary’s lynchpin defender, lining up on the perimeter in base formations and covering the slot in nickel. Losing him for an extended time period would make the Colts’ secondary one to target in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95b4-d90d-a5bd-b7ff97bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce was carted away from Colts practice after suffering an apparent leg injury on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-8b0e-df63-a199-db2f73760000</link>
      <description>FOX59’s Mike Chappell reports Pierce left practice early for an examination in the locker room. He then returned to the field and “did some agility work,” before limping off and being taken back to the locker room by cart. Pierce’s injury coincides with Adonai Mitchell making “strides” in his development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-8b0e-df63-a199-db2f73760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets activated Jermaine Johnson (Achilles) from the active/physically unable to perform list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95d2-d90d-a5bd-b7dbad140000</link>
      <description>Johnson appears to be on track for Week 1, as he recovers from a season-ending Achilles tendon rupture suffered in Week 2 last year. The Jets were encouraged by Johnson’s recovery this offseason and activated his fifth-year option in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95d2-d90d-a5bd-b7dbad140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said S Kyle Hamilton and B Jaire Alexander are “OK” after missing practice with undisclosed injuries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ca-d90d-a5bd-b7db345e0000</link>
      <description>Hamilton has been sidelined for a few days and Alexander missed time in late July after having his knee drained. Hamilton typically soldiers through in-season injuries and Alexander has a long history of knee issues. It’s a situation to watch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ca-d90d-a5bd-b7db345e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived LB Baylon Spector (calf) with an injury settlement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95e2-d45c-a7fc-97fa41ac0000</link>
      <description>Spector dealt with injuries in both calves this year. It’s a tough break for a player coming off a season in which he tallied multiple career highs. Spector will likely be invited to try out for backup linebacker/special teams roles once he is in good health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95e2-d45c-a7fc-97fa41ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shane Steichen said Daniel Jones will play “a few series” as the Colts’ preseason Week 2 starter but Anthony Richardson will get the “bulk of the work” in the first half.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95c9-d45c-a7fc-97dbe9ae0000</link>
      <description>Steichen emphasized “consistency,” particularly in joint practices this week, as the key factor in determining who wins the starting role. This can be read as a call to Richardson specifically, who possesses immense talent but continues to be plagued by injuries and errors. If he can simply execute the offense as asked in the coming weeks, the job is likely his.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95c9-d45c-a7fc-97dbe9ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed LB Duke Riley, formerly of the Dolphins, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ec-df63-a199-ddef17170000</link>
      <description>Riley served as a defensive backup in his age-30 season last year, totaling just three tackles along the way. He can still contribute on special teams, though, having just tied his career-best qualifying tackles tally with six.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95ec-df63-a199-ddef17170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tua Tagovailoa completed 5-of-6 passes for 27 yards in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-960f-df63-a199-df2f85ee0000</link>
      <description>Tagovailoa played one drive, and kept things very close to the line of scrimmage via a 4.7-yard aDOT. He averaged just 4.5 yards per attempt. Ideally, we would like to see the Dolphins’ starters successfully all depths of the field next week. Speedsters, Tyreek Hill and Jaylen Waddle, did not play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-960f-df63-a199-df2f85ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 4-of-4 targets for 18 yards and rushed once for six yards in the Dolphins’ preseason Week 1 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d05a-adda-be93d7c50000</link>
      <description>Washington touched the ball on five of the Dolphins’ first 10 plays. He was then bubble-wrapped on the sideline, preserving him for future use. Washington forced two missed tackles overall and looked good navigating the short area of the field. He did, unfortunately, fumble on his lone carry but the ball went out of bounds, preserving the Dolphins’ possession. Washington appears to be in contention for No. 3 wide receiver duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9613-d05a-adda-be93d7c50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
