<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 04:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports James Conner “did in fact suffer a season-ending injury to his right ankle” in the Cardinals’ Week 3 loss to the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f0d-d6a5-adff-ffcd88b60000</link>
      <description>Things were already trending in this direction given the gruesome nature of the injury. The Cardinals still don’t know the full extent of Conner’s injury, which will require surgery, but the veteran running back is likely looking at a long road to recovery. Conner signed a two-year contract extension last offseason and is officially under contract through 2026. However, he also carries alow dead cap hit of just $2.250 millionand given his age (31), and the latest injury, it’s fair to wonder if the his time with the Cardinals could be coming to an end. Conner’s season ends with a rushing line of 32-95-1. Second-year running back Trey Benson is expected to takeover the lead role in Conner’s absence and profiles as a strong RB2 going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f0d-d6a5-adff-ffcd88b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Conklin did not catch either of his targets in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f37-d6a5-adff-fff738ff0000</link>
      <description>It was rookie TE Oronde Gadsden II, not Conklin, who filled in for Will Dissly (knee) against Denver. Gadsden was second on the team with seven targets on the day despite running just 17 pass routes. It would appear Conklin — who has two receptions on the season — is unplayable in all fantasy formats even with Dissly sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f37-d6a5-adff-fff738ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Herbert completed 28-of-47 attempts for 301 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Chargers’ Week 3 win against the Broncos, adding two rushes for six yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f3a-d1b3-a5dd-6f7b06d90000</link>
      <description>Herbert led the Chargers back from a fourth quarter deficit on a relatively inefficient outing. Herbert’s 54 percent completion rate ranked 27th out of 31 qualifying quarterbacks in Week 4. Still, he hit his main pass catchers when it counted, including Keenan Allen for a red zone touchdown, beating tight coverage from an elite Broncos secondary. Herbert narrowly missed Quentin Johnston on a deep ball that would have likely been a long touchdown. The LA offense continued its pass-first ways, with 59 drop backs to 25 rushing attempts. That should continue next week against a middling Giants secondary. Herbert should remain in all fantasy lineups in a game with sneaky shootout potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f3a-d1b3-a5dd-6f7b06d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 1-of-4 targets for four yards in the Broncos’ Week 3 loss against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f41-d6a5-adff-ffc5643a0000</link>
      <description>Mims was again operating as the Broncos’ No. 3 receiver behind Courtland Sutton and Troy Franklin. He logged a pass route on 21 of the team’s 36 drop backs. No Denver pass catcher outside of Sutton (118 yards, TD) did much of anything with Bo Nix once again struggling with accuracy on intermediate and downfield throws. The preseason high hopes for Mims — who has 40 receiving yards in three games — have not come to fruition. That leaves the gadget receiver as a bench stash in 12-team leagues and a waiver wire player in 10-team formats for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f41-d6a5-adff-ffc5643a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 22-of-37 passes for 224 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ 22-9, Week 3 win over the Giants, adding two yards on five carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f56-dfde-a1bd-7fdff7cb0000</link>
      <description>Mahomes took only two sacks but was under constant duress from one of the top defensive lines in the league, averaging just 6.1 yards per attempt as the Chiefs were forced to work the short areas of the field. The Giants never really pushed the Chiefs on the scoreboard as they struggled to move the ball throughout, which allowed the Chiefs to take a methodical approach to their game management. The lone passing score went to Tyquan Thornton from five yards out in the third quarter and the two narrowly missed another score through the air on two separate occasions in the final frame. Thornton couldn’t survive the ground on the first and the next one came on the same series when Thornton was down at the one on a 30-yard hookup. The Chiefs avoid falling to 0-3 with the win ahead of a Week 4 matchup with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f56-dfde-a1bd-7fdff7cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed 10 times for 45 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants, adding three yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f7e-d93f-ad9d-7fff19800000</link>
      <description>Pacheco now has just 25 carries through the first three games of the season, even ceding a short yardage touchdown to Kareem Hunt in the fourth quarter in this one. It’ll be difficult for Pacheco to return usable counting stats in fantasy on such little usage, which is concerning considering the Chiefs have played three games now without their top two options through the air. Pacheco is a difficult start in Week 4 when the Chiefs take on the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f7e-d93f-ad9d-7fff19800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 10 times for 34 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants, adding 10 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f80-d6a5-adff-ffc5e67a0000</link>
      <description>Isiah Pacheco led the backfield in snaps for the third consecutive game but it was Hunt that found the end zone from one yard out late in the fourth quarter. Hunt is unlikely to carry weekly fantasy value while playing behind Pacheco, but his presence has proven to sap much of the upside from his backfield mate. It will be difficult to start Hunt in Week 4 when the Chiefs face the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f80-d6a5-adff-ffc5e67a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyquan Thornton caught 5-of-9 targets for 71 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f82-d6a5-adff-ffc7d0bc0000</link>
      <description>Thornton connected with Patrick Mahomes from five yards out in the third quarter, scoring as the third read in the green zone. He would narrowly miss tacking on a second score to his ledger twice in the final frame, the first of which was ruled incomplete as he failed to survive the ground and the second of which he came down with the football at the one. Thornton has proven his growth in the offense and gives the Chiefs a downfield element in the absences of Rashee Rice and Xavier Worthy, making him a viable fantasy starter when the Chiefs take on the Ravens in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f82-d6a5-adff-ffc7d0bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught 4-of-6 targets for 42 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f86-d93f-ad9d-7fc7694d0000</link>
      <description>Brown has now gone two games with six or fewer targets after his 16-target eruption in Week 1, indicating a high likelihood that the extreme bump in volume was directly correlated to the in-game injury to Xavier Worthy. It has been Tyquan Thornton that has been the most productive receiver the two game since Week 1, leaving Brown bereft of fantasy value in the coming weeks. He can safely be returned to the waiver wire ahead of a Week 4 meeting with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f86-d93f-ad9d-7fc7694d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 4-of-7 targets for 26 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 3 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f89-d93f-ad9d-7fcf1eba0000</link>
      <description>Kelce made it through this one absent any mental mistakes, which now makes one in a row. That didn’t mean he was without the sideline drama as he was seen in a tiff with head coach Andy Reid in the second quarter while the Chiefs were playing the Giants to a 6-6 game. He finished second on the team in targets but continues to see other pass-catchers operate as the primary options through the air, this time being Tyquan Thornton. Kelce remains elite at generating separation in the short area of the field and can pick up third downs with the best of them, but his fantasy value is quickly deteriorating beyond a usable asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6f89-d93f-ad9d-7fcf1eba0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
