<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:04:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mayer suffered an ankle injury in Week 12 against the Browns and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b315-db57-afda-f73711140000</link>
      <description>Mayer went down with the ankle injury in the first half. He was initially listed as questionable to return but the Raiders ruled him out shortly after he went into the locker room. Ian Thomas has taken his spot as the Raiders’ No. 2 tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b315-db57-afda-f73711140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed 12 times for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 12 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b318-d82c-a79a-b39c7a350000</link>
      <description>Monangai out-touched D’Andre Swift 12-9, out-gained him 48-29, and won the Bears’ backfield snap battle for the first time all season. NextGenStats charted Monangai as taking the field on 56 percent of the Bears’ plays compared to 43 percent for Swift. Dominating early downs while Swift mostly featured in the passing game, Monangai scored the Bears’ lone rushing touchdown while Swift lost a fumble. In Swift’s defense, it was surprising the play was not blown dead by forward progress. We wouldn’t necessarily assume this approach travels for Week 13 against the Eagles, but Monangai has seemed like the team’s best early-down option for some time. He will be a reasonable-floor, limited-ceiling FLEX option for Thanksgiving week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b318-d82c-a79a-b39c7a350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 4-of-5 targets for 49 yards and a touchdown in the Bears’ Week 12 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31b-db57-afda-f73bf6bd0000</link>
      <description>This was the fourth straight game Loveland cleared 40 yards, while he’s now caught at least three balls six straight weeks. That’s not the world’s highest floor, but it is a legitimate one. It has made Loveland a safe TE2 who can spike a TE1 week in the right game environment. That is unlikely to be Week 13 as the Bears head east for an Eagles road date, but Loveland is a player who could start producing even more down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31b-db57-afda-f73bf6bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery had five rushes for 18 yards in the Lions’ Week 12 win against the Giants, adding three catches for 19 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31c-d413-ad9f-b7ddafd50000</link>
      <description>Jahmyr Gibbs had the game of his life, going for 219 rushing yards and 45 receiving yards along with two touchdowns against a Giants rush defense that ranks among the NFL’s worst. Montgomery was limited to breather back duties a week after being held to six carries for 27 yards against the Eagles. Gibbs has fully taken over the Detroit backfield with Dan Campbell calling offensive plays. Montgomery is a bench stash in most 12-team leagues and one of the best contingency options in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31c-d413-ad9f-b7ddafd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared G Ben Bredeson, CB Jamel Dean, RB Bucky Irving, CB Benjamin Morrison, OLB Haason Reddick, and DL Elijah Simmons inactive for Week 12 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b320-d82c-a79a-b3b483dc0000</link>
      <description>Irving is reportedly targeting a Week 13 return while Godwin returns from a five-game absence with a fibula injury, playing only his third game of the season in Week 12. Either way, the Buccaneers are inching closer to full health as they make a push for the postseason in the final third of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b320-d82c-a79a-b3b483dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 18 times for 68 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 12 loss to the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31f-db57-afda-f73f7e360000</link>
      <description>In a first for 2025, Warren was not targeted in the passing game. That meant he ended up out-touching Kenneth Gainwell just 18-16 as the Steelers featured their backfield in Aaron Rodgers’ (wrist) absence. Not the best development, though Warren’s ankle injury did not seem to be a factor. With Gainwell producing whenever given the opportunity this season, the Steelers probably need to think about getting him more involved independent of Rodgers and Warren’s health. That would make Warren more of a FLEX than RB2 for Week 13, especially since all 32 teams will be active for Thanksgiving week. That being said, Warren will have a plus home matchup in the Bills’ awful run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b31f-db57-afda-f73f7e360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared K Joshua Karty, WR Xavier Smith, RB Jarquez Hunter, S Chris Smith II, OL David Quessenberry, and DE Desjuan Johnson inactive for Week 12 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b324-d413-ad9f-b7fddfd50000</link>
      <description>Karty is inactive for the second consecutive week, with the team electing to go with Harrison Mevis as their kicker. Smith was unable to practice this week and will miss his first game of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b324-d413-ad9f-b7fddfd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed 10 times for 92 yards in the Steelers’ Week 12 loss to the Bears, adding six receptions for 30 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b326-d82c-a79a-b3b6725e0000</link>
      <description>With Aaron Rodgers (wrist) sidelined, the Steelers featured their backfield. Pro Football Focus charted Gainwell as out-snapping Jaylen Warren 37-36, though Warren narrowly won the touch battle. Gainwell had the most rushing yards thanks to a 55-yard gain to the Bears’ one-yard line on a trick play out of the “tush push” formation. Although that produced the bulk of Gainwell’s production, he was looking explosive and slippery most of the afternoon in Chicago. Although Rodgers’ status is a Week 13 wild card, Gainwell can probably be treated as a decent-enough second FLEX option for a home matchup with the Bills’ awful run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b326-d82c-a79a-b3b6725e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught 1-of-2 targets for 26 yards in the Colts’ Week 12 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b313-db57-afda-f733bb280000</link>
      <description>Daniel Jones couldn’t get anything going downfield. Pierce, in turn, was all but erased from this game. He was on the receiving end of Jones’ only target that traveled more than 15 yards downfield. Jones only attmpted two such passes on the day. Pierce has been hyper-efficient this year, but games like this are bound to happen when he makes his living on almost exclusively deep shots. Pierce will be a shaky start in Week 13 versus a stingy Houston defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-b313-db57-afda-f733bb280000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
