<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs told reporters that he “fractured a finger a couple weeks ago.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d7e-d45b-affe-ddfea4a40000</link>
      <description>This is our first time hearing about it. Per ESPN’s Mike Reiss, there was “never a doubt he would play through it,” which is probably why Diggs has only been listed with chest and ankle injuries this season. The Patriots’ No. 1 wide receiver has finished in the half-PPR WR2-WR3 range for five straight weeks. We have no concerns about the finger fracture. Treat him accordingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d7e-d45b-affe-ddfea4a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d92-d1e7-a1fa-dffaf05b0000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin told reporters yesterday that Rodgers would not practice today, so this should not be viewed as overly alarming, though Rodgers’ Week 12 availability is obviously in question. The wrist fracture Rodgers suffered in his non-throwing left arm could keep him sidelined against the Bears this weekend. If he can resume practicing by the end of the week, he should have a chance to play. He told reporters after practice that he hopes to resume practicing on Thursday, and that “safety” and the ability to “protect” himself are his main concerns, aside from being cleared by the medical staff. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d92-d1e7-a1fa-dffaf05b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders activated Aidan O’Connell (wrist) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9da1-d713-ad9e-fdf5dd3e0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell went down with the wrist injury in the Raiders’ preseason finale. The team then acquired Kenny Pickett to back up Geno Smith. With how poorly Smith has played this year, there’s a remote chance O’Connell sees action late in the season. However, that isn’t something we expect to see anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9da1-d713-ad9e-fdf5dd3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer said QB Dak Prescott (hip) will take a “normal workload” at today’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dab-d673-a39e-bdbb2bc30000</link>
      <description>Prescott picked up a hip injury in the Cowboys’ Week 11 over the Raiders on Monday night. Schottenheimer prefaced Prescott’s injury report appearance by saying the Cowboys’ quarterback “should be fine” for the team’s Week 12 game against the Eagles. Monitoring Prescott’s practice participation is worthwhile, but we expect him to warrant QB1 treatment this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dab-d673-a39e-bdbb2bc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived WR Brandin Cooks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dae-d713-ad9e-fdfe80c70000</link>
      <description>Per NewOrleans.Football’s Nick Underhill, Cooks agreed to a pay cut in a mutual parting of ways. Cooks will be subject to waivers. Assuming no one claims him, the veteran wideout will be free to sign wherever he wants. His release allows him to join a contender and gives the Saints some money back. Cooks has 19 catches for 165 yards this year. He will be a depth option no matter where he signs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dae-d713-ad9e-fdfe80c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton (shin/groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dcf-d673-a39e-bddf1e1e0000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said it was too early to know if Horton will play this week. A DNP on Wednesday is usually a sign that a player isn’t going to suit up, especially if they missed the previous game. Horton hasn’t played since Week 9. The team traded for Rashid Shaheed in his absence, so his role will likely be minor when he returns. Fantasy managers can likely cut ties with Horton this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dcf-d673-a39e-bddf1e1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LG Grey Zabel (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dd4-d45b-affe-ddd6e7bf0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Mike Macdaonld said on Monday that the initial news on Zabel’s knee injury was “really positive.” He could still miss some time, but it doesn’t appear to be a long-term injury. Christian Haynes took Zabel’s spot in the lineup last week and would likely be in line for the start if he can’t suit up on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dd4-d45b-affe-ddd6e7bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ddf-d1e7-a1fa-dfffae2a0000</link>
      <description>Swift missed one game because of the hip injury a few weeks ago but has been playing through it without any issues as of late. He ran 21 times for 90 yards versus the Vikings in Week 11. Swift was limited in last Wednesday’s practice before logging two full sessions to close the week. We expect the same practice regimen this time around. He will be a volume-based RB2 in Week 12 versus Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9ddf-d1e7-a1fa-dfffae2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9de4-d1e7-a1fa-dfeea9e70000</link>
      <description>Fellow linebacker Tremaine Edmunds was also held out of practice. Edwards has been out since Week 9 because of the pair of injuries. Edmunds, on the other hand, suffered his injury in Week 11 versus Minnesota. The Bears have been banged up on defense all year. Edwards doesn’t look likely to return this week while Edmunds could also be out, further hurting a unit that can’t catch a break.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9de4-d1e7-a1fa-dfeea9e70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
