<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders waived QB Cam Miller.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-db7b-a5dd-e8762f1a0000</link>
      <description>Miller was the Raiders’ sixth-round pick, and it seems very likely that the signal-caller will be back with Las Vegas on their practice squad. Tommy Mellott — a former college quarterback who is making the move to wide receiver — was also part of the cuts for the Raiders. The full list of players who won’t make the 53-man roster: aived DT Zach Carter, RB Chris Collier, DE Jahfari Harvey, WR Shedrick Jackson, LB Matt Jones, DT Treven Ma’ae, G Atonio Mafi, RB Sincere McCormick, DE Ovie Oghoufo, TE Carter Runyon, WR Justin Shorter, OL Laki Tasi, S Trey Taylor, CB Greedy Vance, T Dalton Wagner and S JT Woods, WR Alex Bachman, S Terrell Edmunds and TE Albert Okwuegbunam while Lonnie Johnson Jr. was placed on the injured list and designated for return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e876-db7b-a5dd-e8762f1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed CB Maxwell Hairston on injured reserve and designated him for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88b-d332-a1fd-febfed500000</link>
      <description>Hairston suffered a sprained knee at the end of July, and the 22-year-old will need to miss the first four games —at minimum — before having a chance to join the Bills. Once healthy, the 2025 first-round picks should be a cog in the secondary, but he may need to wait until 2026 until he’s ready to make a significant impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88b-d332-a1fd-febfed500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans placed DE Denico Autry on the reserve/physically unable to perform list with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88a-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbe7e00000</link>
      <description>Autry will now miss at least four games. The Texans’ talented pass rush can survive without their veteran rotational player but he will be welcomed upon his return. The Texans face the Ravens in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88a-dbe3-a9bb-f8dbe7e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers released WR Robbie Chosen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e878-db7b-a5dd-e87cd8290000</link>
      <description>Chosen caught 9-of-12 targets for 117 yards this preseason, but he did not crack the roster in a banged-up 49ers wide receiver room. He appeared in just two games for the Dolphins last year and could catch on as practice squad depth. The 49ers also released OL Michael Dunn, WR Russell Gage Jr., DL Jonathan Garvin, DL Trevis Gipson, DL Bruce Hector, WR Isaiah Hodgins, CB Fabian Moreau, P Thomas Morstead, LB Curtis Robinson, LB Chazz Surratt, and WR Malik Turner. They waived WR Junior Bergen, LB Stone Blanton, DL William Bradley-King, DB Derrick Canteen, CB Dallis Flowers, LB Jalen Graham, S Jaylen Mahoney, OL Drake Nugent, WR Terique Owens, DL Sebastian Valdez, TE Brayden Willis and OL Nick Zakelj.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e878-db7b-a5dd-e87cd8290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills waived RB Frank Gore Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88f-dbe3-a9bb-f8dfdac50000</link>
      <description>The Bills also waived WR Stephen Gosnell, OT Travis Clayton, DE Paris Shand, DT Marcus Harris, DT Zion Logue, LB Jimmy Ciarlo, LB Keonta Jenkins and OT Tylan Grable. The Bills released WR Deon Cain, WR Kristian Wilkerson and TE Zach Davidson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e88f-dbe3-a9bb-f8dfdac50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns released RB Trayveon Williams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ad-d332-a1fd-febfccf60000</link>
      <description>Williams signed with the Browns earlier in August as a camp body with Quinshon Judkins still working his way in. The Browns also released WR Chase Cota, WR Kaden Davis, S Christopher Edmonds, CB LaMareon James, WR Kisean Johnson, DE Sam Kamara, RB Ahmani Marshall, WR Cade McDonald, DE Julian Okwara, and OT Kilian Zierer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ad-d332-a1fd-febfccf60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons waived WR Nick Nash.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8a6-dbe3-a9bb-f8f7b4570000</link>
      <description>The Falcons also waived TE Joshua Simon, OL Joshua Gray, WR Dylan Drummond, CB Dontae Manning, DL Simeon Barrow Jr., RB Carlos Washington Jr., CB Cobee Bryant, K Lenny Krieg, RB Elijah Dotson, TE Nikola Kalinic, WR Quincy Skinner Jr. and S Josh Thompson. The Falcons released OL Jordan Williams, S Henry Black, S Jordan Fuller, EDGE Khalid Kareem, OL Brandon Parker, QB Easton Stick, DL Kentavius Street, CB Keith Taylor, OL Jake Hanson, CB CJ Henderson, LB/S Ronnie Harrison, WR Chris Blair, OL Matthew Cindric, QB Ben DiNucci, DL Morgan Fox, LB Caleb Johnson, CB Lamar Jackson, LB Nick Kubitz, WR Jesse Matthews and EDGE Ronnie Perkins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8a6-dbe3-a9bb-f8f7b4570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (ankle) and OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) both passed their physicals today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8c8-de13-afdc-eecbf6970000</link>
      <description>Godwin is still expected to miss regular season games, and could be out until October. He will, however, officially avoid being placed on any type of reserve list. Less is known about Wirfs’ expected return date but both players will now be allowed to practice with their teammates. Godwin could end up returning weekly WR3 value once he gets up to speed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8c8-de13-afdc-eecbf6970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans waived TE Luke Lachey.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8bd-d332-a1fd-febf532d0000</link>
      <description>The Texans spent a seventh-rounder on Lachey, but part ways with him before the start of the season. The team also waived/released WR Quintez Cephus, QB Kedon Slovis, S Myles Bryant, LB Nick Niemann, CB Damon Arnette, TE Luke Lachey, FB Jakob Johnson, LB Jackson Woodard, LB K.C. Ossai, LS Blake Ferguson, DE Solomon Byrd, DT Junior Tafuna, C Eli Cox, OT Conor McDermott, OG LaDarius Henderson, WR Daniel Jackson, DE Casey Toohill, OT Trent Brown, CB D’Angelo Ross, RB J.J. Taylor, CB Arthur Maulet, TE Dalton Keene, S Russ Yeast, Jawhar Jordan, DT Haggai Ndubuisi, OT Jaylon Thomas, and OT Zach Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8bd-d332-a1fd-febf532d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) avoided opening the season on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ce-dbe3-a9bb-f8df162d0000</link>
      <description>Likely will begin the season as a member of the Ravens’ active roster and be eligible to play right away. Had Likely been placed on injured reserve with a designation to return, he would have been sidelined for at least four games. Likely can be stashed on benches by those who wish to see if head coach John Harbaugh’s All-Pro dreams for Likely come to fruition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e8ce-dbe3-a9bb-f8df162d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
