<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Radio 810’s Jason Anderson reports Chiefs are signing DT Mike Pennel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</link>
      <description>Pennel was briefly on the Bengals to begin this season, but was released on Tuesday. The Chiefs waste no time bringing the veteran back, after spending each of the last two seasons in Kansas City. Pennel will play a depth role again for the Chiefs’ defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers acquired EDGE Keion White and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Patriots in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d14-d245-adfb-bd5fd6690000</link>
      <description>White was inactive in Week 8 as the Patriots found a suitor for the former second-round pick. He tallied five sacks last season but fell out of favor on the defensive line this season. The 49ers had been looking for pass rush help with Nick Bosa (ACL) out for the season and now add White for the price of a late-round pick swap. White ranks last in PFF pass rush grade this season but will get a fresh start to make an impact in San Francisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d14-d245-adfb-bd5fd6690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers acquired S Kyle Dugger and a 2026 seventh-round pick from the Patriots in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d27-dab4-a3fb-bf77e5c00000</link>
      <description>The Patriots continue to deal defensive players that have fallen out of favor in their current scheme, sending Dugger to the Steelers just minutes after sending Keion White to the 49ers. Both deals were structured the same, with the Pats swapping late-round picks in exchange for giving up the defensive player. Dugger had started all 45 games played for the Patriots from 2022-2024, but started four out of seven games played this season. The veteran has nine career interceptions, 24 passes defended, and 25 tackles for loss over a six-year career. The Steelers had a need at safety with DeShon Elliott week-to-week due to a knee injury suffered in Week 8. Dugger will mix into a Steelers secondary that needs improvement if they are to make a playoff push.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d27-dab4-a3fb-bf77e5c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers placed S DeShon Elliott (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</link>
      <description>Elliott was considered week-to-week with a knee injury he suffered in Week 8 against the Packers. However, with the Steelers acquiring Kyle Dugger from the Patriots, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Elliott will be placed on injured reserve. He will miss a minimum of four games and could return later in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2d3f-deb1-a39b-2d3fc3610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed EDGE Clelin Ferrell to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers continue to add to their pass rush, signing Ferrell to the practice squad after trading for Keion White. Ferrell began his career with the Raiders and has bounced around the last three years, appearing in one game for the Chargers this season. He brings 17.0 career sacks over six seasons to the 49ers practice squad, including 3.5 sacks during a 2023 stint with the 49ers. San Francisco continues to add pass rush depth with Nick Bosa (ACL) out for the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dcc-deb1-a39b-2dce2d9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jets S Andre Cisco suffered a pectoral tear in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</link>
      <description>Cisco reportedly tore his pectoral muscle in the Jets’ Week 8 win over the Bengals. The 25-year-old signed with the Jets in the offseason and started all eight games, tallying 41 combined tackles on the season. Cisco’s pectoral tear needs repair and he will be sidelined for some period of time, leaving the Jets to turn to Isaiah Oliver and Tony Adams for help at the safety spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2dd9-deb1-a39b-2ddfde890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed CB C.J. Gardner-Johnson, formerly of the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</link>
      <description>Gardner-Johnson will reunite with Bears defensive coordinator Dennis Allen, who coached him in New Orleans from 2019 to 2021. The mercurial cornerback will join a Chicago defense that has allowed the NFL’s fourth highest drop back success rate and the second highest completion rate over expected this season. Look for Gardner-Johnson, who has 18 interceptions over 77 NFL games, to primarily play slot corner in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ff3-d5d8-a3ff-fff308af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants RB Cam Skattebo (ankle) faces a 4-6 month recovery period.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</link>
      <description>The dislocated ankle Skattebo suffered in Week 8 against the Eagles came with a fibula fracture and deltoid ligament rupture, according to Rapoport. The rookie was taken to a local hospital and underwent season-ending surgery. Rapoport seems confident Skattebo will be ready for the team’s offseason program, though his recovery will be worth tracking in the coming months. Tyrone Tracy will take over as the Giants’ lead back in Skattebo’s absence. Tracy had 39 yards on ten rushes and two catches for 14 yards against the Eagles last Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ffe-d48c-ad9f-ffff8cf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB John Wolford, formerly of the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</link>
      <description>Wolford will join the team’s practice squad ahead of Minnesota’s Week 9 game against the Lions. The Vikings last week lost Carson Wentz to a season-ending shoulder injury and will be forced to start J.J. McCarthy in Week 9. McCarthy has missed nearly two months with an ankle injury. Wolford will likely serve as the team’s QB3 behind McCarthy and Max Brosmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3021-d4ed-a9de-77afc58a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio believes the Eagles are “shopping A.J. Brown without officially shopping” him ahead of the NFL’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</link>
      <description>Florio said he’s heard of several contending teams that are interested in acquiring Brown if the Eagles are willing to part with the star wideout. That includes, per Florio, the Patriots, whose head coach — Mike Vrabel — coached Brown in Tennessee. “This to me feels like an effort by the Eagles to shop A.J. Brown without shopping A.J. Brown, to wait for the phone to ring, to not be the one who picks up the phone” to engage in trade talks before the November 4 league deadline. “Something’s been going on there,” Florio said of Brown, who has complained for years about his lack of opportunities in the run-heavy Philadelphia offense. Brown’s fantasy prospects would see a slight bump if he were to land with a more pass-first team, and his exit from the Eagles offense would make DeVonta Smith a borderline elite fantasy option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
