<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cam Heyward (business) was not in uniform and “did not appear” to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ff-d332-a1fd-97ffcfb20000</link>
      <description>Heyward had held-in for a small portion of camp, but it sounds like it’s not completely over yet. The Steelers listed him as “resting vet” on the injury report. We’d still bet on Heyward being there for Week 1’s game against the Jets, but the Steelers would be in significantly more trouble against New York’s run-focused attack without Heyward, so it’s something worth monitoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ff-d332-a1fd-97ffcfb20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Eisen said Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh told him Omarion Hampton will start in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1614-db7b-a5dd-b614f9b70000</link>
      <description>He did lead with “all he would allow,” so we’re not exactly predicting this to not be a timeshare or anything. But it makes plenty of sense that the Chargers would go with the healthy young back as the main portion of their game plan as compared to Najee Harris coming off a lot of missed time in camp. Harris should probably mix in and take up to 30-40 percent of the snaps, perhaps more if the coaches like what they’re seeing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1614-db7b-a5dd-b614f9b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said that DL Micah Parsons (back) “was able to do what we had planned for him today.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1625-d332-a1fd-96376f350000</link>
      <description>We do not yet know Parsons’ participation level, but it sounds like he is on track to play against the Lions in Week 1. It would be unsurprising to see him be restricted to some sort of snap count. The Packers have Super Bowl aspirations, and they’ll want to safely ramp up their well-paid superstar to preserve his health for the stretch run. Packers CB Nate Hobbs (knee) returned to practice in a limited capacity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1625-d332-a1fd-96376f350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said Jordan Love (left thumb) “has not yet tried handing off with his left hand in practice yet.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e4-db7b-a5dd-b5e4b6580000</link>
      <description>This is not overly alarming. The Packers are trying to minimize Love’s re-injury risk in practice. It could make things a tad difficult in live action, but they can scheme around it as the surgically repaired thumb heals. He has been practicing in full this week and is a borderline QB1/2 for Week 1 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15e4-db7b-a5dd-b5e4b6580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Mike DeFabo believes Kenneth Gainwell will “have a number of chances to touch the ball.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1632-db7b-a5dd-b636dd2a0000</link>
      <description>He also writes that Gainwell will be “a bigger contributor than most people realize” and that Mike Tomlin’s listing of Gainwell as No. 2 on the depth chart “isn’t just Tomlin playing games with [Kaleb] Johnson.” It sounds like Gainwell could have some fantasy value when the Steelers get into negative game scripts this year, at least as long as he’s able to hold Johnson off from being a major part of the committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1632-db7b-a5dd-b636dd2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Elijah Moore (personal) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1637-db7b-a5dd-b63764a00000</link>
      <description>Updating a previous item, Moore missed practice today for personal reasons. Unless it is a serious issue, he will likely be on the field for the Bills’ Sunday Night Football game against the Ravens. He does not need to be in re-draft lineups, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1637-db7b-a5dd-b63764a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Tyler Bass (left hip/groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163a-de13-afdd-56fb9f2e0000</link>
      <description>Bass was a limited participant in Wednesday’s practice. Things evidently did not go well because the Bills signed free agent K Matt Prater earlier today. Bass appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 1 against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163a-de13-afdd-56fb9f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Khalil Shakir (ankle) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163b-dbe3-a9bb-367ba5fd0000</link>
      <description>The Bills seem to have managed Shakir’s high-ankle sprain rehab very effectively. Josh Allen’s go-to receiver will be on the field for Week 1 against the Ravens’ top-flight defense. Expecting a ceiling game from Shakir is probably unreasonable, but a primetime offensive outpouring is possible. For now, consider Shakir a PPR WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163b-dbe3-a9bb-367ba5fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett (hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1644-d332-a1fd-9676b1a50000</link>
      <description>The hip designation is new. To say that Cleveland would be in a world of hurt without Garrett against the Bengals in Week 1 is an understatement. We haven’t seen anything extensive from a beat writer about his chances of playing in Week 1 since he arrived on the report, but it certainly seems like he’s now questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1644-d332-a1fd-9676b1a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Tyler Goodson (left elbow) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163f-dbe3-a9bb-367f22950000</link>
      <description>Goodson is on track to suit up for Week 1 against the Dolphins, though he likely lost the No. 2 role to rookie RB DJ Giddens. The team lists both players in the backup spot, but Giddens is the preferred bench stash player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-163f-dbe3-a9bb-367f22950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
