<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh said that Hampton is “working through it” and “doing everything he can” to get the ankle better. Hampton neither practiced nor played last week, as the Chargers shut down multiple key starters, giving off the impression that Hampton’s absence was more of a precautionary move than anything else. Harbaugh’s comments, coupled with Hampton’s absence, suggest he is still working his way back from the ankle fracture he suffered in Week 5. Hampton’s per-game touch counts increased each week after the talented rookie resumed playing in Week 14, culminating in a 22-touch outing in Week 17. It was his second-largest workload of the year. We still think Hampton has strong odds of suiting up for the Chargers’ Wild Card Round game against the Patriots, though his practice participation should be followed closely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a12-d968-a19b-daf3f9760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers head coach Todd Bowles said he will remain the team’s head coach for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</link>
      <description>Per the Tampa Bay Times’ Rick Stroud, Bowles “met with the Glazer family, which owns the team, Tuesday.” He met with his coaching staff on Wednesday and informed the Tampa Bay Times that “there will be some changes to his coaching staff.” The Glazer family reportedly took the offensive line’s myriad injuries into account before they made their decision. While no information was shared about the potential coaching staff changes, Stroud did note that “the offense did not produce under first-year coordinator Josh Grizzard.” Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a24-dc7a-af9b-dfbf74ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2b-dc7a-af9b-dfbf38a20000</link>
      <description>Moore is on track to play, having logged two limited sessions thus far. The Bears face the Packers on Saturday evening, and it would be great to see Moore upgrade to full participation on Thursday. Moore has played through multiple injuries already this season, while delivering both high- and low-end fantasy results. We expect him to be active this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2b-dc7a-af9b-dfbf38a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2c-dc7a-af9b-dfbf51b90000</link>
      <description>Odunze has now logged three straight limited practices dating back to last week. Rest was prescribed as the fix for his stress fracture, but an aggravation occurred during pre-game warmups in Week 15, when he hurried back after taking just one week off. Odunze sat out of practices and games until he resumed practicing late last week. After practice today, Odunze told reporters he plans on “playing” against the Packers on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a2c-dc7a-af9b-dfbf51b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a63-d56e-afff-feeb21480000</link>
      <description>Wicks remains limited through two practices as he attempts to return from a concussion he suffered in Week 17. His availability for the Packers’ Wild Card Round game against the Bears remains up in the air. Having him on the field would provide QB Jordan Love with another capable pass catcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a63-d56e-afff-feeb21480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (Achilles) practiced fully on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a64-dc7a-af9b-dfff4cd20000</link>
      <description>Golden has been a full participant in both practices this week despite the unsettling injury listing. The rookie wide receiver has been unable to carve out a role in the offense and played extensively in Week 18 while the coaching staff rested its key starters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a64-dc7a-af9b-dfff4cd20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos head coach Sean Payton said RB J.K. Dobbins (foot) “could return for the AFC Championship game if the team advances that far.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a01-d35e-a1bf-dfc3038b0000</link>
      <description>Nothing is imminent, but this is nice to hear. Initial reports indicated that Dobbins would be unable to return “before a potential Super Bowl LX appearance.” Dobbins also recently “told a fan” that he has a chance to return before that. The veteran running back suffered a Lisfranc injury against the Raiders in Week 10 via an illegal hip-drop tackle. Before suffering the injury, Dobbins had rushed 153 times for 772 yards and four touchdowns, while catching 11-of-14 targets for 37 yards this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a01-d35e-a1bf-dfc3038b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama QB Ty Simpson declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a88-dc7a-af9b-dfbfacc70000</link>
      <description>Simpson was named Alabama’s starter for 2025 after biding his time with the team from 2022-2024. In his final college season, he completed 275-of-419 passes for 3,282 yards, 27 touchdowns and four interceptions, while rushing 62 times for 282 yards and two touchdowns, earning second-team All-SEC honors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a88-dc7a-af9b-dfbfacc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a90-d56e-afff-fef8cbfb0000</link>
      <description>Goedert is one of the Eagles’ starters who got the week off against the Commanders. He is on track to play against the 49ers this weekend, given his early-week participation. Although the Eagles may choose to employ a run-heavy approach, the 49ers’ injury-weakened linebacker corps profiles as a beatable matchup for Goedert.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9a90-d56e-afff-fef8cbfb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (hip) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9aa4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdc530000</link>
      <description>Eagles LB Nakobe Dean (hamstring) and S Marcus Epps (concussion) were limited as well. Carter and Dean are seemingly on track to play. Epps is best viewed as questionable at this time. The Eagles face the 49ers’ talented, yet somewhat banged-up offense on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9aa4-dc7a-af9b-dfbfdc530000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
