<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:12:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught 5-of-7 targets for 45 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d1-d89c-a1be-efdfb4200000</link>
      <description>A third-year sixth-rounder, Douglas’ production fell off even as the Patriots’ offense ascended. His 31 grabs were a new career low by 18. This, as the “target competition” was Stefon Diggs, Hunter Henry, etc. MVP runner-up Drake Maye likes to throw deep, and Douglas’ game is middle-of-the-field chess play. The pint-sized slot man has managed to stay healthy in back-to-back seasons, no small feat as he enters the final year of his rookie deal. However, a career that once looked like it could turn into a “Wan’Dale Robinson situation” is now little more than a small guy playing a smaller role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d1-d89c-a1be-efdfb4200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams caught 1-of-2 targets for seven yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d3-d629-a1bc-f0df535f0000</link>
      <description>A third-round rookie hype merchant in an offense many were expecting to be better, Williams ended up struggling to get on the field, catching just two passes across his first nine games. He was more involved down the stretch, but still finished the regular campaign with all of 10 grabs. He turned that limited work into more than 20 yards per catch and three touchdowns, but Williams was a strict role player in an offense that has fellow field-stretchers Mack Hollins and Kayshon Boutte. With both those wideouts likely back for 2026, Williams could have a difficult time commanding a bigger role. He turns 24 in November, making him a lower-upside hold in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d3-d629-a1bc-f0df535f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught 4-of-4 targets for 54 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Super Bowl LX win over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d4-d629-a1bc-f0dda9590000</link>
      <description>The No. 121 overall pick of the 2024 Draft, Barner had a solid rookie season but upgraded as a sophomore, turning his initial 30/245/4 line into 52/519/6. The 23-year-old was a consistent big-play threat down the stretch, and finished third on his Super Bowl squad in yards. Quietly, he was also the TE14 by total PPR points. Considering his youth and steady early-career trajectory, Barner could easily ascend to TE1 status in 2026. He is an exciting dynasty league asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d4-d629-a1bc-f0dda9590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elijah Arroyo was held without a catch in the Seahawks’ Super Bowl LX victory over the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d6-d629-a1bc-f0df11130000</link>
      <description>Arroyo was not targeted as he made his postseason debut after battling a knee injury. The No. 50 overall pick of the draft, Arroyo ended up languishing behind second-year fourth-rounder AJ Barner. Arroyo caught more than two passes one time all year, and was a non-factor for the season’s stretch run. Arroyo is young (23 in April) at a complex position, but so is Barner. Arroyo’s draft pedigree means he should maintain some long-term benefit of the doubt in dynasty leagues, but 2026 seems unlikely to be the year he breaks out in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d6-d629-a1bc-f0df11130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 3-of-5 targets for 31 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d7-d629-a1bc-f0dfde8a0000</link>
      <description>Flying under the radar as always, 31-year-old Henry finished with a career-high 768 yards. His 60 receptions tied for his second most, while his seven scores were his most since 2021. Only Stefon Diggs had more receiving yards on the Pats. Although this is a skill corps that needs to be upgraded, Henry should remain an integral part of it for 2026. He is headed into the final year of his contract, and could be a candidate for a short offseason extension. The TE9 by total PPR points this season, Henry will remain in the TE9-12 mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d7-d629-a1bc-f0dfde8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Hooper caught 2-of-3 targets for 10 yards in the Patriots’ Super Bowl LX loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d9-d042-afbc-7ddb33c30000</link>
      <description>Hooper’s second season in New England produced the second fewest yards (263) of his 10-year career. The lowest total came in 2023 in Las Vegas. Hooper has a reliable pair of hands for a backup, but has never been a reliable scorer. He still possesses some down-field juice up the seam, but Hooper’s returns will continue to diminish. He is set for free agency in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-40d9-d042-afbc-7ddb33c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak confirmed he will be taking the Raiders’ head coaching job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-429b-d042-afbc-7fdb772e0000</link>
      <description>Shortly after leading the Seahawks to their second Super Bowl title in franchise history, Kubiak confirmed his decision to join the Raiders with NFL Network’s Stacey Dales. Kubiak joined the Seahawks as their offensive coordinator last offseason and immediately propelled them to the top of the league. Seattle’s offense ranked third in points score and eight in total yards, and was buoyed by an efficient passing game that ranked second in net yards per pass attempt (7.6) this season. He’ll take on a tough challenge with the Raiders, but will hopefully benefit from having the No. 1 overall pick, which is expected to be used on Indiana QB Fernando Mendoza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-429b-d042-afbc-7fdb772e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking with the NFL Insiders, Mike Macdonald said he will immediately begin searching for a new OC to replace Klint Kubiak.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-42e7-d89c-a1be-efff14ad0000</link>
      <description>Macdonald said he and the team will begin reviewing potential candidates on Tuesday. The Super Bowl-winning head coach said he expects to give some in-house candidates a look, but will also look outside of the organization for potential hires. Macdonald will enter his third season as a head coach with a third different offensive coordinator since his arrival. The loss of Kubiak, whose offense ranked third in scoring and eighth in total yards this season, leaves a massive void to fill, and with several options already with new teams, the Seahawks could have their work cut out for them to find their next offensive play-caller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-42e7-d89c-a1be-efff14ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested to interview Giants OLB coach Charlie Bullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4387-d89c-a1be-efdf063c0000</link>
      <description>The Browns are the second team to request an interview with Bullen for their defensive coordinator opening. Bullen spent some time as the Giants’ interim defensive coordinator last season after the team fired Shane Bowen, but was unable to secure the DC role under newly-hired head coach John Harbaugh. Bullen began his coaching career in 2012 as a defensive assistant for the Dolphins and has held a variety of roles over his 13 years in the NFL. He has never been hired as a defensive coordinator, so this would be a completely new role for him outside of his brief interim stint in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4387-d89c-a1be-efdf063c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams assistant head coach and pass game coordinator Aubrey Pleasant will interview for the Browns’ and Cardinals’ defensive coordinator vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4392-d629-a1bc-f39f2dce0000</link>
      <description>It was reported last week that Pleasant was “a name of interest” for the Cardinals’ defensive coordinator vacancy. Now, the long-time coach will meet with both teams to discuss their job openings to see if there could be a fit with either team. Pleasant has never served as a defensive coordinator and has spent time with five different teams since entering the league in 2013. Pleasant was also interviewed by the Chargers earlier this offseason for their defensive coordinator opening but was passed over for Chris O’Leary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-4392-d629-a1bc-f39f2dce0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
