<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders RB Raheem Mostert (knee/ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-529b-d968-a19b-5afb09670000</link>
      <description>Mostert has been mostly a kick returner this season, getting just 22 carries for 104 yards and 12 receptions for 70 yards on offense. He has returned 23 kicks for 673 yards and any potential absence this week would only have special teams impact. Mostert is dealing with knee and ankle issues and is in jeopardy of missing Week 17 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-529b-d968-a19b-5afb09670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams opened CB Roger McCreary’s 21-day practice window to be activated off injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52a8-dc7a-af9b-dfbfab360000</link>
      <description>McCreary was acquired by the Rams in October, but has been sidelined on injured reserve due to a hip injury. The Rams designated him to return to practice, opening his 21-day window to be activated. Head coach Sean McVay also added that DB Quentin Lake’s practice window will likely be activated next week. McCreary and Lake will add reinforcements to the Rams secondary heading into the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52a8-dc7a-af9b-dfbfab360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52c8-dc7a-af9b-dfffee1d0000</link>
      <description>Cross suffered the injury in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win over the Colts and missed Week 16 against the Rams. He was reported to have a 2-4 week hamstring injury last week, marking this the second week of the reported timeline. Cross is likely to miss Week 17 with a DNP designation on Wednesday. Also listed as DNP Wednesday was S Coby Bryant (knee), who suffered a knee injury in Week 16. Bryant will need to practice the rest of the week to play in Week 17 against the Panthers, but he is in jeopardy of missing time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52c8-dc7a-af9b-dfffee1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Rams may “shut down” WR Davante Adams (hamstring) for the final two games of the regular season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52d4-d35e-a1bf-57d609d80000</link>
      <description>Adams is dealing with a hamstring injury that he re-aggravated in Week 15 and caused him to miss Week 16. Head coach Sean McVay said Adams is unlikely for Week 17 and now Fowler is reporting the Rams could shut him down for the final two regular-season games. The Rams still have seeding to deal with, but they will be in the playoffs and could look to get their veteran receiver healthy ahead of the Wild Card round. There is no official injury report yet for Adams as the Rams play on Monday but fantasy managers should stay tuned; it is unlikely he will be good to go for the fantasy championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-52d4-d35e-a1bf-57d609d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez Jr. (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e1-d35e-a1bf-55e3aee60000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez is a late Christmas morning add to the Commanders’ injury report with an illness. Players tend to play through “illness” listings on the report, but it is notable that Rodriguez was added just a few hours before his team’s Week 17 matchup against the Cowboys. If he cannot go, Jacory Croskey-Merritt has RB3 upside against a weaker Cowboys defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e1-d35e-a1bf-55e3aee60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Lions RB David Montgomery (illness) is expected to be active Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e6-d56e-afff-f7eead300000</link>
      <description>The Lions play the afternoon Christmas game and had Montgomery listed as questionable due to an illness. He missed Tuesday’s practice and was limited Wednesday; Garafolo reports he is expected to go Thursday against the Vikings. Montgomery should have more opportunities in the run game this week with a run-heavy game script looking favorable, giving him RB3 upside for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55e6-d56e-afff-f7eead300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez Jr. (illness) is inactive for Week 17 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55f3-d56e-afff-f7fb98b50000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez was a late add to the injury report with an illness and is now officially inactive for the Commanders’ Christmas afternoon game against the Cowboys. Jacory Croskey-Merrit is an RB3 with Rodriguez out. The Commanders also declared QB Jayden Daniels, QB Marcus Mariota, QB Sam Hartman, LT Laremy Tunsil, LB Nick Bellore, and DT Daron Payne out against the Cowboys. Payne did not practice all week with a back issue. Jeff Driskel is Josh Johnson’s backup while Sam Hartman is the emergency third quarterback for Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-55f3-d56e-afff-f7fb98b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared WR Ryan Flournoy (knee) inactive for Week 17 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-565e-d56e-afff-f6fef6ae0000</link>
      <description>Flournoy is dealing with a knee injury he suffered in Week 16 against the Chargers. He failed to get in a full practice on a short week and is now ruled out, making KaVontae Turpin the Cowboys’ No. 3 wide receiver for the week. The Cowboys also declared LB DeMarvion Overshown, CB Caelen Carson, RB Jaydon Blue, DT Jay Toia, and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive for Week 17 against the Commanders. Overshown is out with a concussion suffered in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-565e-d56e-afff-f6fef6ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions LT Taylor Decker (illness) is questionable for Week 17 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-566a-d35e-a1bf-57ea2c690000</link>
      <description>Decker was already questionable with a shoulder injury that he has been playing through, but now adds an illness designation just hours before the Lions’ Week 17 game against the Vikings. We just saw Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez ruled out with an illness after he was added to the injury report in a similar fashion, so Decker looks to be truly questionable to play on Christmas day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-566a-d35e-a1bf-57ea2c690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Jaguars CB Jourdan Lewis will undergo foot surgery and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5698-d35e-a1bf-57da12cf0000</link>
      <description>Lewis started the week not practicing due to the foot issue, which is severe enough to require surgery. As a result, the 30-year-old veteran will miss the rest of the season. It’s a big loss for the Jaguars, who got two interceptions in 12 games out of Lewis after signing him to a three-year deal this past offseason. Jacksonville will reach into its depth to fill the nickel spot, both for this week against the Colts, and for a playoff run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5698-d35e-a1bf-57da12cf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
