<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens waived OG Ben Cleveland.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b9b-d35e-a1bf-7fdb25c70000</link>
      <description>Cleveland has been with the Ravens since they drafted him in the 2021 NFL Draft’s third round, largely playing as a backup during that span. He was set to return from a three-game suspension, but the Ravens evidently have other plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b9b-d35e-a1bf-7fdb25c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB De’Von Achane (shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b8d-d56e-afff-ffed4f250000</link>
      <description>Achane has now missed this week’s first two practices. The diminutive running back often toughs it out on game day, though the Dolphins have been eliminated from playoff contention. Tomorrow’s practice participation should clarify his status. Dolphins No. 2 RB Jaylen Wright would start in his stead if he cannot play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b8d-d56e-afff-ffed4f250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (groin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ba6-dc7a-af9b-ffbfed540000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins have let TE Greg Dulcich play ahead of Waller recently. If Waller is unable to play in Week 18 against the Patriots, the coaching staff will only be further incentivized to see what they have in Dulcich. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7ba6-dc7a-af9b-ffbfed540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (ribs) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b98-d35e-a1bf-7fda77f50000</link>
      <description>Waddle injured his ribs early in Week 17 and could not return. The 27-year-old wide receiver typically plays through injury, though. He has a chance to retake the field this week against the Patriots, though the coaching staff could choose to shut him down, preserving his health for next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7b98-d35e-a1bf-7fda77f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Javonte Williams (shoulder/neck) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb2-d35e-a1bf-7ff26b9a0000</link>
      <description>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer told reporters early on Wednesday that both Williams and RB Malik Davis (calf/eye) would be limited. Instead, the team listed both players with DNPs yesterday and today. Rookie RB Jaydon Blue could see a fantasy-friendly workload this week against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb2-d35e-a1bf-7ff26b9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb9-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3eaa0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson aggravated his old calf injury during his team’s Week 17 game and was unable to practice yesterday. He now has a chance to play in Week 18. Whether the Cowboys allow him to play is a separate issue. The 26-year-old tight end is under contract through 2029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-7bb9-dc7a-af9b-ffbf3eaa0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
