<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared QB J.J. McCarthy, LB Kobe King, OLB Andrew Van Ginkel, OLB Chaz Chambliss and DL Tyrion Ingram-Dawkins inactive for Minnesota’s Week 7 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1c-d651-a9df-fd1dc9170000</link>
      <description>McCarthy will be the emergency third quarterback behind Carson Wentz and Max Brosmer. Active for the Vikings off the questionable line are OT Brian O’Neill (knee) and OL Michael Jurgens (hamstring), while LB Blake Cashman was activated off injured reserve ahead of the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1c-d651-a9df-fd1dc9170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared WR Calvin Ridley, EDGE Anfernee Jennings, QB Tommy DeVito, OG Caedan Wallace, DT Eric Gregory, CB Charles Woods and S Jaylinn Hawkins inactive for Week 7 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1e-d99b-a1dd-ff1e55e90000</link>
      <description>Ridley didn’t appear particularly close to playing this week and should be considered on the wrong side of questionable for Week 8 against the Colts. That leaves a hodge podge of wideouts for interim coach Mike McCoy’s first game in place of Brian Callahan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1e-d99b-a1dd-ff1e55e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared CB Kristian Fulton, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, OT Josh Simmons, and DE Malik Herring inactive for Week 7 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1c-d99b-a1dd-ff1cbbb50000</link>
      <description>Simmons was the only player listed on the Chiefs’ final injury report this week and he was ruled out on Friday, so there’s nothing surprising here. Pat Mahomes and company are operating at near full strength against a Raiders team that will be out two of its top pass-catchers in Jakobi Meyers and Brock Bowers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1c-d99b-a1dd-ff1cbbb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declared OT Jack Conklin, CB Jarrick Bernard-Converse, RB Raheim Sanders, DT Mike Hall Jr., and TE David Njoku inactive for Week 7 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1e-df81-ab9b-ffdfb86b0000</link>
      <description>Conklin suffered a concussion in Week 6 and did not clear the league’s concussion protocol in time for today’s game. KT Leveston is expected to start in his place this week. With David Njoku out, Harold Fannin is surging into the TE1 ranks as Dillon Gabriel’s top target for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd1e-df81-ab9b-ffdfb86b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright is active for Week 7 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-da18-a39b-ff3336990000</link>
      <description>Healthy scratched in recent weeks, Wright is up for a game expected to feature awful weather on the shores of Lake Erie. It is worth noting that rookie Ollie Gordon II hasn’t exactly been lighting it up as De’Von Achane’s backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-da18-a39b-ff3336990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker (quad) is active for Week 7 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-d651-a9df-fd3531f00000</link>
      <description>With Coker activated, WR Hunter Renfrow — who had taken on the full-time slot role in Carolina — is a healthy scratch. Coker could see a significant role in the run-heavy Panthers offense, operating as the team’s No. 2 wideout behind Tetairoa McMillan. Coker is a workable fantasy option in 14-team leagues. Other Carolina inactives for Week 7: RB DeeJay Dallas, G Damien Lewis, TE James Mitchell, DT Cam Jackson, and DT Jaden Crumedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd20-d651-a9df-fd3531f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Andre Swift (groin) is officially active for Week 7 against the New Orleans Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd23-da18-a39b-ff335b890000</link>
      <description>A report had come out on Saturday that Swift was trending towards playing, and he said himself that he was going to, but now we have the official word. While the rain should stop before kickoff on Sunday, the wind gusts could be up to 30 mph, which means both the Bears and Saints could look to use their running and short passing game more than normal. Swift should be fired up as an RB2, especially after the Bears seemed to fix their running game during the bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd23-da18-a39b-ff335b890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) will not play in Week 7.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd21-d651-a9df-fd35ff0e0000</link>
      <description>This was expected all along after Bowers entered the weekend listed as doubtful. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported early Sunday that the team is hopeful Bowers will be able to return after its Week 8 bye, meaning Michael Mayer will again draw the start for a depleted Raiders pass-catching corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd21-d651-a9df-fd35ff0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared DT Grady Jarrett, K Cairo Santos, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, G Luke Newman, LB Noah Sewell, WR Jahdae Walker, and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 7 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd25-d651-a9df-fd358f7f0000</link>
      <description>Jarrett, who has been battling a knee injury, was said to be likely to suit up on Sunday, but that will not be the case. With the weather making this likely to be a run-heavy game, Jarrett being out is a slight bump for Alvin Kamara and Kendre Miller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd25-d651-a9df-fd358f7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints declared S Ugo Amadi, CB Rejzohn Wright, CB Isaac Yiadom, DT Jonah Williams, OL Torricelli Simpkins III, and OL Xavier Truss inactive for Week 7 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd27-df81-ab9b-ffe780010000</link>
      <description>No surprises here. The Saints will be relatively healthy heading into the Week 7 showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-fd27-df81-ab9b-ffe780010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
