<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (illness) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f81-dbbb-ab9b-7fef0d7c0000</link>
      <description>Players rarely miss games due to illness. We fully expect McCaffrey to play in Week 15 against the Titans. If the 49ers were to jump out to a healthy lead, it is possible the coaching staff gives RB Brian Robinson a little extra work in the fourth quarter, but McCaffrey should be viewed as an elite RB1, regardless.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f81-dbbb-ab9b-7fef0d7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbffe2e0000</link>
      <description>Reed is on track to play in a tough matchup against the Broncos this week. The Packers’ slot receiver ran a route on 60.0% of the pass plays last week, which was encouraging. Reed is on the FLEX radar once again, though his target volume is likely capped. Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) was also limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbffe2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbf54420000</link>
      <description>Golden does not need to be rostered in re-draft formats. His downfield skillset overlaps with WR Christian Watson, and the veteran wide receiver is playing extremely well. Golden will likely handle a small snap share against the Broncos on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f9f-d8cf-affb-bfbf54420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f77-d005-a9bf-df774cb40000</link>
      <description>Last week, the hamstring injury caused Adams to miss practice on Wednesday before logging a limited session on Thursday and practicing fully on Friday. He played on game day but caught just 4-of-6 targets for 29 yards. The Rams face the Lions in what should be a very high-scoring game in Week 15. The Rams are likely just managing Adams’ reps in the lead-up to the big game, though it would be great to see Adams practice on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0f77-d005-a9bf-df774cb40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys TE Jake Ferguson (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fae-d77b-adfb-cfaf19230000</link>
      <description>Ferguson’s absence is discouraging. It is possible that yesterday’s limited session was because Ferguson suffered the injury in practice. Hopefully, today is just a planned rest day and he can resume practicing tomorrow. The Cowboys face the Vikings’ blitz-based pass defense in Week 15. Having a big-bodied target in the short-to-intermediate field depths would help out QB Dak Prescott.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fae-d77b-adfb-cfaf19230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fb8-d005-a9bf-dfbc30930000</link>
      <description>The mediocre blocker should be available to two-hand punch a few chest pads and occasionally earn a target on Sunday. Mayer is largely an afterthought in the Raiders’ passing game, though. His backup, TE Ian Thomas (calf), was limited on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fb8-d005-a9bf-dfbc30930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (collarbone) is active for Week 15 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fcf-d77b-adfb-cfcf35e70000</link>
      <description>Evans takes the field on game day for the first time since Week 7. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes Evans will be on “somewhat of a pitch count” in his first game back, though coaches often allow players to play without restrictions if their body responds positively to early-game work. Evans is a tad risky, but his upside remains high. He should probably be in most fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0fcf-d77b-adfb-cfcf35e70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
