<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 21:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Lawrence completed 8-of-10 passes for 77 yards and one touchdown in the Jaguars’ preseason game against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b91e-d45c-a7fc-bb1e89cf0000</link>
      <description>Lawrence played on two drives in the Jaguars’ second preseason game and saw four of his completions go for 10-plus yards. A strong first drive ended on a fumbled handoff between Lawrence and Tank Bigsby after Lawrence’s foot got caught up under his center when taking the snap. His second drive, however, ended on a seven-yard touchdown pass to Parker Washington and gave Lawrence his first touchdown of the preseason. Through two games, Lawrence has completed 14-of-17 passes for 120 yards and one touchdown and has taken no sacks on three pressures. For now, he’ll profile as a mid QB2 in fantasy but could be a candidate for a breakout season in his first year under Liam Coen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b91e-d45c-a7fc-bb1e89cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Malik Nabers is dealing with a back injury that’s been described as “normal back tightness.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b937-d45c-a7fc-bb3f8d9b0000</link>
      <description>It was reported last week that Nabers was missing practice due to a shoulder injury. Now, there’s a back injury that may or may not be related to his shoulder injury. It’s hard to know without an official team injury report. Regardless, Nabers hasn’t practiced in 11 days and seems unlikely to appear in the team’s final preseason game against the Patriots next week. Head coach Brian Daboll declared last week that he’s “not going to get into any injuries,” which he has largely stuck to this offseason. At this point, the best we can do is hope this is a minor issue for Nabers that won’t keep him out for Week 1 when the Giants visit the Commanders, but we may not get any clear insight on his situation until the week leading up to the game. Nabers caught 109 passes for 1,204 yards and seven touchdowns last season and profiles as a strong WR1 in half and full-PPR formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b937-d45c-a7fc-bb3f8d9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Bengals “have been actively engaged in trade discussions surrounding Trey Hendrickson for weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b94c-d05a-adda-bbce650c0000</link>
      <description>This report comes after NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported that the Bengals are now listening to trade offers. It’s minor semantics, but worth pointing out that a prolonged discussion to move the star pass rusher could suggest that the Bengals are willing to deal Hendrickson for the right price. According to Russini, the Bengals are specifically eyeing defensive players in addition to draft capital for Hendrickson. Regardless of asking price, the most difficult part of getting a deal done will come down to what the acquiring team is willing to offer the Bengals and also Hendrickson in a contract extension. A trade won’t be impossible to pull off, but it will come at a very steep price.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b94c-d05a-adda-bbce650c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) passed his physical and is cleared to return to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b94f-d45c-a7fc-bb5fa2f60000</link>
      <description>Nwosu opened training camp on the PUP list after undergoing a cleanup procedure on his knee earlier in the offseason. The eighth-year pro totaled 14 tackles and one sack in six games for the Seahawks last season and has been limited to just 12 games since 2023. With roughly three weeks to go until the start of the season, there’s a good chance Nwosu will be active for Week 1 against the 49ers if he looks good in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b94f-d45c-a7fc-bb5fa2f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Shough completed 9-of-12 passes for 65 yards in the Saints’ preseason game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b959-df63-a199-f97baa510000</link>
      <description>Shough played the entire first half, leading the Saints to three points on four drives while taking an intentional grounding penalty along with two sacks. His only completion of 10-plus yards came on a 28-yard pass to second-year UDFA Treyton Welch. He didn’t turn the ball over, but Shough’s outing wasn’t exactly mistake-free, and it won’t do much to separate him from the pack in the Saints’ quarterback competition. This remains a QB battle to watch heading into the final week of camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b959-df63-a199-f97baa510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles acquired WR John Metchie III from the Texans in exchange for a Day 3 pick swap and TE Harrison Bryant.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b972-d45c-a7fc-bb7a16470000</link>
      <description>Jordan Schultz reports that the 49ers were also trying to trade for Metchie but the Eagles made a stronger offer. Metchie missed his 2022 rookie season, battling acute promyelocytic leukemia. He debuted in 2023 and has since caught 40-of-66 targets for 412 yards and one touchdown through his two active NFL seasons. He could compete with Jahan Dotson and Johnny Wilson for the Eagles’ No. 3 wide receiver role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b972-d45c-a7fc-bb7a16470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Walker III (foot) practiced in full on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b98c-d90d-a5bd-bbdf315d0000</link>
      <description>Foot soreness has bothered Walker for some time, and he even had a few recent absences due to undisclosed reasons. We assume the latter absences were because of the foot as well. The Seahawks can be slow to confirm these things, though. It would be great to see Walker string together a few injury-free practices this week. He is expected to fully participate in the Seahawks’ joint practice with the Packers on Thursday. Fantasy managers can use that outing as a benchmark for his foot recovery process. The Seahawks are expected to employ a run-heavy attack under new OC Klint Kubiak, with Walker functioning as the featured offensive weapon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b98c-d90d-a5bd-bbdf315d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed QB Bryce Perkins, formerly of the UFL, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9a7-d90d-a5bd-bbff9f410000</link>
      <description>Perkins quarterbacked the UFL’s Memphis Panthers last year, winning the UFL MVP award, the UFL Offensive Player of the Year award and earning a spot on the All-UFL team. He completed 109-of-158 passes for 1,342 yards, nine touchdowns and two interceptions. He rushed 46 times for 274 yards and five touchdowns while fumbling five times. Panthers backup QB Andy Dalton suffered an elbow injury in the team’s preseason Week 2 game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9a7-d90d-a5bd-bbff9f410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (ankle) did not practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b96c-d90d-a5bd-bb7f31e70000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said the injury does not appear to be serious. Horton injured the ankle in the Seahawks’ preseason Week 2 game against the Chiefs on Friday. The Day 3 rookie had been separating from journeyman WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling. An extended absence would give MVS a second chance to secure the role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b96c-d90d-a5bd-bb7f31e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed FB Adam Prentice, formerly of the Saints, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9ca-d90d-a5bd-bbdb654f0000</link>
      <description>Prentice’s signing makes sense, at least in the short term. The Broncos’ starting FB Michael Burton is dealing with a hamstring injury. It’s unlikely the team will keep two fullbacks on the active roster, though. The Broncos correspondingly placed OG Nick Gargiulo on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b9ca-d90d-a5bd-bbdb654f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
