<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ty Johnosn (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be45-dc7a-af9b-ffff8d4f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed the Wild Card Round because of the ankle issue. Two DNPs to open this week suggest he will sit for at least one more game. Ray Davis didn’t touch the ball last week and Frank Gore Jr. caught his only target. Johnson’s likely absence will simply mean more snaps for James Cook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be45-dc7a-af9b-ffff8d4f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad/calf) is practicing in full for the Divisional Round against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be53-dc7a-af9b-ffff7d5d0000</link>
      <description>Prater was listed as a DNP for Tuesday’s walkthrough but should be good to go now. He nailed both of his field goal tries in the Wild Card Round. The Bills will continue to ease his workload with Mitch Wishnowsky handling punts in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be53-dc7a-af9b-ffff7d5d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders completed an interview with Seahawks DB coach and pass game coordinator Karl Scott for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf92160000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s John Keim notes that Scott is the Commanders’ only defensive coordinator candidate lacking prior defensive coordinator experience. Scott was brought onboard in his current roles under former head coach Pete Carroll in 2022. While Scott lacks defensive coordinator experience, he has spent the last four seasons learning from two of the NFL’s most well-respected defensive minds in Carroll and current head coach Mike Macdonald.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be3f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf92160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots TE Hunter Henry (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-d56e-afff-fefe12240000</link>
      <description>Henry dealt with a knee injury in Week 18 as well before catching 5-of-5 targets for 56 yards. We expect him to be his normal self for the Patriots’ Divisional Round game against the Texans on Sunday. Despite being 31 years old, Henry totaled a career-high 768 receiving yards this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-d56e-afff-fefe12240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Bucs will interview former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be60-d968-a19b-fef1f5c30000</link>
      <description>McDaniel has been a busy man since being fired by Miami. He has several interviews for both head coaching and OC vacancies. McDaniel will likely be stuck with a less-than-deal head coaching job if he lands one. It could be smarter for him to rehab his image as a play-caller in a great situation before returning to a better opening as a head coach down the road. An opportunity to work with Baker Mayfield and the Bucs’ deep cast of pass-catchers would certainly allow McDaniel to prove his worth. Detroit and Philadelphia are also intriguing offensive coordinator openings for the former Miami boss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be60-d968-a19b-fef1f5c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots designated RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be87-d968-a19b-fef7c0ac0000</link>
      <description>Jennings landed on injured reserve after suffering a concussion back in December. He handled short-yardage rushing duties from roughly Weeks 7-10, but burly RB Rhamondre Stevenson and rookie RB TreVeyon Henderson have seemingly established themselves as a reliable duo for head coach Mike Vrabel. Jennings is a nice backup to have active on game day, though. Jennings was limited on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be87-d968-a19b-fef7c0ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbffde50000</link>
      <description>Moore played through the knee injury last week, catching 6-of-7 targets for 64 yards and one touchdown in the Bears’ Wild Card win over the Packers. We expect him to be good to go for the Bears’ Divisional Round game against the Rams. The Bears’ passing results can be somewhat game script-dependent. We like the odds of a high-scoring game developing this weekend, as two talented offenses meet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbffde50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-dc7a-af9b-ffff68170000</link>
      <description>Odunze was a bit rusty last week, but he appears to have made it through the game without suffering a setback. The Bears face the Rams’ explosive offense in the Divisional Round on Sunday, which should result in a fantasy-friendly game script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-be76-dc7a-af9b-ffff68170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports the Titans interview former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh on Thursday for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbfbc0a0000</link>
      <description>The Giants reportedly made a “massive push” to get Harbaugh to sign with them today. Of note, Harbaugh met with the Giants at their facility, toured the grounds, and even met with Jaxson Dart today. The Titans, on the other hand, are meeting him at his home. While it does seem like the Giants are in pole position to land the cycle’s hottest name, Harbaugh is still going to talk to the Titans. He will likely meet with Atlanta before making a decision as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-bea5-dc7a-af9b-ffbfbc0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears OL Braxton Jones is practicing fully for Chicago’s Divisional Round game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beac-d35e-a1bf-ffee6e910000</link>
      <description>Starting LT Ozzy Trapilo ruptured his patellar tendon in the Bears’ Wild Card win over the Packers, ending his season. Jones has not yet been officially activated from injured reserve, but his full practice participation is a good sign. If activated, he will compete with OL Theo Benedet, who manned the left tackle spot earlier this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-beac-d35e-a1bf-ffee6e910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
