<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington (hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e61e-d90e-a9da-ff1f87ad0000</link>
      <description>Washington went to the ground while fielding a punt in the second quarter of Week 13. He was helped off the field and listed as questionable to return. The team later downgraded him to out. A DNP today suggests he will miss Week 14’s game against the Colts. Dyami Brown was a healthy scratch last week but could get back in the mix on Sunday. Tim Patrick and Austin Trammell are depth options who could see some extra run for the Jags this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e61e-d90e-a9da-ff1f87ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals RB Chase Brown (calf) is practicing fully for Week 14 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e61b-d6c4-abfb-f61bb5f10000</link>
      <description>This is a new injury for Brown. The fact that he is practicing fully is a good sign, but it is worth keeping an eye on his practice participation tomorrow. The Bengals’ lead back has totaled 100-plus scrimmage yards in six straight games. He can be expected to produce fantasy-friendly results against the Bills’ lacking run defense this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e61b-d6c4-abfb-f61bb5f10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars LT Walker Little (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e623-d6c4-abfb-f62310460000</link>
      <description>Little sustained a concussion in the first half of the Jags’ Week 13 win over the Titans. The team ruled him out after halftime. Cole Van Lanen took his spot in the lineup. Van Lanen has taken snaps at every offensive line position but center this year, meaning the Jags have some flexibility in addressing Little’s likely absence this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e623-d6c4-abfb-f62310460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden (wrist) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e627-d316-abff-f6b72f200000</link>
      <description>Golden was limited in all three practices last week before being ruled out. The difference this time around is that the Packers play on Sunday in Week 14 instead of Thursday, which they did last week. The extra rest might be enough to get the rookie back on the field, though he won’t be an appealing fantasy option in his first game back. Golden has topped 60 yards once this year and is still looking for his first career touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e627-d316-abff-f6b72f200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (knee) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e629-d6c4-abfb-f62bfda80000</link>
      <description>Jacobs took a shot from Lions DB Brian Branch in Week 13 and limped off the field for a quick check in the blue medical tent. He returned without missing much time and finished the day with 18 touches for 91 yards. The fact that he wasn’t listed as a DNP today is a good sign. Jacobs should be good to go by Sunday, keeping him in the RB1 mix versus the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e629-d6c4-abfb-f62bfda80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Chimere Dike (quad) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e624-d6c4-abfb-f627222e0000</link>
      <description>Dike has delivered volatile results while playing through small injuries in recent weeks. Although his limited session on Wednesday puts him on track to play, he faces the Browns’ elite defense in Week 14. He is not a recommended FLEX starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e624-d6c4-abfb-f627222e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarShawn Lloyd (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e62c-d316-abff-f6bfdba40000</link>
      <description>Lloyd has been on injured reserve the entire year. He went down with a hamstring issue a few weeks before the start of the season and has been out ever since. The Packers will likely give him a week or two to ramp up to game speed. Even when he is healthy, we expect Emanuel Wilson to operate as Josh Jacobs’ backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e62c-d316-abff-f6bfdba40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e62e-db57-afda-f63ee17d0000</link>
      <description>Reed remains on injured reserve while recovering from the pair of injuries that knocked him out early in the year. He returned to practice just ahead of Week 12 and was limited for all three sessions last week. Reed should be close to getting back on the field, but there’s no guarantee that happens this week. Given the Packers’ low-volume approach through the air, our fantasy expectations for Reed will be kept in check whenever he does retake the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e62e-db57-afda-f63ee17d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e631-db57-afda-f633cd020000</link>
      <description>A limited session is nothing to worry about for Wicks. He should have no issues suiting up this week. Coming off a two-score, 94-yard effort versus the Lions, fantasy expectations will be high for Wicks this week. He could work his way into the WR3 ranks if Matthew Golden remains out. Golden was limited in today’s practice and appears to be questionable for Week 14 as of Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e631-db57-afda-f633cd020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (collarbone) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e634-db57-afda-f636d4fe0000</link>
      <description>Evans has a chance to suit up in Week 14 against the division-rival Saints. It is possible that he will need to shake off rust following a prolonged absence, but Evans can be started as a WR3 if he is able to suit up this weekend. Hopefully, he can resume practicing fully tomorrow. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e634-db57-afda-f636d4fe0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
