<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:37:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 21 times for 132 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 16 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e72-dc7a-af9b-ffff41cc0000</link>
      <description>For the first time in 20 years, there’s a repeat winner of the AFC East. Barkley was as good as he’s been all year, and the stinger that bothered him earlier in the week didn’t appear to bother him in this contest. His long gain was an impressive 48-yarder that featured a disgusting spin move to avoid a tackle for loss, but he was able to consistently gash the Washington front in the Saturday win. Barkley will be back in action in Week 17 against the Bills with an extra day of rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e72-dc7a-af9b-ffff41cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed 15 times for 63 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 16 loss to the Eagles, adding one catch for six yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e73-d35e-a1bf-7ff3338e0000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez returned after missing Week 15 against the Giants with a groin injury, and he was clearly the bellcow with Jacory Croskey-Merritt getting only eight attempts behind the former Kentucky tailback. His touchdown was in garbage time, but still counts, and he was relatively effective with his touches. Rodriguez is a RB2 for Christmas against the Cowboys in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e73-d35e-a1bf-7ff3338e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed eight times for 25 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 16 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e74-d087-addf-bff4aada0000</link>
      <description>After impressing in the win over the Giants in Week 16, “Bill” was a non-factor for most of the contest, although he saved the fantasy day with a short touchdown plunge. The 24-year-old has long-term upside, but Chris Rodriguez is clearly the favorite in this Washington rushing attack when he’s healthy. That likely will be the case on a short week against the Cowboys in Week 17 on Christmas Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e74-d087-addf-bff4aada0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank Bigsby rushed four times for 37 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 16 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e75-dc7a-af9b-ffff802e0000</link>
      <description>Bigsby didn’t receive a touch until late in the fourth, but he made the most of them; taking a pitch 22 yards for a touchdown. The 2023 third-round pick will remain the backup tailback to Saquon Barkley for the foreseeable future, including Week 17 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e75-dc7a-af9b-ffff802e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 9-of-12 targets for 95 yards in the Eagles’ Week 16 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7a-dc7a-af9b-ffff9cb60000</link>
      <description>Brown was a non-factor in the second half as the Eagles were so effective running the football, but he was able to snag several catches in the first 30 minutes to make it a solid — if unspectacular — fantasy day. It’s the fourth time in five games that Brown has gone for at least 90 yards, and it’s worth noting that one game he didn’t was a 31-0 drubbing of the Raiders. Brown remains a WR1 for Week 17 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7a-dc7a-af9b-ffff9cb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 6-of-8 targets for 42 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 16 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7b-d35e-a1bf-7ffb7c110000</link>
      <description>Smith didn’t do much in terms of yardage with a long gain of just 16 yards, but he did have a solid number of targets and was able to connect on a short touchdown with Jalen Hurts to give the Eagles a 7-3 lead. The 27-year-old has his first touchdown of December, and just his fourth of the season. A chance to add to those totals comes in Week 17 against the Bills, but there’s a lot of volatility in Smith’s fantasy profile right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7b-d35e-a1bf-7ffb7c110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught all three of his targets for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 16 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7c-da28-afbb-fe7d67460000</link>
      <description>Goedert was able to pick up his 10th touchdown of the season on a perfect throw from Jalen Hurts in the corner of the end zone. It was a quiet day outside of that, but hard to complain about a trip into the end zone. Goedert will be back in action with an extra day of rest in Week 17 against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e7c-da28-afbb-fe7d67460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 3-of-4 targets for 53 yards in the Commanders’ Week 16 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e81-dc7a-af9b-ffbffaf20000</link>
      <description>It just is what it is at this point. McLaurin and the Commanders’ passing attack was obviously affected by Marcus Mariota (hand) leaving the contest — not to mention Mariota was replacing Jayden Daniels (elbow) in the first place — but it’s not as if the 30-year-old was effective prior to those ailments. McLaurin will be a WR3 for a Week 17 showdown against the Cowboys, and this will go down as one of the most disappointing seasons for a wideout in 2025. If Josh Johnson is the starting quarterback on Christmas, it’d be fair to drop him down considerably lower.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e81-dc7a-af9b-ffbffaf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 3-of-4 targets for 35 yards in the Commanders’ Week 16 loss to the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e83-d087-addf-bff31af00000</link>
      <description>Samuel had a 20-yard catch, and then two more short yardage connections. It’s now three-straight contests that he hasn’t reached 50 yards, and he hasn’t found paydirt since November 16. Long story short, fantasy managers need to look elsewhere for Week 17 against the Cowboys in the majority of fantasy leagues, especially if Josh Johnson has to start that contest for Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3e83-d087-addf-bff31af00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (head) exited in the second quarter of Week 16’s game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3eaf-da28-afbb-feffbb3e0000</link>
      <description>Love was sacked on a first down in the second quarter and took a hard helmet-to-helmet hit from Bears defensive end Austin Booker. Booker was flagged on the play for roughing the passer, but Love remained down for several minutes before heading to the sideline and then the locker room to be evaluated. He is considered as questionable to return at this time. Backup Malik Willis took over for Love.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3eaf-da28-afbb-feffbb3e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
