<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Jaguars “plan to play” Travis Hunter as a full-time cornerback and part-time wide receiver in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5998-d355-a5bd-dfdcf3cf0000</link>
      <description>Per Wolfe, the Jaguars believe Hunter can be an “elite” cornerback, while still being “an impact player” on offense. For fantasy purposes, this is unfortunate. Hunter may be stuck rotating in as a contributor in three-wide receiver sets, which would make him frustratingly unreliable, though head coach Liam Coen will likely try to scheme up ways to get the ball in his hands. On the plus side, Wolfe said Hunter will be “full-go” by Week 1. The Jaguars are reportedly expected to let one of their free agent cornerbacks, Montaric Brown or Greg Newsome, walk in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5998-d355-a5bd-dfdcf3cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe reports that the Colts could “be aggressive” in their pursuit of Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson via a tag-and-trade scenario or free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-59de-d355-a5bd-dfdeccbb0000</link>
      <description>Bengals DC Lou Anarumo and DL coach Marion Hobby both coached Hendrickson, in the exact same roles, when all three were employed by the Bengals for four-plus seasons. Hendrickson’s relationship with the Bengals has soured, though the front office has thus far been unwilling to let the talented pass rusher leave town. This will be worth watching. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-59de-d355-a5bd-dfdeccbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe said “don’t be surprised” if the Browns do not draft a quarterback in the first round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-592e-d629-a1bc-f93fa00e0000</link>
      <description>The Browns have two first-round picks this year. Wolfe reports that the Browns believe they are “close to set” on defense and are expected to “go heavy on offense” in the 2026 NFL Draft. New head coach Todd Monken’s scheme is said to have more “flexibility” than former head coach Kevin Stefanski’s scheme did, and the Browns apparently believe Monken’s scheme could allow Shedeur Sanders to “use his play-making ability” more effectively. The Browns also “believe” Deshaun Watson will compete with Sanders for the starting role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-592e-d629-a1bc-f93fa00e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders interviewed Packers DL coach/run game coordinator DeMarcus Covington for their vacant defensive coordinator position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5d67-d042-afbc-7df735b80000</link>
      <description>The Raiders pounced on their top choice at head coach immediately following the Super Bowl with the hiring of former Seahawks offensive coordinator Klint Kubiak but they have yet to fill any of their coordinator positions. Covington has drawn multiple interviews for defensive coordinator vacancies this hiring cycle but did not land his first play-calling gig, with the Raiders now an additional opportunity to do just that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5d67-d042-afbc-7df735b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders promoted former run game coordinator/defensive line coach Rob Leonard to defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5da6-d629-a1bc-fdbf0df50000</link>
      <description>Leonard previously spent six seasons with the Giants before coaching with the Raiders under Patrick Graham last year. The Raiders conducted their fair share of interviews for the vacant defensive coordinator position before promoting from within. Leonard worked closely with Pro Bowl defensive lineman Maxx Crosby, potentially marking a play at retaining the veteran rusher this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-5da6-d629-a1bc-fdbf0df50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on the Caps Off podcast, Lavonte David said he’s “undecided” on whether or not he will retire.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-61a5-d89c-a1be-efff56ee0000</link>
      <description>David, 36, is set to become a free agent this offseason, but is reportedly only interested in playing for the Bucs if he were to continue playing. The veteran linebacker said he feels good and believes he has plenty of football left in him, but also noted that he’d like to spend more time with his daughter. David tallied 61 tackles and one interception in 17 games for the Buccaneers last season while started all 17 games he appeared in. The team will presumably give him plenty of time to make his decision, but the Bucs could be looking at a major hole to fill on the defensive side of the ball in 2026 should David opt to call it quits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-61a5-d89c-a1be-efff56ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns beat writer Mary Kay Cabot reports the team is meeting in-person with Texans defensive pass game coordinator Cory Undlin for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6239-d629-a1bc-f23d733b0000</link>
      <description>Cabot believes head coach Todd Monken “could name his (defensive coordinator) in the next day or two.” Undlin has over two decades of experience coaching in the NFL, but his lone stint as a defensive coordinator came in 2020 with the Lions. Undlin is one of at least two candidates receiving a second interview for the job, with Falcons’ LB coach Mike Rutenberg also set to meet with the team in person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6239-d629-a1bc-f23d733b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Ian O’Conner reports Giants HC John Harbaugh spoke “at length” with Rex Ryan about the team’s defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6254-d89c-a1be-efdf84770000</link>
      <description>Ryan has met with teams regarding several job openings since last coaching the Bills in 2016. Nothing has materialized from them, and the Giants ultimately went with Dennard Wilson to fill the opening. Ryan will be 10 years removed from the league, assuming he doesn’t coach anywhere in 2026. While it wouldn’t be surprising to see the 63-year-old coach take one more job, the fact so many interviews haven’t resulted in a hire begs the question if his time in the league could truly be over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6254-d89c-a1be-efdf84770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks completed an interview 49ers run game coordinator and TE coach Brian Fleury for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-62c2-d042-afbc-7fd28e950000</link>
      <description>Fleury has an interesting background, having held diverse coaching and operational roles after playing quarterback in college. Fleury coached at Maryland, Sacred Heart and Towson from 2003-2012, serving as a graduate assistant, secondary coach, outside linebackers coach, defensive coordinator and special teams coordinator. He entered the NFL coaching ranks with the Bills in 2013, serving as a quality control coach. The Browns then employed him as an assistant linebackers coach (2014) and outside linebackers coach (2015), where he notably coached alongside 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan. Fleury signed on with the Dolphins as a football research analyst in 2016 before being promoted to director of football research in 2017. He became the 49ers’ defensive quality control coach in 2019 before switching to the offensive side of the ball in 2020. He has since served as the 49ers’ offensive quality control coach, tight ends coach and run game coordinator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-62c2-d042-afbc-7fd28e950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders will interview Seahawks QB coach Andrew Janocko for their offensive coordinator vacancy today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-62ff-d89c-a1be-efffe7820000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter notes that Janocko is also a candidate for the Seahawks’ offensive coordinator vacancy. Janocko and new Raiders head coach Klint Kubiak have worked together for years. Janocko served as the Vikings, Saints and Seahawks’ quarterbacks coach while Kubiak concurrently held each team’s offensive coordinator role. Schefter’s colleague, Jeremy Fowler, said last week that he believes Janocko is a “natural candidate” to be the Raiders’ offensive coordinator under Kubiak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-62ff-d89c-a1be-efffe7820000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
