<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared RB Tyler Goodson, CB Jonathan Edwards, QB Riley Leonard, TE Will Mallory, LB Chad Muma, OT Luke Tenuta, and DE JT Tuimoloau inactive for Week 1 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d66d290000</link>
      <description>Goodson is battling an elbow injury, but he has also likely been passed by rookie DJ Giddens on the depth chart, which makes Goodson just the third running back in Indianapolis. Leonard might earn his way onto the field later in the season, but he’s just the emergency quarterback right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d66d290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared Nick Herbig (hamstring) inactive for Pittsburgh’s Week 1 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-dbe3-a9bb-34db9d5c0000</link>
      <description>Herbig was on the questionable tag and should be considered questionable for Week 2 at this point. Also inactive for the Steelers are: DT Derrick Harmon (knee), QB Skylar Thompson (third quarterback/hamstring), G Max Scharping, G Andrus Peat, and DT Esezi Otomewo. The latter three are all healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24c8-dbe3-a9bb-34db9d5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals OG Will Hernandez (knee) is inactive for Week 1 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d670950000</link>
      <description>Hernandez tore his ACL in Week 5 of last season and has been working his way back. He is not ready yet, now set to miss Week 1 still rehabbing his knee. Isaiah Adams is the team’s starting right guard for now. Also inactive for the Cardinals are RB Bam Knight, CB Kei’Trel Clark, CB Elijah Jones, and LB Xavier Thomas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d2-db7b-a5dd-a4d670950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Efton Chism (knee) is inactive for Week 1 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d6-db7b-a5dd-a4d66cf00000</link>
      <description>It’s technically a healthy scratch since Chism was removed from the injury report on Friday, but he had been listed with a knee issue. The UDFA drew some summer hype — evidently justified since he made the team — but isn’t a part of the receiver rotation to begin the year. He’s an end-of-bench stash in deeper Dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d6-db7b-a5dd-a4d66cf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Nick Chubb will be the “bell cow” running back for the Texans in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24da-db7b-a5dd-a4deb5880000</link>
      <description>We’re expecting to see Chubb take a majority of the early-down snaps and Dare Ogunbowale to be the third-down back for the Texans. The fact that Chubb will have the majority of the snaps makes him a worthwhile RB2/FLEX starter, and it makes Dameon Pierce and Woody Marks hard to play at this point. If Chubb is available in your league — he was a late riser due to Joe Mixon’s injury — he’s a worthwhile pickup ahead of the rosters locking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24da-db7b-a5dd-a4deb5880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Texans WR Xavier Hutchinson is expected to get “starter snaps” in Week 1 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d9-de13-afdd-66db9dc10000</link>
      <description>Christian Kirk has already been ruled out for Week 1, leaving a vacant slot role up for grabs. Hutchinson and third-round rookie Jaylin Noel are vying for the job and it sounds like the veteran has the upper hand. Noel was an interesting Week 1 sleeper for the Rapoport report, but fantasy managers should now find another DFS dart throw for their lineups. Both he and Hutchinson should only be rostered in deep formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24d9-de13-afdd-66db9dc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chris Godwin (ankle) is targeting a Week 5 return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24e6-d332-a1fd-b6f6bc110000</link>
      <description>Per Rapoport, Godwin is expected to return to practice soon. Rapoport isn’t breaking any ground here as Bucs GM Jason Licht previously mentioned Week 5 as a potential return date for the veteran wideout. As both he and Rapoport have noted, it’s possible Godwin is still held out a few weeks longer. With Jalen McMillan out because of a neck injury, the Bucs are starting first-round rookie Emeka Egbuka opposite Chris Godwin. Egbuka looked like a slow burn rookie when the Bucs drafted him, but things have since broken in his favor and he’s now sitting in the fantasy WR3/4 range heading into his first game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24e6-d332-a1fd-b6f6bc110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) listed qustionable for Week 1 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24f4-db7b-a5dd-a4f4faad0000</link>
      <description>Johnson got in a week of limited sessions, prompting the questionable tag for the Bears’ Monday Night Football game against the Vikings. The former second-round corner is slated to start opposite Tyrique Stevenson and is likely a big piece of defensive coordinator Dennis Allen’s game plan to slow down Justin Jefferson. We’ll get one final update when inactives are released 90 minutes prior to kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-24f4-db7b-a5dd-a4f4faad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Jayden Reed (foot) is expected to play in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-250e-dbe3-a9bb-355f144e0000</link>
      <description>Reed missed Wednesday’s practice but got in a pair of limited sessions before being listed as questionable. He missed much of training camp with the foot issue and spent some time in a walking boot. Reed will likely be dealing with the foot injury for much of the early portion of the season, but the good news is that he will be out there for Week 1. Per usual, Reed will be taken off the field for two-receiver sets, limiting his upside and keeping him in the WR4/5 range versus Detroit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-250e-dbe3-a9bb-355f144e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports’ Jay Glazer reports Christian McCaffrey (calf) is a “full go” for Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2516-dbe3-a9bb-35577ca80000</link>
      <description>This echoes a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter that McCaffrey, who re-injured his calf on Thursday, is “good to go” after the injury scare. It’s quite the turnaround for CMC, 29, who missed most of the 2024 regular season with a calf injury. He missed Friday’s practice and was considered iffy for the start of the season. Fantasy managers should closely monitor the Niners’ inactives ahead of their late afternoon Sunday game against the Seahawks. Brian Robinson would likely operate as the team’s top back should McCaffrey miss the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2516-dbe3-a9bb-35577ca80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
