<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 18:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB Carson Wentz.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc7d-de13-afdc-deffb7ec0000</link>
      <description>Wentz completed a workout for the Vikings Saturday and quickly signed with the team Sunday. The Vikings dealt former backup Sam Howell to the Eagles in a corresponding move. Wentz offers a considerable upgrade to Howell behind starter J.J. McCarthy and also has a play style that more closely aligns with that of McCarthy, providing an easier transition should the Vikings be hit by the dreaded quarterback injury bug at any point in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc7d-de13-afdc-deffb7ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears released WR Samori Toure.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc86-de13-afdc-decf4f8c0000</link>
      <description>The former Packer joined the Bears this offseason but ultimately missed the cut amidst a massive overhaul of key offensive pieces this offseason. The team invested heavily in this year’s draft to improve their pass-catching options, rendering Toure expendable in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc86-de13-afdc-decf4f8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys RB Jaydon Blue suffered a low ankle sprain Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc98-d332-a1fd-debeaeae0000</link>
      <description>Blue was removed from the team’s final preseason game with a low extremity injury, which has now been ruled a low ankle sprain. The team relayed that he could still be ready for Week 1 to fight for carries with Javonte Williams and Miles Sanders. Blue’s uncertainty for the start of the regular season could influence personnel decisions as roster cuts loom, potentially leading to the retention of either Phil Mafah or Deuce Vaughn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc98-d332-a1fd-debeaeae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers waived S Shilo Sanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc9c-dbe3-a9bb-fcdfdcdc0000</link>
      <description>Sanders will now head to waivers, where he can be claimed by teams in need of safety play. There are multiple teams in need of positional help currently but there is no guarantee he will land on his feet, which would then make him available to be added to the Buccaneers’ practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dc9c-dbe3-a9bb-fcdfdcdc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said he expects WR Jauan Jennings to be ready for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dccc-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf479c0000</link>
      <description>Speaking to media Sunday, 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said he expects wide receiver Jauan Jennings to be ready for Week 1. When asked about his wide receiver’s availability, Shanahan said, “I expect him to be back, I think he should be back from it, but you never know with calves. I’m not a doctor, so like I said, calves take time. You never know with calves.” It seems Shanahan is expecting Jennings for Week 1 but also wasn’t exactly speaking with a great deal of certainty, giving himself outs to the statement. The 49ers surely want Jennings out there against the Seahawks considering the multitude of injuries up and down their roster, potentially setting up a highly concentrated attack amongst Christian McCaffrey, Ricky Pearsall, and George Kittle to start the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dccc-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf479c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Aidan O’Connell (wrist) will miss 6-8 weeks with a fractured wrist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dce4-d332-a1fd-def6e9900000</link>
      <description>O’Connell suffered the fractured wrist in the team’s final preseason game and is set to miss six to eight weeks, potentially setting up an injured reserve stint to start the regular season. Sixth-round rookie Cam Miller is the only other quarterback currently on the roster, meaning we could see the Raiders exploring the waiver wire or potential trades to satisfy their need for a backup quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dce4-d332-a1fd-def6e9900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets traded DT Derrick Nnadi to the Chiefs for a swap in conditional seventh-round and sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dceb-dbe3-a9bb-fcfb45fc0000</link>
      <description>Nnadi played the first seven seasons of his professional career with the Chiefs before signing with the Jets this offseason. He returns to the Chiefs for conditional pick swaps after playing a reserve role during the 2024 regular season, something we should expect in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dceb-dbe3-a9bb-fcfb45fc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys activated CB Trevon Diggs from the Physically Unable to Perform List.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dcfe-de13-afdc-deff04240000</link>
      <description>Diggs gets added to the active roster ahead of the start of the regular season, making good on the team’s promises that he would be ready to go for Week 1. He should immediately reenter the starting lineup opposite DaRon Bland for a Cowboys secondary that was devastated by injuries a season ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dcfe-de13-afdc-deff04240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said he expects QB Kenny Pickett to be ready for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd00-dbe3-a9bb-fd53c2520000</link>
      <description>Stefanski also added that he is still working through who will back up Joe Flacco to start the season, potentially opening the door for one of the rookies to serve as the team’s top backup for Week 1. Pickett was originally in the running for the starting role for the Browns but an ill timed hamstring injury derailed those plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd00-dbe3-a9bb-fd53c2520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings released QB Brett Rypien.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd1d-de13-afdc-dfdf94140000</link>
      <description>That means the Vikings are moving forward with J.J. McCarthy, recent signee Carson Wentz, and undrafted free agent rookie Max Brosmer for the 2025 season. Rypien remains highly regarded for his veteran status, something that could lead to another opportunity elsewhere in short order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dd1d-de13-afdc-dfdf94140000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
