<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports the Eagles are looking to get A.J. Brown involved “more and early” in Week 2 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4911-dc44-a9d9-4f7740a70000</link>
      <description>It’s hard to be less involved than Brown was in Week 1 when he saw just one target. The Eagles relied on their ground game versus the Cowboys, but Brown’s lack of opportunities was still stunning. With Dallas Goedert out, Brown and DeVonta Smith, who only caught three passes in Week 1, should both see the ball more this time around. Despite the slow start, Brown remains a fantasy WR1 for his Super Bowl rematch with the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4911-dc44-a9d9-4f7740a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow left the Bengals’ Week 2 game against the Jaguars with an apparent ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-496a-dc44-a9d9-4f6e15ec0000</link>
      <description>Burrow went down on a sack in the second quarter and stayed on the ground in pain for a few beats. Trainers came out to look at him and helped him into the blue medical tent. Burrow then left for the locker room, walking off under his own power, though he did eventually get assistance from the medical staff. The fact that he didn’t ride the cart might mean the issue isn’t serious, but it’s simply too early to make any sweeping conclusions. Jake Browning will close out the first half under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-496a-dc44-a9d9-4f6e15ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Carter (concussion) exited Week 2’s game against the Ravens and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4972-da67-a99f-cdf779660000</link>
      <description>Carter went down in the first quarter of Sunday’s game on the opening kickoff and immediately left to be evaluated for a concussion. The long-time special teamer was later ruled out and will now need to clear concussion protocol if he hopes to suit up for Week 3 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4972-da67-a99f-cdf779660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared RB Jaleel McLaughlin inactive for Week 2 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4977-da67-a99f-cdf70e500000</link>
      <description>McLaughlin has lost his spot on the game day roster to passing game specialist, RB Tyler Badie. Broncos head coach Sean Payton and OC Joe Lombardi sang Badie’s praises this week, highlighting his ability to keep Bo Nix upright in pass protection. Badie also earned five targets against the Titans in Week 1. His usage reduces J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey’s fantasy-scoring projections for Nos. 1 and 2 RBs, J.K. Dobbins and RJ Harvey. Dobbins is a high-end RB3/FLEX. Harvey is a borderline RB3/4. The Broncos also declared LB Dre Greenlaw (quad), DL Sai’vion Jones, OLB Que Robinson, TE Nate Adkins, OT Frank Crum and QB Sam Ehlinger inactive for Week 2 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4977-da67-a99f-cdf70e500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow (toe) is questionable to return in Week 2 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4987-da67-a99f-cdf7f42d0000</link>
      <description>Burrow went down with the injury in the second quarter. He walked into the locker room after a brief stay in the medical tent and was unable to return despite the Bengals getting in two more drives before the end of the half. Jake Browning took his place in the lineup. Browning has successfully executed Zac Taylor’s game plan in the past, but losing Burrow would still be a devastating blow to the Bengals’ offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4987-da67-a99f-cdf7f42d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared DT Tershawn Wharton, WR Jimmy Horn Jr., OT Yosh Nijman, WR Dalevon Campbell, and TE James Mitchell inactive for Week 2 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4976-d86f-abdd-4dff7d4a0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers’ struggling run defense could be worse than usual in Week 2 against the run-first Cardinals with Wharton sidelined. Wharton could miss up to a month with a hamstring injury he sustained in Week 1’s blowout loss against the Jaguars. Carolina could be among the league’s softest front sevens with Wharton out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4976-d86f-abdd-4dff7d4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts declared EDGE Laiatu Latu, CB Charvarius Ward, RB Tyler Goodson, QB Riley Leonard, TE Will Mallory and OT Luke Tenuta inactive for Week 2 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4986-d86f-abdd-4dbf458b0000</link>
      <description>Latu is sidelined by a hamstring injury and Ward failed to clear the NFL’s concussion protocol. Both absences should make life easier on the Broncos’ passing offense. Goodson is rehabbing an elbow injury that kept him sidelined in Week 1. He practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday and Thursday before practicing in full on Friday, which seemingly put him on track to play. His inactive status suggests rookie RB DJ Giddens has already sewn up the No. 2 running back role behind Jonathan Taylor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4986-d86f-abdd-4dbf458b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Adams is questionable to return to Week 2 against the Bills with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-498f-d294-a19b-edff60610000</link>
      <description>Adams was dinged up early in the first quarter. He has his helmet in his hands on the sideline, but it seems unlikely that he will come back into this game. Adams really struggled in Week 1, so the Jets will turn to rookie Malachi Moore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-498f-d294-a19b-edff60610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals declared OL Will Hernandez, CB Elijah Jones, LB Xavier Thomas, WR Xavier Weaver, TE Tip Reiman, and LB Cody Simon inactive for Week 2 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4992-dc44-a9d9-4ff696cb0000</link>
      <description>Hernandez, dealing with a lingering knee issue, will miss his second straight game. The Cardinals offensive line should be OK against a poor Carolina front seven, however. Kyler Murray last week against the Saints was only hurried once and took two sacks, both of which he caused by refusing to throw the ball away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4992-dc44-a9d9-4ff696cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared TE Dallas Goedert, EDGE Azeez Ojulari, QB Tanner McKee, RB Will Shipley, EDGE Ogbo Okoronkwo and OL Drew Kendall inactive for Philadelphia’s Week 2 game against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-492d-d294-a19b-edfdb3340000</link>
      <description>No surprises here, Goedert and Shipley were ruled out on Friday. McKee was questionable with a right thumb injury that has not yet healed. The others are healthy scratches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-492d-d294-a19b-edfdb3340000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
