<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Werder reports the Cowboys and George Pickens have not engaged in contract extension talks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</link>
      <description>Well, yeah, that’s how the Cowboys do things. We have read a few columns out of Dallas arguing for a Pickens trade, but there seems to be no legitimate smoke on that. We’re anticipating a Pickens franchise tag or tag-and-trade in the offseason. Certainly nothing about the fit has been bad thus far with Pickens on pace for a little under 1,300 yards and 13 touchdowns through eight games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) said “I’m ready to go now” when asked about playing in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</link>
      <description>Things were trending the right way before this, but Jackson actually meeting the media all but confirms he’ll be back for Thursday night’s game against the Dolphins. He raises all boats on the Baltimore offense and is an easy QB1, even against a Dolphins defense coming off a surprising Week 8 win over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (hamstring) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</link>
      <description>It looks like Marcus Mariota’s latest stint as a stopgap superflex quarterback is done. The reporting on Daniels returning for Week 9 has been encouraging so far. We expect to do plenty of Daniels blurbs leading up to Seahawks-Commanders on Sunday night, and it wouldn’t be surprising if Daniels is limited in practice at times this week. But the Commanders need this game badly to avoid falling in a 3-6 hole and it would be surprising if it weren’t all hands on deck to take it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released K Matthew Wright.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c7f-dab4-a3fb-bf7fa3680000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign for Matt Gay’s availability for Week 9. Wright did not attempt a field goal against the Chiefs on Monday night as the Commanders scored seven points and went for two fourth downs with Marcus Mariota under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c7f-dab4-a3fb-bf7fa3680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent TE Marcedes Lewis visited with the Broncos on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cad-d245-adfb-bdff23d80000</link>
      <description>Denver is reportedly bracing to be without No. 2 tight end Nate Adkins for a bit, though nothing has officially been said on his status. They attempted to claim a pair of tight ends on waivers Monday and lost out on them due to priority. Lewis has been looking for One Last Job since the offseason started and could be an interesting fit in Denver as a blocker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cad-d245-adfb-bdff23d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Diontae Johnson visited the Giants on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</link>
      <description>Desperation will drive one to that. Darius Slayton was active again in Week 8 and Wan’Dale Robinson has been performing up to par, but sans Malik Nabers the Giants have had trouble finding another wideout they can count on. Johnson makes some sense given that idea — the baggage is there, but he can certainly earn some targets in a way that Jalin Hyatt has not yet proven he can.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2caf-deb1-a39b-2daf656e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams signed WR Tyler Scott to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ce9-deb1-a39b-2def2b920000</link>
      <description>Scott is a former fourth-round draft pick by the Bears, tallying 18 receptions for 173 yards in two seasons with the team. He was the odd man out in the Chicago pass-catching group heading into the season and was released in August. Scott has bounced around the Colts and Seahawks since then and now joins the Rams practice squad with Tutu Atwell hitting injured reserve. CB Tre Brown was cut in a corresponding move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2ce9-deb1-a39b-2def2b920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Julian Hill (ankle) did not participate in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf1-deb1-a39b-2dff6f940000</link>
      <description>Hill was listed as a non-participant for the second straight day due to an ankle issue. S Ashtyn Davis (quad) also has back-to-back DNPs to start the week. It will be difficult for either player to come back on a short week for a Thursday showdown against the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf1-deb1-a39b-2dff6f940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) was a full participant in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf8-dab4-a3fb-bff8e7c90000</link>
      <description>Jackson said himself that he is ready to go for Week 9 against the Dolphins. Back-to-back full practice participant listings support his statement as he returns to fantasy QB1 status for the rest of the season. Fantasy managers can safely fire Jackson up against a middling Dolphins defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cf8-dab4-a3fb-bff8e7c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Radio 810’s Jason Anderson reports Chiefs are signing DT Mike Pennel.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</link>
      <description>Pennel was briefly on the Bengals to begin this season, but was released on Tuesday. The Chiefs waste no time bringing the veteran back, after spending each of the last two seasons in Kansas City. Pennel will play a depth role again for the Chiefs’ defensive line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2cfd-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdffd40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
