<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e25-d713-ad9e-fe750dc70000</link>
      <description>This is somehow Etienne’s first appearance on the injury report this year. A limited session for a veteran is usually nothing more than a rest day. We will assume that is the case for Etienne for now. He should see plenty of work in Week 12 as a field goal favorite over the lowly Cardinals. Barring a surprise with this shoulder issue, Etienne is headed for an RB2 ranking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e25-d713-ad9e-fe750dc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams placed RT Rob Havenstein on injured reserve with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e20-d1e7-a1fa-deea36c50000</link>
      <description>The Rams’ right tackle has dealt with a high-ankle sprain for much of the season. Hopefully, this move allows him the time needed to fully rehab the injury. The Rams also officially placed S Quentin Lake on injured reserve after undergoing surgery to correct the dislocated elbow injury he suffered in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e20-d1e7-a1fa-deea36c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e29-d45b-affe-dfbf40d60000</link>
      <description>Tuten was on pace for a breakout of epic proportions in Week 11 before going down with the ankle injury. He still managed 74 yards and a touchdown on 15 attempts despite leaving in the second half. A limited session to open the week puts him on track to play in Week 12 versus Arizona. He will be behind Travis Etienne in the pecking order for carries, but the gap between the two is closing. Tuten should hit the RB3 ranks if he is cleared for action on the final injury report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e29-d45b-affe-dfbf40d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Kamara (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e2e-d713-ad9e-fe7e47070000</link>
      <description>Kamara has been playing through the ankle issue for most of the season and it has yet to cost him a game. This week will be no different. The Saints are favored at home against the down-bad Falcons, creating the potential for positive game script. That has been a rare sight for the 2-8 Saints this year. Kamara, in turn, will be a volume-based RB2 for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e2e-d713-ad9e-fe7e47070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) will not play in Week 12 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e34-d673-a39e-beb544700000</link>
      <description>Kincaid will miss a second game due to the hamstring injury he suffered in Week 10. He did not practice at all this week, so his absence doesn’t come as a surprise. The extra time between Thursday’s game and his Week 13 contest might be enough to get Kincaid back on the field. Dawson Knox will be a touchdown-based TE2 for Week 12 versus Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e34-d673-a39e-beb544700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (personal) will play in Week 12 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e3c-d45b-affe-dfbe9edf0000</link>
      <description>Shakir was excused from practice this week to be there for the birth of his daughter, Sunny Haven Shakir. He was not given a game-day status for Thursday’s contest, meaning he will be back with the team for kickoff versus Houston. Shakir will sit on the WR2/3 border for Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e3c-d45b-affe-dfbe9edf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curtis Samuel (neck/elbow) will not play in Week 12 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e41-d1e7-a1fa-deebcecb0000</link>
      <description>Mecole Hardman will also be sidelined for this game. Josh Palmer should be locked in as the Bills’ No. 2 receiver for Week 12. Gabe Davis and Tyrell Shavers will also be in the mix for routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e41-d1e7-a1fa-deebcecb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed K Matt Gay, formerly of the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e44-d673-a39e-bed58cc50000</link>
      <description>Eddy Piñeiro suffered a hamstring injury in Week 11 and is expected to miss some time. Gay will take his place in the lineup for now. The Commanders cut Gay on Monday after he missed two field goals versus Miami. Gay has missed six field goals on 19 attempts this year. All but one of his misses have come from 50 yards out, so the 49ers may only send him onto the field for short kicks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e44-d673-a39e-bed58cc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4b-d1e7-a1fa-deeb39310000</link>
      <description>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin told reporters yesterday he was optimistic about Warren playing in Week 12. Warren went down with the ankle injury in the second half of Sunday’s game versus the Bengals. He did not return, but both Warren and Tomlin have said he could have if needed. Today’s DNP might just be some rest for a banged-up player, but this is a situation fantasy managers will need to monitor throughout the week. Kenneth Gainwell would be in line for a massive role and an RB2 fantasy ranking if Warren can’t suit up this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4b-d1e7-a1fa-deeb39310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4f-d45b-affe-dfdfc8f60000</link>
      <description>Andy Reid mentioned before practice that Worthy could get in a limited session. The team ultimately chose to hold him out entirely. Reid did note that Worthy participated in the team’s walkthrough. There is still a chance he returns to practice later this week and can play on Sunday, but a DNP for the first session is typically an ominous sign. Worthy’s absence would be more work for Hollywood Brown, who has largely fallen by the wayside since the return of Rashee Rice. If active, Worthy will be a high-risk WR4 versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9e4f-d45b-affe-dfdfc8f60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
