<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:02:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports David Moore (elbow) “likely will miss multiple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c16-d95b-addb-fc56851c0000</link>
      <description>Rookie sixth-rounder Jimmy Horn — you may remember him as Travis Hunter’s Colorado teammate — will get a chance to ply his trade in Moore’s absence, with Dave Canales saying he wants to “make sure he’s able to go out there and give us significant reps. We’ll carve out a role because there’s certainly things he can bring to our offense with his speed and ability to carry the ball and make yards.” Horn could make an interesting pickup in deeper leagues right now with Hunter Renfrow not exactly blossoming last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c16-d95b-addb-fc56851c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Devonte Wyatt (knee) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c1d-dca3-a9fb-bd9d8a640000</link>
      <description>Wyatt’s injury appeared to be a big factor in Green Bay’s trouble stopping Dallas on Sunday night. Nazir Stackhouse and Karl Brooks filled in inside, but neither is as effective as the 2022 first-rounder had been in the first few games of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c1d-dca3-a9fb-bd9d8a640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c2c-d95b-addb-fc6eb34d0000</link>
      <description>Most importantly, when asked about Purdy, Shanahan said he’d play “if we feel he can play up to 100 percent of his ability.” Mac Jones was interviewed by reporters on Tuesday. Purdy looked shaky and was sailing some balls against the Jaguars in Week 4’s return. Jones could be in line for another start against the Rams in Week 5. We already learned that Purdy would be questionable earlier this morning from John Lynch, but this is a discouraging sign for his chances of being active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c2c-d95b-addb-fc6eb34d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c69-dca3-a9fb-bdf9bb080000</link>
      <description>After saying that he felt some instability in his knee following Sunday’s loss, we’re not surprised to see Pearsall not practicing today. John Lynch said earlier this morning that he’d be on the questionable line for Week 5. We’d ultimately be very surprised if he played.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c69-dca3-a9fb-bdf9bb080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder/ankle/ribs) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c6b-d6e9-af9d-9efb1b820000</link>
      <description>Jennings seems very unlikely to go on Thursday against the Rams, but has not yet been officially ruled out. If Jennings and Ricky Pearsall are both out, this passing game could go almost exclusively through Christian McCaffrey in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c6b-d6e9-af9d-9efb1b820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins waived CB Cam Smith.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c6d-deb6-a7fd-dfff925e0000</link>
      <description>The 2023 second-rounder was on the non-football injury list. He managed just 155 snaps over two years with the Dolphins and will go down as a big whiff by Chris Grier with the 51st overall pick. Smith will look to catch on elsewhere once healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c6d-deb6-a7fd-dfff925e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Drew Rosenhaus said that Tyreek Hill’s “realistic goal” is to be ready for the start of the 2026 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c84-dca3-a9fb-bd9daeb80000</link>
      <description>What team he’s with at that point, we do not know. Apparently there’s no nerve damage or cartilage issues for Hill, so even though the surgery is complex, there’s a chance he’ll be ready to go at the start of the 2026 season. We’d be surprised if the 32-year-old, coming off a major and complex knee injury, was more than a WR3 dart throw in 2026. But it can’t be completely ruled out at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c84-dca3-a9fb-bd9daeb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed CB Tre Flowers to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9cea-d6e9-af9d-9efa1d480000</link>
      <description>According to KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson, the Lions signed Flowers to their practice squad on Tuesday. The 30-year-old veteran began his career with the Seahawks and bounced around since then, totaling four interceptions and 22 passes defended in seven seasons. With injuries to Terrion Arnold and D.J. Reed, Flowers adds depth to the Lions’ secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9cea-d6e9-af9d-9efa1d480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Buccaneers RB Bucky Irving is “gathering medical opinions” on a potential foot/ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d18-dca3-a9fb-bd9934c80000</link>
      <description>Irving seemingly hurt his foot or ankle in the Buccaneers’ Week 4 loss to the Eagles. He still played the full game, including a 72-yard touchdown catch in the second half, but his status for Week 5 is still up in the air. Head coach Todd Bowles said Irving would undergo an MRI on Monday, but come Tuesday, Irving is still getting information on his injury. If he does miss time, Rachaad White is propelled up to fantasy RB2 status while Sean Tucker is a waiver add.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d18-dca3-a9fb-bd9934c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee did not participate in Tuesday’s walkthrough practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d77-d6e9-af9d-9ff78b460000</link>
      <description>Higbee was listed as a non-participant for the second straight day with a hip injury that first popped up last week. He played in Week 4, catching 2-of-5 targets for 25 yards after suffering the hip injury last Thursday. Higbee was active after missing last Friday’s practice, so this may be precautionary, but it is a short week for the Rams. Wednesday’s report will show if Higbee is ready to play Thursday against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9d77-d6e9-af9d-9ff78b460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
