<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 03:14:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT DaQuan Jones (calf) will not play in Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfd6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7786d0000</link>
      <description>Jones reportedly suffered a calf injury in pre-game warmups and will not play against the Falcons in Week 6. Jones leads Buffalo’s defensive tackles in snaps played this season and the team will likely adopt a looser rotation at the position to fill the void.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-dfd6-dd4c-afb9-ffd7786d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Joshua Palmer (lower leg) is questionable to return to Week 6 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e008-def2-abdb-fd699fba0000</link>
      <description>Palmer was tackled awkwardly in the second quarter Monday as he appeared to have his leg caught under him and twisted. He remained down on the field before being helped to the medical tent. No further update has yet to be provided from the team, but it did not look good in real time. Palmer caught both targets for 60 yards prior to the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e008-def2-abdb-fd699fba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen completed 15-of-26 passes for 180 yards, two touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Bills’ 24-14, Week 6 loss to the Falcons, adding 42 yards on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e087-dd4c-afb9-e7c7d1d70000</link>
      <description>The Bills couldn’t overcome mounting injuries against the Falcons, managing just 291 yards of offense while scoring their only points of the game on their first possession of each half. Defensive tackle DaQuan Jones was injured in pre-game warmups and did not suit up, wide receiver Joshua Palmer departed early in the second quarter with an ankle injury and did not return, and linebacker Terrel Bernard was injured at the end of the first quarter and did not return. Those key injuries simultaneously paved the way for Bijan Robinson to amass 238 yards of total offense and forced the Bills into a more one-dimensional offense absent their downfield threat. Overcoming injuries is not anything new for the Bills, but it sure seems to be an unwanted similarity when looking back at their recent seasons. The Bills fall to 4-2 with the loss after dropping their second in a row, heading into their bye week tied with the Patriots atop the AFC East, with the Patriots now holding the tiebreaker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e087-dd4c-afb9-e7c7d1d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 17 times for 87 yards in the Bills’ Week 6 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e08e-dd4c-afb9-e7cf98400000</link>
      <description>He gained more yards on the team’s first possession of the second half than he did the rest of the game, which highlights the general inability of the Buffalo offense to move the football consistently amidst mounting injuries. Losing field stretcher Joshua Palmer early in the second quarter left the offense in a state of one-dimensionality they were unable to overcome in the face of consistent pressure from an aggressive Atlanta defensive front. Cook’s splits in wins versus losses this season are stark, something fantasy managers hope alter course when the Bills exit their Week 8 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e08e-dd4c-afb9-e7cf98400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 3-of-6 targets for 33 yards in the Bills’ Week 6 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e093-db72-a199-fadb73960000</link>
      <description>The fact that Joshua Palmer led the team in receiving on just over one quarter’s worth of play sums up the night for the Bills, who were left completely unable to move the football with any consistency the rest of the way. Shakir tied with second-year wide receiver Keon Coleman in targets, meaning little considering Josh Allen attempted only 26 passes. The Bills surely have aspects of their game to correct as they head into their Week 7 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e093-db72-a199-fadb73960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught 1-of-2 targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 6 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e096-dd4c-afb9-e7d7a88c0000</link>
      <description>Knox scored on the team’s first possession of the game and saw just one more target the rest of the way. He was thrust into a lead role after Dalton Kincaid was ruled inactive, playing elevated snaps alongside Jackson Hawes as the team played primarily from 12-personnel. The increase in snap rate did little for his fantasy upside and fantasy managers can safely leave him on the waiver wire moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e096-dd4c-afb9-e7d7a88c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Davis caught both targets for 19 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 6 loss to the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e09b-d94a-a79d-e99f2ac50000</link>
      <description>He did not receive a carry behind James Cook but managed to score from 16 yards out on the team’s first possession of the second half, playing limited snaps the rest of the game. Davis would likely need an injury to Cook to return any meaningful fantasy upside .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e09b-d94a-a79d-e99f2ac50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Penix completed 20-of-32 passes for 250 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ 24-14, Week 6 win over the Bills, adding six yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e09d-dd4c-afb9-e7dd6af20000</link>
      <description>Penix and the Falcons came out firing on all cylinders, scoring touchdowns on two of their first three possessions to have the Bills playing from behind from the jump. He leaned on his top two options in Drake London and Bijan Robinson as the team played without Darnell Mooney, targeting the top play makers on 24 of his 32 pass attempts. 226 of Penix’s 250 yards also were accounted for by the duo as the Bills had no answers. In all, it was a consistent showing for Penix even though the fantasy returns were less than appealing. Up next for the 3-2 Falcons are the 49ers on the road in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e09d-dd4c-afb9-e7dd6af20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bijan Robinson rushed 19 times for 170 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 6 win over the Bills, adding 68 yards on six receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0a2-d94a-a79d-e9affa260000</link>
      <description>The highlight of the game for Robinson was an 81-yard touchdown run on an outside zone attempt at the beginning of the second quarter to put the team up by two scores, which went down as the longest run of Robinson’s already electric career. He accounted for over half of the team’s 443 total yards of offense on a night they played without Darnell Mooney due to injury, also combining with alpha wide receiver Drake London to account for 236 of quarterback Michael Penix’s 250 yards through the air. It was a truly dominant performance from one of the league’s top backs, and he’ll look to keep the momentum going when the Falcons travel to the Bay area to face the 49ers in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0a2-d94a-a79d-e9affa260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed 10 times for 32 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 6 win over the Bills, adding six yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0a7-def2-abdb-fde741030000</link>
      <description>Allgeier was handily outperformed by both Bijan Robinson and Drake London, the latter two of whom combined to account for 406 yards of the team’s 443 yards of total offense against the Bills. It would likely take an injury to Robinson for Allgeier to carry any meaningful fantasy value moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-e0a7-def2-abdb-fde741030000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
