<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 21:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LB Jonathan Greenard will not return in Week 10 against the Ravens due to a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a44-d713-ad9e-6e548f0d0000</link>
      <description>Greenard exited in the third quarter and could be seen favoring his shoulder while making his way to the medical tent. The veteran pass rusher was ruled out shortly after exiting, leaving the Vikings defense short in a game they trailed 19-10 at the time of his injury. Greenard has totaled 18 tackles and two sacks for the Vikings this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a44-d713-ad9e-6e548f0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman caught both of his targets for 19 yards in the Colts’ Week 10 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a3f-d45b-affe-7fbf03700000</link>
      <description>Tyler Warren operated as the team’s top pass-catcher in this game, easily leading the way with 10 targets. Alec Pierce was also heavily involved, seeing seven looks. There simply weren’t enough touches to go around with those two players stepping up and Jonathan Taylor seeing 35 touches. Better days should be ahead for Pittman, but an increase in looks for Warren could cut into his role. He will get at least one more week in the WR2 ranks when the Colts return from their upcoming bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a3f-d45b-affe-7fbf03700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp (hamstring) is active for Week 10 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a48-d673-a39e-eed99cb90000</link>
      <description>Kupp was questionable to suit up in Week 10 after sitting out Week 9’s win over Washington with the hamstring issue. Meanwhile, the Seahawks will be without Tory Horton against the Cards. Kupp could be the team’s WR3 if the newly-acquired Rashid Shaheed emerges as a viable downfield threat for Sam Darnold. Seahawks declared WR Jake Bobo, WR Tory Horton, DE Jared Ivey, CB Josh Jobe, LB Ernest Jones, QB Jalen Milroe, and OT Mason Richman inactive against Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a48-d673-a39e-eed99cb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart (concussion) exited the Giants’ Week 10 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4a-d713-ad9e-6e5e42260000</link>
      <description>Dart took a wicked head shot late in the third quarter and fumbled the ball away to the Bears. He was reportedly evaluated for a concussion and helped to the Giants’ locker room at the start of the fourth quarter. It would be surprising if Dart was able to return to the game. That leaves Russell Wilson as the Giants’ starting quarterback. It’s a downgrade for all New York pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4a-d713-ad9e-6e5e42260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills EDGE Landon Jackson suffered a knee injury in Week 10 and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4a-d673-a39e-eedb518c0000</link>
      <description>Jackson left in the first half and was spotted on the sidelines with crutches later in the game. The rookie was also sporting a brace on his right knee. It looks like he will be sidelined well beyond just the rest of this game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4a-d673-a39e-eedb518c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid suffered a hamstring in Week 10 against the Dolphins and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4f-d1e7-a1fa-7aefb3160000</link>
      <description>Kincaid hobbled off the field in the third quarter, unable to put any weight on his injured hamstring. He was taken to the locker room before being ruled out. Dawson Knox is the next man up at tight end. Rookie Jackson Hawes could also see more work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a4f-d1e7-a1fa-7aefb3160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals S Budda Baker (hamstring) is active for Week 10 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a54-d1e7-a1fa-7afe89c60000</link>
      <description>Baker was limited through most of the week in practice but will suit up against Seattle after practicing in full on Friday. Cardinals declared OT Josh Fryar, OT Demontrey Jacobs, CB Will Johnson, CB Max Melton, DT Bilal Nichols, WR Xavier Weaver, and LB Mack Wilson inactive against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a54-d1e7-a1fa-7afe89c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 1-of-2 targets for three yards in the Colts’ Week 10 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a53-d673-a39e-eed397ec0000</link>
      <description>Downs had seemingly established a PPR floor heading into this game with six catches in three of his past four games. He also had a touchdown in three straight games entering Sunday morning. Downs has emerged as a strong third receiver for the Colts over the past month, but his role leaves a lot to be desired. It also drastically drops his fantasy floor, even if he’s more than capable of stringing together a month of usable performances. He will be ranked in the WR4 range when the Colts face the Chiefs coming out of their Week 11 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a53-d673-a39e-eed397ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart (concussion) was ruled out in Week 10 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a60-d45b-affe-7ff614ce0000</link>
      <description>Dart appeared to be out cold on the turf after taking a head shot from a Chicago defender late in the third quarter. He did not return to the game in the fourth quarter. Dart will enter the NFL’s concussion protocol and could be iffy to suit up in Week 11 against the Packers. That would leave Russell Wilson as the team’s starter — a marked downgrade for Giants pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a60-d45b-affe-7ff614ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young completed 17-of-25 passes for 124 yards and an interception in the Panthers’ 17-7, Week 10 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d713-ad9e-6d7c10130000</link>
      <description>Young had 26 yards passing on the Panthers’ 12-play, 67-yard opening drive that went for a touchdown. He couldn’t lead Carolina to any more points on the board for the rest of the game, though. Young and the Panthers trailed 10-7 against the one-win Saints at halftime. He lost a fumble in the third quarter and threw an interception in the fourth quarter. Five plays after his interception, the Saints scored a touchdown to take a commanding 10-point lead. The Panthers take on the Falcons on the road in Week 11, where they’ll surely try to hide Young as much as possible while Rico Dowdle continues to be the centerpiece of the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-697c-d713-ad9e-6d7c10130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
