<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 02:29:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings WRs Jordan Addison and Tai Felton left practice early on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c925-de13-afdc-cfefbb800000</link>
      <description>We don’t have confirmed status updates from the team yet, but The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes Addison jammed “something” and that Felton “looked like he dinged his arm.” Felton, per ESPN’s Kevin Seifert, walked off the field with a wrap on his left hand. If there’s one thing that would accelerate trade talks for wideouts ahead of last cuts, it’s more injuries to this room. The Vikings should update Addison’s (and Felton’s) status in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c925-de13-afdc-cfefbb800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said both Tyler Shough and Spencer Rattler will play in New Orleans’ preseason finale.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c937-de13-afdc-cfff07150000</link>
      <description>He declined to give an order of play, though it seemed like Rattler was up first in practice today. The last starting quarterback should be announced in the next week or so — whether it’s Rattler or Shough, it’s hard to believe either player will remain the starter all season based on how tight the process has been. Neither of them qualify as desirable options even in superflex leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c937-de13-afdc-cfff07150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nicki Jhabvala reports Terry McLaurin asked for “more than DK Metcalf.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c973-dbe3-a9bb-f9734a010000</link>
      <description>Metcalf got a four-year, $132 million extension with the Steelers this offseason, but is also both younger than McLaurin and had more leverage after the Steelers surrendered a second-round pick to acquire him. The contract that the Commanders point to is Courtland Sutton, who signed a four-year, $92 million deal earlier in training camp. There’s a canyon between Metcalf’s $33 million a year and Sutton’s $23 million — it’s likely that McLaurin will have to settle for something closer to the midpoint of those two numbers than what Metcalf got. Unless of course he’d like his holdout to continue into the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c973-dbe3-a9bb-f9734a010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Demarcus Robinson was suspended three games for violating the NFL’s substance abuse policy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c99a-dbe3-a9bb-f9db52f20000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kyle Shanahan told KNBR radio that Robinson is slated to miss three games for violating the NFL’s substance abuse policy. The 30-year-old signed with the 49ers after two season in the Rams’ receiving room. He was potentially going to be a key receiver for the team with Brandon Aiyuk (knee) likely out well into the season and Jauan Jennings (calf) also injured. Robinson also dealt with a DUI charge early in the offseason and was faced with a suspension from that, so a suspension for substances is an interesting turn of events. Robinson’s early season absence means even more opportunities for Ricky Pearsall and keeps open the likelihood the 49ers try to add another veteran receiver before the season starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c99a-dbe3-a9bb-f9db52f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jacob Cowing missed Wednesday’s practice with a hamstring strain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9a3-d332-a1fd-dfb76b770000</link>
      <description>Cowing strained his hamstring in practice last month. Just as he was set to return, he now suffers a setback, having strained his hamstring again in Tuesday’s practice. The 49ers wideout group continues to take hits, with Demarcus Robinson facing suspension and Jordan Watkins (ankle), Brandon Aiyuk (knee), and Jauan Jennings (calf) all out for now. Ricky Pearsall seems to be the only wide receiver slated for targets, but the 49ers may shop around for a veteran to add to the mix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9a3-d332-a1fd-dfb76b770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired DT Harrison Phillips and a 2027 seventh-round pick from the Vikings in exchange for 2026 and 2027 sixth-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ad-dbe3-a9bb-f9ffc9950000</link>
      <description>The Jets added their second defensive lineman of the day, acquiring Phillips from the Vikings after getting Jowon Briggs from the Browns. Phillips is a seven-year veteran who has split time with the Bills and Vikings. He started all 51 games for Minnesota over the last three seasons and tallied two sacks, 56 combined tackles, and a forced fumble last season. The Jets beef up their defensive line heading into year one under defensive-minded head coach Aaron Glenn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ad-dbe3-a9bb-f9ffc9950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints acquired WR Devaughn Vele from the Broncos in exchange for a 2026 sixth-round pick and 2027 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9bb-dbe3-a9bb-f9fba5cd0000</link>
      <description>Vele heads to the Saints after a productive rookie season with the Broncos in 2025. He was a 26-year-old rookie, posting 41 receptions for 475 yards and three touchdowns while primarily working out of the slot. An offseason knee procedure limited Vele in camp, while the emergence of second-year receiver Troy Franklin and rookie Pat Bryant made him more expendable. The Saints add Vele’s 6-foot-5 frame to a receiver room in need of reinforcement behind Chris Olave and Rashid Shaheed. Vele has some value as a late-round dart throw in fantasy drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9bb-dbe3-a9bb-f9fba5cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer believes EDGE Micah Parsons will play Week 1 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9c3-de13-afdc-cfcb72740000</link>
      <description>Schottenheimer said, “I feel good that Micah will be out there against the Philadelphia Eagles.” Parsons and the Cowboys are still at a contract impasse, with little to no progress being made on a new deal. The 26-year-old has also reportedly been dealing with back tightness while he holds out. Schottenheimer’s vote of confidence doesn’t have much substance behind it in terms of Parsons’ progression back to practice, but things can change quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9c3-de13-afdc-cfcb72740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams offensive coordinator Mike LaFleur said, “the more opportunities [RB Jarquez Hunter] gets, the better it’s going to be.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9cd-d332-a1fd-dfffc7310000</link>
      <description>The Rams drafted the 22-year-old Hunter in the fourth-round of April’s draft. He brings pass-catching upside to the Rams backfield and has received praise from the Rams’ coaching staff throughout camp. This spells bad news for Blake Corum, who did not carve out a sizeable role last season. Kyren Williams is still slated to take the vast majority of backfield touches, but Hunter can mix in on passing downs and earn handcuff value for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9cd-d332-a1fd-dfffc7310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers acquired WR Skyy Moore from the Chiefs in exchange for swapping 2027 sixth and seventh-round picks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ed-d332-a1fd-dfffe8830000</link>
      <description>Moore was a second-round pick in the 2022 NFL Draft, but could never really stick with the Chiefs’ receiving corps. He caught 43 passes for 494 yards and a touchdown over his first two seasons, while failing to catch any of his three targets last season. Moore adds value as a returner, recently returning a punt for a touchdown in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 2 game. The 49ers’ receiver group has been decimated by injuries and the recent suspension to Demarcus Robinson. They now add Moore, who is a shot in the dark at some production from the receiver spot. He is unlikely to hold fantasy relevance heading into the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-c9ed-d332-a1fd-dfffe8830000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
