<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 01:29:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan said the team could open WR Brandon Aiyuk’s (knee) 21-day practice window next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180e-d245-adfb-9d5f99da0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan adds that the team is in “week-to-week” territory for opening Aiyuk’s practice window. Aiyuk can be stashed on fantasy benches at this time, but the 49ers could still delay the practice window by a week or two, and then there is the matter of whether Aiyuk actually uses up most of said window. While this report is positive, there is still a wide range of potential outcomes at play here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-180e-d245-adfb-9d5f99da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints waived RB Velus Jones Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-181d-dab4-a3fb-9b7dbf240000</link>
      <description>Jones was waived to make room for recent signee, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, formerly of the Ravens. Mitchell-Paden caught 1-of-2 targets for three yards this year. He entered the league as a 2022 undrafted free agent but had not taken any live receiving snaps until now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-181d-dab4-a3fb-9b7dbf240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LB Matt Milano (pectoral) is questionable to play in Week 8 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182e-d5d8-a3ff-f96ff6bb0000</link>
      <description>Fellow Bills’ LB Terrel Bernard (ankle) is also questionable, as is rookie CB Maxwell Hairston (knee). DT DaQuan Jones (calf) and S Taylor Rapp (knee) have both been ruled out. The injuries should allow the Panthers to continue running ball efficiently with RBs Rico Dowdle and Chuba Hubbard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182e-d5d8-a3ff-f96ff6bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out WR Nico Collins (concussion) for Week 8 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1835-dab4-a3fb-9b754a4b0000</link>
      <description>Both Collins and slot receiver Christian Kirk (hamstring) failed to practice all week. The injuries leave WRs Xavier Hutchinson, Jayden Higgins, Jaylin Noel and Braxton Berrios as a likely four-player platoon. While Noel led Texans wide receivers with 77 yards last week, he was stuck splitting slot snaps with Berrios. Noel can be expected to play efficiently, but he may be stuck in a positional rotation again this week. Noel, Hutchinson and Higgins are all on the FLEX radar, with Higgins and Noel likely possessing the highest upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1835-dab4-a3fb-9b754a4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans ruled out WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) for Week 8 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182c-d5d8-a3ff-f96d2b380000</link>
      <description>With Kirk sidelined in Week 7, veteran WR Braxton Berrios and exciting rookie WR Jaylin Noel split snaps. Noel led the receiving corps with 77 yards while Berrios finished with minus-one. Noel’s upside may be capped by Berrios’ presence, but he looked like the most capable, healthy Texans wide receiver last week after Nico Collins (concussion) was forced from play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-182c-d5d8-a3ff-f96d2b380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Dalton Schultz (back/shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 8 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1829-dab4-a3fb-9b796e2a0000</link>
      <description>Schultz’s removal from the injury report is great news for Texans QB C.J. Stroud, who relied heavily upon Schultz in Week 7. Schultz led the team with nine catches for 98 yards and is a candidate to operate as a featured pass catcher again this week. He is a TE1 with decent upside against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1829-dab4-a3fb-9b796e2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nate Taylor reports that Chiefs LT Josh Simmons “is expected to rejoin the team in a few weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1853-deb1-a39b-395fe9840000</link>
      <description>Yesterday, The Athletic’s Jesse Newell identified Week 11 as a “natural target date” for Simmons to resume playing. Taylor agrees, writing, “a logical time for Simmons to return to the Chiefs could be in early November, during the team’s bye” in Week 10. Until Simmons returns, veteran OT Jaylon Moore will continue manning the left tackle spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1853-deb1-a39b-395fe9840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Ravens are “preparing for Lamar Jackson (hamstring) to be out there starting” in Week 8 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1883-d245-adfb-9ddf79050000</link>
      <description>To be clear, Rapoport stopped short of saying that Jackson will play this week, and instead included a lengthy preface and qualifying language during the segment. The team has publicly taken the position that Jackson will be allowed to determine his ownreadinessthis weekend. Per Rapoport, “it does seem like Lamar Jackson is preparing to start.” The team reportedly just wants to “get through the next day or so to make sure that the MVP is back.” This story is worth following closely over the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1883-d245-adfb-9ddf79050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that J.J. McCarthy (ankle) “is going to be the starting quarterback for the Vikings, assuming he is healthy, which they believe he will be.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-188b-dab4-a3fb-9bfbbec50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport harped on the importance of full practice participation, saying the Vikings “want J.J. McCarthy to be successful,” and “in order to do that, you have to practice.” McCarthy’s “additional workouts” and “meetings” with head coach Kevin O’Connell have been undertaken in an effort to get the injured youngster up to speed. O’Connell has proven himself as a capable quarterback developer. For Vikings fans and fantasy managers alike, one must trust the process. If McCarthy is deemed healthy enough to play, he will be under center in Week 9 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-188b-dab4-a3fb-9bfbbec50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Cameron Wolfe said it “sounds like” QB Bryce Young’s ankle injury is “just a one-week injury” and the “hope” is he plays in Week 9 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-18ac-d5d8-a3ff-f9edf0bb0000</link>
      <description>The Panthers listed Young as doubtful to play in Week 8 against the Bills, rather than ruling him out immediately on Friday, so a Week 9 return makes sense. Over the last three weeks, Young finished as the QB23, QB12 and QB24. He will likely return to the low-end QB2 ranks against the Packers’ talented defense, if active next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-18ac-d5d8-a3ff-f9edf0bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
