<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Penix completed 12-of-28 passes for 177 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ 31-25, Week 10 overtime loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a02-d45b-affe-7f96fa7b0000</link>
      <description>Penix could not get anything going when he was forced to target someone other than Drake London. Atlanta’s star wideout caught 6-of-8 targets for 104 yards and a score. Penix went 6-of-22 when throwing to anyone else. That included Darnelly Mooney reeling in one catch on eight targets. Both Mooney and Kyle Pitts failed to do Penix any favors with multiple drops between the two pass-catchers. The Falcons are operating a run-first offense and Penix brings nothing to the table with his legs. His struggles as a passer make it almost impossible for him to spike a week for fantasy purposes. Penix will sit at the back of the QB2 ranks for Week 11 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a02-d45b-affe-7f96fa7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) is questionable to return in Week 10 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a16-d713-ad9e-6e5643fe0000</link>
      <description>Slayton hobbled to the blue medical tent late in the second quarter after racking up 85 yards on three receptions, including an impressive one-handed catch in traffic. It would be something of a surprise if he were able to return to action in the second half. Jaxson Dart is likely to be without his main downfield pass catcher as the Giants try to upset the Bears in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a16-d713-ad9e-6e5643fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans S M.J. Stewart (leg) left Houston’s Week 10 game against the Jaguars and won’t return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a19-d713-ad9e-6e5d35950000</link>
      <description>He left on a cart and in an aircast, it would be surprising if he weren’t ruled out for the rest of the season. Myles Bryant replaced Stewart, and the Texans will likely have Jimmie Ward replacing him at some point down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a19-d713-ad9e-6e5d35950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London caught 6-of-8 targets for 104 yards and a touchdown in the Falcons’ Week 10 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a0d-d1e7-a1fa-7aefb5ca0000</link>
      <description>London was the only player the Falcons could get going in the passing game. He accounted for well over half of the team’s total output through the air and came down with Michael Penix’s only touchdown of the day. London was shaken up after hitting the ground hard on his touchdown. He spent some time in the medical tent but was cleared to return without receiving an injury designation. It will be something to watch on the Falcons’ injury report this week, but he played through the issue for the remainder of the game. Barring a surprise in practice, London will remain in the WR1 ranks for Week 11 against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a0d-d1e7-a1fa-7aefb5ca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings was forced from New England’s Week 10 game against the Bucs with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a15-d673-a39e-ee9548050000</link>
      <description>The second-year UDFA got the start over TreVeyon Henderson and was featuring early, albeit in an ineffective fashion. He was then announced as questionable in the second quarter and was ruled out after the break. It has predictably thrust Henderson into a bigger role, though it has also gotten recent signee D’Ernest Johnson onto the field. Failing to return with a knee injury often presages a multi-week absence, so stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a15-d673-a39e-ee9548050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts caught 2-of-5 targets for 38 yards in the Falcons’ Week 10 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a1d-d45b-affe-7f9fa0b80000</link>
      <description>Pitts committed a ghastly drop that would have been a long gain, if not a touchdown. Later in the game, Michael Penix had him open for a deep shot into the end zone and underthrew him for an incompletion. He could have posted a strong fantasy performance had either play turned out differently. Instead, fantasy managers were left holding the bag on his worst game in a month. With Drake London hogging targets and the passing game as a whole struggling, Pitts will return to the TE2 ranks for Week 11 versus the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a1d-d45b-affe-7f9fa0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (shoulder) is questionable to return in Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a27-d1e7-a1fa-7aefa4b10000</link>
      <description>Moore landed hard on his right arm in the second quarter and did not return to the game after halftime. He would seem to be done for the day. Moore had zero catches on three targets before he sustained the shoulder injury. He’s been mostly used as a gadget player in Ben Johnson’s offense this year. A Moore absence could open up more snaps and routes for Luther Burden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a27-d1e7-a1fa-7aefa4b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooeny caught 1-of-8 targets for 17 yards in the Falcons’ Week 10 loss to the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a25-d713-ad9e-6e7596740000</link>
      <description>Mooney committed multiple drops on a day when the Falcons desperately needed a second pass-catcher to step up. He has now caught exactly one pass in three straight games. Drops and missed opportunities have been a headline feature of his slump. Mooney has been banged up throughout the year, which could be contributing to his poor play. Either way, fantasy managers should put him on the bench until he turns things around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a25-d713-ad9e-6e7596740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught 4-of-7 targets for 84 yards and a touchown in the Colts’ Week 10 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a2c-d713-ad9e-6e7c5c320000</link>
      <description>The NFL’s leader in yards per catch got home again this week with a 37-yard score in the first quarter. Pierce has at least 67 yards in 5-of-7 games this year. He has quietly become one of the league’s premier deep threats and the Colts’ offense is perfect for creating those big-play opportunities. He will sit in the WR3 ranks when the Colts return from their Week 11 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a2c-d713-ad9e-6e7c5c320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Azareye’h Thomas suffered a concussion in New York’s Week 10 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a31-d713-ad9e-6e7552230000</link>
      <description>Thomas looked like he was going to be backboarded in the second quarter before thankfully making his way to the sideline under his own power. The No. 73 overall pick of the draft, Thomas had been playing roughly 30 weekly snaps but is ticketed for a bigger role in the absence of Sauce Gardner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6a31-d713-ad9e-6e7552230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
