<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 18:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (wrist) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe40fa0000</link>
      <description>Golden is good to go for his fantasy-unfriendly role as a rotational wide receiver. Golden could catch a long pass, but he does not have the snap share requisite for season-long, re-draft FLEX consideration. He does not need to be rostered at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe40fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe3b400000</link>
      <description>Reed and WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) are ready to rock against the Broncos this week. Both players are forced to play efficiently thanks to the team’s deep receiving corps, but Reed can still be started in the FLEX. Wicks is a bit more volatile, but is capable of making big plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-149c-d8cf-affb-bcbe3b400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (illness) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 15 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14b0-d77b-adfb-deb3e7f70000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey practiced fully on Friday after logging a limited session on Thursday. He can be treated as an elite RB1, per usual, against the Titans this week. He leads the NFL with 322 touches this season, boasting 59 missed tackles forced per PFF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14b0-d77b-adfb-deb3e7f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers TE Darnell Washington (concussion) was limited on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e0-d77b-adfb-dee316cc0000</link>
      <description>That is unfortunate. One would hope to see Washington increase his participation every day, as he works his way through the NFL’s five-phase concussion protocol. It is possible he stalled out in the third phase. Hopefully, he upgrades to full tomorrow and can be on the field when his team faces the Dolphins on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e0-d77b-adfb-dee316cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said it “certainly seems like” QB Philip Rivers will start for the Colts in Week 15 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e4-d8cf-affb-bcee46860000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s segment broke no news, but he has ostensibly been working the phones since last night’s pre-game report. Rivers is taking “some” first-team reps and, per Rapoport, is throwing the football “well.” Rookie QB Riley Leonard would seemingly have a better chance of rushing his way to QB2 viability, but the Colts apparently prefer Rivers’ theoretical pocket-passing ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-14e4-d8cf-affb-bcee46860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the franchise tag is “potentially” in play for Falcons TE Kyle Pitts at the end of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</link>
      <description>Pitts is in the fifth and final year of his rookie contract. Last night, he caught 11-of-12 targets for 166 yards and three touchdowns in the Falcons’ Thursday Night Football victory over the Buccaneers. Before the game, Falcons owner Arthur Blank reportedly visited the NFL Network’s pre-game broadcast set. Rapoport followed up the visit with a televised report saying Blank will “evaluate” all football operations after the season. Although head coach Raheem Morris and general manager Terry Fontenot may end up being let go, Pitts may have played his way into a new contract, or at least a one-year deal on the lucrative franchise tag. Rapoport notes, though, that Pitts’ agent, David Mulugheta, “hates the franchise tag” and could play hardball in pursuit of a long-term deal. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1527-d77b-adfb-dfa7b1370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Bears are optimistic WR Rome Odunze (foot) will play in Week 15’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10e6-d77b-adfb-dae7ae440000</link>
      <description>Odunze is listed as questionable with a foot injury after missing last week’s Bears loss in Green Bay. The 23-year-old wide receiver practiced all week in a limited fashion. Odunze had just two catches and eight yards in his last game action against the Eagles in Week 13. If active, he’ll be a risky FLEX option for desperate teams in the first round of the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-10e6-d77b-adfb-dae7ae440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (concussion) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186a-d8cf-affb-bc6a4e990000</link>
      <description>Jennings was already ruled out for Week 15’s matchup with the Bills, but now he’s set to miss the next four games after being placed on injured reserve. Jennings had already seen his role in the offense evaporate with the return of Rhamondre Stevenson. D’Ernest Johnson will serve as the Patriots’ third running back in Jennings’ absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186a-d8cf-affb-bc6a4e990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fowler: Colts QB Philip Rivers is trending towards starting against the Seahawks in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186e-d77b-adfb-daef29180000</link>
      <description>While Rivers hasn’t officially been named the starter, reports that it seems like he’ll start against the Seahawks continue to pile up. Riley Leonard (knee) practiced in full all week and has no injury designation, but the Colts seem convinced after last week’s loss to the Jaguars that Rivers, who has a wealth of experience that includes familiarity with Shane Steichen’s offense from his Chargers days, gives them the best chance to win. Rivers isn’t a recommended fantasy option in his first game action since January 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-186e-d77b-adfb-daef29180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Colts QB Philip Rivers will start against the Seahawks in Week 15.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</link>
      <description>Schefter reports that the Colts are signing Rivers to the active roster. The quarterback who turned 44 earlier this week and ranks seventh in all-time passing yards entering Week 15 was a semifinalist for this year’s Pro Football Hall of Fame class. Rivers will now have to wait another five years before he’s eligible again, assuming he retires again after this season. Fantasy managers considering using the signal caller who was in the same draft class as Eli Manning, who last played in 2019, in the fantasy playoffs have lost the plot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1882-d1bc-a3fb-9da6b5e00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
