<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 2-of-4 targets for 68 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</link>
      <description>Per usual, Doubs was the Packers’ most trusted receiver, leading the team in routes. He ran a route on 18-of-24 Jordan Love dropbacks. He also finished second on the team in targets behind only Jayden Reed. Doubs isn’t the flashiest fantasy option, but his role is secure and he plays on an offense that won’t have any issues putting up points. He will stick in the WR4/5 range for Week 2 against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-271f-de13-afdd-67df87e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chig Okonkwo caught 3-of-4 targets for 19 yards in the Titans’ Week 1 loss against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2723-de13-afdd-67eb1c570000</link>
      <description>Okonkwo’s usage was solid enough, as he ran a route on 31 of Cam Ward’s 36 drop backs. He was third in targets on a day when Ward threw for a meager 112 yards and had just 12 completions. Things will loosen up for Okonkwo and the other Tennessee pass catchers following their brutal Week 1 matchup against a stellar Denver defense. Okonkwo will be a legit streaming play in Week 2 against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2723-de13-afdd-67eb1c570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught both of his targets for 30 yards in the Packers’ Week 1 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2725-dbe3-a9bb-3777a5430000</link>
      <description>Wicks entered Sunday listed as questionable with a calf issue but never appeared to be at risk of missing Week 1. He was good to go by kickoff and playing a surprisingly robust role. He ran 11 routes, all of which came from an outside alignment. Though that’s not enough to be a relevant fantasy player in his own right, it did kneecap the role of first-round rookie Matthew Golden. The Packers’ receiver room is once again a messy rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2725-dbe3-a9bb-3777a5430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White had two rushes for 14 yards in the Bucs’ Week 1 win against the Falcons, adding one catch for two yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2729-d332-a1fd-b73fc93b0000</link>
      <description>The short of it: White was the team’s distant No. 2 back behind Bucky Irving, who handled 14 rushes and had four receptions, one for a touchdown. Irving dominated the pass-catching role out of the Tampa backfield; he ran 23 pass routes to just nine for White. For now, White profiles purely as a contingency option. If Irving were to miss time in 2025, White would suffice as a top-20 PPR option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2729-d332-a1fd-b73fc93b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (left shoulder) will undergo an MRI and “additional testing” to determine the severity of his injury in the next 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d3-de13-afdd-66db08bf0000</link>
      <description>Jennings injured his left shoulder in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks. Although he was initially deemed questionable to return, he spent the rest of the game on the sideline. The 49ers’ receiving corps is extremely thin, with Brandon Aiyuk (knee) still rehabbing and George Kittle (hamstring) also set to under an MRI and additional testing. Marquez Valdes-Scantling is the next man up. The error-prone speedster could catch one or two deep passes against his former team, the Saints, in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-26d3-de13-afdd-66db08bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Nix completed 25-of-40 attempts for 176 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Broncos’ 20-12 Week 1 win against the Titans, adding eight rushes for 17 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-272f-db7b-a5dd-a72f599c0000</link>
      <description>Nix posted a hideous 4.3 yards per attempt, missing open pass catchers and making baffling decisions in critical moments against a poor Tennessee defense. Nix tried to get something going as a rusher to no avail. Nix connected with his WR1 Courtland Sutton for his lone touchdown on a nicely throw red zone jump ball, but couldn’t get anything going in a game that should not have been close. Nix should continue giving fantasy managers a handful of rushing attempts every week, giving him some fantasy juice that can compensate for poor passing performances. Nix will be a borderline starting option in 12-team formats next week against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-272f-db7b-a5dd-a72f599c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 4-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Broncos’ Week 1 win against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2735-dbe3-a9bb-377722e80000</link>
      <description>Franklin operates as Denver’s No. 2 receiver behind Courtland Sutton and ahead of Marvin Mims, who was held to 12 yards on three grabs. Franklin saw 23 percent of the Broncos’ air yards and was second in target share behind Sutton. He could pass for a usable fantasy option in deep leagues next week against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2735-dbe3-a9bb-377722e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Allen completed 33-of-46 passes for 394 yards and two touchdowns in the Bills’ 41-40, Week 1 win over the Ravens, adding 30 yards and two touchdowns on 14 carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2767-db7b-a5dd-a767b7170000</link>
      <description>The Ravens seemed to be running away with the game on the backs of Lamar Jackson and Derrick Henry, taking a 15-point lead into the fourth quarter. The Bills would cut the lead to nine early in the frame but Henry quickly answered with his second long score of the game. Allen then entered Super-Josh mode, leading two touchdown drives in under two minutes but the teams third failed two-point conversion left them down by two points with 1:58 left on the clock. The defense did their job and put the ball back into Allen’s hands and he would make them pay, connecting with deep passes to Josh Palmer and Keon Coleman to set Matt Prater up for a chip shot as time ran out. The late game heroics sent the Bills to a 1-0 record to start the 2025 regular season before they go on the road to face the 0-1 Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2767-db7b-a5dd-a767b7170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook rushed 13 times for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens, adding 58 yards on five receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-276e-de13-afdd-67efc4c90000</link>
      <description>Cook’s modest snap rates from 2024 carried into the first game of the 2025 season, but a touchdown plunge from two yards out in the third quarter and increased passing volume via negative game script propelled him to a usable fantasy week as the Bills stormed back in the fourth quarter to steal the victory from the Ravens. The Bills attempted 46 passes to just 16 running back carries while playing from behind throughout, something that isn’t likely to be the case against most opponents this season. Either way, Cook managed to return a solid score for fantasy managers that capitalized on his falling stock through his offseason hold-in. Up next is another difficult matchup on the ground against the Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-276e-de13-afdd-67efc4c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 8-of-11 targets for 112 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2774-d332-a1fd-b776339c0000</link>
      <description>Coleman and the rest of the Buffalo offense had a relatively quiet first half but scored 16 points in the final four minutes to steal the victory from the Ravens. Coleman’s touchdown went down as the first points in that span, which came on fourth down on a tipped pass off of tight end Dawson Knox’s hands. The incredible comeback win sends the Bills to a 1-0 record ahead of a road meeting with the Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2774-d332-a1fd-b776339c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
