<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Commanders RB Jacory Croskey-Merritt is “expected to be the starting running back” moving forward.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4024-d294-a19b-e4f48c2a0000</link>
      <description>Austin Ekeler suffered a non-contact lower-leg injury on Thursday that is believed to be a season-ending Achilles tendon rupture. He has not yet undergone an MRI, but as Rapoport notes, “it feels like everyone knows the results.” Croskey-Merritt has minimal experience in the passing game, so journeyman RB Jeremy McNichols will likely get the first shot at handling passing down duties. As evidenced by his first two NFL games, Croskey-Merritt’s weekly performance can be impacted by game script, operating largely in an early-down role. That said, he should at least see more opportunities on those downs with Ekeler sidelined, and Croskey-Merritt notably converted a third-and-short carry on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4024-d294-a19b-e4f48c2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that the Packers believe WR Jayden Reed (collarbone) will return in early November.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-408e-d294-a19b-e4fe26df0000</link>
      <description>Reed will undergo surgery to repair his broken collarbone early next week, likely on Tuesday. The Packers’ star slot receiver will then rehab the injury for 6-8 weeks. It’s a lengthy absence, and one that is likely only navigable for fantasy managers possessing an open injured reserve spot. Unfortunately, the Packers will likely still be running their fantasy-unfriendly wide receiver rotation when he returns, and their established field-stretcher, WR Christian Watson (knee), could return from the reserve/physically unable to perform list before then, keeping Reed in the efficiency-based WR3/FLEX territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-408e-d294-a19b-e4fe26df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Browns RB Quinshon Judkins is expected to play in Week 2 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4372-da67-a99f-cff7999f0000</link>
      <description>Judkins is still officially listed as questionable, though it’s not injury-related. The 21-year-old running back from Ohio State missed all of training camp, but was able to practice on Thursday and Friday ahead of Week 2’s matchup with the Ravens. Judkins being active is significant for his season-long value, but it’s unclear how much work he might receive in his first game alongside Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford in the backfield. Sampson and Ford combined for 37 rushing yards on 18 carries against the Bengals in Week 1 and the Browns’ backfield has another difficult matchup on the ground against the Ravens on Sunday. Judkins or any Browns running back is likely best left on the bench this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4372-da67-a99f-cff7999f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Dolphins have no plans to trade WR Tyreek Hill.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-437e-dc44-a9d9-477ee8720000</link>
      <description>Schefter goes as far as to say that the Dolphins haven’t received calls from any teams interested in Hill. His report flies in the face of a Pro Football Talk report earlier this week that said the Chiefs and Steelers were interested in the 31-year-old wide receiver. With Hill wearing out his welcome in Miami and the Dolphins season already nosediving, he’s an obvious trade candidate. The Chiefs make logical sense as a landing spot given that he’s played there before and the team has a need at wide receiver until Rashee Rice returns from suspension. Still, no trade appears imminent at this time and his value could be complicated by his recent domestic violence allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-437e-dc44-a9d9-477ee8720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) has been ruled out for the Week 2 matchup against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43d4-d294-a19b-e7f4a4b10000</link>
      <description>Not a big surprise here as Chiefs head coach Andy Reid described Worthy’s odds of playing in Week 2 as “slim” on Friday. Reid would go on to say that Worthy is doing well, which bodes well for his availability in Week 3, after suffering a shoulder injury that stemmed from a collision with tight end Travis Kelce in Week 1 against the Chargers. The Chiefs’ wide receiver room is wide open without Worthy and Rashee Rice, who still has five games of his suspension left. Hollywood Brown and JuJu Smith-Schuster are next up for Kansas City in the passing game with Brown seeing 16 targets in Week 1 against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43d4-d294-a19b-e7f4a4b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Commanders RB Austin Ekeler suffered a torn Achilles and will miss the rest of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43e0-d294-a19b-e7f0a1670000</link>
      <description>An MRI confirmed that Ekeler suffered a torn Achilles in Thursday’s game against the Packers. The 30-year-old running back will miss the remainder of the season. Jacory “Bill” Croskey-Merritt and Jeremy McNichols figure to handle the running back duties for the Commanders going forward with Chris Rodriguez now as the third running back active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43e0-d294-a19b-e7f0a1670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints acquired WR Ja’Lynn Polk and a 2028 seventh-round pick from the Patriots in exchange for 2027 sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43ee-d294-a19b-e7fe59730000</link>
      <description>Polk is currently out for the year after undergoing shoulder surgery. The former second-round pick in 2024 is another in a long line of wide receiver busts with the Patriots. Polk should have an opportunity to crack a Saints wide receiver room that’s currently led by Chris Olave and Rashid Shaheed next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43ee-d294-a19b-e7fe59730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers ruled out WR Chris Godwin Jr. (ankle) and OT Triston Wirfs (knee) for Week 2 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43f4-d294-a19b-e7f429cd0000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as Godwin missed practice on Friday and Wirfs was limited. Godwin’s target date to return remains at Week 5 at the earliest. The 29-year-old receiver was back on the practice field earlier this week, which is positive, but he never had a realistic chance of suiting up in Week 2. Tampa Bay will continue to rely on Emeka Egbuka and Mike Evans in the passing game until Godwin returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-43f4-d294-a19b-e7f429cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed CB Jaylon Jones on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4409-dc44-a9d9-476fecd10000</link>
      <description>Johnson missed the first game of the season for the Colts while tending to a hamstring injury sustained in camp. His placement on injured reserve means he will miss the next four games, at minimum. The Colts suddenly find themselves lacking depth in the secondary with Charvarius Ward dealing with a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4409-dc44-a9d9-476fecd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns activated RB Quinshon Judkins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-440c-d86f-abdd-45bd110b0000</link>
      <description>Judkins is now clear to make his professional debut for the Browns against the Ravens in Week 2. He has had very little time with the team after dealing with offseason legal issues but will at least be available for the first time this season. Don’t expect Judkins to see many snaps after missing all of his rookie camp and preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-440c-d86f-abdd-45bd110b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
