<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a317-d82c-a79a-b3978f8b0000</link>
      <description>Ward is firmly on track to play in Week 12 against the Colts. The Colts’ secondary has been banged up this year, so Ward’s return is a positive occurrence. Colts slot CB Kenny Moore II is also fully healthy after dealing with an Achilles injury for much of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a317-d82c-a79a-b3978f8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a31b-d90e-a9da-bf1f19e00000</link>
      <description>We anticipate that after back-to-back full sessions he’ll simply be good to go on Sunday. The Vikings would do well to try to #EstablishIt against the Packers given how poor J.J. McCarthy has played to this point, but Minnesota also quietly has struggled at times to run the ball this year. Jones will be a low-end RB2 in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a31b-d90e-a9da-bf1f19e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings EDGE Jonathan Greenard (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a31e-d413-ad9f-b7df2d910000</link>
      <description>It’s the first session Greenard has participated in since injuring his knee in Week 10’s loss to the Ravens, tracking with Ian Rapoport’s reporting that he’d possibly miss only one game. Greenard will likely be joined on the questionable line ahead of Week 12 by G Will Fries (knee), who returned to a limited practice on Thursday as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a31e-d413-ad9f-b7df2d910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Chimere Dike (chest) is practicing in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a320-d90e-a9da-bf2fff350000</link>
      <description>Dike took a vicious lick on special teams in Week 11 and was initially evaluated for a concussion before the Titans re-affirmed that he was dealing with a chest injury. Fortunately it doesn’t seem likely to keep him out this week. Dike and Van Jefferson will split whatever depths of depravity “Titans passing game versus Seahawks” can dredge up for fantasy managers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a320-d90e-a9da-bf2fff350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a322-d82c-a79a-b3b6ef7b0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs told reporters that this isn’t a “pain issue” but is a “range of motion” issue, which makes it sound like something that may not be entirely in his hands at this point. He also noted that his “worst-case scenario” is missing this week, and that he’s adamant about playing against the Lions on Thanksgiving. These are all promising things in the grand scheme of things, but it still sounds like Emanuel Wilson has a chance to head a committee against the Vikings this week. Jacobs probably will get to the questionable line at this point if the Packers don’t shut him down on Friday. The fact that he’s speaking to the media at all is another point in favor of him playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a322-d82c-a79a-b3b6ef7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals QB Joe Flacco (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a321-db57-afda-f7337c120000</link>
      <description>Flacco took reps as the QB2 today, while Joe Burrow (toe) took snaps with the first-team offense. It sure looks an awful lot like Burrow will be the Week 12 starter, though the team could hold him out for one more week. If Flacco gets the start against the Patriots, he is a borderline QB1/2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a321-db57-afda-f7337c120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a327-d82c-a79a-b3b7337f0000</link>
      <description>So were Romeo Doubs (wrist), Matthew Golden (shoulder/wrist), Dontyavion Wicks (calf), Savion Williams (foot), Robert Brooks, Jordy Nelson, and Corey Bradford. Most of these injuries were played through last Sunday, with Williams (foot) getting the lone Wednesday DNP. We wouldn’t trust any of these receivers beyond the FLEX line at this point, with Watson leading the rankings there, but we bet most of them will be active on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a327-d82c-a79a-b3b7337f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a336-d82c-a79a-b3b6fa990000</link>
      <description>Jackson sat out yesterday before upgrading to full today. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said this would be the case. The Ravens face the lowly Jets in Week 12, so Jackson’s dual-threat talents may not be fully needed. Still, his ability to break slates keeps him squarely in the QB1 tier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a336-d82c-a79a-b3b6fa990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d413-ad9f-b7fd92e70000</link>
      <description>Likely is firmly in the questionable camp for the Ravens’ Week 12 game against the Jets. He, unfortunately, can only be viewed as a touchdown-dependent TE2, who takes a backseat to TE Mark Andrews in the red zone. If Likely sits, Andrews should snag an extra target or two here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d413-ad9f-b7fd92e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d82c-a79a-b3bd8ab50000</link>
      <description>Bateman has not yet recovered enough from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 10 to resume practicing. The Ravens’ field-stretching wide receiver is unlikely to be needed against the Jets anyway. Hopefully, he can return in time for the Ravens’ Week 13 game against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a33d-d82c-a79a-b3bd8ab50000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
