<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:04:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders will play a 2026 regular season game in London.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</link>
      <description>Jayden Daniels, coming off an injury-plagued 2025 season in which he threw eight touchdowns and three interceptions over seven games, will lead Washington into London for one of the NFL’s many international games in 2026. The Commanders will look to get back to their 2024 offensive form after scoring points on just 37 percent of their offensive possessions in 2025, the tenth lowest rate in the league. Daniels last season had a drop back EPA on par with Tyler Shough and Kirk Cousins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-951a-dbf6-abdd-ff1b98d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jaguars will play two 2026 regular season games in London.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-952d-d042-afbc-fdff62b30000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars, with an avid UK fanbase, will once again play a couple games overseas in 2026. Jacksonville is 7-7 over 14 regular season games in London since the 2013 NFL season. Last year Trevor Lawrence and the Jaguars were blown out 35-7 by the Rams at Wembley stadium. Lawrence and head coach Liam Coen will look to bounce back from that loss in 2026 after a 2025 season in which they ranked 12th in EPA per play and 16th in offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-952d-d042-afbc-fdff62b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LG Tyler Smith underwent knee surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9532-dbf6-abdd-ff335d3c0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports Smith should be ready for offseason activities in April following the knee procedure. The Pro Bowl left guard gutted it out through the knee injury for much of the 2025 season. Pro Football Focus graded Smith 31st among guards in pass blocking last season. He ranked top-5 among guards in run blocking grade. The Cowboys last year made Smith, their 2022 first round pick, the NFL’s highest paid interior offensive lineman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9532-dbf6-abdd-ff335d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings executive vice president of football operations Rob Brzezinski said the team is “casting a wide net” in exploring quarterback options for 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9546-d89c-a1be-bfdfdfa80000</link>
      <description>Neither Brzezinski nor head coach Kevin O’Connell committed to J.J. McCarthy as the team’s 2026 starter following McCarthy’s ugly 2025 campaign. McCarthy, coming off a knee injury that wiped out his 2024 rookie season, ranked 39th out of 40 qualifying QBs in accuracy and 37th in drop backs success rate over ten games. O’Connell reportedly had to simplify the Minnesota playbook because McCarthy could not grasp the offense. “What we do know is we need a level of baseline quarterback play for us to be effective,” Brzezinski said. “A lot of this has been J.J. in unfortunate [situations] with some of the injuries and things that he’s dealt with, but we’re going to explore every opportunity, and I don’t think there’s anything specifically we’re looking for.” The team’s firing of GM Kwesi Adofo-Mensah last month might mean McCarthy’s time with the Vikings is all but over. Look for the Vikings to talk with Kirk Cousins in the coming weeks as the Falcons are expected to part ways with the former Minnesota starter. They could also show interest in Kyler Murray and Aaron Rodgers this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9546-d89c-a1be-bfdfdfa80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman reports Eagles OC Sean Mannion is “expected to install more zone-blocking concepts that originate from the Shanahan tree offensive philosophies.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-959c-d042-afbc-fddebcad0000</link>
      <description>Mannion is expected to lean on run game coordinator and tight ends coach Ryan Mahaffey in installing a zone-blocking scheme reminiscent of the one used by the Shanahans and their acolytes over the decades. Eagles head coach Nick Sirriani said he expects Saquon Barkley — coming off a down 2025 season — to be “exceptional” in the team’s new rushing scheme. “He’s been highly productive in many of the schemes,” Sirianni said of Barkley, who had 28 rushes of more than ten yards in 2025 after having 46 such runs in 2024. The Eagles in 2025 used zone rushing concepts on 45 percent of their carries, the 13th lowest rate in the NFL. They were efficient with zone rushes, logging a 50 percent success rate, the tenth highest in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-959c-d042-afbc-fddebcad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano said NFL teams are “monitoring” the trade market for Jaguars WR Brian Thomas, Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-95df-d89c-a1be-bfdf746c0000</link>
      <description>Thomas was drafted by a previous Jaguars regime and his play fell off dramatically — completed with major effort issues — in 2025. “There has been no indication that trading Thomas is something the Jaguars are planning, but there are teams monitoring the situation in case the hypertalented LSU product has fallen far enough down the Jacksonville depth chart that the front office would consider a move,” Graziano said. ESPN’s Ben Solak named the Patriots, Bills, Steelers, and Raiders as potential Thomas suitors this offseason. As a rookie in 2024, Thomas went for 1,282 yards and 10 touchdowns as an explosive threat, mostly with Mac Jones under center for the Jags. Thomas has shown vanishingly little chemistry with Trevor Lawrence, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-95df-d89c-a1be-bfdf746c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Todd Monken said the Browns will have an “open competition” at quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9604-d89c-a1be-bfdf3c360000</link>
      <description>Monken praised Sanders’ “elite play-making ability” and said he will have a shot at the starting job for Week 1. The Browns currently have Sanders, Dillon Gabriel, and Deshaun Watson on the roster as potential Week 1 starters. Given how poorly all three of them played in 2025, or 2024 for Watson, Cleveland will almost certainly be in the market for a veteran passer in free agency. Barring a surprise in the draft, the Browns will have plenty of options at quarterback, none of which inspire much confidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9604-d89c-a1be-bfdf3c360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Tribune’s Brad Biggs reports the Bears have given LB Tremaine Edmunds permission to seek a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9610-dbf6-abdd-fe110d490000</link>
      <description>Edmunds is entering the final season of his four-year, $72 million contract. The Bears could save $15 million by cutting him, though it would be in everyone’s best interest to find a trade partner. However, with his release looking increasingly likely, it may be hard to convince another team to give up draft capital for a player who is about to hit the open market. If that happens, Edmunds should still fetch a high-end contract for a linebacker. He led the Bears with 112 total tackles in 2025 despite missing four games. Edmunds also added four interceptions, nine pass breakups, and one sack to his ledger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9610-dbf6-abdd-fe110d490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Panthers have “been getting calls about Andy Dalton for a potential trade.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9621-dbf6-abdd-fe31a0440000</link>
      <description>Dalton has one year left on his current deal in Carolina. The team signed him as Bryce Young’s backup in 2023. He saw significant playing time in 2024 and the team kept him around as a break glass incase of emergency option to replace Young. Dalton was only needed for one start last year. He threw for 175 scoreless yards and an interception while taking seven sacks. The Panthers got trounced by the Bills with a final score of 9-40. The fact that there are still teams interested in Dalton, even as a backup, speaks to the stagnant state of quarterback play across the league. The Panthers wouldn’t fetch more than a late-round pick for Dalton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9621-dbf6-abdd-fe31a0440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons released WR KhaDarel Hodge.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-963f-dbf6-abdd-fe3fa7340000</link>
      <description>The move isn’t quite official yet, but the Falcons have already informed Hodge of his release, per Jordan Schultz. He will join a thin pool of wideouts available in free agency. Hodge appeared in a dozen games in 2025, catching three passes for 31 yards. He is largely a special teamer at this point in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-963f-dbf6-abdd-fe3fa7340000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
