<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kyler Murray completed 23-of-31 passes for 220 yards in the Cardinals’ 22-21, Week 5 loss to the Seahawks, adding four rushes for 25 yards, a touchdown and a fumble.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6b8-dca3-a9fb-bfb91fda0000</link>
      <description>Murray had a strong connection with Marvin Harrison Jr. to begin the game, tossing up a 43-yard jump ball on the first drive. The Cardinals offense clicked early against the stumbling Titans and Murray took advantage of soft pressure for a rushing score in the first quarter (his first rushing touchdown since December 2024). The offense regressed later in the game, with Murray committing an intentional grounding penalty in the second quarter and fumbling on an early snap miscommunication in Titans territory in the third quarter. He left the game for two plays to get his foot checked out and returned for an anemic finish from the Cardinals offense. Outside of the first two drives of the game, Murray could not successfully push the ball downfield and the offensive struggles left the door open for the Titans’ comeback victory. The Murray-Jonathan Gannon duo continues to be the face of mediocrity and the latest appalling blown lead adds to the saga. For fantasy purposes, Murray is a fantasy QB2 against the Colts for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6b8-dca3-a9fb-bfb91fda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 4-of-5 targets for 81 yards in a Week 5 win over the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6bc-dca3-a9fb-bfbddfec0000</link>
      <description>Otton had just nine yards in Week 4 and didn’t have a single target in Week 3, so this performance seemingly came out of nowhere. However, his usage was clearly part of the game plan, since Baker Mayfield targeted him right out of the gate. Given how little Otton has done up until this point, it’s hard to know how much the Bucs will rely on him next week against the 49ers. Still, given how good the Bucs’ passing game has looked, Otton remains a risky TE2 for as long as Mike Evans is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6bc-dca3-a9fb-bfbddfec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Marr Chase caught 6-of-10 targets for 110 yards and two touchdowns in the Bengals’ Week 5 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c1-deb6-a7fd-f7df934c0000</link>
      <description>Chase hauled in two touchdowns in the fourth quarter once the game was already out of reach. The first was an impressive toe-taping 15-yard catch on the far sideline and the second was a 65-yard house call on a blown coverage on third and long. While the Bengals are certainly not done going through the struggle of the Jake Browning experience in 2025, Chase seems to be one of the few that remembers Browning was able to put up some numbers and even win a few games as a fill-in two years ago. Chase is a WR1 against the Packers in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c1-deb6-a7fd-f7df934c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins caught 3-of-7 passes for 22 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 5 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c9-deb6-a7fd-f7df1d2f0000</link>
      <description>Higgins scored for the first time with Jake Browning under center this season, hauling in a two-yard touchdown in the fourth quarter. The Bengals offense scored 21 points in the final frame and ideally the team will carry some of that momentum going forward. Even with Browning, the Bengals don’t have the defense to play any other way than lean on their passing game, which should be good news for Higgins’ fantasy managers. He’s just a WR3 against the Packers in Week 6, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c9-deb6-a7fd-f7df1d2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper reports Omarion Hampton (ankle) was seen in a walking boot after the Chargers’ Week 5 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c9-d95b-addb-fecf8fe30000</link>
      <description>Hampton’s injury during the game didn’t appear too severe, but the level of concern is immediately raised whenever a player is sporting a walking boot. Hopefully, this is more out of precaution, but we’ll hopefully have more clarity on the situation soon from Jim Harbaugh. Hampton exited in the second half of Sunday’s contest and did not return to the field. Kimani Vidal and Kassan Haskins split backfield duties pretty evenly after Hampton exited. It’s possible both backs see work in Week 6 if Hampton is unable to go, which could make for a difficult fantasy situation against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c9-d95b-addb-fecf8fe30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pollard rushed 14 times for 67 yards, a touchdown, and a fumble in the Titans’ Week 5 win over the Cardinals, adding three catches for 11 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c3-d95b-addb-fec72b040000</link>
      <description>Pollard’s day was salvaged by a fourth-quarter goal line touchdown. He still had 17-of-22 backfield touches with Tyjae Spears’ return, but a second quarter fumble hurt his output. Pollard has not shown a whole lot of burst throughout the first five weeks of the season, but is on pace for a 1,000-yard rushing year. Spears’ return will cap his receiving ceiling, but Pollard is still the starter. He is in the RB2 range for Week 6 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6c3-d95b-addb-fec72b040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels completed 15-of-26 passes for 231 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ 27-10, Week 5 win over the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6ce-d6e9-af9d-bede715c0000</link>
      <description>He added eight carries for 39 yards on the ground. It was almost a touchdown-less game altogether for Daniels, who needed to hit a fourth-and-goal touchdown with less than two minutes left with the Commanders up 10 just to find the one passing score. It’s clear that this offense misses Terry McLaurin and that Daniels really doesn’t have a secondary option beyond Deebo Samuel right now. The Bears defense should be healthier off their bye, but Daniels will remain in the QB1 ranks against them in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6ce-d6e9-af9d-bede715c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears rushed 4 times for 14 yards in the Titans’ Week 5 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6d0-d6e9-af9d-bed06e120000</link>
      <description>Spears played his first game of the season, returning from a preseason ankle injury. He saw a couple of touches on the Titans’ first drive and mixed in throughout the game with 17 total snaps. Julius Chestnut also had some involvement, with one carry for three yards and one target. Spears is a valuable handcuff to Tony Pollard and could see some standalone FLEX value as he ramps back up to full speed. He will be in the low-end RB3 range for Week 6 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b6d0-d6e9-af9d-bed06e120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
