<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots added C Garrett Bradbury (illness) to the injury report ahead of Week 13’s game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dacf-d90e-a9da-dfcf51ec0000</link>
      <description>Bradbury is now considered questionable for Monday night’s tilt with the Giants. With the Patriots already down rookie offensive tackle Will Campbell and left guard Jared Wilson, the team can ill-afford to lose a third starter along the line. The good news is that players listed with illnesses tend to play through those things more often than not. In the event he can’t go, however, Ben Brown would be next in line to fill his spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dacf-d90e-a9da-dfcf51ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings waived WR Adam Thielen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dada-d82c-a79a-fbdeeeb10000</link>
      <description>Thielen was a healthy scratch in Week 13. In a statement released by the team, the decision to release Thielen was “out of respect for Adam,” who hopes to secure a bigger role elsewhere in what he has said will be his final NFL season. The Vikings traded a 2026 fifth-round pick and a 2027 fourth-round pick for Thielen in hopes of bolstering their receiving corps while Jordan Addison served a three-game suspension. We’ll see where things go from here, but 35-year-old receivers are seldom in high demand at this point in the season, and Thielen only caught eight passes for 69 scoreless yards in 11 games with the Vikings this season. It’s possible he finds a role on a contender in the coming days, but we wouldn’t expect Thielen to be much more than added depth wherever he lands next.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dada-d82c-a79a-fbdeeeb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said “it’s a possibility” that Mike Evans (collarbone) practices this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-daf6-db57-afda-def65a320000</link>
      <description>Evans suffered a broken collarbone in Week 7 against the Lions. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported shortly after that Evans could miss “eight weeks or fewer,” and the veteran receiver has now been sidelined for the better part of six weeks. The Buccaneeers would need to designate Evans for a return before he takes to the practice field, which would still give the team 21 days before activating him or ruling him out for the season. Evans could still be a few weeks away from being game-ready, but with the Buccaneers sitting on a 7-5 record and in the thick of a playoff race, his return would be a welcome addition to the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-daf6-db57-afda-def65a320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said Maliek Collins will miss the remainder of the season due to a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db14-d90e-a9da-df1f4c530000</link>
      <description>Collins was carted from the field in the third quarter of the Browns’ Week 13 loss to the 49ers and will now miss the remainder of the season. Collins is expected to undergo surgery in the coming days. The 10-year vet has been playing at a high level in his first year with the Browns, notching a career-high 6.5 sacks in the 12 games he’s appeared in while also totaling 25 tackles, seven TFLs, and 13 QB hits. Collins joined the Browns on a two-year, $20 million contract this offseason and should be ready in time for the start of training camp next season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db14-d90e-a9da-df1f4c530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks coach Mike Macdonald said Sam Darnold (ankle) “should be good to go” for Week 14.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db15-d6c4-abfb-df178d0f0000</link>
      <description>We might see him pop up on the injury report ahead of Week 14’s matchup with the Falcons for maintenance reasons. Darnold spent some time in the medical tent against the Vikings on Sunday. He’ll be a risky start in one-quarterback leagues against a solid Falcons pass defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db15-d6c4-abfb-df178d0f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy (concussion) will “have an opportunity to play next week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1b-d6c4-abfb-df1b2ded0000</link>
      <description>He can be cleared from concussion protocol as soon as Monday. The Commanders would represent a step down in competition for McCarthy (or Max Brosmer) after two rounds in the Packers-Seahawks torture chamber, but neither of these players can be reliably started in superflex leagues given how poor they and the Vikings offense have been of late.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1b-d6c4-abfb-df1b2ded0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Jones is believed to be day-to-day after suffering a shoulder injury in Week 13’s loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1d-d6c4-abfb-df1fea540000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, Jones “is likely to be considered day-to-day” with his injury. Jones exited in the third quarter of Sunday’s shutout loss to the Seahawks and didn’t return to the field. The phrasing in Schefter’s report suggests the Vikings are still waiting to get a final word on Jones’ injury, but it sounds like he avoided the worst. If he is day-to-day, Jones will have a chance to suit up in Week 14 when the Vikings face the Commanders this week, but if he’s unable to go, we can expect Jordan Mason to step into a lead role with Zavier Scott likely working in on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db1d-d6c4-abfb-df1fea540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db54-d82c-a79a-fbd43ef70000</link>
      <description>Most reporting has this as a 1-2 week injury, so it would be surprising if St. Brown were able to get active for Thursday night’s game against the Cowboys but not exactly unprecedented. A Monday DNP definitely puts him on the wrong side of active, though. If St. Brown misses the game, Jameson Williams will be in a smash role as the only volume pass-catcher the Lions have available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db54-d82c-a79a-fbd43ef70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons HC Raheem Morris said Drake London (knee) “has a chance to play” in Week 14 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db60-d82c-a79a-fbf4e1740000</link>
      <description>London has missed the last two games for the Falcons after suffering a sprained PCL in Week 11. The Falcons’ WR1 avoided a stint on injured reserve, meaning he can come back whenever the team thinks he’s healthy enough to do so. London did not log a practice last week, so a return to the practice field on Wednesday would be a step in the right direction. His status will be one to monitor throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db60-d82c-a79a-fbf4e1740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Justice Hill (neck) could return in “3-4 weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db77-d90e-a9da-df7f0aba0000</link>
      <description>Rasheen Ali will continue as the Ravens third-down back in the meantime, per Harbaugh. Keaton Mitchell is probably a better second Ravens back to roster at this point for most fantasy leagues than Ali. Hill can be dropped in all shallow formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-db77-d90e-a9da-df7f0aba0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
