<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions waived QB Hendon Hooker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2cb-de13-afdc-e6cbf2350000</link>
      <description>Well, you can’t say they didn’t telegraph this as Hooker played behind Kyle Allen in their fourth preseason game and was pulled early in Detroit’s second game of the preseason for turning the ball over too often. Hooker could wind up back with Detroit on the practice squad, but it’s possible some other team likes the 27-year-old enough to give him a 53-man roster spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2cb-de13-afdc-e6cbf2350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs waived QB Bailey Zappe.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e28a-db7b-a5dd-e28e2ccf0000</link>
      <description>Zappe was unable to unseat Gardner Minshew for the Chiefs’ No. 2 quarterback gig, so he’ll seek a roster spot elsewhere. Zappe will likely find a home on a practice squad somewhere. He spent time on the Chiefs’ last year, before the Browns signed him to a rest-of-season deal in October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e28a-db7b-a5dd-e28e2ccf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans placed RB Joe Mixon (ankle) on the reserve/non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d2-d332-a1fd-f6f67cbd0000</link>
      <description>He’ll miss at least the first four weeks of the season. Nick Chubb should be Houston’s early-down back to begin proceedings in September. Mixon has not been spotted practicing in any real form just yet and is a candidate to miss more than the first four weeks of the season. It’s a major setback for the Texans running game after Mixon’s sublime 2024 season. Dameon Pierce could also carve out a role early on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d2-d332-a1fd-f6f67cbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released WR Michael Gallup.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d4-db7b-a5dd-e2d4feb80000</link>
      <description>Gallup last played in an NFL game back in 2023. He caught 34-of-56 targets for 418 yards and two touchdowns that year. The Commanders also released CB Essang Bassey, C Nick Harris and OT Tyre Phillips, and waived DT Norell Pollard and WR Braylon Sanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d4-db7b-a5dd-e2d4feb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals waived DT McTelvin Agim.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2da-d332-a1fd-f6fecb540000</link>
      <description>Agim was a third-round pick by the Broncos in 2020, but hasn’t done better than a rotational role at the NFL. Never a good sign when you’re getting dropped by the Bengals as an interior lineman. The team also waived CB Nate Brooks, WR Cole Burgess, HB Quali Conley, S Shaquan Loyal, WR Rashod Owens, C Andrew Raym, CB Lance Robinson, G Andrew Stueber, QB Payton Thorne and LB Craig Young. Additionally they released DT Taven Bryan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2da-d332-a1fd-f6fecb540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that the Steelers plan to waive K Ben Sauls if they cannot trade him before Tuesday’s cutdown deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d2-dbe3-a9bb-f2d35a440000</link>
      <description>The undrafted free agent kicker converted 6-of-6 extra point attempts and went 5-of-6 on field goals in the preseason, missing once from 40-plus yards out. Sauls’ preseason performance could land him a spot elsewhere in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2d2-dbe3-a9bb-f2d35a440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers released QB Bryce Perkins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2e0-dbe3-a9bb-f2f362310000</link>
      <description>Perkins was signed following Andy Dalton’s elbow injury, so we take Perkins’ release as a positive regarding Dalton’s recovery. The Panthers also waived CB Mello Dotson, CB JaTravis Broughton, S Isaac Gifford, OG Luke Kandra, OG Steven Loyosa, WR TJ Luther, RB Kay’Ron Lynch-Adams, OLB J.J. Weaver and ILB Jacoby Windmon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2e0-dbe3-a9bb-f2f362310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers released P Cameron Johnston.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2e9-de13-afdc-e6eb08e60000</link>
      <description>That’s right, Corliss Waitman has won the starting punting job! Bill Burr look-a-like Johnston will peddle his punting wares elsewhere after a 2024 ACL tear. Johnston punted 14 times this preseason, so he is healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2e9-de13-afdc-e6eb08e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Daniel Popper believes Najee Harris (eye) will begin the season on the non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2f8-db7b-a5dd-e2fc1c040000</link>
      <description>While Chargers GM Joe Hortiz sounded an optimistic note on Harris playing in Week 1, The Athletic’s Chargers beat writer disagrees with that assertion. Should Harris be placed on NFI and miss the first four weeks of the season, it would put Hassan Haskins into the No. 2 role, per Popper. That should mean plenty of Omarion Hampton with Haskins mixing in — perhaps at the goal line given Haskins’ size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e2f8-db7b-a5dd-e2fc1c040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
