<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (foot/ankle) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32fc-d35e-a1bf-77fe66600000</link>
      <description>The rookie wideout logged a full practice on Thursday, which should push the chances of him playing on Sunday in Carolina’s must-win against the Buccaneers way up. McMillan practicing on Friday would likely lead him to be an optimistic questionable or removed from the injury report altogether. Despite his stats taking a hit of late, McMillan will be a low-end WR2 in an enormous NFC South showdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-32fc-d35e-a1bf-77fe66600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LT Laremy Tunsil (oblique) will not play in Week 16 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3313-d087-addf-b3f35cbd0000</link>
      <description>Tunsil strained his oblique in Week 15. Now Marcus Mariota will draw another start, this time without his left tackle. Brandon Coleman took over for him mid-game last week and will likely keep that gig into Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3313-d087-addf-b3f35cbd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos coach Sean Payton said “we need to get [Jaleel McLaughlin] more touches, I made that note after the game.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3314-d35e-a1bf-77d6dadb0000</link>
      <description>RJ Harvey is dealing with a rib injury but practiced in full on Wednesday and should still be locked into the lead back role in Denver. This is something that Payton says a lot after games — this idea that he needs to get backup backs or wideouts (like Marvin Mims) more involved. We wouldn’t necessarily read into it so far as to say that Harvey is going to split carries or anything, but it is at least possible that McLaughlin is more involved than the seven touches he’s seen over the past two games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3314-d35e-a1bf-77d6dadb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers EDGE T.J. Watt (lung) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3330-d35e-a1bf-77f2e15b0000</link>
      <description>It definitely appears to be trending towards Watt missing another week after emergency surgery to repair a partially-collapsed lung last week. He hasn’t practiced since, understandably so. The Steelers will likely be without their best pass rusher against the Lions. Nick Herbig (hamstring) also missed his second-straight practice on Thursday and seems unlikely to go in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3330-d35e-a1bf-77f2e15b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers C Zach Frazier (triceps) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3302-d35e-a1bf-77c2b0ba0000</link>
      <description>Frazier was not on the injury report yesterday, which suggests this is a new injury. That is bad news. The Steelers face the Lions this week and Frazier is a very capable pass protector and run blocker. He is firmly in the questionable camp at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3302-d35e-a1bf-77c2b0ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes Minnesota’s cap situation “will, at minimum, require a reworking of Hockenson’s [cap] figure.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3337-d087-addf-b3f7b81e0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson’s projected cap hit for 2026 is $21.3 million, an untenable amount for someone who is at best the third option for the Vikings at this point in his career. “The Vikings could also save around $9 million for next season by cutting him,” notes Lewis. It sure sounds like the Vikings, entering the offseason at roughly $36 million over the cap per OverTheCap, may have to make a business decision on Hockenson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3337-d087-addf-b3f7b81e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes it is a “predictable offseason move” for the Vikings to cut DT Javon Hargrave.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-333b-d087-addf-b3fb77a40000</link>
      <description>Hargrave can be cut for $11 million in cap savings. The veteran has been solid-but-unspectacular and turns 33 this offseason. He’d probably have a real market as a veteran plugger somewhere, but Hargrave has been a so-so run defender since leaving the Steelers and likely won’t command the same kind of salary in 2026 as he did last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-333b-d087-addf-b3fb77a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Saquon Barkley (stinger) is not on Philadelphia’s final injury report for Week 16.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-333f-d35e-a1bf-77ff10820000</link>
      <description>He got in a full practice and will be good to go in a smash spot against the playing-out-the-string Commanders. Barkley will be a volume-based RB1 in this matchup. The Eagles did establish it fairly well against the Raiders last week with Jalen Hurts more involved in the running game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-333f-d35e-a1bf-77ff10820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) will not play in Philadelphia’s Week 16 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3341-da28-afbb-f77d798f0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles will at least get Landon Dickerson (calf/rest) off the injury report and up for this one, but it will be at least one more week off for Johnson, who has needed One More Week for about three weeks now. The Eagles don’t have much incentive to rush him with the NFC East all but sewn up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3341-da28-afbb-f77d798f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
