<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested an interview with Giants OLB coach Charlie Bullen for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a49-d629-a1bc-ba5d69860000</link>
      <description>Bullen took on the role of interim defensive coordinator for the Giants this year after they fired Shane Bowen. The team interviewed him for the permanent DC job after John Harbaugh signed on as head coach. While they ultimately went in a different direction, Bullen was retained by the new staff. Bullen previously served as a position coach for the Cardinals under Kliff Kingsbury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a49-d629-a1bc-ba5d69860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye (shoulder/illness) said he expects to practice in full ahead of Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a6f-d629-a1bc-ba7f32860000</link>
      <description>Maye was listed as questionable on the Pats’ initial injury report last week. He was limited for the first two practices of the week. The team then held him out of Friday’s session because of the illness, not the shoulder issue. There was never any risk of him missing this game and his comments today confirm that. A full practice today means the shoulder injury shouldn’t affect Maye in any capacity on the biggest stage in football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a6f-d629-a1bc-ba7f32860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed WR Terrace Marshall to a reserve/future contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a79-d042-afbc-7ffb48120000</link>
      <description>The former second-round pick was cut by the Panthers after three seasons. He caught three passes for the Raiders in 2024 and most recently spent time on the Eagles’ practice squad. His R/F deal with the Dolphins will give him a chance to make a good impression early in the offseason program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a79-d042-afbc-7ffb48120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested an interview with Texans defensive backs coach Dino Vasso for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a81-d355-a5bd-afd5afcc0000</link>
      <description>Vasso interviewed with Tennessee for their DC opening in January but didn’t get the job. Ariona also requested an interview with Giants OLBs coach Charlie Bullen for their DC job. Expect them to bring in a few more names over the next week. Vasso has been a position coach for the Texans since 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2a81-d355-a5bd-afd5afcc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NFL’s Jay Glazer believes Maxx Crosby’s time with the Raiders is done.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2aae-d629-a1bc-babf29b20000</link>
      <description>Speaking with Yahoo Sports, Glazer speculated that the Raiders could get more in return for Crosby than the Cowboys did when they traded Micah Parsons. For reference, Dallas netted defensive tackle Kenny Clark and a pair of first-round picks. Glazer also noted that the two sides are at a crossroads as a result of Crosby’s desire to not see another rebuild. It’s possible that the new regime, likely led by Klint Kubaik, can sell him on this not being a lengthy rebuild. However, it’s safe to say Crosby has also heard that pitch before. Crosby has 44.5 sacks over the past four seasons and won’t turn 29 until the end of training camp. He is under contract for three more seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2aae-d629-a1bc-babf29b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans signed CB Brandon Codrington, formerly of the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b2c-d629-a1bc-bb3d025b0000</link>
      <description>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Codrington visited the Texans Wednesday and signed with the team. The 25-year-old spent the better part of the last two seasons as a return specialist with the Bills but was released from Buffalo’s practice squad in January. The Texans now have Codrington to evaluate over the course of the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b2c-d629-a1bc-bb3d025b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b5c-d355-a5bd-af5c18220000</link>
      <description>Also limited was LT Charles Cross (foot). Darnold and Cross have been limited in practice for the playoffs, but have played through their respective injuries. The Seahawks’ passing game has operated well in their two playoff games and neither player will be at risk of being limited for the Super Bowl, barring setbacks in practice. Expect both to fire it up in a battle for the Lombardi Trophy against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b5c-d355-a5bd-af5c18220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b62-d355-a5bd-af76e0da0000</link>
      <description>Spillane said Wednesday that he is confident he will play in the Super Bowl, despite missing practice with an ankle injury. The 30-year-old aggravated the injury in the AFC Championship game and has yet to hit the practice field. However, the DNP is early in the week and Spillane’s confidence in playing indicates he will suit up for the Super Bowl. Practice reports the rest of the week will tell if that is indeed the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2b62-d355-a5bd-af76e0da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori suffered an ankle injury in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2bd6-d89c-a1be-afdf098a0000</link>
      <description>Emmanwori was listed as limited on Wednesday’s practice report as a result of an ankle injury he suffered in practice. Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told ESPN’s Kalyn Kahler, “we brought him in to look at it, and we’ll kind of go from here and figure out what are the next steps?” The rookie 21-year-old has been a key piece of the Seahawks defense and an absence would be largely impactful for Macdonald’s squad in the Super Bowl. For now, Emmanwori will be getting the ankle checked out and the Seahawks will make a determination on his status as the Super Bowl matchup against the Pats inches closer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2bd6-d89c-a1be-afdf098a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
