<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Samaje Perine (ankle) is doubtful to play in Week 12 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d4d-d1e7-a1fa-dfef89ee0000</link>
      <description>Perine is still working his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 9. Chase Brown saw 24-of-27 backfield touches in Week 11. Perine’s continued absence will ensure a three-down role for Brown again this week, keeping him at the top of the RB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d4d-d1e7-a1fa-dfef89ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears designated CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d56-d673-a39e-bdd7181c0000</link>
      <description>Gordon will return to practice this week. Chicago has 21 days to activate him from injured reserve. Gordon aggravated a lingering hamstring issue early in the year and has been sidelined since Week 2. Both he and fellow defensive back Jaylon Johnson are practicing this week. The Bears could be getting healthy on defense just as they attempt to make a playoff push.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d56-d673-a39e-bdd7181c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d61-d45b-affe-ddf7746c0000</link>
      <description>Flacco hasn’t practiced on Wednesday since injuring his shoulder in Week 8. He should be back on the field for a limited session tomorrow and, barring a new development, won’t have a game day status after Friday’s session. We fully expect Flacco to suit up versus the Patriots on Sunday. He will remain a volume-based QB2, though his outlook will take a hit with Ja’Marr Chase suspended for one game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d61-d45b-affe-ddf7746c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d65-d673-a39e-bdf5eb670000</link>
      <description>The Ravens haven’t released their injury report yet, but we are assuming he is still dealing with the minor knee injury that cropped up last week. Jackson was held out of practice last Wednesday and returned for the following two sessions. He played in Week 11, though it was far from his best showing. Jackson threw for 193 scoreless yards with two interceptions and added a measly 10 yards on the ground. The knee issue may be affecting his play, even if it isn’t serious enough to keep him off the field entirely. Jackson should be able to suit up again this week, but fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on the Ravens’ injury report just to be safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d65-d673-a39e-bdf5eb670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Rams S Quentin Lake (elbow) underwent surgery and “the hope is he’s back before or during the playoffs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d70-d713-ad9e-fd74d75f0000</link>
      <description>Lake will presumably be placed on injured reserve, sidelining him for at least four weeks. Lake was having a breakout year before going down with the injury. He had 10 pass breakups, one interception, and one sack in 10 games, all of which were starts. Losing him will be a short-term blow to LA’s defense, but the good news is that it doesn’t sound like a season-ending injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d70-d713-ad9e-fd74d75f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d79-d45b-affe-ddff81760000</link>
      <description>Bateman suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 10 and did not practice at all last week before being ruled out. A DNP today suggests he will miss at least one more week because of the ankle issue. DeAndre Hopkins took his place in the lineup last week and ran 71 percent of the routes. He only caught one pass for 11 yards,</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d79-d45b-affe-ddff81760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs told reporters that he “fractured a finger a couple weeks ago.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d7e-d45b-affe-ddfea4a40000</link>
      <description>This is our first time hearing about it. Per ESPN’s Mike Reiss, there was “never a doubt he would play through it,” which is probably why Diggs has only been listed with chest and ankle injuries this season. The Patriots’ No. 1 wide receiver has finished in the half-PPR WR2-WR3 range for five straight weeks. We have no concerns about the finger fracture. Treat him accordingly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d7e-d45b-affe-ddfea4a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d92-d1e7-a1fa-dffaf05b0000</link>
      <description>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin told reporters yesterday that Rodgers would not practice today, so this should not be viewed as overly alarming, though Rodgers’ Week 12 availability is obviously in question. The wrist fracture Rodgers suffered in his non-throwing left arm could keep him sidelined against the Bears this weekend. If he can resume practicing by the end of the week, he should have a chance to play. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9d92-d1e7-a1fa-dffaf05b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders activated Aidan O’Connell (wrist) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9da1-d713-ad9e-fdf5dd3e0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell went down with the wrist injury in the Raiders’ preseason finale. The team then acquired Kenny Pickett to back up Geno Smith. With how poorly Smith has played this year, there’s a remote chance O’Connell sees action late in the season. However, that isn’t something we expect to see anytime soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9da1-d713-ad9e-fdf5dd3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer said QB Dak Prescott (hip) will take a “normal workload” at today’s walkthrough.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dab-d673-a39e-bdbb2bc30000</link>
      <description>Prescott picked up a hip injury in the Cowboys’ Week 11 over the Raiders on Monday night. Schottenheimer prefaced Prescott’s injury report appearance by saying the Cowboys’ quarterback “should be fine” for the team’s Week 12 game against the Eagles. Monitoring Prescott’s practice participation is worthwhile, but we expect him to warrant QB1 treatment this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-9dab-d673-a39e-bdbb2bc30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
