<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn said Breece Hall should be “fine” ahead of Week 8’s game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0249-da18-a39a-da5b8b3c0000</link>
      <description>Whatever injuries Hall is dealing with appear to be from the normal wear and tear of the season. The Jets RB1 totaled 52 yards from scrimmage in Week 7’s loss to the Panthers, and has been noticeably limited in the passing game despite the constant negative game scripts the Jets find themselves in. Hall gets a generous Week 8 matchup against the Bengals and should have a chance at a decent fantasy day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0249-da18-a39a-da5b8b3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports an MRI revealed Bryce Young suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 7’s win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0254-df81-ab9b-7ed781ee0000</link>
      <description>According to Pelissero, Young’s injury is the type that “is generally a 2-4 week injury,” but he adds that the Panthers are hopeful he could be back after just one game. Young’s practice availability throughout the coming weeks will tell us everything we need to know regarding his outlook come game day, but it doesn’t come as much of a surprise to hear he is expected to miss Sunday’s game against the Bills. Assuming Young does miss, Andy Dalton would make his first start of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0254-df81-ab9b-7ed781ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys designated LB DeMarvion Overshown (knee) for return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-026c-df81-ab9b-7eeff1ed0000</link>
      <description>Overshown has been recovering from a knee injury he suffered in Week 14 of last season. The talented linebacker totaled 90 tackles and five sacks in the 13 games he appeared in during the 2024 campaign after missing all of 2023 with a knee injury he suffered during the preseason. Now that he’s designated for return, the Cowboys will have 21 days to activate Overshown to the 53-man roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-026c-df81-ab9b-7eeff1ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Saints C Erik McCoy is believed to have suffered a torn biceps in Week 7’s loss to the Bears, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-028e-da18-a39a-da9fa20f0000</link>
      <description>Once the injury is confirmed, McCoy’s season will be over. The seven-year vet missed 10 games last season due to groin and shoulder injuries, but remains one of the league’s top centers when healthy. We’ll likely receive official word on his injury in the coming days, but for now, it sounds like the team already fears the worst. Backup Luke Fortner would be next in line to draw the start in place of McCoy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-028e-da18-a39a-da9fa20f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendre Miller suffered a torn ACL in Week 7 against the Bears, ending his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029d-d651-a9df-6b9d09a10000</link>
      <description>Miller’s season ends with a 47-193-1 rushing line to go with five receptions for 30 additional yards. The third-year back was carving out a small role in Kellen Moore’s offense, earning 6.3 touches per game while averaging a career best 4.1 YPC. Miller, who was drafted by the Saints in the third round of the 2023 NFL Draft, will enter next season on the final year of his rookie contract in what will be a prove-it season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029d-d651-a9df-6b9d09a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid told reporters to “move on from it” when pressed about the status of Josh Simmons (personal).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029f-da18-a39a-da9f3a480000</link>
      <description>We don’t want to trivialize whatever Simmons is going through, the only information that has surfaced so far is that he returned home to San Diego. Reid’s words make it clear that Simmons should remain sidelined for the forseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-029f-da18-a39a-da9f3a480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said David Njoku (knee) remains “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02a2-df81-ab9b-7ee7aa2c0000</link>
      <description>Njoku’s practice status will be the guiding light here regarding Week 8’s game against the Patriots, but he called Njoku day-to-day before last week and Njoku did not practice once. Until we see positive news here, it should be assumed that Harold Fannin will continue to operate as Cleveland’s No. 1 tight end and be in line for low-end TE1 duties against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02a2-df81-ab9b-7ee7aa2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs DT Omarr Norman-Lott suffered a torn ACL in Week 7’s win over the Raiders and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b2-df81-ab9b-7ef71d190000</link>
      <description>Norman-Lott exited in the third quarter of Sunday’s game. He remained down on the field for several minutes before eventually being helped to the sideline by teammates, but now the rookie second-rounder will set his sights to a return in 2026. Norman-Lott appeared in five games for the Chiefs this season, totaling five tackles, one sack, and one TFL. Assuming his recovery goes as planned, he should be ready to go around the time training camp starts up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b2-df81-ab9b-7ef71d190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Darren Waller (pectoral) is “week to week” and isn’t expected to require surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b7-df81-ab9b-7ef7c8f40000</link>
      <description>Waller is reportedly dealing with a pectoral strain. It’s all fun and games when Waller is catching touchdowns, but the cost of what it does to his body is: We have to blurb him 15 more times before he gets on the field again. Oh, it’s probably not fun for him either, we shouldn’t minimize that. Anyway, given Waller’s injury history, this will probably take multiple weeks. The passing game tree in Miami is already pretty concentrated — maybe this pushes Malik Washington into a few more six-yard catches, enough to be a PPR scam as a FLEX play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02b7-df81-ab9b-7ef7c8f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said the team will continue using a two-back approach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</link>
      <description>Chuba Hubbard outsnapped Rico Dowdle 38-33, but Dowdle out-touched Hubbard 18-16. Six teams on bye probably squeezes each of them into the low-end RB2 ranks against the Bills in Week 8, though perhaps the Bills can squeeze the box tight enough to create an Andy Dalton pass funnel coming out of the bye. It’s clear that Carolina’s best approach is through the ground, and that Dowdle is here to stay as either a pest (complimentary) or a pest (derogatory) depending on who you have rostered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-02be-d651-a9df-6bbf03440000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
