<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d1e7-a1fa-5fffcb480000</link>
      <description>Monangai kicked off the week with a limited practice session before upgrading to full on Thursday. He remained full on Friday. Teammate, RB D’Andre Swift, logged the same participation levels on Wednesday and Thursday, nursing a groin injury, but was absent on Friday, evidently due to a personal matter. He is questionable to play, which should yield another fantasy-friendly workload for Monangai. He is on the low-end RB2 spectrum, even if Swift is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d1e7-a1fa-5fffcb480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears TE Cole Kmet (concussion) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe6-d1e7-a1fa-5fee180e0000</link>
      <description>Kmet evidently remains setback-free after practicing in full on Thursday and Friday. His presence complicates projections for rookie TE Colston Loveland, who broke out in Week 9 by catching 6-of-7 targets for 118 yards and two touchdowns. Loveland can likely still be started as a TE1, but his range of outcomes is considerably wider with Kmet active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe6-d1e7-a1fa-5fee180e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaguars WR Brian Thomas Jr. (ankle) will miss Week 10’s game against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ff7-d45b-affe-5ff7ef190000</link>
      <description>As expected after the first two DNPs this week. Thomas Jr. has a chance of being ready for Week 11, but should be considered questionable heading into the practices. Jakobi Meyers and Parker Washington will be Jacksonville’s main receivers this week against the Texans with Thomas and Travis Hunter sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ff7-d45b-affe-5ff7ef190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (shoulder/toe) is questionable to play in Week 10 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ff9-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb59f70000</link>
      <description>Jones sat out on Wednesday before practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday. Knowing his Friday status would help one assess where he sits on the questionable spectrum, but today’s report has not yet been released. Were he to practice in full, he would seemingly have strong odds of suiting up this weekend. If active, he would carry re-injury risk, but could still be started as a borderline RB2/3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ff9-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb59f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers RB Sean Tucker (groin) is not on Tampa’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffc-d713-ad9e-7ffc9fba0000</link>
      <description>Bit of a weird one here, with Tucker downgrading to a limited practice on Friday with a groin injury, but not being given a status on the final Week 10 injury report. It’s possible that Rachaad White gets more snaps against the Patriots on Sunday than he had been getting before the bye, but this is probably just the Buccaneers being overly thorough in the wake of the Lamar Jackson listing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffc-d713-ad9e-7ffc9fba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings ruled out TE Josh Oliver (foot) for Week 10 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffc-d45b-affe-5ffe25400000</link>
      <description>Oliver’s absence will more likely be felt in the run game than the pass. The veteran tight end has earned just six targets on the season, but has generally fared well as a run-blocker. The Vikings face the Ravens’ fantasy-friendly defense this weekend, so hopefully his absence ultimately goes unnoticed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffc-d45b-affe-5ffe25400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Ollie Gordon (ankle) is questionable for Miami’s Week 10 game against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffe-d1e7-a1fa-5ffed5120000</link>
      <description>He got in limited practices all week after injuring the ankle in Week 9’s loss to the Ravens on Thursday. Gordon is probably on the optimistic side of questionable and should serve his normal backup role to De’Von Achane, which means he has little fantasy value on Sunday barring Achane sitting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ffe-d1e7-a1fa-5ffed5120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions RT Penei Sewell (shoulder) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6002-d673-a39e-e4936d400000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, Lions head coach Dan Campbell said things were “looking good” for Sewell and LT Taylor Decker (shoulder) to play on Sunday. Backup OT Dan Skipper (back) is questionable to play and S Kerby Joseph (knee) has been ruled out. Hopefully, at least one of Decker and/or Skipper is good to go this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6002-d673-a39e-e4936d400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) was seen working off to the side at practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-600a-d45b-affe-759e2f6c0000</link>
      <description>To be clear, Hampton was not participating in the team’s official practice. Working off to the side typically suggests the player is simply going through exercises with the team’s coaching staff. The Athletic’s Daniel Popper opines, this is a “positive sign for the rookie RB as he works his way back from an ankle injury.” Earlier this week, Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh said the team will wait to open Hampton’s 21-day practice window until after the Week 12 bye. Hopefully, he can return in Week 13 or soon thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-600a-d45b-affe-759e2f6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders fired special teams coordinator Tom McMahon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6017-d45b-affe-7597f1170000</link>
      <description>That’ll fix it. McMahon was seen getting into it with Pete Carroll on the sideline during Thursday night’s loss. A.J. Cole knocked two punts inside the two-yard-line and watched Chip Kelly’s offense go nowhere while scoring just seven points. We’re guessing this won’t be the last Raiders firing of this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6017-d45b-affe-7597f1170000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
