<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Treylon Burks caught 1-of-4 targets for a five-yard touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 13 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87c-db57-afda-de7ece7a0000</link>
      <description>Burks showed a glimpse at what made him a first-round pick for the Titans in the 2022 draft as he elevated over a defender for a one-handed touchdown in the third quarter. Unfortunately for him, that would go down as his only reception of the evening with the return of Terry McLaurin. He does not hold any fantasy value while playing behind McLaurin, Deebo Samuel, and Jaylin Lane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d87c-db57-afda-de7ece7a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Myers converted all four of his field goal attempts and made both of his extra point attempts in the Seahawks’ Week 13 win against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d9f6-d90e-a9da-dfffa5ae0000</link>
      <description>Myers went Goblin Mode for fantasy managers, scoring around 20 fantasy points depending on your league’s scoring. Myers has been solid in 2025, making 28 of his 33 field goal tries. The Seahawks lead the NFL with 2.8 field goal attempts per game through Week 13. Myers is an every-week starter in 12-team leagues for the front-running Hawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d9f6-d90e-a9da-dfffa5ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Reichard did not attempt a field goal or extra point in the Vikings’ Week 13 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d9fe-db57-afda-dffec74f0000</link>
      <description>Reichard is all but useless for fantasy purposes, attached to a lifeless Minnesota offense that rarely produces the neutral and positive game script that creates field goal opportunities. Reichard has made 21 of 23 field goal tries this season. The Vikings, meanwhile, average just 1.8 field goal attempts per game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d9fe-db57-afda-dffec74f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions HC Dan Campbell said he has “no indication” about whether or not Frank Ragnow will attempt to return in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-da1b-db57-afda-de3b76b00000</link>
      <description>Ragnow’s attempt at a comeback was dashed when the veteran center failed his physical due to a Grade 3 hamstring injury. Ragnow was hoping to un-retire and help the Lions make a playoff push over the final month of the season, but given the nature of his injury and the amount of rehab he would need in order to play, a return didn’t make much sense. Still only 29 years old, Ragnow’s decision to walk away from the game was due to the myriad of injuries he has suffered in his career. If he feels physically up to it after a year away, it wouldn’t be surprising to see Ragnow attempt another return for the 2026 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-da1b-db57-afda-de3b76b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports a source familiar with the situation said Sauce Garder will likely miss “a few weeks” due to his calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-da96-db57-afda-deb658d90000</link>
      <description>Gardner is undergoing additional tests to determine the exact severity of the injury, but as Fowler notes, Gardner seems to have avoided a major injury. We’ll likely get a clearer timeline on Gardner’s impending absence in the next 24 hours or so, but it sounds like he’ll be a lock to miss Week 14’s game against the Jaguars, and perhaps Week 15’s game against the Seahawks. In three games with the Colts this season, Gardner has totaled 13 tackles and two pass breakups while holding opposing receivers to 38 yards on 10 targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-da96-db57-afda-deb658d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Sauce Gardner is considered week-to-week after an MRI revealed he suffered a calf strain in Week 13’s loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dab9-db57-afda-debb922e0000</link>
      <description>It’s the best Gardner and the Colts could have hoped for after the initial injury appeared to be much worse on the field. Gardner will miss a few weeks with what is officially being diagnosed as a strained calf, but according to Rapoport, the Colts hope to have him back before the end of the regular season. Barring an unexpected turn of events, Gardner should avoid a stint on injured reserve. Mekhi Blackmon is listed behind him on the depth chart and should step in to replace Gardner during his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dab9-db57-afda-debb922e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Steelers LB Patrick Queen is believed to have suffered a lower back bruise in Week 13’s loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dac1-d90e-a9da-dfcf60400000</link>
      <description>It’s quite a shift from the hip injury this was initially classified as, but Queen is undergoing further tests to determine the specifics of his injury. According to Rapoport, the Steelers hope Queen’s injury isn’t something long-term, but it sounds like he could be sidelined for at least one game. Queen and the Steelers have a pivotal Week 14 matchup against the Ravens on tap as they battle for supremacy in the down bad AFC North. If he’s unable to go, Malik Harrison would be the next man up on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dac1-d90e-a9da-dfcf60400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots added C Garrett Bradbury (illness) to the injury report ahead of Week 13’s game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dacf-d90e-a9da-dfcf51ec0000</link>
      <description>Bradbury is now considered questionable for Monday night’s tilt with the Giants. With the Patriots already down rookie offensive tackle Will Campbell and left guard Jared Wilson, the team can ill-afford to lose a third starter along the line. The good news is that players listed with illnesses tend to play through those things more often than not. In the event he can’t go, however, Ben Brown would be next in line to fill his spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dacf-d90e-a9da-dfcf51ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings waived WR Adam Thielen.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dada-d82c-a79a-fbdeeeb10000</link>
      <description>Thielen was a healthy scratch in Week 13. In a statement released by the team, the decision to release Thielen was “out of respect for Adam,” who hopes to secure a bigger role elsewhere in what he has said will be his final NFL season. The Vikings traded a 2026 fifth-round pick and a 2027 fourth-round pick for Thielen in hopes of bolstering their receiving corps while Jordan Addison served a three-game suspension. We’ll see where things go from here, but 35-year-old receivers are seldom in high demand at this point in the season, and Thielen only caught eight passes for 69 scoreless yards in 11 games with the Vikings this season. It’s possible he finds a role on a contender in the coming days, but we wouldn’t expect Thielen to be much more than added depth wherever he lands next.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dada-d82c-a79a-fbdeeeb10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said “it’s a possibility” that Mike Evans (collarbone) practices this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-daf6-db57-afda-def65a320000</link>
      <description>Evans suffered a broken collarbone in Week 7 against the Lions. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported shortly after that Evans could miss “eight weeks or fewer,” and the veteran receiver has now been sidelined for the better part of six weeks. The Buccaneeers would need to designate Evans for a return before he takes to the practice field, which would still give the team 21 days before activating him or ruling him out for the season. Evans could still be a few weeks away from being game-ready, but with the Buccaneers sitting on a 7-5 record and in the thick of a playoff race, his return would be a welcome addition to the offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-daf6-db57-afda-def65a320000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
