<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said Brock Purdy complained of soreness in his toe following Week 4’s loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9652-dca3-a9fb-bfdb201d0000</link>
      <description>This isn’t all that surprising after Purdy missed two games due to a toe injury he suffered in Week 1. According to Shanahan, while speaking with Purdy on the phone after the game, Purdy “said (his toe) was starting to bother him,” but noted that he didn’t feel anything during the game. This remains a situation to watch heading into Week 5, especially with the Niners playing on a short week this Thursday. If he’s unable to go, Mac Jones would again be in line for the start against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9652-dca3-a9fb-bfdb201d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said the team is hopeful Ricky Pearsall’s knee injury is a “minor PCL” issue.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9656-d95b-addb-fe5691400000</link>
      <description>“Hopefully it won’t be too bad,” Shanahan said while speaking to the media on Monday. Pearsall exited Week 4’s game against the Jaguars after landing hard on his knee, and said after the game that he felt some “instability” when he tested his knee to see if he could go back in. The 49ers have a short week to get ready for Week 5’s contest against the Rams on Thursday night. It could prove too short a time for Pearsall to get right in time to play, which could leave an already thin receiving corps with even fewer options in the passing game. Pearsall’s name will be one to watch when the team’s injury report is released on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9656-d95b-addb-fe5691400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said the team is hopeful that safety Malik Mustapha can practice after Week 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-965a-dca3-a9fb-bfdb5f850000</link>
      <description>Mustapha landed on injured reserve last October with a torn ACL and has been working his way back ever since. The second-year player and former fourth-round pick started 12 of the 16 games he appeared in for the 49ers last season and totaled 72 tackles, two TFLs, and one interception in his rookie campaign. While he could return to practice after Week 6, it wouldn’t be surprising if the Niners take a few weeks to ramp him up before letting him return to game action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-965a-dca3-a9fb-bfdb5f850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Titans are expected to designate Tyjae Spears (ankle) for return this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9668-dca3-a9fb-bff97dc50000</link>
      <description>The 0-4 Titans will take all the help they can get. Spears suffered an ankle injury in mid-August and opened the season on injured reserve as a result. Spears will now have 21 days to return to the active roster or be shut down for the season, but the expectation is he will eventually return to the field after having some time to ramp up. Spears totaled 536 yards from scrimmage and five touchdowns on 114 touches for the Titans last season, but struggled to the tune of just 4.7 yards per touch. His return will put a slight damper on Tony Pollard’s fantasy value, but Spears averaged just 9.9 opportunities per game in 12 games last season. He’d need to see a bit more than that in 2025 if we hope to view him as a weekly fantasy option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9668-dca3-a9fb-bff97dc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans HC DeMeco Ryans said the team has designated DE Denico Autry (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-966d-deb6-a7fd-d7ff50a30000</link>
      <description>Autry now has 21 days to return to the field. The veteran pass rusher totaled three sacks in 10 games for the Texans last season and will likely serve as a rotational piece for the defense once he returns to action. Per PFF, Autry saw 226 of his 314 defensive snaps come in pass rush situations, setting the expectation for what we should expect with his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-966d-deb6-a7fd-d7ff50a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said Cedric Tillman will miss “weeks” after suffering a hamstring injury in Week 4’s loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9673-dca3-a9fb-bffb7bfe0000</link>
      <description>Tillman has caught 11 passes for 106 yards and two touchdowns on the season, with most of that production coming in the first two weeks of the season. He’s seen just five targets over the last two weeks and doesn’t have much fantasy value at this time. Fantasy managers still holding him can drop him if they don’t have an injured reserve spot to stash him on. In addition to Tillman, WR/KR DeAndre Carter is also set to miss multiple weeks with a knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9673-dca3-a9fb-bffb7bfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns HC Kevin Stefanski said “my focus is on making sure this offense plays better” when asked if he was sticking with Joe Flacco entering Week 5 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-967a-d6e9-af9d-9efa34750000</link>
      <description>A day after the team’s 34-10 loss to the Lions, Stefanski’s tone on the offense and the quarterback situation remains unchanged. Rather than lay the blame solely at the feet of Flacco, who is currently sitting on an 815-2-6 passing line through four weeks, Stefanski continues to focus on improving the offense as a whole. The move to rookie Dillon Gabriel feels inevitable at this point, although it wouldn’t be surprising if Stefanski waits until the team returns to the states. The Browns play the Vikings in London in Week 5, which could make for a semi-tough environment for the third-round rookie. Another disastrous showing by Flacco should be enough to force Stefanski’s hand into a chance by Week 6 if it doesn’t come this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-967a-d6e9-af9d-9efa34750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teans HC DeMeco Ryans said Joe Mixon (foot) won’t be activated from the NFI list yet.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9684-d6e9-af9d-9e94038e0000</link>
      <description>Mixon is officially eligible to return from the NFI list after missing the required four games to start the season. Mixon reportedly had a challenging rehab this offseason, which has understandably slowed his return to the field. Until the Texans announce the decision to open Mixon’s 21-day return window, we can safely assume he’ll be sidelined for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9684-d6e9-af9d-9e94038e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bills P Cameron Johnston (leg) is likely to miss time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9688-dca3-a9fb-bf99fbed0000</link>
      <description>Johnston was banged up in the Bills’ Week 4 win over the Saints, but gutted things out for the remainder of the game. Despite the courageous effort, Johnson is now slated to miss some time with what is being classified as a lower-leg injury that could result in a stint on the IR. Johnston is averaging 44.0 yards per punt on seven punts this season, with two landing inside the opponent’s 20-yard line. The Bills will likely try out a handful of guys this week to see who they will have replace him in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9688-dca3-a9fb-bf99fbed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Marlon Humphrey (calf) is expected to miss a couple of weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9696-d95b-addb-fed69cfc0000</link>
      <description>Humphrey was one of multiple Ravens to exit Week 4’s game against the Chiefs. According to Rapoport, Humphrey’s injury is “not as bad as it could have been,” while adding that the soft tissue injuries to all Ravens players appear to be week-to-week.” We’ll get more player-specific updates soon, but the Ravens will clearly be without Humphrey in Week 5 against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9696-d95b-addb-fed69cfc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
