<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:04:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (back) is listed as doubtful for Week 17 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57a1-d35e-a1bf-57e337310000</link>
      <description>Jackson was listed as a non-participant for Thursday’s practice before getting the doubtful designation. The 28-year-old almost assuredly will be out for Saturday’s game against the Packers, meaning Tyler Huntley will get the start in that contest. Whether Jackson plays in Week 18 against the Steelers will depend on how the signal-caller heels, and also if that game has any meaning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57a1-d35e-a1bf-57e337310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Love (concussion) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57a6-d56e-afff-f7ee4f020000</link>
      <description>Both Love and Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) are listed as questionable for the Saturday night showdown against Baltimore. Signs seem to be pointing for Love to be the starter for that contest after being a limited participant estimate Thursday, but he’ll need to clear the protocol before that can happen. There should be more clarification on this situation Friday, and fantasy managers who “need” to use either should be prepared for alternate paths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57a6-d56e-afff-f7ee4f020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Willis (shoulder/illness) was listed as a limited participant for Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ab-dc7a-af9b-dfbf21620000</link>
      <description>Willis is officially listed as questionable for Saturday’s Week 17 showdown against the Ravens. The 26-year-old picked up an illness that apparently has been making its way through the team before Wednesday’s practice on top of the shoulder issue he suffered at the end of the previous week’s overtime loss to the Bears. If Jordan Love (concussion) can’t go, Willis stands a decent chance to start against Baltimore on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ab-dc7a-af9b-dfbf21620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (illness) is listed as questionable for Week 17 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ae-d56e-afff-f7eef9a20000</link>
      <description>Watson was listed as a non-participant for Thursday’s practice ahead of the Saturday showdown with Baltimore. The wideout would be on the WR3 precipice if he can go, but fantasy managers obviously need to be prepared for a substitute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ae-d56e-afff-f7eef9a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshoun Boutte (concussion) was listed as a non-participant for Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57cb-d35e-a1bf-57cb2bac0000</link>
      <description>Boutte has missed both practices this week while still being in the concussion protocol. If he can get back on the field Friday he has a chance to play, but it seems more likely than not that Boutte will be out of action for Week 17 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57cb-d35e-a1bf-57cb2bac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mack Hollins (abdomen) was listed as a non-participant for Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57cd-d968-a19b-5ffd1c0d0000</link>
      <description>Hollins has missed back-to-back practices with the injury. The Patriots also may be without Kayshoun Boutte (concussion), so Drake Maye will likely be working with a less-than-spectacular receiving crops in Week 17 against the lowly Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57cd-d968-a19b-5ffd1c0d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson (concussion) was listed as a limited participant Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57d2-d56e-afff-f7fa6d130000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimate because of the holiday. Henderson participated in warmups Wednesday in the open part of practice, and if he can clear the protocol, he’ll be the top offensive option that could be down several receivers in Week 17 against the Jets. Rhamondre Stevenson would be the bellcow if Henderson misses the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57d2-d56e-afff-f7fa6d130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) was listed as a limited participant in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57d4-d56e-afff-f7fcc95b0000</link>
      <description>It’s an estimate since the Cardinals didn’t actually practice during Christmas Day. Harrison has been limited in both practices, but if he can get in another day he stands a pretty solid chance of playing in Week 17 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57d4-d56e-afff-f7fcc95b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared LB Dre Greenlaw (hamstring), WR Pat Bryant (concussion), TE Nate Adkins (knee), DL Jordan Jackson, DL Sai’vion Jones, OL Geron Christian, OLB Que Robinson inactive for Week 17 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57e7-d35e-a1bf-57e7a8980000</link>
      <description>Greenlaw was ruled out for the Christmas showdown with Kansas City after suffering a non-contact injury against the Jags. Bryant was unable to clear the concussion protocol, so he’ll also miss Thursday’s divisional battle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57e7-d35e-a1bf-57e7a8980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared RB Dameon Pierce, CB Melvin Smith, DE Ethan Downs, DE Tyreke Smith, OL C.J. Hanson, OL Jaylon Moore and DT Derrick Nnandi inactive for Week 17 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ee-d35e-a1bf-57eea6950000</link>
      <description>Pierce was promoted to the active roster last week, but he won’t be active for the Christmas showdown against Denver as Kansas City looks to play out the string.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-57ee-d35e-a1bf-57eea6950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
