<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White (groin) returned to practice and is expected to play in Week 1 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f761-dbe3-a9bb-f77393af0000</link>
      <description>Updates have been sparse but White returned to practice last week and has been participating since then without any reported issues. August reports on the Bucs’ backfield have been unfavorable to White, though, with Bucky Irving being considered for a high-volume role that includes “pass-catching work” and head coach Todd Bowles saying he needs to give Sean Tucker the ball more. At this point, White can only be stashed in PPR leagues. His standalone value is liable to evaporate if Irving siphons away passing down snaps and the tackle-breaking Tucker could eat into White’s rushing work. If Irving misses time, White could take on a specialized role featuring his receiving skillset while Tucker leads the way on early downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f761-dbe3-a9bb-f77393af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed OT Kilian Zierer, formerly of the Texans, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f76e-d332-a1fd-f77e561e0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also signed DL Evan Anderson and correspondingly released DE William Bradley-King. Per The Athletic’s Matt Barrows, “Zierer is from Munich and is part of the NFL’s International Pathway Program,” which allows them to have 17 players on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f76e-d332-a1fd-f77e561e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed DT Eric Gregory, formerly of the Bengals, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f729-db7b-a5dd-f72d982e0000</link>
      <description>The undrafted free agent rookie totaled four quarterback pressures and two tackles in the preseason. The Patriots also signed OT Thayer Munford Jr. to the practice squad and released OL Jack Conley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f729-db7b-a5dd-f72d982e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed LB Anthony Walker, formerly of the Buccaneers, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f793-dbe3-a9bb-f7d368dd0000</link>
      <description>A knee injury kept Walker sidelined throughout the Buccaneers’ training camp. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported earlier this week that Walker is “healthy and ready to go” and the Colts were evidently pleased with his workout performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f793-dbe3-a9bb-f7d368dd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cowboys listed Javonte Williams as the team’s Week 1 starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7ba-d332-a1fd-f7bec5a40000</link>
      <description>The starting job was Williams’ to lose, and indeed, he did not lose it. The praise stops there. Williams will likely handle a flex-worthy workload against the Eagles’ vaunted defense in Week 1, while Miles Sanders and Jaydon Blue rotate in behind him. Unless Williams regains his long-lost burst, he could end up ceding touches quickly as the weeks progress. Sanders does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues. Buy Blue’s potential ADP dip. The talented receiving back is a good fit for the Cowboys’ expectedly pass-heavy game scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7ba-d332-a1fd-f7bec5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL suspended free agent DT Isaiah Buggs for the first 10 weeks of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f789-de13-afdc-f7cb0f2e0000</link>
      <description>The suspension relates to Buggs’ 2024 arrest for burglary and domestic violence charges. The charges were reportedly reduced to misdemeanor criminal trespass as part of a plea agreement. Buggs had previously been sentenced to 60 days of hard labor after being convicted of misdemeanor animal cruelty, but NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that those charges were dismissed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f789-de13-afdc-f7cb0f2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers head coach Dave Canales said TE Ja’Tavion Sanders “has really improved as a pass catcher.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7df-de13-afdc-f7df75010000</link>
      <description>The Associated Press’ Steve Reed adds that it “sort of sounds like he will be the primary pass receiver at that position,” but he notes nothing is “etched in stone.” Sanders has decent odds of etching it in stone if his improved play translates to early-season success. Tommy Tremble, Sanders’ primary competition at the position, “hopes” he will be ready for Week 1 but has not yet returned to practice after undergoing back surgery in May. Sanders is a worthwhile dart throw, who can be paired with a reliable, if unexciting, veteran option in drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7df-de13-afdc-f7df75010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent RB Keilan Robinson worked out for the Chargers on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7e5-dbe3-a9bb-f7f701c30000</link>
      <description>Robinson was joined by free agent RBs, Amar Johnson, Anthony Tyus and Owen Wright. The Chargers’ Week 1 running back depth is shaky at the moment, with Najee Harris’ (eye) availability still up in the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7e5-dbe3-a9bb-f7f701c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent WR Javon Baker worked out for the Eagles on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7f5-de13-afdc-f7ff01100000</link>
      <description>Both Baker and Rice are former Day 3 picks. Neither player had a great preseason. Baker caught 1-of-10 targets for 13 yards with the Patriots while Rice caught 3-of-9 targets for 32 yards with the Chargers. They are not on the fantasy radar at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f7f5-de13-afdc-f7ff01100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Howe reports that the Patriots have a “strong internal belief that quarterback Drake Maye will take another step forward” in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f784-d332-a1fd-f7b6cc5a0000</link>
      <description>Maye took over as the Patriots’ starter in Week 6 last year and produced five QB1 finishes thereafter. The towering dual-threat should be drafted as a high-upside QB1 after having an “impressive initial offseason with coach Mike Vrabel and offensive coordinator Josh McDaniels.” He enters 2025 with significantly improved skill position players around him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-f784-d332-a1fd-f7b6cc5a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
