<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett was named Defensive Player of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3071-d355-a5bd-bf753d7e0000</link>
      <description>Garrett totaled 23 sacks this season, setting a new NFL record along the way. He notably won Defensive Player of the Year in 2023 as well, following a 14-sack season. The nine-year veteran has astonishingly totaled double-digit sack tallies in all but his 2017 rookie season. The 30-year-old defensive end deservedly signed a four-year contract, averaging $40 million per year last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3071-d355-a5bd-bf753d7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos OLB Nik Bonitto underwent a cleanup procedure on his wrist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-308a-d629-a1bc-b09f02750000</link>
      <description>Per the Denver Post’s Luca Evans, Bonitto injured his wrist by “slamming the ground” moments after the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts. He then played the rest of the season with a large club on his right hand. Despite the issue, Bonitto still totaled 17 sacks this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-308a-d629-a1bc-b09f02750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan was named Offensive Rookie of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30c1-d042-afbc-7dd390310000</link>
      <description>McMillan caught 70-of-120 targets for 1,014 yards and seven touchdowns this season, leading all NFL rookies in the latter two categories. The Panthers’ promising youngster proved himself as an NFL-ready No. 1 wide receiver. He is primed for another big outing in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30c1-d042-afbc-7dd390310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Thuney was named Protector of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd91e60000</link>
      <description>Thuney wins the NFL’s inaugural offensive linemen award in his first season with the Bears, who acquired him in exchange for a 2026 fourth-round draft pick in March 2025. Although the left tackle position remains one of the most important positions in football, Thuney, a left guard, winning the award proves that Protector of the Year will not simply be handed to the NFL’s best left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd91e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey was named the 2025 Associated Press NFL Comeback Player of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cf-d89c-a1be-bfdf22d90000</link>
      <description>McCaffrey astonishingly handled a career-high 413 touches in his age-29 season, totaling 102 receptions, 2,126 scrimmage yards and 17 touchdowns. To say he deserves this award is an understatement. He notably won the Offensive Player of the Year award in 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cf-d89c-a1be-bfdf22d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Vrabel was named NFL Coach of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30dd-d355-a5bd-bfdd1b370000</link>
      <description>The Patriots finished with a 4-13 record one year ago. Now, in Vrabel’s first season as head coach, they are preparing to play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks following a 14-3 season. Patriots OC Josh McDaniels was named Assistant Coach of the Year earlier this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30dd-d355-a5bd-bfdd1b370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Charlotte Carroll reports that the Giants are “bringing on Greg Roman to the staff.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30ea-d355-a5bd-bffe96630000</link>
      <description>The move reunites him with Giants head coach John Harbaugh. Roman previously served as Harbaugh’s offensive coordinator with the Ravens from 2019-2022. He served as the Chargers’ offensive coordinator under head coach Jim Harbaugh over the last two seasons. Per Carroll, Roman’s role will be on the offensive side of the ball.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30ea-d355-a5bd-bffe96630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxon Smith-Njigba was named Offensive Player of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30dc-d355-a5bd-bfdc6ad90000</link>
      <description>Smith-Njigba put together an extremely impressive stat line in his third NFL season, catching 119-of-163 targets for 1,793 yards and 10 touchdowns. He also earned first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors this year after blossoming into a true No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30dc-d355-a5bd-bfdc6ad90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford was named the 2025 Associated Press Most Valuable Player.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3116-d042-afbc-7dd6d7f70000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter notes that this was the closest MVP race since Peyton Manning and Steve McNair shared the award in 2003. Stafford narrowly beat Patriots QB Drake Maye, winning 24 first-place votes to Maye’s 23 while totaling 366 points to Maye’s 361. Stafford closed his acceptance speech by telling the audience he will return for another season in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3116-d042-afbc-7dd6d7f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carson Schwesinger was named Defensive Rookie of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-311a-d89c-a1be-bfdfa5760000</link>
      <description>Schwesinger notched 156 total tackles, 67 solo tackles, 2.5 sacks, 11 TFLs, three pass breakups and two interceptions despite missing Week 18 with a high-ankle sprain. It was an extremely impressive season for the No. 33 overall pick in last year’s draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-311a-d89c-a1be-bfdfa5760000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
