<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 19:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (appendicitis) is out for Week 11.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7901-d713-ad9e-7d55420e0000</link>
      <description>Harrison underwent appendicitis surgery and will be sidelined for at least one week, according to the Cardinals. Harrison’s absence comes as Jacoby Brissett — with Kyler Murray on IR — has breathed new life into the previously dormant Arizona passing attack. The Cardinals will also be without Zay Jones, who injured his Achilles in Week 10’s loss against Seattle. Look for Greg Dortch to take on a full-time role this week against a weak 49ers pass defense. Michael Wilson could see a slight increase in targets with MHJ sidelined. Trey McBride will continue seeing ample targets in the pass-first Arizona offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7901-d713-ad9e-7d55420e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said he’s “excited” about WR Mecole Hardman.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-790d-d673-a39e-fd9dc6440000</link>
      <description>McDermott complimented the “flexibility” Hardman brings to the offense. The Bills signed Hardman to their practice squad on Tuesday. The longtime Chiefs gadget player and kicker returner could suit up for the Bills as soon as Week 11 against the Bucs. He had just 26 receptions over his past final two seasons with the Chiefs and hasn’t scored a regular season touchdown since 2022. Hardman will likely be a situational player in the run-heavy Buffalo offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-790d-d673-a39e-fd9dc6440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants QB Jameis Winston will start Week 11 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7927-d45b-affe-7db712780000</link>
      <description>Interim head coach Mike Kafka made the announcement after Jaxson Dart was placed in the league’s concussion protocol. Winston’s aggressiveness and willingness to push the ball downfield should benefit Darius Slayton, Theo Johnson, and Wan’Dale Robinson in Week 11 and beyond, if Dart misses more time while recovering from his latest head injury. Winston last season in Cleveland threw 13 touchdowns to 12 picks over seven starts. He averaged nearly 300 passing yards per game for the Browns. Winston should be picked up in all superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7927-d45b-affe-7db712780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Joe Flacco (shoulder) will not throw during Wednesday’s practice but is expected to resume throwing tomorrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-793a-d45b-affe-7dbe7a6f0000</link>
      <description>The Bengals are taking a cautious approach with Flacco’s shoulder injury, just like they did in Week 9 before their bye. He sat out of practice on Wednesday and Friday but got some light work in on Thursday. Flacco still played in Week 9, throwing for an astounding 470 yards and four scores. He will likely get a similar practice regimen this week. Flacco should be good to go as a volume-based QB2 for his Week 11 date with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-793a-d45b-affe-7dbe7a6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton (hamstring) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7943-d713-ad9e-7d57193b0000</link>
      <description>Slayton could get in some light work later in the practice, but it looks like a DNP for now. Slayton left Week 10’s game with the hamstring injury, only to return later in the contest. Either he was running on adrenaline and this injury could be costly, or Wednesday’s DNP is a precaution. We will get more info on tomorrow’s injury report. Slayton will be a boom/bust WR5 with Jameis Winston under center if he manages tos suit up this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7943-d713-ad9e-7d57193b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7956-d673-a39e-fdd725e50000</link>
      <description>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid alluded to this earlier in the week, saying Pacheco “may take more time.” It sounds like he is on the wrong side of questionable as of Wednesday. Assuming Pacheco is out for Week 11, Kareem Hunt is in line for the bulk of the Chiefs’ carries. Hunt ran 11 times for 49 yards and a touchdown before the team’s Week 10 bye. Brashard Smith and Clyde Edwards-Helaire will be in the mix for backup duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7956-d673-a39e-fdd725e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson is not practicing Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-795d-d673-a39e-fddd67790000</link>
      <description>As ESPN’s Jamison Hensley notes, Jackson took a few hard hits on Sunday versus the Vikings. He was never listed with an injury and did not miss any snaps. Jackson previously missed a handful of games with a hamstring issue this year. We won’t find out what his latest issue is until the Ravens drop their first injury report of the week later today. The hope is that he didn’t re-aggravate the hamstring injury in Week 10. Tyler Huntley would be in line to start if Jackson misses more time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-795d-d673-a39e-fddd67790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7964-d713-ad9e-7d7445d50000</link>
      <description>Bateman reportedly suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 10 against the Vikings. He was spotted in a boot after the game. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reports on Monday that Bateman will be okay, but he didn’t say whether or not the wideout would be able to suit up in Week 11. Our best guess as of Wednesday is that Bateman will miss at least one game. His absence could mean more 2TE sets for the Ravens, putting both Mark Andrews and Isaiah Likely on the field more often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7964-d713-ad9e-7d7445d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports C.J. Stroud (concussion) did not practice Wednesday and is still experiencing symptoms.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7968-d45b-affe-7dfe1b430000</link>
      <description>Per Wilson, Davis Mills is prepping to start in Week 11 against the Titans. Mills drew the start last week and pulled off a miraculous comeback over the Jags. The Texans scored 26 unanswered points in the fourth quarter, punctuated by a 14-yard rushing touchdown with less than a minute left on the clock. His heroics likely won’t be needed this week. Even without Stroud, Houston should have no issues handling business versus the Titans. Mills will remain buried in the QB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7968-d45b-affe-7dfe1b430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Davis Mills is “prepping to start” in Week 11 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee82a10000</link>
      <description>C.J. Stroud is still experiencing concussion symptoms and remains in the league’s protocol. He did not practice Wednesday. Mills threw for 292 yards and two scores in an upset win over the Jags last week. He also ran for 30 yards and a game-winning touchdown. Mills won’t be asked to do nearly as much against the lowly Titans this week. He will slot in as a low-end QB2 for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee82a10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
