<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Parker Washington caught 1-of-3 targets for 26 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 13 game against the Titans prior to exiting with a hip injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d658-db57-afda-d67a64200000</link>
      <description>Washington fell on a punt return and subsequently left in the second quarter of the Jaguars’ game against the Titans. He was initially questionable to return but officially ruled out after halftime. The 23-year-old was getting increased opportunities when Brian Thomas Jr. was out and saw three targets before exiting. Washington will try to work his way back for Week 14 against the Colts; Austin Trammell will take slot snaps with Washington out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d658-db57-afda-d67a64200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declare TE Michael Mayer, RB Zamir White, QB Aidan O’Connell, CB Darnay Holmes, LB Jamin Davis, OG Jordan Meredith and DT Tonka Hemingway inactive for Week 13 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d659-d90e-a9da-df5f3f8d0000</link>
      <description>Mayer was unable to practice all week, rehabbing an ankle injury. He is not fantasy-relevant when active, though. O’Connell will be available to the team as the emergency third quarterback. Holmes’ illness-induced absence against a talented Chargers passing attack is unfortunate. Raiders DT Adam Butler (illness) is active, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d659-d90e-a9da-df5f3f8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared WR Adam Thielen, QB J.J. McCarthy, S Theo Jackson, T Christian Darrisaw, G Donovan Jackson, TE Ben Yurosek, and DL Elijah Williams inactive for Week 13 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d660-db57-afda-d67226480000</link>
      <description>Thielen did not have an injury headed into this week, so we’re assuming he’s a health scratch after managing eight receptions over 11 games. Look for Jalen Nailor to see more routes and possibly more targets against Seattle with Thielen out. Nailor could be started in deeper formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d660-db57-afda-d67226480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) is officially inactive for Week 13 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d662-d6c4-abfb-d6637be90000</link>
      <description>The Bills offense could really use Kincaid back right now, but it seems like they’ll have to wait for Week 14 against the Bengals at the earliest. That would seem to be a good landing spot for Kincaid, who was putting together a career-best season before this hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d662-d6c4-abfb-d6637be90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared RB Cam Akers, WR Jake Bobo, CB Shaquill Griffin, LB Jared Ivey, QB Jalen Milroe, LB Connor O’Toole, and OT Mason Richman inactive for Week 13 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d665-db57-afda-d6778c360000</link>
      <description>Akers, who signed with the Seahawks on Wednesday, will be a healthy scratch for now, leaving Zach Charbonnet and Ken Walker as the team’s rushers for another week. Walker last week saw an uptick in usage last week and should be a flex option Sunday against the Vikings. Akers is a decent bench stash in deeper leagues for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d665-db57-afda-d6778c360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer (ankle) is inactive for Week 13 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d665-db57-afda-d677131e0000</link>
      <description>The Bills were already down Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) and both starting tackles, Dion Dawkins (concussion) and Spencer Brown (shoulder), so Palmer also being inactive will leave this offense extremely short-handed. On defense, the Bills also declared DT Phidarian Mathis, LB Terrel Bernard, and CB Ja’Marcus Ingram inactive for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d665-db57-afda-d677131e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman is active for the Bills in Week 13 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d667-d6c4-abfb-d667efd80000</link>
      <description>With Curtis Samuel on the IR and Josh Palmer battling an ankle injury, Keon Coleman will be back on the active roster after two weeks as a healthy inactive. If there was ever a time for the 2024 second-round pick to get back in his team’s good graces, it would be with the offense short-handed against the Steelers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d667-d6c4-abfb-d667efd80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared WR Scotty Miller, QB Will Howard, CB Darius Slay. DL Logan Lee, and DT Derrick Harmon inactive for Week 13 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d66a-d90e-a9da-df6f681b0000</link>
      <description>Darius Slay is a healthy inactive with Asante Samuel Jr. on the active roster now. The other inactives are to be expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d66a-d90e-a9da-df6f681b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shedeur Sanders completed 16-of-25 attempts for 149 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 13 loss against the 49ers, adding one rush for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d677-d6c4-abfb-d677132a0000</link>
      <description>Sanders was dinged up in the fourth quarter after being hit by two Niners defenders on an awkward slide. He was sacked three times on the day in an extremely conservative offensive approach full of designed check downs to running backs and tight ends. Eleven of Sanders’ 16 completions were to tight ends and running backs. The Browns were calling screen passes down three scores in the fourth quarter, much to the home crowd’s chagrin. Sanders, who could start for the rest of the season as the team evaluates him, will be a superflex option in Week 14 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d677-d6c4-abfb-d677132a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
