<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RT Zach Tom (knee) said he’s “leaning towards surgery” on a partially torn patellar tendon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b35f-dc7a-af9b-ffff9ec40000</link>
      <description>The estimated recovery time on the surgery is six months, which would put Tom as likely to be ready for training camp. Tom played 604 snaps and was one of Green Bay’s best offensive linemen, with an 83.5 PFF grade between a couple of major injuries. His status is worth monitoring, but for now we’re assuming he’ll be ready for camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b35f-dc7a-af9b-ffff9ec40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released EDGE Darrell Taylor.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b362-dc7a-af9b-ffff7fbf0000</link>
      <description>They needed the roster spot ahead of tonight’s Wild Card playoff game against the Steelers, as they’re activating S Jaylen Reed from injured reserve. Taylor played just 35 snaps for the Texans in 2025 and has been a moderate disappointment. If the Texans survive the night, it’s possible he’s brought back on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b362-dc7a-af9b-ffff7fbf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes reports that there is “belief amongst other coaching candidates that it’s the Giants or Falcons” for John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b364-d968-a19b-fbf543030000</link>
      <description>Per Hughes’ report, the loser of the sweepstakes would then land Kevin Stefanski. Not a bad consolation prize. Harbaugh is “No. 1" on the Giants board, per Hughes, which jives with all the reporting we’ve seen so far on the situation. The Falcons have played things closer to the vest as they worked on settling their ridiculously-named “president of football” situation, but appear to be a team to monitor in the Harbaugh sweepstakes as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b364-d968-a19b-fbf543030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (shoulder) will miss the remainder of the playoffs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b367-d56e-afff-f7efea260000</link>
      <description>He re-aggravated his scapula injury and will be placed on season-ending injured reserve. The 31-year-old enters free agency having played just 186 snaps this year and 598 the year before. The Rams seem to have an affinity for the corner and will likely keep paying him the veteran minimum if no one else wants to snap him up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b367-d56e-afff-f7efea260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay was “optimistic” that TE Terrance Ferguson (hamstring) will play in the Divisional Round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36a-d35e-a1bf-f7eace810000</link>
      <description>McVay added that G Kevin Dotson also has a good chance to return against the Bears. With all four of his tight ends healthy, the Rams’ 13-personnel set will become a more complicated situation to read for fantasy purposes. Ferguson seemed to be coming on late in the season before injuring his hamstring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36a-d35e-a1bf-f7eace810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns completed an interview with former Dolphins head coach Mike McDaniel for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36f-d56e-afff-f7ef8e590000</link>
      <description>That’s the Browns, Falcons, Ravens and Titans with interviews scheduled or completed for McDaniel, who has taken exclusively head-coaching interviews so far. (The Lions have reached out to McDaniel about their offensive coordinator vacancy, but he hasn’t taken the interview as far as we can tell.) McDaniel is probably one of the most valuable 32 head coaches in the league given what he managed to squeeze out of the Dolphins in the Tua Tagovailoa Era, but he doesn’t exactly have widespread appeal amongst the eight head-coaching vacancies. He’s one of the more fascinating coaching free agents this go-around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b36f-d56e-afff-f7ef8e590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Chargers DC Jesse Minter for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b37d-d968-a19b-fbfdcc820000</link>
      <description>This was actually one of the expected names that surfaced up in the immediate moments after John Harbaugh was fired, so the only surprising thing is that it took this many days for the request to formally be submitted. Minter has interview requests from the Browns and Titans for their head-coaching vacancies as well, and has some time to set up those interviews now that the Chargers have been eliminated from the playoffs despite holding Drake Maye’s high-flying show to 16 points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b37d-d968-a19b-fbfdcc820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens completed an interview with Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b380-d35e-a1bf-f7c22b1c0000</link>
      <description>That’s the first completed interview for Weaver, who was also requested by the Cardinals and Falcons last week. The 45-year-old Dolphins defensive coordinator mostly has a recent reputation of making something out of nothing as the Dolphins were given little chance on defense last year with a rough secondary and finished 24th in defensive DVOA. Weaver played for the Ravens and also coached them for quite a bit, rising as high as Assistant Head Coach to John Harbaugh before taking the Dolphins job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b380-d35e-a1bf-f7c22b1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens requested an interview with Rams pass game coordinator Nate Scheelhaase for their head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b385-d968-a19b-fbf5ee8b0000</link>
      <description>So have the Raiders. The McVay assistant coaching tree continues to be well-plumbed. Scheelhaase stayed put this year after nearly signing on as Jaguars offensive coordinator in 2025 silly season. It’s possible that he leaps to an offensive coordinator gig this year, but the fact that he’s already drawing head-coaching interviews shows his name is on the rise. The Ravens have a crowded board right now, about 10-15 candidates deep, and the Raiders have requested just six names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b385-d968-a19b-fbf5ee8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested an interview with Rams DC Chris Shula for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b388-dc7a-af9b-ffbf8e140000</link>
      <description>They’re joined by the Cardinals and Raiders, adding to the initial two names of the Titans and Dolphins from over the weekend. Shula’s defense has faded down the stretch, but finished fourth in defensive DVOA during the regular season. It should not be lost on anybody that Shula is doing this despite almost no investment on that side of the ball — the Rams have the lowest defensive payroll in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-b388-dc7a-af9b-ffbf8e140000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
