<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said Darren Waller will practice this week and is on track to play in Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05bb-dbe3-a9bb-35fb794a0000</link>
      <description>There’s no way to know what we should expect from Waller, who is attempting to return to football after a year away and missed most of training camp. The veteran tight end could see a very limited workload in Week 1 as he returns to action, and shouldn’t be counted on in fantasy until we see him earning a reliable snap share and/or target share.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05bb-dbe3-a9bb-35fb794a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed RB Jaylen Warren to a two-year extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05c9-db7b-a5dd-a5cd3a530000</link>
      <description>A former UDFA who made the Steelers’ 53-man roster during the 2022 season, Warren is now being rewarded for his efforts with a multi-year extension. Since joining the Steelers, Warren, who will receive $12 million in guaranteed money on his new deal, has rushed for 346-1,674-6 while adding another 127 receptions for 894 scoreless yards over that span. The fourth-year back is set to open the season as the Steelers’ RB1, but will have to fight off rookie Kaleb Johnson, who was drafted with the No. 83 overall pick in this year’s draft. Warren profiles as a decent RB2 for fantasy based on his expected volume, but his underwhelming touchdown production has limited his upside thus far in his career. He’s far from a must-start in Week 1 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05c9-db7b-a5dd-a5cd3a530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports free agent WR Kendrick Bourne is visiting with the 49ers on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05d4-d332-a1fd-97f6abea0000</link>
      <description>Bourne spent the first four years of his career with the 49ers before joining the Patriots during the 2021 offseason. He has never surpassed 800 yards in a season and was phased out by the Patriots this offseason, which ultimately led to the team’s decision to release him. The Niners are dealing with multiple injuries at receiver, which could create an immediate opening for playing time for Bourne should the two sides reunite. According to Schultz, if Bourne and the Niners don’t agree to a deal, he is scheduled to visit with the Commanders on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05d4-d332-a1fd-97f6abea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) won’t practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05f5-de13-afdd-47ff214a0000</link>
      <description>This news comes just days after the team declined to specify a return date for the star corner, who first suffered the injury on July 28. There will still be time for Gonzalez to take the practice field before the team has to decide on his availability heading into the weekend, but an early absence isn’t a great start. If Gonzalez is unable to go, second-year corner Charles Woods is listed behind him on the depth chart and would presumably draw the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-05f5-de13-afdd-47ff214a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said Jalen Coker has a “significant quad strain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0606-dbe3-a9bb-36575fce0000</link>
      <description>Coker has already been placed on injured reserve and will miss at least the first four games of the season. However, Canales’ most recent comments suggest the second-year receiver could be looking at an absence that extends beyond the four-game minimum. The Panthers re-signed Hunter Renfrow late last week, giving them an easy replacement for Coker in the slot, but we wouldn’t expect Renfrow to have much fantasy upside at this time. We will provide any additional updates on Coker as they come available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0606-dbe3-a9bb-36575fce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns CB Greg Newsome said his shoulder “feels amazing” after being limited due to the injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0616-db7b-a5dd-a61631cc0000</link>
      <description>Newsome was limited throughout most of training camp due to his shoulder injury, but the veteran corner says the shoulder “will not be a factor” as he prepares for Week 1’s game against the Bengals. Newsome was once thought to be a cap casualty by the Browns this offseason, but remains on the roster and is expected to play a key role as the team’s second corner opposite Denzel Ward. Newsome, 25, totaled 27 tackles and one interception in 13 games for the Browns last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0616-db7b-a5dd-a61631cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyreek Hill (oblique) is expected to play in Week 1 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0622-d332-a1fd-963682e80000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t come as much of a surprise after the team said last week that the star receiver “looks great” for the team’s season opener. Hill was reportedly participating in Monday’s practice, but we’ll have a better sense of his availability when the first practice report is released on Wednesday. Assuming he’s active, Hill should profile as a fringe WR1/WR2 against a Colts secondary that allowed the seventh-most passing yards per game last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0622-d332-a1fd-963682e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton (leg) is practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0649-de13-afdd-46cb65690000</link>
      <description>It’s not exactly a guarantee that Otton will avoid missing this week’s game against the Falcons — Todd Bowles said he’d be “out for a little bit” last week — but it is a step in the right direction. The injury reports starting Wednesday will tell the tale of Otton’s Week 1 status better than this report does. Sean Tucker also returned to practice per Stroud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0649-de13-afdd-46cb65690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (knee) believes he will play against the Eagles in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-064c-dbe3-a9bb-365f71810000</link>
      <description>Nothing has been decided yet. The teams have not put up an injury report yet, but Guyton seems to have a chance to shake his injury off ahead of the 4-6 week timeline. Guyton went down with what was feared to be a torn ACL but wound up as “merely” a bone fracture in his knee in late July and has not participated in the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-064c-dbe3-a9bb-365f71810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said the coaching staff is still evaluating Travis Hunter’s usage in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0667-de13-afdd-46ef5d230000</link>
      <description>The question asked was if Hunter would start on both sides of the ball. Coen emphasized that they’re working through it and he “missed a lot of time” with his upper body injury. This isn’t necessarily a fantasy football fire alarm, but it does sound like Hunter’s preseason injury should have us with slightly lowered expectations for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0667-de13-afdd-46ef5d230000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
