<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bears HC Ben Johnson said Jaylon Johnson will undergo core muscle surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-730b-d6a5-adff-f7cfc0d90000</link>
      <description>Johnson didn’t rule out a possible return this season for his corner, but this surgery will likely land him on injured reserve for the foreseeable future. Johnson was injured in the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Lions and hasn’t seen the field since, but his extended absence is bad news for a Bears secondary that has already struggled out of the gate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-730b-d6a5-adff-f7cfc0d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers HC Jim Harbaugh confirmed Najee Harris suffered a torn Achilles in Week 3’s win over the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7323-d1b3-a5dd-73735a0c0000</link>
      <description>Harbaugh didn’t leave much to the imagination following Sunday’s game when he said preliminary tests indicated a torn Achilles for Harris, who went down on a non-contact play. It’s a season-ender for the 27-year-old running back whose 2025 challenges began with a fireworks accident on July 4th. Harris signed a one-year contract with the Chargers this offseason and sees his season come to an end with a 15-61-0 rushing line to go with three receptions for 25 scoreless yards. Harris will be a free agent this offseason and could be faced with having to sign a one-year prove-it deal wherever he lands next.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7323-d1b3-a5dd-73735a0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys HC Brian Schottenheimer said DaRon Bland (foot) is “trending to play” in Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7358-d93f-ad9d-7bdfce2a0000</link>
      <description>Bland has missed the last two games due to a foot injury he suffered in Week 1, but the fourth-year corner could be on the field in a pivotal Week 4 matchup against a tough Packers team. Bland avoided being placed on injured reserve after going down in the season-opener, so a return within four weeks was always on the table. The Cowboys will release their first injury report of the week on Wednesday. Bland’s name will be one to keep an eye on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7358-d93f-ad9d-7bdfce2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals HC Jonathan Gannon confirmed James Conner will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-735d-d1b3-a5dd-737d07990000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported late last night that Conner “did in fact suffer a season-ending injury,” but Gannon officially confirmed things on Monday. The veteran running back suffered a devastating ankle injury that required him to be carted from the field and will undergo surgery soon. Conner, 30, remains under contract with the Cardinals through the 2026 season and will turn 31 in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-735d-d1b3-a5dd-737d07990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed RB Khalil Herbert to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7370-dfde-a1bd-7ffdf8bd0000</link>
      <description>Herbert worked out for the Commanders after being released by the Colts at roster cuts this offseason, now catching on with the Seahawks. Whether his signing is correlated to the injury to Zach Charbonnet remains to be seen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7370-dfde-a1bd-7ffdf8bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys G Tyler Booker (ankle) will miss 4-6 weeks with a high-ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7374-d6a5-adff-f7f59bcb0000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are now with two-thirds of the interior of their offensive line as Booker joins center Cooper Beebe on the sideline with multi-week injuries. Both Booker and wide receiver CeeDee Lamb emerged from the team’s Week 3 loss to the Bears with high-ankle sprains, making it that much more difficult to claw their way out of a 1-2 start to the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7374-d6a5-adff-f7f59bcb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said he expects QB Brock Purdy (toe/shoulder) to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-738c-d1b3-a5dd-73fd28280000</link>
      <description>Purdy has missed the previous two games with toe and shoulder issues, leaving Mac Jones to start in his absence. Jones reportedly aggravated a PCL injury in Week 3, something that could push Purdy to return at less than full strength ahead of a meeting with the 2-1 Jaguars. Fantasy managers will want to monitor his practice statuses throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-738c-d1b3-a5dd-73fd28280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Falcons fired WR coach Ike Hilliard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7395-d6a5-adff-f7d59cbe0000</link>
      <description>Passing game coordinator T.J. Yates will be given additional responsibilities as he now takes over the wide receiver coach duties. Hilliard was hired before the 2024 season but made it just over a season before being let go. His departure comes in the wake of a 30-0 loss to the reeling Panthers in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7395-d6a5-adff-f7d59cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared S Thomas Harper, RB Craig Reynolds, OL Kingsley Equakun, DL Chris Smith, and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Week 3 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-739a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf8ce30000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here as the Lions enter Week 3 as one of the healthier teams in the league. They will have their hands full against the 1-1 Ravens on Monday Night Football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-739a-d93f-ad9d-7bdf8ce30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared RB Keaton Mitchell, CB Jaire Alexander, OT Carson Vinson, DT Nnamdi Madubuike, OLB Kyle Van Noy, TE Isaiah Likely, and FB Patrick Ricard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-739d-d1b3-a5dd-73fdcf5a0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens have been bitten hard by the injury bug to start the season, with at least five regular starters watching from the sidelines against a tenacious Lions team. Alexander, Madubuike, and Van Noy are particularly massive absences in each level of the defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-739d-d1b3-a5dd-73fdcf5a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
