<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:03:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Falcons head coach Raheem Morris will interview with the Titans, Cardinals, and Giants for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</link>
      <description>Morris, fired by the Falcons after going 20-25 over three seasons, will join a bevy of former head coaches and coordinators in interviewing with the Cardinals, Titans, and Giants, who are reportedly “all in” on hiring former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh. Morris, 49, struggled with in-game decision making and was among the league’s most conservative fourth down decision makers during his three years in Atlanta. His defensive background would be appealing to any of these three teams after their defenses collapsed in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Bengals offensive coordinator Dan Pitcher for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</link>
      <description>Pitcher, 39, has garnered some head coaching interest in previous hiring cycles but has never been considered a leading candidate for any job. He would be a long shot to land the Browns head coaching job, though the team could fall back on Pitcher if other, more experienced candidates turn down one of the most thankless jobs in football. Pitcher is known for his work with quarterbacks — a key qualification for anyone who gets the head coaching gig in Cleveland. Pitcher once worked for the Colts scouting department alongside Browns general manager Andrew Berry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (foot) was a “full go” for Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996c-d968-a19b-d9fd7fb00000</link>
      <description>Allen played just one snap in a meaningless Week 18 against the Jets after struggling with a foot injury the week before. Allen, among the toughest NFL players in recent memory, should be fine for the Bills’ Wild Card game against the Jaguars. Jacksonville’s ability to stop the run could force Allen into more drop backs than usual. He’s had more than 30 pass attempts in a game six times in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996c-d968-a19b-d9fd7fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills opened the 21-day practice window for S Damar Hamlin (pec).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5d6d0000</link>
      <description>Hamlin could return as soon as this week against the Jaguars in the Wild Card round. He’s been sidelined since early October with the pectoral injury. Hamlin would likely be a rotational player in the Buffalo secondary against the Jags. He had one tackle and zero interceptions before his pec injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5d6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin could part ways with the team this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9972-d968-a19b-d9f3550c0000</link>
      <description>While Fowler conceded there “is no firm evidence as of now” that Tomlin will walk away from the Steelers head coaching job following the 2025-26 season, a source close to Tomlin “believes stepping away is at least a possibility.” Another source told Fowler Tomlin will return to the team for a 20th season at the helm. Fowlers said Tomlin “would be more intrigued by doing TV than returning to the coaching market, should he leave the Steelers. The source wonders what Tomlin has left to chase as an NFL coach.” The team rallied around Tomlin in December and January when it was clear his job could be on the line without a postseason berth. It’s possible Monday night will be Tomlin’s final game on the Pittsburgh sideline, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9972-d968-a19b-d9f3550c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (knee) practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-997e-d35e-a1bf-ddfedc600000</link>
      <description>Kincaid should be able to suit up in the Wild Card round against the Jaguars if he can practice in some capacity on Thursday and Friday. Kincaid, who had three receptions for 48 yards last week against the Jets, could be a key player for Buffalo as they face the NFL’s most extreme pass-funnel defense. Jacksonville allows 8.7 tight end targets per game, the second highest mark in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-997e-d35e-a1bf-ddfedc600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9986-d35e-a1bf-ddc63f3f0000</link>
      <description>Prater appeared to re-injure his quad in Week 18’s meaningless game against the Jets and is now iffy for the Wild Card round against Jacksonville. The Bills could re-sign veteran journeyman K Michael Badgley, who spent time on the practice squad in December. Prater has converted 18 of his 20 field goal tries this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9986-d35e-a1bf-ddc63f3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers placed CB Bo Melton on injured reserve with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-999f-d35e-a1bf-dddfa22c0000</link>
      <description>Melton injured his knee in Week 18. Having been placed on injured reserve, he must now miss at least four games. The Packers only have four potential games left to play this season, so we will not see Melton until next season. The coaching staff switched Melton from wide receiver to cornerback last offseason, but he never once lined up on defense this year, instead logging 96 snaps on offense and 186 on special teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-999f-d35e-a1bf-dddfa22c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders have requested an interview with Raiders DC Patrick Graham for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d35e-a1bf-ddee67990000</link>
      <description>The Raiders had a bumpy year, but Graham’s defense allowed the 11th-fewest yards per play (5.1) to opponents this season. Graham interviewed for the Jaguars, Chargers and Seahawks head-coaching vacancies in 2025. The Commanders’ defense struggled under defensive-minded head coach Dan Quinn this year. Adding Graham to his staff could be a very smart move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d35e-a1bf-ddee67990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys co-owner Stephen Jones said re-signing RB Javonte Williams to a multi-year extension is “at the top of the list” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d968-a19b-d9ff94950000</link>
      <description>Williams, 25, produced multiple career-bests this season, notably rushing for more than 1,000 yards for the very first time. A multi-year extension could keep Williams in a Cowboys uniform through the rest of his prime. Hopefully, the team can get the No. 2 RB role sorted out in 2026 to help keep Williams fresh down the stretch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-99ae-d968-a19b-d9ff94950000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
