<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:02:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Football Talk’s Mike Florio believes the Eagles are “shopping A.J. Brown without officially shopping” him ahead of the NFL’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</link>
      <description>Florio said he’s heard of several contending teams that are interested in acquiring Brown if the Eagles are willing to part with the star wideout. That includes, per Florio, the Patriots, whose head coach — Mike Vrabel — coached Brown in Tennessee. “This to me feels like an effort by the Eagles to shop A.J. Brown without shopping A.J. Brown, to wait for the phone to ring, to not be the one who picks up the phone” to engage in trade talks before the November 4 league deadline. “Something’s been going on there,” Florio said of Brown, who has complained for years about his lack of opportunities in the run-heavy Philadelphia offense. Brown’s fantasy prospects would see a slight bump if he were to land with a more pass-first team, and his exit from the Eagles offense would make DeVonta Smith a borderline elite fantasy option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-303a-de12-a19e-363ac3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers opened the 21-day practice window for G Chandler Zavala (knee).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</link>
      <description>Zavala has been on injured reserve with a knee injury since October 1. The Panthers, struggling to protect the passer in recent weeks, could use Zavala back in action this week against a ferocious Packers front seven. Pro Football Focus grades Carolina’s offensive line as the 12th worst pass blocking unit through Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-305d-d4ed-a9de-77dfe5a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Joe Flacco’s (shoulder) Week 9 status is “up in the air.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</link>
      <description>Flacco is dealing with an AC joint sprain, per Rapoport. He sustained the injury late in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss against the Jets and could miss this week’s game against the Bears. That would force Jake Browning back under center for the Bengals, a huge hit to the fantasy prospects of every Cincy pass catcher, including Ja’Marr Chase. Fantasy managers should keep a close eye on Flacco’s Thursday and Friday practice status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-306f-d321-a5bf-b2ff23cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed TE Marcedes Lewis, formerly of the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</link>
      <description>The Broncos are looking for some tight end depth with Nate Adkins potentially missing time with injury. Lewis, 41, has played 19 NFL seasons. He has six receptions over his past three years in the league. It’s safe to say he won’t have any fantasy usefulness in Denver’s offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3073-d48c-ad9f-fc7f99c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed EDGE Aidan Hutchinson to a four-year contract extension worth $180 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3091-de12-a19e-36b1590d0000</link>
      <description>The mega-deal includes $141 million in guarantees, according to NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero. It’s the most guaranteed money ever for a non-quarterback in the NFL. Hutchinson, 25, who’s now signed with Detroit through 2030, has been stellar in 2025, recording six sacks and forcing four fumbles through seven games. He has 34.5 sacks in 46 NFL games since entering the league in 2022. Pro Football Focus grades Hutchinson as the league’s second best pass rusher behind Micah Parsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3091-de12-a19e-36b1590d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Michael Penix (knee) will take the “majority” of first-team practice snaps this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30a9-de12-a19e-36a9b3450000</link>
      <description>Kirk Cousins took most of the Falcons’ first-team practice snaps late last week with Penix dealing with a knee issue. Cousins started in Week 8 against the Dolphins and struggled mightily, throwing for 173 scoreless yards with an adjusted yards per attempt of 5.5. “Michael is in the building. He’ll go out there today and do walk-through. We’ll get a chance to get a feel for what he can do in practice, if he can do anything,” Morris said. “But obviously we’ll get to that right after this and find out what he’s doing, how he can do it and how he feels and all that type of stuff. Obviously he feels better than he did last week. Obviously he feels better than he did every single day with it being a bone bruise. That stuff gets better every day. So, I feel really good about him.” Penix’s return this week against the Patriots would be a boost for every Atlanta pass catcher, though it remains to be seen whether Drake London (hip) will be ready for Week 9. Among the most inaccurate passers in the league, Penix is only usable in deeper superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30a9-de12-a19e-36a9b3450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders opened the 21-day practice window for QB Aidan O’Connell (wrist).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ad-de12-a19e-36ad903b0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell has been sidelined for nearly two months with a wrist injury. He could be back as the Raiders’ backup QB for Week 9 against the Jaguars, or the team could wait until Week 10 or 11 to make him active. O’Connell could end up seeing playing time in 2025 unless Geno Smith can turn it around in the next few weeks. Smith has been among the least efficient quarterbacks in football this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ad-de12-a19e-36ad903b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Davis (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30b5-d48c-ad9f-fcfdc01d0000</link>
      <description>Davis still has a good chance to suit up in Week 9 against the Chiefs if he can get in a limited practice on Thursday and Friday. Davis is purely a contingency fantasy option behind James Cook for now. In Week 8, Davis had nine rushes for 16 yards in garbage time against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30b5-d48c-ad9f-fcfdc01d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills activated WR Gabe Davis to the team’s practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30c1-d48c-ad9f-fccd1d540000</link>
      <description>Davis will practice with the Bills for the first time this season after signing with the team in early September. He’s coming off a terrible 2024 season in Jacksonville, where he managed 20 catches for 239 yards and two touchdowns over ten games before injuring his knee. Davis could be active for Week 9 against the Chiefs, who in the 2023 postseason allowed 201 yards and four touchdowns to Davis as the Bills fell in overtime to KC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30c1-d48c-ad9f-fccd1d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports there’s “no chance” Myles Garett will be traded ahead of the league’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30e3-de12-a19e-36e335150000</link>
      <description>“People have a better chance of winning the lottery,” a source told Schefter. It appears Garrett, who has ten sacks through eight games this season, will remain with the Browns for at least another lost season. Garrett, 29, would surely draw a king’s ransom from a contending team looking to shore up their defense ahead of the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30e3-de12-a19e-36e335150000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
