<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins K Jason Sanders (hip) is questionable for Week 17 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c57-d56e-afff-feffe7f80000</link>
      <description>Riley Patterson has been kicking in Sanders’ stead all year, converting 24-of-26 field goals and 31-of-32 extra points. Although the conversion rates are good, he lacks the requisite kick volume for K1 treatment. We do not know which player will be active on game day, but Sanders remained limited in practice all week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c57-d56e-afff-feffe7f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers LB T.J. Watt (lung) won’t play in Pittsburgh’s Week 17 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c44-d56e-afff-feec03400000</link>
      <description>He was limited in practice all three days this week, but apparently wasn’t quite ready yet. Steelers beats believe he will talk to reporters next week. It’s possible Watt misses Week 18 if the Steelers clinch a playoff spot on Saturday or Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c44-d56e-afff-feec03400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DB Jalen Ramsey (illness) is questionable for Pittsburgh’s Week 17 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c5f-d35e-a1bf-5ddf43560000</link>
      <description>He did not practice on Thursday or Friday after apparently receiving the illness for Christmas. Generally players with a questionable status with illnesses play, though it’s possible the Steelers exercise caution if the Ravens lose on Saturday and clinch a playoff spot for Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c5f-d35e-a1bf-5ddf43560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers WR Calvin Austin (hamstring) will not play in Pittsburgh’s Week 17 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c60-d56e-afff-fee8bf9e0000</link>
      <description>Apparently it will be Marquez Valdes-Scantling and Adam Thielen that you’ll want in the Pittsburgh passing game against Cleveland as the Steelers try to make due without the suspended D.K. Metcalf. Pittsburgh also listed Isaac Seumalo (triceps) as questionable after three limited sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c60-d56e-afff-fee8bf9e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers RB Jaylen Warren (hip) is not on Pittsburgh’s final Week 17 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c63-d35e-a1bf-5de30fb70000</link>
      <description>He’ll be a useful RB2 bet against the Browns in what projects as a good game script for running the football. Warren was limited during Wednesday’s practice, but got in full sessions on Thursday and Friday and appears to be whatever the NFL version of “100 percent” is for the Steelers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c63-d35e-a1bf-5de30fb70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Noah Fant (ankle) is questionable to play in Week 17 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c62-d35e-a1bf-5de204c10000</link>
      <description>Fant’s potential absence could free up a couple of targets for the Bengals’ remaining tight ends, but none of them are truly fantasy-relevant. Fant himself has not yet produced 45 yards in a game this season. It is a lost season for the 28-year-old veteran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c62-d35e-a1bf-5de204c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders ruled out EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) for Week 17 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c67-d35e-a1bf-5de78ba00000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Crosby has been playing through his knee injury since October, and the Raiders made this decision “with Crosby’s best interest in mind.” The star pass rusher “has been fighting to play and wants to play.” The Raiders shut down TE Brock Bowers, who played through much of this season with a PCL sprain in his knee, placing him on injured reserve earlier this week. FOX’s Jay Glazer reports that this “could lead to questions on his future in Vegas.” Crosby has one year remaining on his contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c67-d35e-a1bf-5de78ba00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) is questionable for Arizona’s Week 17 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c6d-d56e-afff-feed6de20000</link>
      <description>He got in three limited sessions this week — the same as last week — and clearly is trying to play through the injury. Given his lack of production on Sunday (1/14) and the lack of production of late, it would make sense to break ties against Harrison in Championship Week lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c6d-d56e-afff-feed6de20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals EDGE Josh Sweat (ankle/knee) is questionable for Arizona’s Week 17 game against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c71-dc7a-af9b-dfff3f080000</link>
      <description>Sweat is definitely in danger of missing the game after three straight DNPs this week. He left Week 16’s game with the ankle designation. Also questionable for the Cardinals’ defense are Max Melton (heel) and Will Johnson (thumb/chest), each of whom got in three limited sessions in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c71-dc7a-af9b-dfff3f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (teeth) is not on Philadelphia’s final Week 17 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c74-d35e-a1bf-5df6a4130000</link>
      <description>Neither is Devonta Smith (illness), and both figure to remain involved borderline WR1 and borderline WR2 starters, respectively, in Week 17 fantasy championships. Brown practiced in full today and should be good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-5c74-d35e-a1bf-5df6a4130000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
