<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LT Joe Alt (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b3-db72-a199-fffbf5d30000</link>
      <description>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Alt is doing “really well” despite his DNP status. Alt suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 4 and has already missed one game. It doesn’t look like he will be back this week, though there is at least a chance he manages to return to practice at some point this week before suiting up on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5b3-db72-a199-fffbf5d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5bd-def2-abdb-ddfdd32e0000</link>
      <description>Lamb is still dealing with the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. He hasn’t practiced since going down with the injury and doesn’t look likely to suit up in Week 6 either. George Pickens will continue to operate as the team’s top wideout if Lamb remains sidelined for Week 5. Pickens came back to Earth in Week 5 with just two catches for 57 yards, but he saved the day for fantasy managers with a touchdown. He is on track for a WR2 ranking this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5bd-def2-abdb-ddfdd32e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavontae Turpin (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c3-db72-a199-ffcb27540000</link>
      <description>Both Turpin and CeeDee Lamb missed Week 5 with ankle injuries. Both wideouts also look likely to miss Dallas’s upcoming game against the Panthers. Ryan Flournoy stepped up as the team’s No. 3 receiver on Sunday and made the most of the increased role with six catches for 114 yards. He will move into the WR4 conversation if Turpin and Lamb are both ruled out before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c3-db72-a199-ffcb27540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c7-d94a-a79d-cdcf33230000</link>
      <description>Pete Carroll has insisted that Bowers is considered day to day, but all reports have him as unlikely to suit up in Week 6. Bowers is dealing with a PCL injury and a bone bruise in his knee. He suffered the pair of injuries in Week 1 and attempted to play through them for a while. The injuries eventually caught up with him and the Raiders put him on the bench for Week 5. Michael Mayer missed Week 5 with a concussion but should be available for the Raiders’ upcoming trip to Tennessee. He will be a streaming TE2 option if he is cleared for action and Bowers remains out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5c7-d94a-a79d-cdcf33230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders (knee/ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ce-def2-abdb-ddef45d00000</link>
      <description>Sanders missed Week 5 with the injury combo. In turn, rookie running back Jaydon Blue was active for the first time this year. Blue only saw four carries and ran for just seven yards. No matter who the backup is, Javonte Williams has a stranglehold on the backfield touches in Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ce-def2-abdb-ddef45d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans K Joey Slye (calf) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5dd-db72-a199-ffdf27340000</link>
      <description>Slye is listed with a right calf injury for Wednesday. It is unclear when he suffered the injury as the 29-year-old kicked the game-winner in the Titans’ win over the Cardinals in Week 5. The Titans may look to add a kicker to the practice squad should Slye not practice the rest of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5dd-db72-a199-ffdf27340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Tyjae Spears (ankle) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5e8-d94a-a79d-cded652b0000</link>
      <description>Spears just returned from injured reserve due to an ankle injury he suffered before the season. He saw limited usage in his Week 5 return, but head coach Brian Callahan said on Monday his role will expand. Take this as a precautionary limited practice as the Titans ramp up Spears’ workload, but monitor his status throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5e8-d94a-a79d-cded652b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Van Jefferson (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ea-d94a-a79d-cdef816a0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson is seldom-used in the Titans’ passing game, getting just 12 snaps in Week 5. He did not practice Wednesday with an ankle injury. If Jefferson misses time, it could lead to increased snaps for Chimere Dike and Tyler Lockett, though no Titans receiver outside of Calvin Ridley or Elic Ayomanor should be considered for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5ea-d94a-a79d-cdef816a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (ankle) did not participate Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5f6-db72-a199-ffffe08c0000</link>
      <description>Simmons did not participate in Wednesday’s practice while nursing an ankle injury. The 28-year-old is the Titans’ top defensive tackle and an important anchor for the defense. If he cannot go this week, Ashton Jeanty will have be in line for an even-better matchup against the Titans in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5f6-db72-a199-ffffe08c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOF Network’s Nick Underhill reports Saints RB Alvin Kamara is “day-to-day” with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5fb-d94a-a79d-cdffc2ef0000</link>
      <description>We have an update on the severity of Kamara’s ankle injury. Though initial reporting had his injury occurring on Wednesday, Underhill reports Kamara actually suffered the injury in the first half of the Saints’ Week 5 win against Giants and it “isn’t anything serious.” The veteran experienced soreness in practice and backed off of it. Should Kamara miss time, Kendre Miller is in the fantasy RB2 range. Regardless, Miller has been cutting into Kamara’s workload and needs to be rostered, while Kamara has fallen to the low-end RB2 range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c5fb-d94a-a79d-cdffc2ef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
