<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harold Fannin (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b0-d56e-afff-f7f8c17e0000</link>
      <description>As expected, David Njoku also remained out of practice. Njoku is likely out for Week 18, while head coach Kevin Stefanski is leaving the light on for Fannin. With the Browns only playing for a better draft pick, there isn’t much reason to push either player to suit up on Sunday. Backup tight ends Blake Whiteheart and Sal Cannella would be in line for more work if both starting options are ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b0-d56e-afff-f7f8c17e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javonte Williams (shoulder) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b9-d35e-a1bf-75fb89650000</link>
      <description>Williams went down with a shoulder injury in Week 17 against the Commanders. He left in the second quarter and was listed as questionable to return but never did so. Malik Davis would be an option for the Cowboys, but his availability for Week 18 is also in doubt because of an eye issue. Jaydon Blue would be the next man up if both backs are ruled out for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75b9-d35e-a1bf-75fb89650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell said QB J.J. McCarthy (hand) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75c9-dc7a-af9b-ffff5d3e0000</link>
      <description>On Monday, O’Connell told reporters that McCarthy, rehabbing a fracture in his throwing hand, is “progressing” and has a chance to play in Week 18. O’Connell provided an update today, saying McCarthy “had a positive day yesterday, going through [a] workout with trainers.” These are steps in the right direction for the young, developing quarterback. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75c9-dc7a-af9b-ffff5d3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said DT Ed Oliver underwent a meniscus cleanup surgery on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75c8-dc7a-af9b-ffff1f5f0000</link>
      <description>Oliver is currently on IR because of a bicep injury. He was initially expected to return early in the playoffs. After injuring his knee during rehab, his timeline has now been pushed back. McDermott didn’t rule him out of the playoffs, but the Bills would likely need to make a deep run for Oliver to see the field again this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75c8-dc7a-af9b-ffff1f5f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (toe) is practicing in full for Week 18 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75da-d56e-afff-f7fa2fc40000</link>
      <description>Dowdle was listed as a DNP on Tuesday, but the team upgraded him to a full session for today’s walkthrough. He doesn’t appear to be at any risk of missing Week 18 versus the Bucs. Dowdle out-touched Chuba Hubbard 15-7 last week, though he posted a quiet box score for fantasy purposes. Expect the Panthers to try to get him going early in a must-win spot versus the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75da-d56e-afff-f7fa2fc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dalton Kincaid (knee) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75cf-dc7a-af9b-ffff23a60000</link>
      <description>This is Kincaid’s second consecutive limited practice, dating back to last week. He was sidelined on Wednesday and Thursday and did not play on Sunday. Bills No. 2 TE Dawson Knox (knee) was also limited today, though he suited up in Week 17, catching 5-of-5 targets for 30 yards. Earlier today, Bills head coach Sean McDermott said Kincaid “is in a better spot now than he was last week.” He seemingly has a chance to play in Week 18, but the Bills are only playing for playoff seeding at this point, having locked up a Wild Card Weekend spot already. They could choose to keep him inactive against the lowly Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75cf-dc7a-af9b-ffff23a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Austin (hamstring) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75df-d968-a19b-7dff8a030000</link>
      <description>Austin missed Week 17 with the hamstring issue. DK Metcalf will be out for Week 18 to finish serving his two-game suspension, meaning Austin could immediately return to a high-volume role. The Steelers will lean on their ground game this week in battle for the AFC North with the Ravens, but fantasy managers can pencil Austin in for a handful of targets if he is active, putting him on the WR4/5 radar for the final week of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75df-d968-a19b-7dff8a030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) is practicing fully for Week 18 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75d1-d56e-afff-f7f92b1e0000</link>
      <description>The Bills released K Michael Badgley from the practice squad on Monday. He had an extra point attempt blocked by the Eagles last week. Given Badgley’s release and Prater’s full participation, we expect Prater to kick for the Bills in Week 18 against the Jets. He could be fairly busy in his first game back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75d1-d56e-afff-f7f92b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons coach Raheem Morris said DT Brandon Dorlus “dodged a big-time bullet” with his knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75ee-d35e-a1bf-75ee96870000</link>
      <description>Dorlus went down with the knee injury in Week 17 and there was concern that it was a major issue. He won’t play in Week 18, meaning his season is over, but Morris said he would only be out for a couple of weeks. It doesn’t sound like this will affect his offseason routine at all, which is good news for the former fourth-round pick. His breakout second season comes to an end with 8.5 sacks and 26 pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75ee-d35e-a1bf-75ee96870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Nation’s Vincent Bonsignore believes the Raiders will use “a combination of Kenny Pickett and Aidan O’Connell” in Week 18 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75e6-d968-a19b-7df7b90b0000</link>
      <description>Bonsignore seems to imply both players will take reps in Week 18. Pickett has been the first player off the bench, so we assume he will get the start. Should the Raiders actually employ a two-quarterback game plan, neither player should be anywhere near a re-draft or DFS lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-75e6-d968-a19b-7df7b90b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
