<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals designated DL Bilal Nichols (neck) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-969f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f32de0000</link>
      <description>Nichols’ 21-day return window is now open, as the Cardinals will work on ramping him up for game action. The veteran tackle suffered his neck injury last October, so it wouldn’t be surprising if the Cardinals used all the time they have available to them before officially removing him from IR. Nichols totaled 10 tackles and one TFL in six games for the Cardinals last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-969f-dca3-a9fb-bf9f32de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Michael Carter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96a4-dca3-a9fb-bfbd04320000</link>
      <description>Carter is now on the 53-man roster, making him a slightly more valuable fantasy stash than he was when he was bouncing between the game day roster and the practice squad. He saw just one touch in his first game of the season in Week 4, but could find his way into a role behind Trey Benson. Carter had limited success with the Cardinals last season, totaling 188 yards from scrimmage and one touchdown on 46 touches, but there’s no reason to rush to add him just yet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96a4-dca3-a9fb-bfbd04320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants owner John Mara announced he has been diagnosed with cancer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96ab-d95b-addb-feef6af90000</link>
      <description>Mara has a treatment plan and has been consulting with doctors. We wish Mr. Mara well on his road to try to beat the deadly illness. This has little in-season on-field impact for the Giants, obviously, but if Mara is busy fighting cancer he may be less inclined to make major changes to the Giants in the short-term future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96ab-d95b-addb-feef6af90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Nnamdi Madubuike will miss the remainder of the season with a neck injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96a8-d95b-addb-feee32e10000</link>
      <description>Madubuike was placed on injured reserve last week, but now the sixth-year tackle has been ruled out for the season due to a neck injury he suffered in Week 2. Madubuike’s absence for the remainder of the season strikes a serious blow to a Ravens defense that has been gouged through the first four weeks of the season. He totaled seven tackles, two sacks, and two TFLs in limited action this season, and will hopefully make a full recovery in time for training camp in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96a8-d95b-addb-feee32e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said there was “no way” Lamar Jackson (hamstring) could have returned in Week 4’s loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c6-deb6-a7fd-d7df292f0000</link>
      <description>Knowing this, it’s only fair to assume that Jackson’s Week 5 status against the Texans is somewhat questionable entering the week. Harbaugh said the decision to keep Jackson on the sideline following his injury was strictly due to the nature of the injury and had nothing to do with the fact that the Ravens were facing a multi-possession deficit at the time. Jackson’s status will be one to watch when the team’s first injury report drops on Wednesday. It goes without saying that the fantasy values of Zay Flowers, Mark Andrews, and all other pass catchers would take a hit should Cooper Rush start in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c6-deb6-a7fd-d7df292f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving will undergo an MRI on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c8-dca3-a9fb-bfd915b60000</link>
      <description>What part of Irving was injured in Sunday’s loss to the Eagles was left undisclosed, but Bowles admitted that Irving was one of the injured players he was “concerned” about. This will be a major storyline to follow this week. Rachaad White and Sean Tucker would figure to have much bigger roles if Irving was sidelined in any real way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96c8-dca3-a9fb-bfd915b60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans coach Brian Callahan said Calvin Ridley was “fighting through something” during Week 4’s loss to Houston.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cb-dca3-a9fb-bfdbce940000</link>
      <description>It helps explain his declining usage — Ridley played just 27 of 50 snaps on Sunday. Nobody needs to be holding Ridley in a shallow league at this point either way, but this at least gives you some hope that there could be fantasy volume if you have Ridley in a deep league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cb-dca3-a9fb-bfdbce940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Cesar Ruiz (ankle) is out for Week 5 and is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cd-deb6-a7fd-d7dfc9690000</link>
      <description>Torricelli Simpkins III took Ruiz’s place after he left Week 4’s game against the Bills and played 39 snaps. If Dillon Radunz is unable to get off the injury report this week, Simpkins will likely play guard for the Saints in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96cd-deb6-a7fd-d7dfc9690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints coach Kellen Moore said Foster Moreau (PUP/knee) will practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d2-d95b-addb-fed6281f0000</link>
      <description>That will open a 21-day window for Moreau’s return when it happens. It sounds like there’s a chance that both Moreau and Taysom Hill could be back in the near future for the Saints. Is it a cancelling of the Juwan Johnson coming out party? We’ll have to see. Johnson managers are probably going to have at least a few additional weeks of respite, but this seems like it will loom over his rest of season value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d2-d95b-addb-fed6281f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints designate TE Taysom Hill (knee) for return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d1-deb6-a7fd-d7dfd3a30000</link>
      <description>In his first week eligible to return from the PUP list, Hill is expected to practice with the Saints when they take the field on Wednesday. Hill last saw regular-season action in Week 13 of last season, when he suffered a season-ending knee injury against the Rams. How the veteran gadget player will be used in Kellen Moore’s offense is to be determined, but as always, there could be some fantasy value to be had if he’s still used in the role we’ve grown accustomed to seeing over the years. The Saints have 21 days to officially activate Hill from the PUP list, meaning there’s no guarantee he plays in Week 5 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-96d1-deb6-a7fd-d7dfd3a30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
