<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:02:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) practiced on a limited basis Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e52e-db57-afda-f73e2caf0000</link>
      <description>It’s a good sign that Kincaid could finally return to the Buffalo offense in Week 14 against the Bengals, a defense that has been tormented by opposing tight ends all year. No defense allows more tight end receptions, targets, yards, or touchdowns than the Bengals. If Kincaid suits up for Week 14, he’ll be a must play option in all formats. Kincaid in 2025 has been targeted on 27 percent of his routes, the highest rate in the league among tight ends. Dawson Knox would be an excellent streamer if Kincaid is sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e52e-db57-afda-f73e2caf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said EDGE Joey Bosa (hamstring) is considered “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e538-d90e-a9da-ff3f1d1c0000</link>
      <description>Bosa did not practice Wednesday and seems unlikely to play in Week 14 against the Bengals. His absence could make things a little easier for Joe Burrow and the Bengals offense, as the Bills sports the league’s tenth highest QB pressure rate (24 percent) and the 11th highest QB hurry rate (9 percent). McDermott suggested the team’s medical staff believed Bosa wouldn’t be out for long.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e538-d90e-a9da-ff3f1d1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e549-db57-afda-f77b3e340000</link>
      <description>It’s a bad sign for London’s Week 14 availability against the Seahawks. London has missed the Falcons’ past two games and the team doesn’t appear to be in a hurry to rush him back into game action with the postseason out of reach. With London sidelined over the past two weeks, Kyle Pitts has led Atlanta pass catchers with 13 targets and nine receptions. Bijan Robinson has nine targets over those two games and Darnell Mooney has eight. Mooney is a viable 14-team league flex option for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e549-db57-afda-f77b3e340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Josh Palmer (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e554-d6c4-abfb-f75729a40000</link>
      <description>The oft-injured Palmer would seem to be a long shot for Week 14 against the Bengals. Palmer missed Week 13 against the Steelers while dealing with his lingering ankle issue. He has 18 receptions for 272 yards over eight games in 2025 and would not be fantasy relevant if he suits up. Keon Coleman should continue operating as a starter in the run-heavy Buffalo offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e554-d6c4-abfb-f75729a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs placed LT Josh Simmons (wrist) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e55d-d6c4-abfb-f75f1bae0000</link>
      <description>Simmons had surgery on his injured wrist and will miss at least a month, making a postseason return possible if the Chiefs finish the season strong and sneak into the playoffs. The loss of Simmons is significant for Patrick Mahomes and the KC offense: Pro Football Focus grades Simmons 21st in pass blocking out of 85 qualifying tackles this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e55d-d6c4-abfb-f75f1bae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks designated S Julian Love (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e566-d6c4-abfb-f7678a390000</link>
      <description>DT Jarran Reed and WR Dareke Young were also designated to return. All three players will be at practice this week. They have 21 days to be officially activated off injured reserve. Getting Love and Reed back will bolster a defense that has already been one of the best in the league this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e566-d6c4-abfb-f7678a390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e579-d90e-a9da-ff7fd5d00000</link>
      <description>Higgins remains in the league’s concussion protocol. He went down with the brain injury in Week 12 and was forced to miss the team’s Thanksgiving win over the Ravens. A limited practice puts him on track to return this week, but he will need to get in a full session before clearing the league’s protocol. Assuming that happens, Higgins will return to a WR2 ranking against the Bills this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e579-d90e-a9da-ff7fd5d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e57e-d316-abff-f7ff67f80000</link>
      <description>MHJ could return later in the session and receive a limited designation on the official report, though we doubt he will get in any work today. Harrison Jr. went down with a heel injury late in the Cardinals’ Week 13 loss to the Bucs. He was spotted on the sidelines getting ready to return, but the team ultimately held him out for the remainder of the game. He now appears to be on the wrong side of questionable for Week 14. Michael Wilson totaled 25 catches for 303 yards in the two games MHJ missed a few weeks ago. He would return to the top of the WR2 ranks if Harrison Jr. is out versus the Rams this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e57e-d316-abff-f7ff67f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Benson (knee) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e583-d316-abff-f79309c50000</link>
      <description>Head coach Jonathan Gannon was noncommittal when asked about Benson’s status. The young back appeared to be nearing a return from injured reserve last week, but he was downgraded to a DNP on Thursday and was ruled out the following day after another missed practice. It’s possible he suffered a setback during practice. Needless to say, it doesn’t look like he will be back in the lineup this week. Emari Demercado was back at practice today, giving him a shot to suit up on Sunday after missing last week’s game with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e583-d316-abff-f79309c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks (foot) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e58b-d6c4-abfb-f78bf1bb0000</link>
      <description>Marks left Week 13’s game with a foot injury but did eventually return. He finished the day with 19 attempts for 64 yards. This could just be a rest day for a banged-up player. It could also be an indication that Marks was running on adrenaline on Sunday and may be more injured than he or the team thought. Tomorrow’s practice report will be more informative. Nick Chubb would take over the Houston backfield if Marks misses Week 14, though it would be hard to treat him as anything other than a low-end RB3 versus the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e58b-d6c4-abfb-f78bf1bb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
