<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer (knee/ankle) is questionable for Week 10 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f26-d673-a39e-ffb713240000</link>
      <description>Palmer has been limited in practice throughout the week but has a chance to suit up for his first game since Week 6. Palmer hasn’t offered much to the Bills when on the field, seeing just 20 targets on the season, with nine of those coming in Week 1. Any value he may have is in the real-world sense, as fantasy managers shouldn’t be looking to him in Week 10, even if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f26-d673-a39e-ffb713240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills DT DaQuan Jones (calf) is questionable for Week 10 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f30-d1e7-a1fa-5ffa06af0000</link>
      <description>Cornerbacks Taron Johnson (groin) and Christian Benford (groin) will also be questionable after being limited in back-to-back practices to close out the week. Jones was also limited on Thursday and Friday after being a DNP on Wednesday, and appears to have a chance to play after missing last week’s game. With DE A.J. Epenesa (concussion) and LB Shaq Thompson (hamstring) already ruled out for Sunday’s game, the Bills will hopefully get some good news on Jones and Johnson when inactives are announced before kickoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f30-d1e7-a1fa-5ffa06af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets HC Aaron Glenn was non-committal on whether or not Adonai Mitchell would play in Week 10 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f3b-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb4cc30000</link>
      <description>Glenn was also non-committal on John Metchie suiting up. Metchie was acquired from the Eagles back on October 29th and was called a “master” route runner from the slot by Glenn. The Jets are in desperate need of help at receiver behind Garrett Wilson, and may get that much-needed help from both Mitchell and Glenn at some point in the season. Even if they do suit up this week, fantasy managers shouldn’t count on either receiver offering much upside. The Jets remain one of the most run-heavy teams in the league and also boast one of the worst passing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f3b-d1e7-a1fa-5ffb4cc30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants HC Brian Daboll said to “assume it’s going to be Younghoe Koo” kicking in Week 10 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f49-d713-ad9e-7f5dad300000</link>
      <description>Graham Gano (neck) hasn’t practiced all week, making the odds of seeing Koo all the greater. The Giants will release their final injury report soon, but fantasy managers expecting Gano to be available should prepare to go without the veteran kicker. Koo signed with the Giants after being cut by the Falcons following a Week 1 loss to the Buccaneers and is 2-of-3 on field goal attempts this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f49-d713-ad9e-7f5dad300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts placed DT DeForest Buckner (neck) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f4e-d45b-affe-5fde3c960000</link>
      <description>It’s a tough loss for the Colts and a defense that currently ranks seventh in points allowed. The decision to place Buckner on injured reserve means he will miss at least the next four games, making Week 15 against the Seahawks the earliest he could return. Buckner has totaled 26 tackles, four sacks, and nine TFLs this season while earning a PFF defensive grade of 74.9. Neville Gallimore is listed behind him on the team’s depth chart and should be next in line for work along the Colts’ d-line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f4e-d45b-affe-5fde3c960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Godwin (fibula) has been ruled out for Week 10 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f56-d713-ad9e-7f56fe460000</link>
      <description>It was reported on Thursday that Godwin may not return until late November or early December, so this news doesn’t come as much of a surprise. Godwin continues to deal with difficulties from the fibula injury that ended his 2024 season and could still be several weeks away from a return. Sterling Shepard and Tez Johnson could continue to benefit from Godwin’s absence but remain well-behind Mike Evans and Emeka Egbuka in the target pecking order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f56-d713-ad9e-7f56fe460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) will not play in Week 10 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f5c-d673-a39e-ffdd106d0000</link>
      <description>Irving hasn’t played since Week 4. Despite there being hope he would be able to return after the team’s Week 9 bye, but after being a DNP all week, the second-year back will again be watching from the sidelines. His absence will put Rachaad White back in high-end RB2 territory for fantasy managers, as White has averaged 16.8 touches per game since Irving has been sidelined while finding the end zone three times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f5c-d673-a39e-ffdd106d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haason Reddick (ankle/knee) will not play in the Buccaneers’ Week 10 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f65-d713-ad9e-7f75369a0000</link>
      <description>Reddick missed the Bucs’ Week 8 against against the Saints with the same injury and was unable to practice this week following the team’s bye. The veteran pass-rusher will now target a Week 11 return against the Bills. Reddick has totaled just nine tackles and 1.5 sacks this season. In addition to Reddick, LB Markees Watts (hand) will also be held out of Sunday’s contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f65-d713-ad9e-7f75369a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f6b-d45b-affe-5fff29fe0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle was upgraded to a full-participant in Friday’s practice and will be good to go against the Saints. The Panthers’ RB1 continues to produce for fantasy managers, rushing for 130 yards and a touchdown on 25 carries last week while maintaining his bell cow role over Chuba Hubbard. Dowdle will be in the RB1 conversation in Week 10 against the Saints and is a must-start in all formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f6b-d45b-affe-5fff29fe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan (hamstring) was added to Friday’s injury report and is questionable for Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f6e-d713-ad9e-7f7e41e80000</link>
      <description>Panthers beat writer David Newton wrote shortly after practice that head coach Dave Canales “told reporters there is concern after the injury popped up today.” Late-week injuries are never a good sign for a player’s availability come Sunday, and the fact that Canales is suggesting there could be something to be concerned about makes this even worse. We won’t press the panic button until there’s reason to do so, but fantasy managers counting on McMillan in Week 10 should have a backup plan in place in the event he ends up being ruled out. If McMillan did miss Sunday’s game, Xavier Legette and Jalen Coker could both be in line to see increased workloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5f6e-d713-ad9e-7f7e41e80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
