<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs rushed 17 times for 83 yards in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions, adding one reception for eight yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c77d-db57-afda-d77f76b50000</link>
      <description>Jacobs was left out of the touchdown-oriented fun, as Packers WRs Romeo Doubs, Christian Watson and Dontayvion Wicks stole the show. Jacobs missed time after taking a hard hit on his left thigh from Lions DB Brian Branch, but he returned for the following drive. Jacobs looked good in this one and showed no ill effects from the recent bone bruise in his knee. He is a locked-in RB1 against a Bears defense that could be without multiple linebackers next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c77d-db57-afda-d77f76b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions head coach Dan Campbell told reporters that WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) “could be” sidelined for “a week or two, if we’re lucky.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c784-db57-afda-d7b630eb0000</link>
      <description>That is bad news. Campbell adds that the Lions should know more tomorrow, but St. Brown’s injured right ankle is expected to sideline him for some time. The Lions face the Cowboys, Rams, Steelers and Vikings in Weeks 14-17. Hopefully, he can at least return in time for the latter two contests. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c784-db57-afda-d7b630eb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson rushed four times for 14 yards in the Packers’ Week 13 win over the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c785-d90e-a9da-df8fb7410000</link>
      <description>Wilson was seemingly set for a FLEX-worthy role, rotating in on the Packers’ first drive. The workload never materialized, though, despite starting RB Josh Jacobs missing a few plays after taking a hard hit on his left thigh. Wilson is now just a high-upside bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c785-d90e-a9da-df8fb7410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Goff completed 20-of-26 passes for 256 yards and two touchdowns in the Lions’ 31-24, Week 13 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c791-d90e-a9da-df9f654f0000</link>
      <description>Goff lost WR Amon-Ra St. Brown to an ankle injury on the Lions’ second drive. TE Sam LaPorta is also on injured reserve with a back injury. The veteran quarterback handled the situation well, funneling passes to WR Jameson Williams on in-breaking routes over the middle, but the thinned-out pass-catching corps, coupled with the Packers’ pass rush, made it tough sledding. To his credit, journeyman WR Tom Kennedy operated as a serviceable emergency option. Goff is a QB1 in what should be a high-scoring game environment against the Cowboys next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c791-d90e-a9da-df9f654f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jameson Williams caught 7-of-10 targets for 144 yards and one touchdown in the Lions’ Week 13 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c792-db57-afda-d7b280110000</link>
      <description>Williams was nearly unstoppable on in-breaking routes, racking up catches over the middle. Ironically, his 22-yard touchdown occurred on a screen pass, in which he absorbed a hit from a diving Packers defender post-catch, before slithering through a jumbled mess of Lions and Packers on the left side of the field. He emerged from the fray near the 10-yard line, high-stepping the rest of the journey into the end zone. Williams could warrant fantasy WR1 treatment against the Cowboys next week. Slot WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) is expected to miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c792-db57-afda-d7b280110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaac TeSlaa caught 2-of-2 targets for 35 yards and one touchdown in the Lions’ Week 13 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c793-d6c4-abfb-d793e4350000</link>
      <description>TeSlaa scored his touchdown on the Lions’ sixth drive, getting open on an in-breaking route inside the end zone. The play went for 17 yards, marking his third career score. He is a boom-bust FLEX option with Kalif Raymond (ankle) sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c793-d6c4-abfb-d793e4350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jahmyr Gibbs rushed 20 times for 68 yards in the Lions’ Week 13 loss to the Packers, adding three receptions for 18 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c795-d90e-a9da-df9f30a90000</link>
      <description>The Packers’ defense played very well in this one, though the Lions also featured RB David Montgomery in the wildcat in goal-to-go situations this afternoon. Although Gibbs was held out of the end zone, he still notched a typically impressive play by lining up as a wide receiver at the Packers’ 10-yard line against CB Keisean Nixon and beating him for a six-yard reception. Gibbs is an elite RB1 against the Cowboys next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c795-d90e-a9da-df9f30a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed eight times for 32 yards and one touchdown in the Lions’ Week 13 loss to the Packers, adding two receptions for 16 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c796-db57-afda-d7b6e33c0000</link>
      <description>The Lions deployed Montgomery in the wildcat near the goal line in this one. The first sequence resulted in a successful run to the right for a three-yard touchdown. The Lions tried it again later, this time asking Montgomery to throw a pass to TE Ross Dwelley, but the two were unable to connect. Regardless, Montgomery was able to return FLEX-worthy numbers on Thanksgiving. Be thankful. He is a decent FLEX option in what should be a high-scoring game against the Cowboys next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c796-db57-afda-d7b6e33c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared WR Tylan Wallace, QB Cooper Rush, G Ben Cleveland, T Carson Vinson, and OLB David Ojabo inactive for Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c770-d6c4-abfb-d7739df90000</link>
      <description>There are no real surprises here as the Ravens enter Week 13 as one of the healthier teams in the league. They hunt for their sixth consecutive victory against their division rivals on Thanksgiving as they continue their bid for a late-season push towards the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c770-d6c4-abfb-d7739df90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Tee Higgins is inactive for Week 13 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7bb-db57-afda-d7bbad450000</link>
      <description>This is purely a formality after Higgins was ruled out on Monday, although the team does get both quarterback Joe Burrow and wide receiver Ja’Marr Chase back. also inactive for the Bengals are QB Jake Browning, RB Tahj Brooks, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DE Trey Hendrickson, and DE Cam Sample.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7bb-db57-afda-d7bbad450000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
