<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (knee) is “truly day-to-day” and that he “can’t tell” what that means for Sunday now.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4edf-da67-a99f-ceff62940000</link>
      <description>It’s coach-speak — Quinn added that “in the return to play, he and all of the guys have to hit all of the markers” — but it sure seems like Daniels has a real chance to miss Week 3. This will be one of the most significant injury situations to monitor ahead of Week 3. Marcus Mariota is set to play against the Raiders if Daniels is unable to go. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport said earlier today that Daniels status for Week 3 is “in doubt.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4edf-da67-a99f-ceff62940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (nose) is “good to go” Thursday against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-dc44-a9d9-4fe67c9f0000</link>
      <description>Not a surprise after he returned to play in-game, but good to hear an affirmative answer on it. McDermott said “his nose looks good to me. It’s always looked good to me.” Allen will be a locked-in QB1 against a Dolphins defense that is redefining what it means to be Down Bad through two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-dc44-a9d9-4fe67c9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Noah Brown (groin) is “a long shot” to play in Week 3 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-d86f-abdd-4fffd5ea0000</link>
      <description>Quinn said the same of tight end John Bates, who is also dealing with a groin injury. Brown has three catches for 38 yards on seven targets this season and was already well off the fantasy radar. Assuming he’s unable to play in Week 3, the Commanders would likely feature veteran Chris Moore in his spot, who is listed behind him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee6-d86f-abdd-4fffd5ea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Chris Rodriguez will “be back in the fold” in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee8-d86f-abdd-4ffd5e550000</link>
      <description>We assume this means Rodriguez will be active behind Jacory Croskey-Merritt in the RB room, with Jeremy McNichols stealing some third-down snaps. Quinn also mentioned that they feel comfortable with Croskey-Merritt in pass protection. There’s a lot of runouts on the table for the Commanders in Week 3 at running back, especially when you consider Jayden Daniels’ health at the moment. Given where he’s starting from it seems unlikely that Rodriguez will be more than a small part of a committee in Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4ee8-d86f-abdd-4ffd5e550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Daiyan Henley (illness) is questionable for Week 2’s game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eff-d294-a19b-eeff2c520000</link>
      <description>The Chargers announced on Monday that Henley will be added to the injury report due to an illness. The third-year linebacker totaled eight tackles and a sack in the team’s Week 1 win over the Chiefs, and would join fellow linebacker Denzel Perryman on the sideline if he is unable to play. It’s not often we see players miss games due to illnesses, so we would still expect to see Henley suit up despite this late development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4eff-d294-a19b-eeff2c520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said Ed Oliver (ankle) won’t practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f04-da67-a99f-cff5af120000</link>
      <description>Oliver missed Week 2’s game against the Jets due to his ankle injury and is at risk of missing a second-straight game with the Bills facing the Dolphins on a short week this Thursday night. It was reported last week that Oliver’s injury was expected to be a multi-week injury, meaning expectations of him suiting up on Thursday should be low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f04-da67-a99f-cff5af120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills coach Sean McDermott said Matt Milano (pectoral) won’t practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4efb-dc44-a9d9-4fff17ed0000</link>
      <description>Milano played only 23 snaps against the Jets before leaving and being spotted with a wrap on his right arm on the sideline. Joe Andreessen played 10 snaps behind Milano and would seem to be the logical replacement. Milano is no longer the star he was in his prime and took a paycut this offseason, so this is not a huge short-term loss for the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4efb-dc44-a9d9-4fff17ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Packers worked out free agent QB Dorian Thompson-Robinson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f3a-da67-a99f-cfffefd90000</link>
      <description>Our best guess here is that the Packers are meeting with DTR due to the minor thumb injury Jordan Love is dealing with. Love was spotted at Monday’s practice with his left thumb taped, but there’s been little mention about the injury, leaving us to believe it’s a near non-issue. Thompson-Robinson has appeared in 15 games in his NFL career while making five starts, and has a career passing line of 880-1-10. He has also rushed 35 times for 187 scoreless yards. Thompson-Robinson is unlikely to be anything more than a practice squad QB for the Packers if he were to sign with the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f3a-da67-a99f-cfffefd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared TE Devin Culp, WR Chris Godwin, WR Tez Johnson, RB Josh Williams, T Tristan Wirfs, and S Rashad Wisdom inactive for Week 2 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4a-d294-a19b-effa48580000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here after both Godwin and Wirfs were ruled out earlier in the week. The Buccaneers enter Week 2 in a similar situation to their first game of the season, a game that saw rookie Emeka Egbuka and veterans Mike Evans and Sterling Shepard dominate targets from quarterback Baker Mayfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4a-d294-a19b-effa48580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Dameon Pierce is inactive for Week 2 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4c-da67-a99f-cffda1640000</link>
      <description>The Texans carried four running backs and a fullback on their active roster in Week 1, with Pierce now the lone man out in the equation for Week 2. Expect Dare Ogunbowale to serve as the third-down back while Woody Marks mixes in for change of pace duties behind lead rusher Nick Chubb. Also inactive for the Texans are WR Christian Kirk, WR Braxton Berrios, QB Graham Mertz, C Jake Andrews, and DT Tommy Togiai.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4f4c-da67-a99f-cffda1640000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
