<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert believes if Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) can’t stay healthy, QB Max Brosmer “will merit the next look” as the team’s starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-261c-dab4-a3fb-bf7c82700000</link>
      <description>McCarthy, almost two months after sustaining an ankle injury, is reportedly set to start in Week 9 against the Lions. This comes after the team essentially sacrificed Carson Wentz to the Chargers in Week 8 as the veteran dealt with a severe arm injury and appeared to be in agony from start to finish. “A person with knowledge of the Vikings’ thinking half-joked that O’Connell left Wentz in last Thursday’s game because Brosmer — who had a strong training camp and preseason — might prove a better short-term option than McCarthy.” If McCarthy’s struggles continue in the coming weeks, the Vikings could see what they have in Brosmer, a rookie who last year at the University of Minnesota threw for 2,828 yards, 18 touchdowns, and six interceptions. Brosmer should be rostered in deeper superflex formats in case McCarthy once again flames out as the Vikings’ starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-261c-dab4-a3fb-bf7c82700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB Tyler Shough will start in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2b77-deb1-a39b-2b7f4d4e0000</link>
      <description>Saints head coach Kellen Moore made the QB switch official on Tuesday, two days after he benched Spencer Rattler in favor of Shough, who was selected in the second round of the 2025 NFL Draft. Shough last week against the Bucs completed 17 of his 30 attempts 128 yards and one interception. He was the most inaccurate quarterback of Week 8 and had a far lower QB rating than Rattler. Shough starting for the Saints makes the Rams defense an elite fantasy play in Week 9. Chris Olave and the rest of the team’s pass catchers get a significant downgrade with Rattler’s benching. Rattler will likely be back under center in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2b77-deb1-a39b-2b7f4d4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed punt returner Marcus Jones to a three-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bae-d245-adfb-bfff2d7b0000</link>
      <description>Though the terms of the new deal were not immediately announced, the Patriots seemed eager to reward Jones, a corner back and excellent return man. His 216 yards on ten punt returns in 2025 ranks third in the NFL, and his 21.6 yard return average is the best mark in the league through Week 8. Last season Jones had the fifth highest yards per punt return. He’ll stay in New England for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bae-d245-adfb-bfff2d7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed EDGE Trevis Gipson off the 49ers’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</link>
      <description>Gipson had actually been one of San Francisco’s main outside players last week while they dealt with injuries, but figures to play a backup role in Carolina. It’s another blow for a 49ers defensive line group that struggled to rush the passer against the Texans last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Isiah Pacheco (knee) is “week-to-week” with an MCL sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</link>
      <description>Kareem Hunt and Brashad Smith could find themselves in bigger roles in Week 9 against the Bills, but with the Chiefs holding a Week 10 bye, this feels like something that may only cost Pacheco a week of action. We’d be extremely surprised if Pacheco made a real attempt to play on a short week after suffering the injury with the bye as extra incentive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed RB Michael Carter to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2be7-d245-adfb-bfff9bce0000</link>
      <description>He’s bumped D’Ernest Johnson (released from squad) from the Cardinals Backs Who Will Annoy You wiki listing. Carter was released yesterday, but it appears that was just roster manipulation. He probably isn’t set for a major role even if elevated, but check back on Monday evening when it leaks that the plan is actually to use Michael Wilson as the starting running back instead of Carter or Bam Knight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2be7-d245-adfb-bfff9bce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter believes “at least one” of the Saints wide receivers will be dealt, and added that “if I had to bet, I’d say Rashid Shaheed is the guy who interests most teams.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c01-deb1-a39b-2d0f4b0c0000</link>
      <description>Schefter listed the Bills, Steelers, and Broncos as main suitors looking for a wideout, and added that the Saints would be open to this if “the compensation was fair and right.” We’d bet the remaining 10 weeks of Shaheed’s contract could fetch at least a swap up to a fourth-rounder, maybe more. Schefter noted that he thinks there will be a flurry of moves at the actual deadline, after Week 9’s games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c01-deb1-a39b-2d0f4b0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Werder reports the Cowboys and George Pickens have not engaged in contract extension talks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</link>
      <description>Well, yeah, that’s how the Cowboys do things. We have read a few columns out of Dallas arguing for a Pickens trade, but there seems to be no legitimate smoke on that. We’re anticipating a Pickens franchise tag or tag-and-trade in the offseason. Certainly nothing about the fit has been bad thus far with Pickens on pace for a little under 1,300 yards and 13 touchdowns through eight games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c09-d5d8-a3ff-fd6907850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) said “I’m ready to go now” when asked about playing in Week 9.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</link>
      <description>Things were trending the right way before this, but Jackson actually meeting the media all but confirms he’ll be back for Thursday night’s game against the Dolphins. He raises all boats on the Baltimore offense and is an easy QB1, even against a Dolphins defense coming off a surprising Week 8 win over the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c23-deb1-a39b-2d2fac080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (hamstring) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</link>
      <description>It looks like Marcus Mariota’s latest stint as a stopgap superflex quarterback is done. The reporting on Daniels returning for Week 9 has been encouraging so far. We expect to do plenty of Daniels blurbs leading up to Seahawks-Commanders on Sunday night, and it wouldn’t be surprising if Daniels is limited in practice at times this week. But the Commanders need this game badly to avoid falling in a 3-6 hole and it would be surprising if it weren’t all hands on deck to take it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2c43-dab4-a3fb-bf73f1060000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
