<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brashard Smith rushed three times for eight yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2916-dab4-a3fb-bb76a15e0000</link>
      <description>Smith was not targeted, leaving his fantasy value in the dumps as Kareem Hunt scored twice and Isiah Pacheco continued in the lead back role. Pacheco appeared to tweak his knee in the fourth quarter, something Smith’s fantasy managers will want to track ahead of a Week 9 meeting with the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2916-dab4-a3fb-bb76a15e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 6-of-8 targets for 99 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2918-deb1-a39b-291e4ecc0000</link>
      <description>Although Kelce returned a vintage performance in the box scores, he had yet another drop that turned into a Patrick Mahomes interception that hit him in the hands - the second such occurrence of the season. Kelce did most of his damage in the YAC department in this one, breaking free for gains of 38 and 31 yards against the beleaguered Washington defense. The offense remains centered on Rashee Rice, but Kelce brings an established red zone role to an offense that has now scored 28 points or more in five straight. That sets the veteran up well to return TE1 numbers against in Week 9 when the Chiefs face off against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2918-deb1-a39b-291e4ecc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught all nine targets for 93 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders, adding 12 yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bb7690000</link>
      <description>Rice now has consecutive games of leading the team in targets and has notched three scores in two games since returning from suspension. His fantasy day could have been even bigger had he not been tackled twice inside the two, the first on a run from wildcat inside the 10 and the second on a reception in the flat. Both of those plays resulted in short touchdowns by Kareem Hunt. Rice’s role appears to be one of the most valuable in the league considering the hefty volume and elite red zone role, all while playing for an offense that has now scored 28 points or more in five straight. He is likely to remain busy when the Chiefs take on the Bills in Week 9, keeping him firmly entrenched as a fantasy WR1 moving forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291b-dab4-a3fb-bb7bb7690000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 5-of-7 targets for 53 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291e-d245-adfb-bd5fb6360000</link>
      <description>Worthy saw his role in the offense morph yet again following the return of Rashee Rice from suspension, this time working more short and intermediate areas of the field. He could struggle to return to the elite production he showed towards the end of his rookie season considering the elite involvement from both Rice and tight end Travis Kelce, particularly in the red zone. Consider Worthy a middling WR4 ahead of a showdown with the Bills in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-291e-d245-adfb-bd5fb6360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown failed to catch his only target in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2921-deb1-a39b-292f83c10000</link>
      <description>Brown was targeted only once and took a backseat in the offense in the second game with Rashee Rice, playing well behind Rice and Xavier Worthy while splitting time with JuJu Smith-Schuster. His days of fantasy utility appear to be in the rearview mirror unless the injury bug strikes again ahead of him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2921-deb1-a39b-292f83c10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert believes if Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (ankle) can’t stay healthy, QB Max Brosmer “will merit the next look” as the team’s starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-261c-dab4-a3fb-bf7c82700000</link>
      <description>McCarthy, almost two months after sustaining an ankle injury, is reportedly set to start in Week 9 against the Lions. This comes after the team essentially sacrificed Carson Wentz to the Chargers in Week 8 as the veteran dealt with a severe arm injury and appeared to be in agony from start to finish. “A person with knowledge of the Vikings’ thinking half-joked that O’Connell left Wentz in last Thursday’s game because Brosmer — who had a strong training camp and preseason — might prove a better short-term option than McCarthy.” If McCarthy’s struggles continue in the coming weeks, the Vikings could see what they have in Brosmer, a rookie who last year at the University of Minnesota threw for 2,828 yards, 18 touchdowns, and six interceptions. Brosmer should be rostered in deeper superflex formats in case McCarthy once again flames out as the Vikings’ starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-261c-dab4-a3fb-bf7c82700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints QB Tyler Shough will start in Week 9 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2b77-deb1-a39b-2b7f4d4e0000</link>
      <description>Saints head coach Kellen Moore made the QB switch official on Tuesday, two days after he benched Spencer Rattler in favor of Shough, who was selected in the second round of the 2025 NFL Draft. Shough last week against the Bucs completed 17 of his 30 attempts 128 yards and one interception. He was the most inaccurate quarterback of Week 8 and had a far lower QB rating than Rattler. Shough starting for the Saints makes the Rams defense an elite fantasy play in Week 9. Chris Olave and the rest of the team’s pass catchers get a significant downgrade with Rattler’s benching. Rattler will likely be back under center in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2b77-deb1-a39b-2b7f4d4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed punt returner Marcus Jones to a three-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bae-d245-adfb-bfff2d7b0000</link>
      <description>Though the terms of the new deal were not immediately announced, the Patriots seemed eager to reward Jones, a corner back and excellent return man. His 216 yards on ten punt returns in 2025 ranks third in the NFL, and his 21.6 yard return average is the best mark in the league through Week 8. Last season Jones had the fifth highest yards per punt return. He’ll stay in New England for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bae-d245-adfb-bfff2d7b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed EDGE Trevis Gipson off the 49ers’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</link>
      <description>Gipson had actually been one of San Francisco’s main outside players last week while they dealt with injuries, but figures to play a backup role in Carolina. It’s another blow for a 49ers defensive line group that struggled to rush the passer against the Texans last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bcd-d5d8-a3ff-fbed97c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Isiah Pacheco (knee) is “week-to-week” with an MCL sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</link>
      <description>Kareem Hunt and Brashad Smith could find themselves in bigger roles in Week 9 against the Bills, but with the Chiefs holding a Week 10 bye, this feels like something that may only cost Pacheco a week of action. We’d be extremely surprised if Pacheco made a real attempt to play on a short week after suffering the injury with the bye as extra incentive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2bde-d245-adfb-bfdf35f00000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
