<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Bowers caught his only target for 28 yards in the Raiders’ preseason Week 2 game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4af-d45c-a7fc-b6bffae10000</link>
      <description>Bowers displayed his elite athleticism while hauling in a 28-yard bomb down the right sideline over a defender in tight coverage against the 49ers Saturday, reinforcing his status as fantasy’s top tight end off the board for the 2025 season. He played on two drives with the starters, the second of which ended in an Ashton Jeanty touchdown plunge from one yard out. The Raiders offense looked much better than it did a week ago, calming some of the offseason nerves for fantasy managers in the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4af-d45c-a7fc-b6bffae10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geno Smith completed 6-of-8 passes for 55 yards in the Raiders’ preseason game against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4ae-d90d-a5bd-b6ff410f0000</link>
      <description>Smith started things off with a deep throw to the outside to Brock Bowers, who “mossed” his defender in single coverage to haul in a 28-yard reception. Smith has now completed 7-of-11 preseason passes for 70 scoreless yards and has looked in command of the offense in limited action. He’ll profile as a QB2 for most weeks for fantasy, but could have some upside as a matchup-based streamer in the right situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4ae-d90d-a5bd-b6ff410f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said he’s not concerned about De’Von Achane’s (soft tissue lower-body injury) Week 1 availability against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b8-d05a-adda-beba0ca10000</link>
      <description>It’s a nondescript soft tissue lower-body injury for the Dolphins’ RB1. McDaniel said Achane could be out between “days and weeks,” to further add to the mystery, making his status one to watch until he officially returns to action. Second-year back Jaylen Wright would be the immediate favorite to replace Achane on most downs, but rookie sixth-rounder Ollie Gordon could also see some work in short-yardage and goal-line situations. The Dolphins kick off the 2025 season in 22 days, which will hopefully prove to be enough time for Achane to get right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b8-d05a-adda-beba0ca10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said ZDT Zach Sieler (unspecified) will be out “between days and weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4d0-d90d-a5bd-b6dbabf90000</link>
      <description>McDaniel said that Sieler likely would have suited up for Saturday’s preseason game against the Lions if it were a regular season game. The veteran lineman who signed a three-year extension this offseason now has 22 days to get right before the Dolphins visit the Colts in Week 1. While the timeline for Sieler’s return is murky, McDaniel said he is not concerned about his Week 1 availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4d0-d90d-a5bd-b6dbabf90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts HC Shane Steichen said he’s “very close” to a decision on the starting quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b3-d05a-adda-beb326610000</link>
      <description>Speaking to media following the team’s preseason loss to the Packers, Colts head coach Shane Steichen said he would like to make a decision on the starting quarterback soon, adding that he was “very close.” We should see a decision made in the coming days to give the winner enough camp and in-game reps during the two weeks before the regular season starts. Both Anthony Richardson and Daniel Jones have traded sinusoidal reports, with both seemingly shifting between standing out and struggling in camp to this point. Steichen has continually mentioned consistency when speaking to the quarterback competition, and while Jones appears to give his team more consistent play, Richardson continues to demonstrate tantalizing upside if he can get his decision making process tighter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4b3-d05a-adda-beb326610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Gardner (calf) won’t play Saturday in the Jets’ preseason game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4fd-d45c-a7fc-b6ffc5160000</link>
      <description>Per Jets beat writer Rich Cimini, Gardner’s injury is “not believed to be serious,” but the Jets won’t risk anything with their star corner. We’ll see if head coach Aaron Glenn offers a different take after the game, but for now, it sounds like this is a non-issue as far as his Week 1 availability is concerned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4fd-d45c-a7fc-b6ffc5160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Sarah Barshop reports “a Rams spokesperson declined comment” on whether or not Matthew Stafford (back) worked out as scheduled on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b518-d45c-a7fc-b71af0b00000</link>
      <description>Similar to what he did last weekend, Stafford was scheduled to work out before Saturday’s preseason game to test the back injury that has sidelined him throughout training camp. The same spokesperson also said head coach Sean McVay would address the situation on Monday, leaving us to wonder what the next report in this saga could entail. Stafford was unable to practice last week despite plans for him to return to the field on Monday, and now the team is being cagey about his Saturday workout after publicizing it the previous week. It’s worth reminding folks that the Rams decided earlier this week that backup Jimmy Garoppolo would not play in the second preseason game, which may or may not prove meaningful in the coming days. This remains a situation to monitor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b518-d45c-a7fc-b71af0b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (neck) was carted off the field in the first quarter Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4f9-d90d-a5bd-b6fb990a0000</link>
      <description>Johnston drew the start alongside Ladd McConkey but was injured on the team’s second play from scrimmage early in the first quarter. He remained down on the field for a solid 10 minutes before eventually standing under his own power and walking to the cart. His day is likely done but he appears to have avoided a significant injury after initial medical response seemed to indicate an issue requiring spinal stabilization. The third-year player is likely headed for a situational role in 2025 after the team brought back veteran wide receiver Keenan Allen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b4f9-d90d-a5bd-b6fb990a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said OL Dominick Puni (knee) will likely miss “a few” weeks with a PCL injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b52f-d45c-a7fc-b73fb4030000</link>
      <description>Puni was almost immediately ruled out following a field goal attempt Saturday but was later seen on the sidelines in street clothes, a welcomed development for fans and fantasy managers invested in the offensive skill position players alike. Puni enters 2025 as a key piece on the interior offensive line for a 49ers team eyeing a bounce-back after a disappointing 2024 season. That does place Puni’s availability for Week 1 in question but it appears as if he avoided a major knee injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b52f-d45c-a7fc-b73fb4030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields completed 1-of-5 passes for four yards in the Jets’ preseason game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b52f-d05a-adda-bfaf3a120000</link>
      <description>Fields’ lone completion came on a four-yarder to rookie Mason Taylor. The Jets’ QB1 would then miss his next four pass attempts while appearing on three drives for the Jets. It’s hard to get much of a gauge on where Fields is at this point in the season. Per PFF, he’s completed 4-of-8 passes in limited action and is boasting a 3.4 ADOT. Regardless, it’s safe to say Saturday’s brief outing was forgettable, despite him leading a scoring drive to start the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b52f-d05a-adda-bfaf3a120000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
