<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:25:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed six times for 16 yards and one touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d1e7-a1fa-7beffab80000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez out-snapped Jacory Croskey-Merritt 17-4 in the first half before hurting his shoulder after logging one snap in the third quarter. He was initially labeled as questionable to return, but never retook the field. While Croskey-Merritt has continued to disappoint, Rodriguez hardly played better, averaging 2.7 yards per carry. His touchdown was an easy one-yard scamper off the left tackle on the Commanders’ fourth drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d1e7-a1fa-7beffab80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison, Jr. caught 3-of-12 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b85-d673-a39e-ef95218f0000</link>
      <description>Harrison nearly came down with another touchdown on an inefficient outing against Seattle’s stingy secondary. Twenty-five of Jacoby Brissett’s 44 pass attempts went to Harrison and Trey McBride, a good formula for weekly fantasy upside. Harrison has 22 targets over his past two games; he had a career day last time the Cards played in Week 8 against Dallas. Brissett’s play — and the increased pass volume of the Arizona offense with Kyler Murray benched — makes MHJ a weekly top-12 fantasy option. That should continue in Week 11 against a weak Niners defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b85-d673-a39e-ef95218f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado had four rushes for 64 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding three catches for 40 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8a-d673-a39e-ef9be93c0000</link>
      <description>When Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said the team’s backfield usage in Week 10 would be “similar but not the same,” he meant it. Demercado, a week after functioning as the main rushing back, took on the pass-catching role against the Seahawks. He ran 22 routes on the day to 19 routes for Bam Knight, who had one grab for five yards. Demercado remains the most explosive backfield option for the Cardinals, though Trey Benson’s return to the lineup — which could come as soon as Week 11 against the 49ers — would make Demercado little more than a bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8a-d673-a39e-ef9be93c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacoby Brissett completed 22-of-42 attempts for 258 yards and two touchdowns in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding four rushes for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8f-d673-a39e-ef9f4f150000</link>
      <description>Brissett lost not one but two fumbles for Seattle touchdowns early in the game as the Seahawks built a 35-0 lead in the middle of the second quarter. The game functionally over, Brissett and the Cardinals shifted into pass-heavy comeback mode, leading to 56 Brissett drop backs. He targeted Marvin Harrison Jr. (12 targets) and Trey McBride (13 targets) relentlessly, especially in the red zone. Brissett nearly had a third and a fourth touchdown in furious second half drives after a series of Seattle miscues. Brissett continues to make McBride a league-winning tight end play and puts MHJ in the weekly top-12 wideout conversation. He’ll be a reasonable streamer in Week 11 against an injury-marred Niners defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8f-d673-a39e-ef9f4f150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught both of his targets for 74 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</link>
      <description>Kupp, returning from a hamstring injury that kept him sidelined in Week 9, had an electric 67-yard catch and run in the second quarter before the Seahawks shut down the passing offense up 35-0 on the hapless Cards. Kupp ran a route on 10 of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs on the day. He should hold some PPR value coming down the stretch of the regular season. Kupp will be a top-36 play in Week 11 against a vulnerable Niners secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Knight had 10 rushes for 28 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding one catch for five yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b99-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbe0a90000</link>
      <description>Knight couldn’t get anything going with his team-leading ten rushes while Emari Demercado was efficient with his touches, racking up 104 yards on just seven touches (four carries). Knight will be an entirely touchdown-dependent RB3/4 option in Week 11 against the 49ers. Demercado would seem to be the superior weekly fantasy play in the Arizona backfield until Trey Benson returns from IR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b99-d1e7-a1fa-7bfbe0a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) was seen in a walking boot after the Ravens’ Week 10 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b9d-d45b-affe-7f9f29ff0000</link>
      <description>Bateman reportedly suffered a high-ankle sprain in Sunday’s victory after being taken down by an illegal hip-drop tackle that was not flagged. Bateman appeared fine after the play and walked off under his own power, but reports of his injury began surfacing following the game. If he’s unable to play in Week 11 against the Browns, DeAndre Hopkins or Devontez Walker would potentially be in line for more work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b9d-d45b-affe-7f9f29ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AJ Barner caught both of his targets for three yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bbd-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb0310000</link>
      <description>Barner ran a route on five of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs. The Seahawks shut down their passing attack after the team seized a 35-0 lead in the second quarter. Barner, who has seen some involvement near the goal line as the Hawks’ tush push quarterback, has had more than three receptions in a game just once in 2025. He’ll be a thin streaming option in Week 11 against the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bbd-d1e7-a1fa-7bffb0310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker had 14 rushes for 67 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals, adding one catch for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc2-d713-ad9e-6fd650890000</link>
      <description>Walker once again split the backfield with Zach Charbonnet in one of the least appealing backfields in all of fantasy football. Charbonnet also had 14 rushing attempts (for 83 yards) and scored on a short touchdown. Charbonnet’s inside-the-ten domination has left Walker with little to no weekly touchdown upside. Sunday marked Walker’s fourth highest carry total of the season, thanks mostly to the Seahawks entering clock-killing mode early in the second half. Walker, who ran eight routes on 13 Seattle drop backs in Week 10, profiles as a top-30 running back play for Week 11 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6bc2-d713-ad9e-6fd650890000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
