<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Mike Reiss believes Kyle Williams will open the season as the Patriots’ WR5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d232-de13-afdc-d6fbedf50000</link>
      <description>It goes without saying that the rookie third-rounder can work his way up the depth chart as the season goes on, but any dynasty leaguers hoping for an early payoff will likely have to wait. Reiss projects Stefon Diggs, Kayshon Boutte, and DeMario Douglas to open the season as the Patriots’ top three receiver, leaving Williams on the outside looking in. Williams shouldn’t be on redraft radars at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d232-de13-afdc-d6fbedf50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Daniel Oyefusi believes Browns RB Dylan Sampson “will push Jerome Ford for carries in the backfield early on.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d236-dbe3-a9bb-f277387c0000</link>
      <description>The Browns selected Sampson in the fourth round of this year’s draft, with the expectation being that he would see a split with Ford and fellow rookie Quinshon Judkins this season. Judkins did not participate in training camp and has yet to sign his rookie deal as a result of a domestic arrest from earlier this offseason. Even if he does eventually join the team, it will take a few weeks for him to get up to speed and he’s also at risk of serving a suspension. The possibility of Sampson pushing Ford for touches makes him a strong late-round value in fantasy drafts, as he could eventually emerge as the top back for the Browns if things break right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d236-dbe3-a9bb-f277387c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes Jets TE Mason Taylor “will have a major role on offense” this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d240-de13-afdc-d6cb07960000</link>
      <description>Taylor was dealing with an ankle injury earlier in camp, but returned to practice on August 12th. The rookie second-rounder was already emerging as a receiving threat early in camp, per Cimini, but now he believes Taylor will be a key player in the offense. According to Cimini, coaches believe Taylor’s blocking is “better than advertised” and that he can serve as a true two-way tight end this season. It’s not often that rookie tight ends make a meaningful fantasy impact, so we wouldn’t pound the table for Taylor this season. With that said, the Jets have a thin receiving corps behind Garrett Wilson, which could create more opportunities for Taylor than expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d240-de13-afdc-d6cb07960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Courtney Cronin believes Kyle Monangai “projects to have a sizable role behind D’Andre Swift.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d248-de13-afdc-d6cb1dc50000</link>
      <description>We have to take these reports with a grain of salt, but Monangai did handle all of the snaps on the Bears’ first two preseason drives against the Dolphins in the first week of the preseason. The rookie seventh-rounder has been praised for his physicality, and it sounds like he could quickly surpass incumbent backup Roschon Johnson on the depth chart — if he hasn’t already. Johnson averaged an underwhelming 2.7 YPC on 55 rush attempts last season and has done little to impress during his first two years in the league. Monangai is worth remembering for those who are looking for late-round running backs to stash in drafts over the next few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d248-de13-afdc-d6cb1dc50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder believes DJ Giddens “is destined to be the Colts’ No. 2 running back.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d257-db7b-a5dd-f257092c0000</link>
      <description>A camp injury to Tyler Goodson (elbow) may be playing a bit of a role in this take, but Holder adds that “Giddens’ skills in the passing game complement Taylor nicely,” and Goodson has just 17 career receptions to his name in 22 games. It’s hard to imagine Giddens seeing enough work behind Taylor to have fantasy relevance as long as Taylor is active, but he could be the back fantasy managers want to stash later in drafts if they’re looking for handcuffs to round out their roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d257-db7b-a5dd-f257092c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers HC Dave Canales said EDGE Nic Scourton (lung) is “doing great” and could practice next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d274-db7b-a5dd-f274bcfa0000</link>
      <description>Scourton suffered a collapsed lung just over a week ago and has been sidelined ever since. The rookie pass-rusher appears to be trending toward a return and could even be on track to play in Week 1 against the Jaguars if he’s able to log enough practices leading up to game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d274-db7b-a5dd-f274bcfa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person believes Hunter Renfrow may not be a lock to make the Panthers’ 53-man roster.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d289-dbe3-a9bb-f2dbfcf20000</link>
      <description>It’s worth pointing out that in his latest roster projections, Person has Renfrow making the roster. The former Pro Bowler battled through a hamstring injury during part of camp, but has reportedly impressed in camp. Person believes “others in the organization are higher on Renfrow” than head coach Dave Canales, which could be why the 29-year-old slot receiver remains firmly on the roster bubble even with a strong camp. Renfrow’s chances of making the roster improve if the Panthers were to trade Adam Thielen to the Vikings, a move that has reportedly been discussed between the two teams. Even if he makes the roster, it’s hard to imagine Renfrow having much, if any, fantasy impact in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d289-dbe3-a9bb-f2dbfcf20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers acquired RB Brian Robinson from the Commanders in exchange for a sixth-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d296-db7b-a5dd-f296aaef0000</link>
      <description>The Commanders’ trading Robinson felt like a lock after it was announced last week that the team was shopping the fourth-year back. A day later, Robinson and the Commanders mutually agreed to sit him in the team’s preseason game against the Bengals, and now he’ll be on his way to the Bay Area to help a depleted Niners backfield. Robinson rushed for 799 yards and eight touchdowns in his first season in Kliff Kingsbury’s offense, but wasn’t deemed a scheme fit by the season’s end. The selection of Jacory “Bill” Croskey-Merritt, who has impressed in camp, has made Robinson expendable, and a now valuable addition to the Niners. He should immediately slot in as the RB2 behind Christian McCaffrey, but it seems unlikely that he will earn much work if McCaffrey sees his normal workload. Robinson is a solid between-the-tackles grinder who has averaged 4.1 YPC for his career. He could make for a decent handcuff in deeper leagues if McCaffrey were ever to miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d296-db7b-a5dd-f296aaef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports “financial hurdles remain before any potential Adam Thielen-Vikings reunion can occur.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d293-dbe3-a9bb-f2d3ad980000</link>
      <description>Russini points out that in March, the Panthers bumped up Thielen’s 2025 salary. The 35-year-old receiver comes with a cap hit just north of $10.108 million this season, per Over the Cap, and the Vikings have already been working to increase their cap flexibility with the trade of Harrison Phillips earlier in the week. Thielen would be a natural fit in the Vikings’ offense if a trade is able to get done, but there’s still plenty to work out here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d293-dbe3-a9bb-f2d3ad980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants released WR Zach Pascal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d2e0-d332-a1fd-d6f6ffee0000</link>
      <description>Pascal is again looking for work after being a part of the Giants’ initial cutdown to 53 players. The 30-year-old receiver has bounced between three different teams since 2022 and didn’t catch a pass in 17 games with the Cardinals last season. In addition to Pascal, the Giants also cut WR Jordan Bly, LB K.J. Cloyd, CB O’Donnell Fortune, LB Dyontae Johnson, C Jimmy Morrissey, WR Montrell Washington, and OL Jaison Williams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d2e0-d332-a1fd-d6f6ffee0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
