<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 19:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts QB Anthony Richardson had surgery to repair his orbital bone.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-216e-d5d8-a3ff-f96f153d0000</link>
      <description>There remains a chance, per Rapoport, that Richardson returns this season. It likely won’t matter for the Colts unless Daniel Jones misses time with injury. Richardson injured his eye in a freak pre-game accident earlier this month. He’s likely done with the Colts and could be dealt this offseason to a QB-needy team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-216e-d5d8-a3ff-f96f153d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrell Bernard (ankle) is active for Week 8 against the Panthers but will only play in an emergency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-218c-d245-adfb-b5dfce110000</link>
      <description>With Matt Milano (pec) inactive this week, the Bills wanted to have Bernard available to play, but they are hoping that he won’t be needed. The goal appears to be to have Shaq Thompson and Dorian Williams play the entire game and save Bernard and Milano for Week 9 against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-218c-d245-adfb-b5dfce110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Skattebo suffered an ankle injury in Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-217f-dab4-a3fb-bb7fd7530000</link>
      <description>Jaxson Dart targeted Skattebo in the middle of the second quarter when Skattebo’s ankle got caught beneath a defender. The injury was gruesome enough for the cameras to pan away. Fox did not show a replay as Skattebo’s teammates turned away in horror. Skattebo, who had become a central part of the New York offense over the past month, scored a touchdown — his fourth this season against the Eagles — before his ankle injury. He won’t play again this season, leaving Tyrone Tracy as the Giants’ lead back. It’s a blow to Dart and the entire Giants offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-217f-dab4-a3fb-bb7fd7530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Horn is questionable to return to Week 8 with a shoulder injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21b7-d245-adfb-b5ff3b2f0000</link>
      <description>Horn was hurt midway through the second quarter when he was tackled on a designed screen. The rookie has been getting more touches in recent weeks and would finish this game with two runs for nine yards, even though both of those were screen passes behind the line of scrimmage that count as runs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21b7-d245-adfb-b5ff3b2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out DT Shemar Turner (knee) for the remainder of Week 8’s game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21b9-d5d8-a3ff-f9f9320c0000</link>
      <description>This looked like a minor injury when it first occurred. Turner went down in the first quarter, and was slow to get up before hobbling off the field under his own power. The rookie tackle, however, was later carted from the field and has now been ruled out for the game. The Bears drafted Turner in the second round of this year’s draft. He entered the day with six tackles and two TFLs in four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21b9-d5d8-a3ff-f9f9320c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Oliver was ruled out for the remainder of Week 8 with a bicep injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21c2-dab4-a3fb-bbf26f8f0000</link>
      <description>Oliver was engaged with an offensive lineman in the second quarter and was trying to make a tackle when his outstretched arm was pulled back behind him. He was taken into the blue medical tent and then immediately ruled out for the remainder of the game. The immediate rule out is usually a bad sign, and the initial fear is for a biceps tear, which would likely land Oliver on the IR. Larry Ogunjobi, fresh off his return from suspension, should get more playing time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21c2-dab4-a3fb-bbf26f8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers declared RB Bucky Irving, WR Chris Godwin, OLB Haason Reddick, G Luke Haggard, CB Kindle Vildor, S Sebastian Castro and DL C.J. Brewer inactive for Week 8 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21cb-dab4-a3fb-bbfb8dea0000</link>
      <description>The Buccaneers will again be without two of their top players this week. Long-time No. 1 WR Mike Evans (collarbone/concussion) was also placed on injured reserve earlier this week. Rookie WR Emeka Egbuka will continue to operate as a fantasy WR1, while fellow rookie WR Tez Johnson can be started as a high-upside WR3/FLEX. Reddick’s absence is a plus for the Saints’ offense. His 27 quarterback pressures lead all Buccaneers defenders by three.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21cb-dab4-a3fb-bbfb8dea0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints CB Isaac Yiadom (hamstring) is active for Week 8 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21d0-d245-adfb-b5dfae3b0000</link>
      <description>Yiadom has been sidelined since straining his hamstring in Week 4. Although the Buccaneers are without WRs Mike Evans (collarbone/concussion) and Chris Godwin (fibula), their deep receiving corps, led by rookies WR Emeka Egbuka and WR Tez Johnson, still poses problems for defenses. Yiadom’s return is helpful. The Saints declared OG Xavier Truss, TE Zaire Mitchell-Paden, DB Ugo Amadi, CB Rejzohn Wright, DL Jonah Williams and DT Khristian Boyd inactive for Week 8 against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21d0-d245-adfb-b5dfae3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden was seen heading to the locker room in the third quarter of Week 8’s game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21dc-d5d8-a3ff-f9fdd4ab0000</link>
      <description>According to Bears beat writer Brad Biggs, Burden was seen heading for the locker room with a “red hat official,” which could be a sign of a concussion evaluation. Burden caught his lone pass of the game to kick off the second half and was tackled for a one-yard loss. We’ll be sure to check back in if he returns/is ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21dc-d5d8-a3ff-f9fdd4ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared LB Jack Sanborn (groin), S Juanyeh Thomas (migraines), S Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder), OT Ajani Cornelius (knees), WR Jonathan Mingo and DT Jay Toia inactive for Dallas’ Week 8 game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21e1-d5d8-a3ff-f9e154600000</link>
      <description>Sanborn was a late add to the injury report with a groin injury, and with him and Kenneth Murray out the Cowboys will be vulnerable on the second level today. Active for the Cowboys are C Cooper Beebe (ankle) and DE Marshawn Kneeland (ankle), both playing off questionable tags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-21e1-d5d8-a3ff-f9e154600000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
