<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Matt Schneidman reports that the Packers will place RB MarShawn Lloyd (calf/hamstring) back on injured reserve after activating him on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4b-d005-a9bf-fe7ffc550000</link>
      <description>This is a “procedural move” that will potentially allow the team to activate him later this season, in the event that they make a playoff run. Lloyd, 24, has had a brutal start to his career, plagued by lower-body injuries. He was placed on injured reserve after straining a hamstring in training camp. While rehabbing that injury, he picked up a calf injury. He then suffered another hamstring injury after the Packers activated him to return from injured reserve a couple of weeks ago. He should not be rostered in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e4b-d005-a9bf-fe7ffc550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs CB Trent McDuffie (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e53-d77b-adfb-eed357bb0000</link>
      <description>McDuffie went down with the knee issue in Week 14 and was forced to miss the Chiefs’ following game. He was listed as questionable, but the team ruled him out with their inactives. Now that the Chiefs are out of the playoff hunt, they could shut down some of their injured veterans. It’s possible that McDuffie gets the rest of the year offer to let his knee heal properly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e53-d77b-adfb-eed357bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Rashee Rice (concussion) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e52-d1bc-a3fb-af76c3480000</link>
      <description>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid said Rice “reported concussion symptoms on Monday and entered the league’s protocol.” Chiefs WR Tyquan Thornton is also in the league’s concussion protocol, potentially leaving the receiving corps short-staffed for QB Gardner Minshew against the Titans this week. Chiefs TE Travis Kelce could get a chance to pad his stats, given the state of things, on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e52-d1bc-a3fb-af76c3480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece hall (knee) is practicing in full for Week 16 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e59-d1bc-a3fb-af7d07990000</link>
      <description>Hall was held out of last Wednesday’s practice entirely. His full participation today is a sign that the knee issue is behind him. Hall will close out the year as a workhorse back on one of the league’s worst offenses, confining him to the RB2 ranks despite his RB1 ceiling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e59-d1bc-a3fb-af7d07990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e5e-d77b-adfb-eedf60480000</link>
      <description>No NFL season is complete without a Lamar sickness. Feel free to check your bingo cards at this point. Jackson shouldn’t have any issues suiting up on Sunday, and it’s a minor relief that the team didn’t list him with another injury. Nearing the end of a grueling season, Jackson is a low-end QB1 Week 16 versus the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e5e-d77b-adfb-eedf60480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings C Ryan Kelly (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e63-d77b-adfb-eee37d8d0000</link>
      <description>Right tackle Brian O’Neill was also held out of practice. He is dealing with a heel issue. Christian Darrisaw has been in and out of the lineup with a knee issue of his own in recent weeks. All three linemen may miss Week 16. That would put J.J. McCarthy, who has performed much better in recent weeks, in a tough spot versus the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e63-d77b-adfb-eee37d8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders LB Bobby Wagner (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e52-d005-a9bf-fe7638da0000</link>
      <description>Wagner did not practice on Tuesday either. The veteran linebacker easily leads the Commanders in combined tackles with 137. He also has three sacks and two interceptions. Though Wagner isn’t the superstar linebacker he was years ago, he is still an integral part of Dan Quinn’s defense. Losing him would be a big blow to the Commanders ahead of Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e52-d005-a9bf-fe7638da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 16 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e78-d1bc-a3fb-af7c1c910000</link>
      <description>Bryant missed Week 15 because of the hamstring issue. A full practice means he should be ready to return in Week 16 against the Jags. Bryant had quietly flipped Troy Franklin for the No. 2 role in Denver before being forced to sit last week. He should return to that role on Sunday, but Franklin did just go for 85 yards and a touchdown for the Packers. His latest spike week could complicate things in Denver’s receiver rotation. With the fantasy semi-finals on tap, this is a situation managers should likely avoid for at least one week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e78-d1bc-a3fb-af7c1c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey (ribs) is practicing in full for Week 16 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e7f-d005-a9bf-fe7f706a0000</link>
      <description>Harvey left Week 15 with the rib injury late in the fourth quarter. He did not return, though there was barely any time left on the clock when he was officially listed as questionable. He should be good to go for Week 16. Per usual, Harvey will sit in the top half of the RB2 ranks versus the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e7f-d005-a9bf-fe7f706a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring) will not play in Week 16 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e82-d8cf-affb-beaab8590000</link>
      <description>Cross injured his hamstring on Seattle’s walk-off field goal versus the Colts last week. He did not practice this week before being ruled out, putting his availability for Week 17 in doubt as well. Josh Jones will be the next man up at left tackle for the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e82-d8cf-affb-beaab8590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
