<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:06:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons placed LB Divine Deablo (forearm) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cd3-d245-adfb-9ddfd5de0000</link>
      <description>Deablo suffered a fractured forearm in the team’s Week 7 loss to the 49ers and will now miss at least four games on injured reserve. His absence creates a significant hole in the interior for a defense allowing the second fewest yards per game this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cd3-d245-adfb-9ddfd5de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons downgraded WR Drake London (hip) to questionable for Week 8 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cf9-deb1-a39b-3dff0a9b0000</link>
      <description>The move comes after a limited showing Friday. The veteran receiver was initially absent from the final injury report but was downgraded by the team Saturday, placing his status in legitimate question considering the late-week status update. His status will be one to monitor into Sunday when the team will release its inactives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cf9-deb1-a39b-3dff0a9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants activated K Graham Gano (groin) from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cfc-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdd72c0000</link>
      <description>Gano returns after missing the minimum number of games. Even so, he has struggled through multiple injuries for the previous two seasons and has been inconsistent when healthy since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1cfc-d5d8-a3ff-fdfdd72c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns downgraded QB Shedeur Sanders (back) to questionable for Week 8 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1d34-d245-adfb-9d7f041a0000</link>
      <description>The team elevated Bailey Zappe from the practice squad in an associated move, making it likely Sanders is forced to miss Week 8 against the Patriots. Sanders continues to push for playing time behind Dillon Gabriel, although it appears as if his bid for the starting quarterback gig will be on hold for a week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1d34-d245-adfb-9d7f041a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Eagles are not expected to trade A.J. Brown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-206c-dab4-a3fb-bb7c48bd0000</link>
      <description>Cryptic posts and quiet box scores have fueled rumors that the Eagles could look to move Brown at the trade deadline this year. Even Schefter notes that the Eagles “would be willing to listen to any trade offer.” However, they will need a blockbuster proposal to move their star wideout, and Schefter doesn’t see that happening. Even if the Eagles aren’t going to open up their passing game every week, Brown is worth more to them as a Super Bowl contender than most other teams. He was also starting to turn things around before suffering a hamstring injury that has already ruled him out for Week 8. Brown had 121 yards and two scores in Week 7 and hit 80 yards on six grabs in Week 6. As fun as imagining trade scenarios for Brown might be, there is almost no universe in which he gets moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-206c-dab4-a3fb-bb7c48bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Breece Hall (knee) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2072-dab4-a3fb-bb72883b0000</link>
      <description>Tight end Mason Taylor is also expected to play. Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said on Friday that Hall was trending in the right direction. He got in two limited practices to start the week and was upgraded to a full session on Friday. Expect a heavy commitment to the ground game from Glenn this week as he tries to hide Justin Fields, who he was forced to start because of Tyrod Taylor’s knee injury. Hall, per usual, is a volume-based RB1 with big-play upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2072-dab4-a3fb-bb72883b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Mason Taylor (quad) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-207b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b8a580000</link>
      <description>The Jets have ruled out Garrett Wilson and placed Josh Reynolds on injured reserve over the weekend. Taylor and Tyler Johnson will be Justin Fields’ top wideouts for Week 8. Though we don’t expect much passing output from the Jets this week, Taylor will play a de facto WR1 role for his team because of the injuries. That alone puts him in the streaming mix for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-207b-dab4-a3fb-bb7b8a580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Kirk Cousins will start in Week 8 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-207f-deb1-a39b-217f35370000</link>
      <description>Schefter called it official, though the team has not actually made an announcement yet. It’s good enough for us. Michael Penix is dealing with a bone bruise in his knee. He was listed as questionable after three limited practices this week. Penix played through the issue in Week 7 but wasn’t able to recover in time for the Falcons’ date with Miami. It’s a great matchup for Cousins’ first start of the year. He should be able to post strong efficiency numbers, even if the Falcons largely attack the Dolphins on the ground. Cousins will crack the QB2 ranks n a week loaded with byes and quarterback injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-207f-deb1-a39b-217f35370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports “league sources believe Rashid Shaheed can be had for the right price.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2084-d5d8-a3ff-f9e557330000</link>
      <description>Schefter notes that the Saints are attempting to sign Chris Olave to a contract extension. He has one year left on his rookie deal and the Saints aren’t likely to let him see free agency. Shaheed, on the other hand, is 27 years old and an impending free agent, making him a prime candidate for a rebuilding Saints to move at the trade deadline. Schefter mentioned the Steelers, Broncos, and Bills as teams aggressively pursuing wide receivers via trade. Schefter also mentioned Brandin Cooks as a trade candidate, though it’s hard to imagine much of a market for his services at this point in his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2084-d5d8-a3ff-f9e557330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports D’Andre Swift (groin) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2089-deb1-a39b-218ff9140000</link>
      <description>Swift was listed as questionable after a week of limited practices. He did the same thing last week and had no issues suiting up come game time. Swift wound up running for 124 yards and a touchdown on 19 carries. Facing a Ravens team without Lamar Jackson, the Bears are now favored, creating the potential for positive game script for both Swift and Kyle Monangai. Swift remains a staple of the RB2 ranks for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2089-deb1-a39b-218ff9140000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
