<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stafford (back) was spotted in street clothes during Monday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</link>
      <description>Stafford threw upwards of 60 passes on Saturday in preparation for his return to the field on Monday. Instead, his much-anticipated return has again been delayed due to a back injury that required an epidural last week. Head coach Sean McVay said last week that Stafford was feeling well enough to play in games, which may still be the case, but the decision to hold him out on a day he was set to return is somewhat alarming. Hopefully, we’ll get more clarification on his status after practice, but this remains a story to monitor with Week 1 less than a month away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a01-df63-a199-db2ba5390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Rachaad White is day-to-day with a groin injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a17-d90d-a5bd-ba5f694c0000</link>
      <description>White did not practice on Monday after suffering a groin injury in Saturday’s preseason game against the Titans, but it doesn’t sound like the third-year back is going to be out for too long. White led the Buccaneers’ backfield on Saturday with Bucky Irving held out, and rushed six times for 28 yards in the outing. While his calling card has been in the passing game, White is at risk of losing more work to Irving, who has reportedly impressed as a pass-catcher in camp. He remains a decent handcuff to Irving for the time being, but may not have the standalone value he still carried even after Irving stepped into the RB1 role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a17-d90d-a5bd-ba5f694c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams HC Sean McVay said the team will “be flexible and fluid” with Matthew Stafford as he continues to recover from his back injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a4e-df63-a199-db6fff6f0000</link>
      <description>It’s an incredibly vague response from McVay, who indicated over the weekend that Stafford would return to the field after going through a successful workout on Saturday. Instead, Stafford was spotted in street clothes on Monday and was also seen walking into an Ammortal chamber that specializes as a “wellness device that aims to optimize human performance and promote holistic health through a combination of non-invasive technologies.” So there’s that. McVay said surgery has not been talked about as an option for Stafford, but said his quarterback “didn’t feel good enough” to be on the field on Monday. There’s no way to know at this time if Stafford will or will not be available for Week 1, but there’s certainly reason to be skeptical. Like the Rams, we will also remain “flexible and fluid” with all news involving Stafford, and will check back in with any updates as they come. In the event Stafford is unavailable for any part of the regular season, Jimmy Garoppolo would be the favorite to draw starts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a4e-df63-a199-db6fff6f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Jaxson Dart was “Efficient, effective, aggressive, and confident in the pocket” in his preseason debut against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a39-d90d-a5bd-ba7b31500000</link>
      <description>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan said that Daboll was “uncharacteristically effusive in his praise of Dart before adding disclaimers that it was only one game.” The Giants likely will not turn the quarterback position over to Dart early in the season, but the better he looks in the preseason, the easier it would be for them to pull the plug on Russell Wilson. Dart’s 154/1 passing debut on 19 attempts probably helped the rookie’s odds of appearing sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a39-d90d-a5bd-ba7b31500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Eagles LG Landon Dickerson “is thought to have suffered a meniscus injury to his right knee.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a76-d90d-a5bd-ba7fa4870000</link>
      <description>We still don’t know the full extent of Dickerson’s injury, but Schefter also adds that “Dickerson is getting additional options to determine the next course of action and how long he might be sidelined.” It could be nothing, but it’s possible Dickerson is looking at other options after receiving less-than-stellar news on his initial diagnosis. We’ll have a clear answer soon enough, but the three-time Pro Bowler could be on the verge of missing significant time, or at least the start of the season. If he were to be sidelined, former 2022 first-rounder Kenyon Green could be the favorite to replace him. Green was acquired earlier this offseason in the trade that sent C.J. Gardner-Johnson to the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a76-d90d-a5bd-ba7fa4870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed RB Ameer Abdullah (ribs) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a79-d90d-a5bd-ba7bfb3c0000</link>
      <description>The veteran hurt his ribs in preseason Week 1 action. We would only be speculating on his return to play timeline from the injury listing, but rib injuries are not often season-enders and it’s possible he could return at some point in 2025 if he were released. Abdullah’s listing, however, is season-ending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a79-d90d-a5bd-ba7bfb3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said he pulled Hendon Hooker “early” against the Falcons due to Hooker’s turnovers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a7d-df63-a199-db7fa3800000</link>
      <description>Hooker completed 7-of-10 passes for 38 yards against the Falcons in Preseason “Week 1" (the Lions played in the Hall of Fame game), but fumbled twice and the Lions lost both balls. None of what we’ve seen from Detroit this offseason, from the signing of Kyle Allen to the rhetoric about how Hooker has played, speaks well to the job Hooker has done heading into his third season. It’s entirely possible Allen passes him for the QB2 role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a7d-df63-a199-db7fa3800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers signed RB Jase McClellan, formerly of the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a8a-d05a-adda-ba8ab28e0000</link>
      <description>McClellan was a fourth-round pick of the Falcons last season and was let go by the team in June. His signing comes just days after Rachaad White suffered a groin injury, but White was mentioned as being day-to-day by head coach Todd Bowles. There could be nothing to this signing, but the timing of it is interesting. McClellan rushed 13 times for 32 scoreless yards last season and should be considered a long shot to make the final 53-man roster if White is healthy by roster cut down day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a8a-d05a-adda-ba8ab28e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Ja’Lynn Polk (shoulder) won’t play against the Vikings in preseason Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a93-df63-a199-dbbb072d0000</link>
      <description>Polk appeared to suffer an injury during Friday night’s game against the Commanders. He’s been sidelined with a shoulder injury for most of the offseason, though it’s unknown if this is the same shoulder. It’s certainly possible that the Patriots waive/injured Polk or place him on injured reserve in the coming weeks, as the second-rounder never seemed to make a real push in what has become a stacked New England receiving room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a93-df63-a199-dbbb072d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zac Jackson believes Joe Flacco is “probably” the team’s opening-day starter at quarterback.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a9f-d45c-a7fc-9a9f053d0000</link>
      <description>Kenny Pickett, the only serious contender to Flacco, has been dealing with a hamstring injury that has kept him as a 7-on-7 participant for most of the last week. Whoever wins this job will be one of the lowest-regarded fantasy options in the league, but Flacco’s success in Kevin Stefanski’s offense in 2023 at least throws some optimistic scenarios on the table for Jerry Jeudy and David Njoku.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9a9f-d45c-a7fc-9a9f053d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
