<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones said, in his “mind,” the “term, amount, guarantees, everything” for Micah Parsons’ potential extension were established without Parsons’ agent present.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</link>
      <description>Jones’ statement effectively validates the timeline of events that Parsons outlined in a social media post. Parsons’ agent was not present for the private discussion in which Jones says the contract was negotiated, and Jones takes issue with the agent’s attempts to “improve off the mark that we’d already set.” These are bizarre circumstances. Agents are hired to represent players in contract negotiations. Jones seemingly disagrees with that practice in this specific instance. The two sides need to resolve this issue soon, ostensibly with Parsons’ agent involved. For his part, Parsons seems ready to dig in, scrubbing mentions of the Cowboys from his social media profiles and adding a Bible verse: “Even if I fall, I will rise; the Lord is my light.” Best of luck, Jerry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cec6-de13-afdc-cecf0b800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts QB Riley Leonard will start in preseason Week 3 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cee3-d332-a1fd-def7a05a0000</link>
      <description>The sixth-round rookie quarterback is expected to play throughout the first half. Per FOX59’s Mike Chappell, “the vast majority of the Colts’ other front-line players and top backups” will not play. Depending on how the season unfolds, Leonard could see playing time at some point this year, though that would likely mean something has gone terribly awry. Leonard is a capable rusher. Flashing improved arm talent against the Bengals could increase his stock in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cee3-d332-a1fd-def7a05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philly Voice’s Jimmy Kempski reports that Eagles WR Jahan Dotson “seems to have earned” Jalen Hurts’ trust.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef5-de13-afdc-ceffecbe0000</link>
      <description>A.J. Brown (hamstring) and DeVonta Smith (groin) have both missed time in training camp, affording Dotson the opportunity to catch passes “in bulk.” The Eagles’ No. 3 wide receiver reportedly “had a great close to camp” after a “quiet start.” Kempski is now the second beat reporter this month to suggest that Dotson will contribute more than he did last year, though Dotson set the bar quite low. If Brown, Smith and Dallas Goedert are on the field, fantasy managers should not expect Dotson to reliably produce. He could return flex value if Brown and Smith’s soft tissue injuries remain an issue in-season, though, and No. 4 WR Johnny Wilson (knee/ankle) is set to undergo season-ending surgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef5-de13-afdc-ceffecbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles QB Tanner McKee “had the best camp of his career” and will “be a fascinating player to debate next offseason from a trade perspective.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf0-de13-afdc-cffb48fb0000</link>
      <description>The assessment comes from one of the industry’s more reliable NFL beat writers, the Philly Voice’s Jimmy Kempski, who believes McKee “is going to get a shot as a starter in the NFL at some point.” McKee is a name to know for re-draft purposes, should Jalen Hurts miss time. Dynasty managers should consider adding him now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf0-de13-afdc-cffb48fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon was carted away from preseason Week 3 against the Panthers after suffering a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef8-de13-afdc-cefbc87d0000</link>
      <description>Harmon was expected to start from Day 1 on the Steelers’ defensive line after the organization drafted him 21st overall this year. Losing him for an extended period of time would be a big blow to the Steelers’ defense. Through three preseason games, Harmon totaled two tackles, three quarterback pressures and one sack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cef8-de13-afdc-cefbc87d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets placed EDGE Rashad Weaver on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf09-dbe3-a9bb-ff5b6fc90000</link>
      <description>The Jets also released DL Phidarian Mathis and CB Ryan Cooper. The moves come shortly after the Jets finalized their trade for DT Harrison Phillips. Weaver posted a career-best 5.5 sacks in 2022. He spent time with the Texans and Rams over the last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf09-dbe3-a9bb-ff5b6fc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers S Xavier McKinney (calf) resumed practicing in a limited capacity on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf34-db7b-a5dd-ef343eb90000</link>
      <description>McKinney has been sidelined for two weeks now, so his return is a great sign. The veteran safety earned first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors in his first season with the Packers last year. He reiterated today that he will be ready to play in Week 1 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf34-db7b-a5dd-ef343eb90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart was cleared to return after being examined for a concussion in the Giants’ preseason Week 3 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf41-de13-afdc-cfcb5d030000</link>
      <description>Although Dart was cleared to return, we do not expect him to return. Dart took a tumble on a scramble and was summoned into the blue medical tent by medical staffers. Before that play, which nearly resulted in a lost fumble, Dart looked great against the Patriots’ defense. He completed 6-of-12 passes for 81 yards and one touchdown and rushed once for 23 yards. One has to wonder how long Russell Wilson can keep the starting job with Dart showing promise. The rookie passer would have had a much bigger stat line had WR Jalin Hyatt not botched two downfield opportunities. Hyatt let one pass bounce off his shoulder pads and later let another clang off his hands. He then, almost unbelievably, hauled in a 30-yard touchdown pass from Jameis Winston on the play immediately after Dart’s scramble. For fantasy managers wishing to stash a late-round dual-threat quarterback, Dart deserves consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf41-de13-afdc-cfcb5d030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Skattebo rushed three times for 12 yards in the Giants’ preseason Week 3 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf51-dbe3-a9bb-ff5356200000</link>
      <description>Skattebo played on 10-of-10 snaps through the Giants’ first two drives before hanging his cleats up for the day. The team released an unofficial depth chart shortly before the game, listing Tyrone Tracy Jr. as the starter, backed up by Devin Singletary. Skattebo was in the third spot with Dante Miller behind him. Both Tracy and Singletary were held out of Thursday’s game and Miller entered the game only after Skattebo was done. Unofficial depth charts can be unreliable but it appears as though this one does accurately reflect the running back pecking order for the time being. Skattebo forced one missed tackle. He will have chances to work his way up the depth chart in the coming weeks. His hamstring injury appears to be in the rearview.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf51-dbe3-a9bb-ff5356200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed two times for three yards, caught 2-of-2 targets for 12 yards and fumbled once in the Steelers’ preseason Week 3 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf5b-de13-afdc-cfdbd8250000</link>
      <description>It was a tough start for Warren, who split time with Gainwell through the first two drives. Gainwell played 3-of-3 third-down snaps, plus two more on early downs. Warren is in line to start in Week 1, but Gainwell appears to have locked up passing down duties and Kaleb Johnson could steal touches with quality play. Gainwell rushed two times for seven yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cf5b-de13-afdc-cfdbd8250000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
