<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs LG Ben Bredeson suffered a knee injury in Tampa Bay’s Week 14 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb12-da9b-a9bf-ff1f346e0000</link>
      <description>Bredeson recently missed time with a hamstring injury. The fact that he was ruled out in-game is not encouraging. Brederson is a very capable pass blocker. Buccaneers QB Baker Mayfield will miss him if he misses extended time. They face the Falcons in Week 15 and the Panthers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb12-da9b-a9bf-ff1f346e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith did not catch his lone target in the Steelers’ Week 14 win against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb1d-d77b-adfa-fb9fb9170000</link>
      <description>Smith again was not part of Steelers passing offense even with Darnell Washington sideline with a concussion for most of the game. Arthur Smith’s favorite tight end has just 30 receptions on the season and only five receptions over his past five games. Smith can remain on waiver wires ahead of the Steelers’ Week 15 game against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb1d-d77b-adfa-fb9fb9170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashid Shaheed caught 4-of-5 targets for 67 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 14 win over the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb1c-da9b-a9bf-ff1d7daa0000</link>
      <description>This was, by far, Shaheed’s best game as a member of the Seahawks. He had failed to find any semblance of a role in the offense since being traded to Seattle at the deadline. Shaheed had four catches for 37 yards in four games as a Seahawk leading into today’s miniature breakout. Not only did he exceed those numbers versus Seattle, but he ouncayted the performance with a 100-yard kick return touchdown to open the second half. Shaheed still ran fewer routes than Cooper Kupp, but he is gaining ground at the right time. Shaheed will work his way into the WR5 ranks for Week 15 versus the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb1c-da9b-a9bf-ff1d7daa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren had eight rushes for 13 yards in the Steelers’ Week 14 win against the Ravens, adding four catches for 49 yards and a touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb25-d8cf-affb-ff2ff89e0000</link>
      <description>Warren’s eight carries led the Pittsburgh backfield, as Kenneth Gainwell had four rushes for 15 yards and a touchdown. Gainwell was second on the team with six targets, but it was Warren who had a 38-yard screen pass touchdown in the second half. Warren remains the nominal lead back for the run-first Steelers, but Gainwell’s route running involvement and his red zone usage puts a damper on Warren’s weekly upside. Warren, averaging 13.8 rushes per game, will be a top-24 running back next week against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb25-d8cf-affb-ff2ff89e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White rushed 11 times for 53 yards in the Bucs’ Week 14 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb2d-da9b-a9bf-ff2d4f4a0000</link>
      <description>White “added” a two-yard reception. With Baker Mayfield struggling in rainy conditions, the Bucs dialed up 33 running back rushes. White was out-carried just 15-11 by Bucky Irving, but it was Irving who provided the only Bucs RB score, a 24-yarder through the air. White has been spelling Irving plenty since his Week 13 return, but it is predictably failing to produce RB3 returns as Irving gets more overall work and the majority of the high-value touches. Although White has a decent enough touches floor, you will be in trouble if forced to FLEX him during the fantasy playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb2d-da9b-a9bf-ff2d4f4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed seven times for 29 yards and a touchdown in the Bucs’ Week 14 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb32-d8cf-affb-ff3ae09c0000</link>
      <description>Tucker’s one-yard touchdown in the third quarter came after he set the Bucs up at the one-yard with a 13-yard rumble. The Bucs then went hurry up and he punched it in. The score was nice, but Tucker was a distant third in snaps behind Bucky Irving and Rachaad White, and that should remain a theme for the stretch run as the Bucs try to grind out a rock fight NFC South title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb32-d8cf-affb-ff3ae09c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rasheen Ali had one rush for two yards in the Ravens’ Week 14 loss against the Steelers, adding two catches for 11 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb34-d8cf-affb-ff3ea2980000</link>
      <description>Ali could see a marked uptick in snaps, routes, and touches if Keaton Mitchell misses extended time with the knee injury he sustained in the second half of Sunday’s loss to the Steelers. Ali, who drew praise from head coach John Harbaugh last week, is a decent bench stash headed into the fantasy playoffs in case Derrick Henry gets dinged up in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb34-d8cf-affb-ff3ea2980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 2-of-9 targets for 15 yards in the Bucs’ Week 14 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb3b-da9b-a9bf-ff3f3e2c0000</link>
      <description>Horribly inefficient of late, Egbuka very much remained so in the rain. The lowlight was a dropped 22-yard touchdown with the Bucs trying for a game-tying score late in the fourth quarter. It wasn’t a perfect ball from Baker Mayfield, but one Egbuka absolutely has to catch. Struggling to rediscover his early- to mid-season form, Egbuka now has to contend with the likely Week 15 return of Mike Evans against the Falcons on Thursday. With the Bucs now in hand-to-hand combat for a playoff berth, Evans will undoubtedly be a point of emphasis, especially in the red zone. That makes Egbuka an even more volatile WR2 option than he has already been the past few weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb3b-da9b-a9bf-ff3f3e2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared G Trey Smith, T Jawaan Taylor, WR Nikko Remigio, WR Jalen Royals, RB Elijah Mitchell, and CB Kristian Fulton inactive for Week 14 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb3e-d8cf-affb-ff3e1da70000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs elevated G C. J. Hansen Saturday to help with depth up front, but they could find themselves under constant pressure against the vaunted Houston pass rush now down multiple pieces up front. Expect quarterback Patrick Mahomes to eventually lean into a ball-out-quick mentality, likely to benefit wide receiver Rashee Rice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-fb3e-d8cf-affb-ff3e1da70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
