<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Kraft caught 6-of-7 targets for 124 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d86f-abdd-7ffdba0b0000</link>
      <description>Kraft was all alone on the majority of his targets, with the two biggest connections being a 57-yard scamper from the arm of Jordan Love and an eight-yard touchdown throw from Love in the fourth quarter. The 24-year-old wasn’t nearly as involved in Week 1 against the Lions, but that’s back-to-back weeks with a receiving score for the 2023 third-round pick. He’s a TE1 for Week 3 when the Packers face off against the Browns, but don’t expect this kind of yardage total very often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d86f-abdd-7ffdba0b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 3-of-5 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be2-da67-a99f-fff7d2df0000</link>
      <description>Doubs beat the middle of the Washington defense to connect with Jordan Love on a five-yard touchdown to open the scoring. The fourth-year wideout wasn’t involved often after that early touchdown, as Jordan Love was able to find a bevy of wideouts and tight ends throughout the contest. Doubs remains in the WR4 vicinity for the Week 3 tilt against the Browns, but might get a slight bump up if Jayden Reed (shoulder) can’t play in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be2-da67-a99f-fff7d2df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks caught 4-of-6 targets for 44 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d294-a19b-fff396240000</link>
      <description>Wicks ended up leading the Packers’ wideouts in targets and catches on a night where Jayden Reed left Thursday’s win in the first possession with a shoulder injury. The 24-year-old wideout remains a solid option for Jordan Love, but not solid enough to recommend him as a fantasy option even with the Reed injury potentially leading to more snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d294-a19b-fff396240000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden didn’t haul in either of his targets while adding two rushes for 15 yards in the Packers’ Week 2 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be4-dc44-a9d9-3fe63fe20000</link>
      <description>Oh what could have been. Golden just missed a pair of touchdowns; one on a ball that was underthrown by Jordan Love on fourth down in the first possession, and another that would have been a 90-plus yard score on a ball that was just overthrown. He showed off his speed on a pair of end-arounds, but this could — and should — have been a much better fantasy day for the rookie wideout. Golden should remain part of the gameplan for Week 3 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be4-dc44-a9d9-3fe63fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 6-of-8 targets for 64 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d86f-abdd-7fffdd230000</link>
      <description>Ertz was the most reliable target for the Commanders late in the contest after Washington had to go into throw-only mode after being down two scores. He not only scored the first touchdown of the game for the Commanders, but he set up the second score by drawing a holding penalty in the corner of the end zone. That makes back-to-back games with a score, and he’ll be a high-end TE2 — if such thing exists — for Week 3 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be3-d86f-abdd-7fffdd230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 5-of-9 targets for 48 yards in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-dc44-a9d9-3fe7682f0000</link>
      <description>McLaurin’s nine targets were the most of any Washington receiver, but those hoping for more deep chances after his 2-27 line against the Giants came away disappointed. There’s a good chance some of this mediocre production has to do with his training camp absence, but it doesn’t make it any less disappointing. He should still be considered in the WR2 range for Week 3 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-dc44-a9d9-3fe7682f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 7-of-8 targets for 44 yards with a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 2 loss to the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d294-a19b-fff18d380000</link>
      <description>Samuel didn’t have a rushing attempt, but did add a 50-yard kick return to open the second half. The wideout was mostly targeted in the short-to-intermediate range, with a long catch of 12 yards. The touchdown saves the fantasy day, but most of this was rather uninspiring. He profiles as a lower-end WR2 for the Week 3 contest against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3be1-d294-a19b-fff18d380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Reed has been diagnosed with a broken collarbone and is out indefinitely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-36c5-db7b-a5dd-b6c511740000</link>
      <description>Coach Matt LaFleur confirmed the third-year pro will miss “a lot of time.” LaFleur did say Reed should return at some point this season. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the “hope” is Reed misses “only” 6-8 weeks. The Packers have been up to their typical receiver rotation tricks through the first two weeks of 2025, but this might force LaFleur to start putting more on first-round rookie Matthew Golden’s plate. It could help that the Pack now have 10 days to prepare for Week 3 against the Browns. Still, that could prove to be wishcasting with a club that just doesn’t treat receiver the way most other teams do. Considering the aforementioned rotation and Reed’s famously streaky production, you could be hard pressed to stash him for the better part of two months even if you have an open I.R. spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-36c5-db7b-a5dd-b6c511740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Commanders believe Austin Ekeler tore his Achilles during Thursday’s Week 2 loss to the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3c31-d86f-abdd-7dbdbc030000</link>
      <description>Ekeler will undergo imaging Friday to confirm whether there’s structural damage. The 30-year-old looked visibly upset after walking off following the injury, and it would be a surprise if his 2025 campaign isn’t over. Jacorey Croskey-Merritt will almost assuredly be the starting running back going forward, with Jeremy McNichols operating as his backup. This could also lead to more touches in the backfield from Deebo Samuel, as well, and it’s possible the Commanders will look at the trade market for a potential replacement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3c31-d86f-abdd-7dbdbc030000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derek Carr said, “I wouldn’t say never,” when asked about coming out of retirement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3dfc-da67-a99f-fdfd76490000</link>
      <description>Speaking on the Dan Patrick Show, Carr made his return sound like a real possibility. He told Patrick, “I wouldn’t say never because I’ve learned that when I say never, it usually happens.” HW also said he is still training just because he loves it. Carr chose not to undergo surgery on his shoulder in the offseason and called it quits on a lengthy career. Teams typically hold the rights to a player after they retire, so the Saints would also need to find a trade partner for Carr, assuming they don’t want him back. Of course, he still needs to be medically cleared before playing football again. We aren’t holding our breath for a Carr comeback, but the odds appear to be meaningfully higher than zero.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3dfc-da67-a99f-fdfd76490000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
