<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared WR Jermaine Burton, CB Marco Wilson, TE Cam Grandy, DT Jordan Jefferson and DE Shemar Stewart inactive for Week 5 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bc-deb6-a7fd-f7ff03640000</link>
      <description>Despite reports of progress for Burton this offseason, he’s been inactive for all five games so far this year. Andrei Iosivas remains the team’s No. 3 receiver against a depleted Lions secondary and likely the foreseeable future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bc-deb6-a7fd-f7ff03640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers declared TE Will Dissly (knee) inactive for Los Angeles’ Week 5 game against Washington.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bd-d95b-addb-fdff8fe20000</link>
      <description>He was on the questionable line and practiced in full on Friday, so this is a fairly surprising inactive listing. Oronde Gadsden II should benefit from additional snaps and is a worthwhile pivot for those in deeper leagues relying on Dissly. Also inactive for the Chargers are: WR Derius Davis (Knee), S RJ Mickens, CB Nikko Reed, OLB Kyle Kennard, OT Joe Alt (ankle), and DT Naquan Jones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bd-d95b-addb-fdff8fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson was forced from Philadelphia’s Week 5 game against the Broncos with an ankle injury and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfb84b0000</link>
      <description>We aren’t doctors, but the Eagles’ road-paving blocker appeared to suffer a left high-ankle sprain. Already battling through injury coming into Week 5, Dickerson could be given several weeks to heal up, or perhaps even a stint on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfb84b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared LT Taylor Decker, LB Zach Cunningham, CB Khalil Dorsey, RB Sione Vaki, OL Kingsley Equakun, DL Chris Smith and DL Mekhi Wingo inactive for Week 5 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-d6e9-af9d-bfbfc1670000</link>
      <description>No surprise here after Decker was downgraded to doubtful with a shoulder injury on Sunday morning. The 31-year-old left tackle is experiencing constant pain unrelated to offseason shoulder surgery. Giovani Manu will make his first regular season start and it might not be his last start this month with two more games coming up before the Lions’ bye week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-d6e9-af9d-bfbfc1670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders OL Brandon Coleman is inactive for Washington’s Week 5 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfd9b10000</link>
      <description>Coleman hasn’t played since Week 2 and, after a decent rookie season, is now a healthy scratch for the Commanders. Also inactive for the Commanders are: QB Josh Johnson (emergency 3rd QB), WR Terry McLaurin (quad), LB Ale Kaho, LB Kain Medrano and WR Noah Brown (knee/groin).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfd9b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku caught 6-of-9 targets for 67 yards and a touchdown in the Browns’ Week 5 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bd-deb6-a7fd-f7ff20b70000</link>
      <description>The switch to Dillon Gabriel wasn’t good for everyone in the Browns’ offense, but it was clearly a net positive for the tight ends. Njoku set season-highs across the board and logged a monstrous 27 percent target share. Harold Fannin also remained involved with four grabs and a touchdown. Gabriel struggled on his deep throws but had no issues hitting the layups to his tight ends and running backs. That won’t change in his second start next week, meaning fantasy managers can keep Njoku in their lineups as a low-end TE1 versus Pittsburgh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5bd-deb6-a7fd-f7ff20b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Grant Calcaterra suffered an oblique injury in Week 5 against the Broncos and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5c6-d6e9-af9d-bfd69b980000</link>
      <description>Dallas Goedert’s direct backup should be considered week-to-week following the mid-game ruleout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5c6-d6e9-af9d-bfd69b980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 3-of-6 targets for 31 yards in Week 5 against the Saints before leaving with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5e9-d6e9-af9d-bff957e90000</link>
      <description>Slayton was going to be counted on in a big way with Malik Nabers (ACL) out for the season, and the veteran disappointed on Sunday. First, he dropped a potential 50-yard catch that hit him in the hands, and then he and Jaxson Dart were unable to connect on another 50-plus yard flea flicker that should have been an easy touchdown. Near the end of the first half, he made his biggest mistake, which was a fumble while trying to earn extra yards after the catch. The Giants were driving to extend their lead, but the Saints would then recover and score points of their own to take a lead they would not relinquish. With Slayton out, both Jalin Hyatt and Beaux Collins saw more work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5e9-d6e9-af9d-bff957e90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones completed 20-of-29 passes for 212 yards and two touchdowns in the Colts’ 40-6, Week 5 win over the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5e4-d95b-addb-fde611990000</link>
      <description>Uncharacteristically, Jones rushed only one time for two yards. With the Colts doing largely whatever they wanted against a collapsed Raiders team, Jones handed off for four additional scores and rested for approximately the final 10 minutes. Amazingly, today was actually Jones’ first multi-score start through the air as a Colt. Jones has been extremely efficient while hitting far more deep passes than he did as a Giant, but it hasn’t translated to big fantasy box scores the past two weeks due to his more restrained efforts on the ground. His excellent “real life” play coupled with his deep, varied skill corps will still keep him in the low-end QB1 mix for a plus Week 6 matchup with the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5e4-d95b-addb-fde611990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Taylor rushed 17 times for 66 yards and three touchdowns in the Colts’ Week 5 win over the Raiders, adding three receptions for 20 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5ed-deb6-a7fd-f7ff2a9b0000</link>
      <description>Taylor’s latest mammoth fantasy effort came despite resting for the majority of the fourth quarter and losing a two-yard score to Ameer Abdullah when he was still in the game. Healthy with Daniel Jones raising the level of the Colts’ entire offense, Taylor is back in RB1 overall mode after last year’s excellent campaign had him in “just” the RB3-5 range. Now up to seven total scores, Taylor has a home date with the Cardinals on tap for Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-b5ed-deb6-a7fd-f7ff2a9b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
