<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said WR Calvin Austin (shoulder) could return to practice this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0749-d99b-a1df-3f4d9f7c0000</link>
      <description>Tomlin said Tuesday that he’s “optimistic” Austin can return to game action in Week 8 against the Packers after missing the past few weeks with a serious shoulder injury. Austin had been operating as the team’s WR2 behind DK Metcalf before the injury, seeing 17 targets over four games. Austin would barely be a deep league WR option if he’s able to suit up this week against Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0749-d99b-a1df-3f4d9f7c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DC Dennard Wilson said “guys will have to step up” without L’Jarius Sneed (quad) against the Colts in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07b7-df81-ab9b-7ff708470000</link>
      <description>Sneed left Week 7’s game against the Patriots and was quickly ruled out. This seems to confirm he has little chance to play this week. Frankly, with how poorly Sneed has been playing in his limited snaps, the Titans could probably use those snaps to evaluate younger players. The Sneed contract has been a boondoggle for Tennessee through two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07b7-df81-ab9b-7ff708470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Wingo reports that the Cowboys have “made inquiries” about Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07cb-da18-a39a-dfdb49480000</link>
      <description>This is both not a typical source for us to use and something that we doubt comes to fruition without Crosby asking out of Las Vegas, but it is clear that the Cowboys are big-game hunting to replace Micah Parsons. They do have a first-round pick war chest, so nothing can be ruled out. We anticipate the Cowboys will likely have to settle for some more marginal upgrades, but then again, we’d also have anticipated that they’d just keep Parsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07cb-da18-a39a-dfdb49480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets owner Woody Johnson said the Jets offense “would look good” if “we can just complete a pass.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07d3-da18-a39a-dfd3973e0000</link>
      <description>Welp. That’ll be one for the career obituary on Justin Fields. It seems clear that the Jets owner has not soured on Aaron Glenn and instead believes that the Fields play was simply a mistake. The Jets have not announced anything about who their quarterback will be this week, but ownership doesn’t usually just say something like this about a pass offense with a quarterback they intend to keep starting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07d3-da18-a39a-dfd3973e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports the Jets are “moving toward” naming Tyrod Taylor the starter.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07d9-da18-a39a-dfdbaf3d0000</link>
      <description>Well, yeah. Consider this a companion blurb to what we just posted about Justin Fields. We sincerely doubt that Taylor is going to stay healthy for longer than a month at 36 years old, but he can competently shepherd the passing offense in a way that Fields simply hasn’t. Add up a game against the Bengals defense to the ledger and suddenly Taylor is squarely on the QB2 superflex line in a week with six teams on bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07d9-da18-a39a-dfdbaf3d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed EDGE Brandon Graham.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07fa-d651-a9df-6fff6c520000</link>
      <description>Terms weren’t disclosed, but we would be floored if this wasn’t a one-year contract. Graham will replace ZaDarius Smith (retired) at EDGE. The Eagles are lacking production at the position in the absence of Nolan Smith and actually used first-round pick Jihaad Campbell there at times against the Vikings in Week 7. Graham will give them a higher floor even if he’s not 2015 Brandon Graham anymore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07fa-d651-a9df-6fff6c520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers coach Todd Bowles said Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) and Chris Godwin (fibula) are “getting better” but “didn’t know whether either are in play to return to practice this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07fe-da18-a39a-dfff17280000</link>
      <description>It’s only an initial lean after a Monday night game, but we’d be surprised to see Irving or Godwin suit up on a short week. It’s not quite the auto rule-out that we saw last Monday night for Irving, so that’s a small trend in a positive direction. Irving has not played since Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-07fe-da18-a39a-dfff17280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell announced Carson Wentz (shoulder) will start Minnesota’s Week 8 game against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0811-d99b-a1df-3a1d04d70000</link>
      <description>O’Connell did say that J.J. McCarthy (ankle) might have had a chance to go if this was a Sunday game, making him a possible option for Week 9. Given how slow the Vikings have been with McCarthy, we’ll believe it when we see it. Wentz will make a fine superflex QB2 against the Chargers given how poor their defense has played of late. Max Brosmer will be Minnesota’s backup in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0811-d99b-a1df-3a1d04d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings designated RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-080f-d99b-a1df-3a0fc6360000</link>
      <description>His 21-day window is now open, meaning he can be inactive for only three more games before returning to the roster or being ruled out for the season. Per NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero, Jones could “potentially” return for Week 8’s game against the Chargers on Thursday night. Jones doesn’t necessarily need practice reps to play, but we’re still curious about the practice report listings for him today and tomorrow. If Jones does return, he’ll cut Jordan Mason down to a FLEX play and perhaps be a usable-but-risky FLEX play himself against a weak Chargers run defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-080f-d99b-a1df-3a0fc6360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed RB Trayveon Williams to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-081d-da18-a39a-da1f9c0e0000</link>
      <description>It sounds like a hedge against Hassan Haskins missing Week 8. Nyheim Hines is the on-roster backup to Kimani Vidal, though Hines is more of a pass-catching back. It’s possible Williams is active against the Vikings, though we couldn’t confidently predict a real role for him at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-081d-da18-a39a-da1f9c0e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
