<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:02:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers completed 23-of-34 passes for 249 yards, four touchdowns and two interceptions in the Steelers’ 33-31, Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f051-d651-a9df-f955a2fa0000</link>
      <description>The four-score game was Rodgers’ second of the season after he posted only one in all of 2024. That came in Week 18, no less. His yardage ceiling is still feeling hard-capped, however, as 249 is actually his most of 2025. Rodgers’ “two interceptions” are a bit misleading, as one was simply stolen out of DK Metcalf’s hands. The other was a deep ball that badly sailed. His most impressive touchdown was a 68-yard strike to Pat Freiermuth on a coverage bust. Rodgers is obviously playing better than he did in 2024, but with attempts and yards at a premium, he is maxing out as a low-end QB2 because of his complete lack of rushing ability. He’s a more valuable “real life” asset than fantasy. Week 8 is a “revenge game” with the Packers, but Green Bay will be just as interested in dishing it out as Rodgers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f051-d651-a9df-f955a2fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DK Metcalf caught 3-of-5 targets for 50 yards in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f055-d99b-a1dd-fa5daac60000</link>
      <description>Riding a hot streak coming into the proceedings, Metcalf had a rough night. He was the intended target on both of Aaron Rodgers’ interceptions. One was the quarterback’s fault. Rodgers simply sailed a deep ball. The other ... well, Metcalf let it get ripped out of his hands. Not great. Also not a concern. Almost literally the Steelers’ only viable wideout, Metcalf is displaying decent enough chemistry with the mercurial Rodgers to stay locked in as a WR2. The Packers’ strong overall defense is on tap for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f055-d99b-a1dd-fa5daac60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Warren rushed 16 times for 127 yards in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals, adding four receptions for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f058-d651-a9df-f95d63c30000</link>
      <description>Warren’s 158 yards from scrimmage were a new career high by 13. That helped take some of the sting out of his 18-yard touchdown getting called back by holding in the second quarter. It was also nice that Warren out-touched Kenneth Gainwell 20-5 after that advantage was just 13-12 in his Week 6 return. 20-5 is probably a bit excessive, but should be much closer to the weekly norm than 13-12. That helps stabilize Warren as an RB2 after his knee injury interrupted his hot start. The Packers are on deck for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f058-d651-a9df-f95d63c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed three times for 14 yards in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f061-d651-a9df-f9755cc20000</link>
      <description>Gainwell “added” two receptions for one yard. Although PFF charted Jaylen Warren as out-snapping Gainwell “just” 37-22, Warren out-touched his backfield mate 20-5, out-gaining him 158-15. This, after they played to a usage standstill in Warren’s Week 6 return from his knee injury. Tonight should be much closer to the norm going forward, removing Gainwell from FLEX consideration in most 12-team leagues heading into Week 8 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f061-d651-a9df-f9755cc20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase Brown rushed 11 times for 108 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f063-df81-ab9b-fee7d7940000</link>
      <description>Tonight was Brown’s first 100-yard effort either on the ground or from scrimmage this season, though he almost didn’t get there in the latter category after losing eight yards on his two receptions. Brown also committed an awful drop over the middle of the field. Having previously failed to notch a 20-yard carry all season, Brown had 27 and 37-yard rumbles against the Steelers as Joe Flacco created space by ripping holes in the defense through the air. The solid effort at least keeps Brown in the RB2 mix, though this was really just a bare minimum step toward him getting back on the right track. The Jets are an admittedly appetizing Week 8 matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f063-df81-ab9b-fee7d7940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Fant caught 4-of-4 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f066-d99b-a1dd-fa6ef75e0000</link>
      <description>Amidst a Ja’Marr Chase/Tee Higgins targets barrage that saw 33 looks being funneled the elite wideouts’ way, Fant managed to get loose for his first score since Week 1. His 44 yards were also a new season high. What can Joe Flacco do for you? Flacco is going to keep slinging it until his arm falls off, but Fant is still unlikely to see enough volume to push for TE2 status in Week 8 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f066-d99b-a1dd-fa6ef75e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine rushed seven times for 31 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06b-da18-a39b-fa7b44a80000</link>
      <description>Perine was not targeted in the passing game as Chase Brown out-touched him 13-7 and out-snapped him 48-28 (via PFF). Perine did manage new season high in both carries and rushing yards as Joe Flacco helped open up the offense. Perine is still far more likely to hamper Brown’s fantasy value, however, than create any of his own heading into Week 8 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06b-da18-a39b-fa7b44a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrei Iosivas caught 3-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</link>
      <description>Iosivas’ missed connection was a bad drop. Iosivas posted his second best overall statline of the season as Joe Flacco dropped back 49 times and attempted 47 passes, but he was out-targeted 33-4 by Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins’ combined efforts. It would take injury to one of the elite wideouts ahead of him for Iosivas to become fantasy relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 3-of-6 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</link>
      <description>Both the six-target effort and score were Smith’s first since Week 1, while he was the No. 2 producing tight end behind Pat Freiermuth, who turned his six looks into 5/111/2. Improbably, Darnell Washington also found the end zone. That’s the long way of saying no Steelers tight end is producing consistently enough to merit a real TE2 look ahead of Week 8 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 3-of-5 targets for two yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career-high 62-yard effort, Washington posted one of the more bizarre box scores you will ever see. He does now have 10 targets over the past two weeks after that number was four across his first four appearances. Perhaps his usage really is changing, but there has been little indication Washington is about to make a legitimate push for TE2 value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
