<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (hip) won’t play in Minnesota’s Week 18 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8030-d35e-a1bf-c5f2c7fb0000</link>
      <description>Jones finishes the year with a 548/2 rushing line on 132 carries, adding 28/199/1 through the air in 12 starts. Jones plays hurt often, and with Jordan Mason in tow this year, the Vikings were more proactive about sending him to IR. Jones enters his age-32 season on the final year of a two-year, $20 million deal with a $14 million cap figure. He figures to either be asked to restructure that deal or be released with the Vikings currently $36.4 million over the cap for 2026 per Over The Cap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8030-d35e-a1bf-c5f2c7fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings TE T.J. Hockenson (shoulder) won’t play in Minnesota’s Week 18 game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8030-d968-a19b-d8f1ca620000</link>
      <description>With Jordan Addison taking a major leap in 2024, Hockenson has slid into an uninteresting low-end TE1 stab over the past two years, generating 41/455/0 in 2024 and 51/438/3 in 2025. Cutting Hockenson would free up over $8.9 million in cap space for a team that’s currently up against it to get cap-compliant and The Athletic’s Alec Lewis pointed to Hockenson as one contract that could be reworked this offseason. His future with the Vikings is in some question entering 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8030-d968-a19b-d8f1ca620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Luther Burden (quad) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 18 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-802c-d35e-a1bf-c5eef25b0000</link>
      <description>Burden’s injury caused a scare last week, but the exciting rookie missed only half a practice on Wednesday. He practiced full on Thursday and Friday and should be ready to roll against the Lions. The Bears (11-5) currently hold the NFC’s No. 2 playoff seed. They can secure their position with a win. Should they lose, and the Eagles (11-5) beat the Commanders (4-12), the Bears would slip to the No. 3 seed. Burden is a top-25 wide receiver for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-802c-d35e-a1bf-c5eef25b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) is questionable to play in Week 18 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8032-dc7a-af9b-cfbf731f0000</link>
      <description>We do not expect Odunze to play. He aggravated the stress fracture in his foot during pre-game warmups in Week 15, after logging three limited sessions during the week. Odunze has been sidelined ever since and only resumed practicing, in a limited capacity, today. He would be a very risky FLEX option if the Bears allow him to take the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8032-dc7a-af9b-cfbf731f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (rib) won’t play in New York’s Week 18 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803b-d56e-afff-e6fb2e1c0000</link>
      <description>Robinson enters free agency off his first career 1,000-yard season, shedding his label as a quick-game only option by setting a career-high with 11.0 yards per reception. He turns 25 in a few days and will be one of the premiere free agents at wideout to hit the market if the Giants don’t tag him or otherwise extend him. The final seasonal line will be 92/1014/4 for Robinson, and his absence leaves Darius Slayton as a fine FLEX play in Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803b-d56e-afff-e6fb2e1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (illness) won’t play in New York’s Week 18 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803e-d968-a19b-d8ff3d6d0000</link>
      <description>Two weeks missed with an illness is rather unusual. We hope Johnson is alright and the story about the illness isn’t too gruesome. Johnson returned five touchdowns with a 45/528 line, becoming more involved with the offense when Jaxson Dart took over against the Chargers in Week 4. It’s possible that Johnson exits the 2026 offseason with a TE1 case, but he feels more like a high-end TE2 from where we sit today. His absence in Week 18 gives Daniel Bellinger a chance to feast against Dallas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803e-d968-a19b-d8ff3d6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants OL Evan Neal (neck) won’t play in New York’s Week 18 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8041-d968-a19b-d8f1eb140000</link>
      <description>He ended the year on injured reserve. Neal didn’t play a single game all season after disappointing in the second and third years of his rookie deal. The former seventh overall pick will be a free agent this year and could pick up some interest from teams who want to see if they can turn his career around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8041-d968-a19b-d8f1eb140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed DT John Jenkins to a $2.1 million, one-year extension through 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803c-d35e-a1bf-c5fe31ae0000</link>
      <description>Jenkins entered the NFL as a third-round pick in 2013. He informed reporters that, despite being a 13-year veteran, he has played on 11 consecutive one-year deals via free agency. He was reportedly “excited” to hear the news that the Ravens wanted to keep him from hitting free agency again. We are, too. At the time of signing, Jenkins has totaled 24 tackles, 10 quarterback pressures and one sack this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-803c-d35e-a1bf-c5fe31ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Charlie Jones (ankle) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 18 game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8045-d56e-afff-e6ed731d0000</link>
      <description>Jones has been a special-teamer only for the Bengals, falling well behind Mitchell Tinsley on the depth chart this year. He managed 20 offensive snaps and 106 special-teams snaps as a returner. Entering the final year of his rookie deal, Jones is not worth rostering in fantasy leagues, but has been a solid core special teamer for the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8045-d56e-afff-e6ed731d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Los Angeles would activate Tyler Higbee (ankle/IR) ahead of Week 18’s game against the Cardinals “barring any setbacks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8047-d35e-a1bf-c5c7be880000</link>
      <description>It’s back to a four-man tight end room for Los Angeles’ three-TE sets, probably nerfing Colby Parkinson’s Week 18 fantasy value in the process. Higbee has been on IR since Week 11’s win over the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8047-d35e-a1bf-c5c7be880000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
