<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dalton (right thumb) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3149-d4ed-a9de-77cffdef0000</link>
      <description>Bryce Young practiced in full after missing Week 8 with an ankle injury. All signs point to Young drawing the start in Week 9 against the Packers. Superflex managers can safely send Dalton back to the waiver wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3149-d4ed-a9de-77cffdef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers RT Taylor Moton (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-314d-d48c-ad9f-fd4d7e510000</link>
      <description>Moton left the Panthers’ Week 8 loss to the Bills with the knee issue and did not return. A DNP to start the week puts him on the wrong side of questionable for Sunday’s game against the Packers. Yosh Nijman will take his spot in the lineup if he can’t suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-314d-d48c-ad9f-fd4d7e510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Caroll said Brock Bowers (knee) is practicing at full speed for Week 9 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3153-d4ed-a9de-77dfb1b80000</link>
      <description>Carroll told reporters he is “thrilled to have him back.” Carroll may have been talking about getting Bowers back at practice, but it certainly sounds like he will also have his star tight end for Sunday’s game against the Jags. We expect Bowers to be listed as a full participant on the Raiders’ first injury report of the week. Bowers suffered a PCL injury and a bone bruise in Week 1. He played through it for a few games but was eventually shut down. Once officially cleared to play, Bowers will reclaim a spot at the top of the TE1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3153-d4ed-a9de-77dfb1b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin re-injured his quad and will not play in Week 9 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-315e-de12-a19e-377e00250000</link>
      <description>Quinn is confirming what we all knew. McLaurin re-aggravated the quad issue while making a diving catch down the sideline in the fourth quarter. He did not return after suffering the injury. McLaurin initially missed four weeks because of the quad injury. Week 8 was his first game back. At this point, it’s hard to say when McLaurin will be back on the field, but it may not be for a while. In the meantime, Luke McCaffrey and Chris Moore will start in three-receiver sets for Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-315e-de12-a19e-377e00250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald said S Julian Love (hamstring) suffered a setback and his availability for Week 9 against the Commanders is in jeopardy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3178-d48c-ad9f-fd7d48e80000</link>
      <description>Macdonald said injured reserve could be a consideration for Love. That all but guarantees he won’t play this week. He will likely be out much longer than just one game. Love has appeared in three games this year, logging one sack and two pass breakups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3178-d48c-ad9f-fd7d48e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets acquired WR John Metchie and a 2027 sixth-round pick from the Eagles in exchange for CB Michael Carter and a 2027 seventh-round pick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3176-d4ed-a9de-77fe490b0000</link>
      <description>Metchie provides the Jets with much-needed depth in the pass-catching corps, and there is a chance he starts in Week 10, post-bye. Jets No. 1 WR Garrett Wilson has been sidelined by a knee injury, forcing the team to rely on wide receivers like Allen Lazard, Arian Smith, Josh Reynolds and Tyler Johnson. Metchie would be tough to trust as a FLEX option right away, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3176-d4ed-a9de-77fe490b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze (heel) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3182-d4ed-a9de-778ec4a00000</link>
      <description>Odunze was one of the few bright spots for the Bears amidst a blowout loss to the Tyler Huntley-led Ravens last week. He totaled 114 yards on seven grabs, including three gains of 20 or more yards. He didn’t appear to be hampered by a heel injury, though it could have popped up late in the game or after the contest entirely. Either way, the Bears could be without multiple starting wide receivers in Week 9. In addition to Odunze, DJ Moore, Olamide Zaccheaus, and Luther Burden all missed Wednesday’s practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3182-d4ed-a9de-778ec4a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Moore (groin/hip) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3187-d48c-ad9f-fdcf58970000</link>
      <description>Moore has been dealing with hip and groin issues for a few weeks. They haven’t cost him any playing time yet, and a DNP on Wednesday is standard practice for him at this point. Until told otherwise, we expect him to play this week. He could be tasked with a larger role on Sunday versus a soft Cincinnati defense. Rome Odunze, Olamide Zaccheaus, and Luther Burden all missed today’s practice. Moore looks like the most likely to suit up for Week 9, though it’s too early to say definitively who will play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3187-d48c-ad9f-fdcf58970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden (concussion) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-318a-d321-a5bf-b3df2e1a0000</link>
      <description>Bears head coach Ben Johnson confirmed on Monday that Burden is in the league’s concussion protocol. A DNP means he is in the earliest phases of the protocol, making it unlikely for him to be cleared before Sunday’s game. Burden has pitched in for the occasional splash play this year but has failed to unseat Olamide Zaccheaus for the No. 3 role in Chicago. Fantasy managers can finally cut bait on him if he is inactive this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-318a-d321-a5bf-b3df2e1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (hip) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3189-d321-a5bf-b3dffdf10000</link>
      <description>This is an unfortunate development for a player who has already dealt with an ankle injury and a concussion this season. Downs sat out Week 7 with the latter issue, but sandwiched his absence with two WR2 finishes in half-PPR scoring. His practice participation must now be monitored closely. The Colts face the Steelers’ fantasy-friendly defense in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3189-d321-a5bf-b3dffdf10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
