<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Bryant (hamstring) is practicing in full for Week 16 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e78-d1bc-a3fb-af7c1c910000</link>
      <description>Bryant missed Week 15 because of the hamstring issue. A full practice means he should be ready to return in Week 16 against the Jags. Bryant had quietly flipped Troy Franklin for the No. 2 role in Denver before being forced to sit last week. He should return to that role on Sunday, but Franklin did just go for 85 yards and a touchdown for the Packers. His latest spike week could complicate things in Denver’s receiver rotation. With the fantasy semi-finals on tap, this is a situation managers should likely avoid for at least one week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e78-d1bc-a3fb-af7c1c910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey (ribs) is practicing in full for Week 16 against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e7f-d005-a9bf-fe7f706a0000</link>
      <description>Harvey left Week 15 with the rib injury late in the fourth quarter. He did not return, though there was barely any time left on the clock when he was officially listed as questionable. He should be good to go for Week 16. Per usual, Harvey will sit in the top half of the RB2 ranks versus the Jags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e7f-d005-a9bf-fe7f706a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks LT Charles Cross (hamstring) will not play in Week 16 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e82-d8cf-affb-beaab8590000</link>
      <description>Cross injured his hamstring on Seattle’s walk-off field goal versus the Colts last week. He did not practice this week before being ruled out, putting his availability for Week 17 in doubt as well. Josh Jones will be the next man up at left tackle for the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e82-d8cf-affb-beaab8590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e8d-d005-a9bf-febd7cb80000</link>
      <description>Crosby has been playing through the knee issue for a while. We don’t expect this week to be any different at this time. The star defender has 10 sacks, two forced fumbles, and an interception this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e8d-d005-a9bf-febd7cb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e8d-d77b-adfb-ee8f1b6c0000</link>
      <description>Chubb missed Week 15 against the Cardinals due to a rib injury he suffered in Week 14. He practiced once in a limited fashion last week and starts out Week 16 practicing in a limited fashion again. With Woody Marks (ankle) not practicing, Chubb may be in line to share the backfield with Jawhar Jordan against the Raiders on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e8d-d77b-adfb-ee8f1b6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e93-d1bc-a3fb-afb76edb0000</link>
      <description>Marks suffered an ankle injury during the Texans’ Week 15 win over the Cardinals and did not return with Houston holding a large lead. Head coach DeMeco Ryans said Monday that Marks should be fine, but the rookie begins the week not practicing. It could just be load management, but fantasy managers should roster Jawhar Jordan just in case. Jordan would share the backfield with Nick Chubb in the event Marks cannot go in Week 16 against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e93-d1bc-a3fb-afb76edb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (oblique) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e9b-d1bc-a3fb-afbff2c80000</link>
      <description>Though he has played in every game this season, Stingley dealt with the oblique issue early on and now misses the first practice of Week 16 because of it. The 24-year-old has played through it before and certainly can again with some practice time later this week. Fellow CB Kamari Lassiter (foot) also missed practice, though he played through the injury in Week 15. Stingley and Lassiter still have a good chance of playing Week 16 against the Raiders, though practice reports later in the week will provide a clearer picture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2e9b-d1bc-a3fb-afbff2c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is doubtful for Week 16 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea1-d77b-adfb-eea326130000</link>
      <description>Adams did not practice at all this week and is listed as doubtful for Thursday’s game against the Seahawks. He re-aggravated his hamstring injury on Sunday and returning on a short week was always going to be a tough task, despite the fact that Sean McVay refused to completely rule Adams out. Fantasy managers can expect to be without Adams for Week 16, boosting Puka Nacua even further and giving Colby Parkinson some viability in the red zone. The only other Ram listed on the team’s injury report is DE Braden Fiske, who is questionable with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea1-d77b-adfb-eea326130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris (hip) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea7-d8cf-affb-beaf7b140000</link>
      <description>Harris popped up on the injury report with a hip issue, though he still practiced in a limited capacity. The rookie has been used sparingly this season, but did bring in three passes for 49 yards with Quentin Johnston out in Week 15. Harris and Johnston (groin) are both limited Wednesday while WR/KR Derius Davis (ankle) did not practice. The Chargers’ wide receiver depth is mildly banged-up heading into Week 16 against the Cowboys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2ea7-d8cf-affb-beaf7b140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC WR Makai Lemon has declared for the 2026 NFL Draft.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2eb2-d1bc-a3fb-afb697c40000</link>
      <description>Lemon enters draft season as one of the country’s top wide receiver prospects. He finished junior year at USC with 79 receptions for 1,156 yards and 11 touchdowns, winning the Fred Biletnikoff Award for nation’s most outstanding receiver. The 21-year-old announced his intention to declare for the 2026 NFL Draft on social media, foregoing his remaining year of eligibility. Lemon has a chance to be the first USC wide receiver since Jordan Addison in 2023 to be selected in the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2eb2-d1bc-a3fb-afb697c40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
