<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Tee Higgins (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb43-d005-a9bf-fb77941d0000</link>
      <description>He’s not completely out of concussion protocol yet, but this is a great sign about his chances of playing on Sunday against the Bills. It’s an upgrade from a limited session on Wednesday. Higgins would be an easy WR2 despite how the Bills invite the running game with Joe Burrow back feeding Higgins the rock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb43-d005-a9bf-fb77941d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB MarShawn Lloyd (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3e-d77b-adfa-ebbf77db0000</link>
      <description>Lloyd was placed on injured reserve due to a hamstring injury. He is, almost unbelievably, now rehabbing a calf injury. Lloyd is a very capable player, but he is tough to trust as a bench stash at this point. Fellow backup RB Emanuel Wilson has proven himself as a reliable backup, and he would likely be in line to start if Josh Jacobs were to miss time. Stashing Lloyd is a bet on talent, not health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb3e-d77b-adfa-ebbf77db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot/shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb44-dce4-a1da-fb56084e0000</link>
      <description>We were hoping to see Reed upgrade to full participation. He still has a chance to play, but one imagines the Packers will ask him to practice fully before allowing him to retake the field after a prolonged absence. It all comes down to Friday’s official injury report. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb44-dce4-a1da-fb56084e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-dce4-a1da-fb5e7ade0000</link>
      <description>The Packers continue to limit Wicks’ practice reps after a busy Week 13 showing against the Lions, in which Wicks caught 6-of-7 targets for 94 yards and two touchdowns. He seemingly injured his left ankle on one of his touchdown grabs, but it did not slow him down. We expect Wicks to play in Week 14 against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-dce4-a1da-fb5e7ade0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Rashod Bateman (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb51-d77b-adfa-ebd303a40000</link>
      <description>Bateman was already off the FLEX radar, given his recent play and the Ravens’ struggles. His downgrading only furthers that notion. Bateman still has a chance to play, but he is clearly still rehabbing his high-ankle sprain. Having him on the field would at least be helpful for QB Lamar Jackson (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb51-d77b-adfa-ebd303a40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Dylan Sampson (calf) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb56-d005-a9bf-fb7672150000</link>
      <description>Sampson appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 14 against the Titans, elevating RB Jerome Ford to the No. 2 role. Ford does not need to be in fantasy lineups, having lost his job to Sampson earlier this year with ineffectual play. Expect Quinshon Judkins to handle a sizable workload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb56-d005-a9bf-fb7672150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb5c-d77b-adfa-ebdfbcaf0000</link>
      <description>Njoku continues to play through his knee injury as rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr.'s fantasy-unfriendly backup. Njoku does not need to be rostered in re-draft formats, though he technically could be considered one of the rare tight end stash options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb5c-d77b-adfa-ebdfbcaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints RB Alvin Kamara (knee/ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb74-dce4-a1da-fb763e720000</link>
      <description>It sure looks like rookie RB Devin Neal will start for the Saints once again. Kamara has not practiced since spraining an MCL in Week 12 against the Falcons. The team chose not to put Kamara on injured reserve, so we expect him to return either in Week 15 or Week 16. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb74-dce4-a1da-fb763e720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RT Jawaan Taylor (triceps/knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-d005-a9bf-fb7c98050000</link>
      <description>Taylor picked up the triceps injury in Week 13 against the Cowboys. He has missed both practices since then. The Chiefs are already without LT Josh Simmons (wrist) and RG Trey Smith (ankle) has also been sidelined over the last two days. The Chiefs face the Texans’ elite pass-rush unit on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb4c-d005-a9bf-fb7c98050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars LT Walker Little (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb79-dce4-a1da-fb7fec930000</link>
      <description>Little remains sidelined for the Jaguars’ second practice, putting Week 14 availability even more in doubt than it was yesterday. He is backed up by versatile OG Cole Van Lanen. The Jaguars face a Colts defender missing DT DeForest Buckner (neck) this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eb79-dce4-a1da-fb7fec930000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
