<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins (concussion) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e579-d90e-a9da-ff7fd5d00000</link>
      <description>Higgins remains in the league’s concussion protocol. He went down with the brain injury in Week 12 and was forced to miss the team’s Thanksgiving win over the Ravens. A limited practice puts him on track to return this week, but he will need to get in a full session before clearing the league’s protocol. Assuming that happens, Higgins will return to a WR2 ranking against the Bills this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e579-d90e-a9da-ff7fd5d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison Jr. (heel) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e57e-d316-abff-f7ff67f80000</link>
      <description>MHJ could return later in the session and receive a limited designation on the official report, though we doubt he will get in any work today. Harrison Jr. went down with a heel injury late in the Cardinals’ Week 13 loss to the Bucs. He was spotted on the sidelines getting ready to return, but the team ultimately held him out for the remainder of the game. He now appears to be on the wrong side of questionable for Week 14. Michael Wilson totaled 25 catches for 303 yards in the two games MHJ missed a few weeks ago. He would return to the top of the WR2 ranks if Harrison Jr. is out versus the Rams this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e57e-d316-abff-f7ff67f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Benson (knee) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e583-d316-abff-f79309c50000</link>
      <description>Head coach Jonathan Gannon was noncommittal when asked about Benson’s status. The young back appeared to be nearing a return from injured reserve last week, but he was downgraded to a DNP on Thursday and was ruled out the following day after another missed practice. It’s possible he suffered a setback during practice. Needless to say, it doesn’t look like he will be back in the lineup this week. Emari Demercado was back at practice today, giving him a shot to suit up on Sunday after missing last week’s game with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e583-d316-abff-f79309c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Marks (foot) was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e58b-d6c4-abfb-f78bf1bb0000</link>
      <description>Marks left Week 13’s game with a foot injury but did eventually return. He finished the day with 19 attempts for 64 yards. This could just be a rest day for a banged-up player. It could also be an indication that Marks was running on adrenaline on Sunday and may be more injured than he or the team thought. Tomorrow’s practice report will be more informative. Nick Chubb would take over the Houston backfield if Marks misses Week 14, though it would be hard to treat him as anything other than a low-end RB3 versus the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e58b-d6c4-abfb-f78bf1bb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e596-d90e-a9da-ff9fc46a0000</link>
      <description>Sampson went down with a calf injury during the third quarter of Week 13. He was initially listed as questionable to return. The Browns eventually downgraded him to out. A DNP today means he will likely miss at least one game because of the issue. Jerome Ford will take over the low-value RB2 role in Cleveland this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e596-d90e-a9da-ff9fc46a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills LT Dion Dawkins (concussion) was limited on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5a0-d90e-a9da-ffaf802f0000</link>
      <description>Bills RT Spencer Brown (shoulder) also upgraded to limited. Both players were sidelined for the entirety of Week 13. The Bills face the Bengals’ pushover pass-rush unit in Week 14. Although the offense can likely get by without their starting offensive tackles, having them on the field would give Buffalo a significant edge in the trenches. Bills LB Terrel Bernard (elbow) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5a0-d90e-a9da-ffaf802f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5b6-d6c4-abfb-f7b754830000</link>
      <description>Rodgers sat out last Wednesday’s practice as well. He practiced fully on Thursday and Friday before taking the field on game day. He also injured his nose in Week 13 against the Bills, which we imagine is quite sore. Barring a setback, Rodgers will take on the Ravens this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5b6-d6c4-abfb-f7b754830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Xavier Restrepo (ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5ab-db57-afda-f7bb92e70000</link>
      <description>Restrepo’s absence is unsurprising. The rookie wide receiver was carted away from the field after injuring his ankle in the Titans’ Week 13 loss to the Jaguars. Restrepo has caught 3-of-6 targets for 41 yards this season. He does not need to be rostered in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5ab-db57-afda-f7bb92e70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Pickens (calf/knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c1-db57-afda-f7f310470000</link>
      <description>Pickens was limited during Monday’s practice but never appeared to be at risk of missing tomorrow’s game. He played through the pair of issues on a short week in Week 13 and went for 88 yards versus the Chiefs. In a shootout spot with the Lions, Pickens and CeeDee Lamb are both in the WR1 ranks for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c1-db57-afda-f7f310470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys LT Tyler Guyton (ankle) will not play in Week 14 against the Lions</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c5-d90e-a9da-ffcf3a920000</link>
      <description>Guyton went down with a high-ankle sprain in Week 12 and missed the following game on Thanksgiving. Nathan Thomas will continue to start at left tackle this week. Though he will be a clear weak point for the Cowboys, that shouldn’t stop their offensive machine from rolling versus Detroit. Trevon Diggs was not activated from injured reserve and is also out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e5c5-d90e-a9da-ffcf3a920000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
