<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:17:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ reports Rashee Rice was accused of “violent and abusive behaviors” in a lawsuit filed by the mother of two of his children.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7150-d89c-a1be-ffdffcc10000</link>
      <description>Dacoda Jones this week reportedly filed a lawsuit accusing Rice of “choking, strangling, scratching, hitting, and headbutting” Jones over a 19-month period. The lawsuit also says Rice broke furniture and punched holes in walls during arguments with Jones. Much of the violent behavior occurred while Jones was pregnant, according to the lawsuit. Rice’s alleged violence caused “bleeding, swelling, bruising, and other pain and physical injury to her neck, face, mouth, arms, legs, chest, and shoulder,” according to the lawsuit. Jones had previously accused Rice of abusive behavior in social media posts. This is Rice’s most recent run-in with the law after he fled the scene of a major automobile accident last offseason and was suspended by the NFL for the first six games of the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7150-d89c-a1be-ffdffcc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals signed former University of Texas defensive coordinator Pete Kwiatkowski as new defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-71ed-d990-a1de-7def227c0000</link>
      <description>This marks Kwiatkowski’s first forray into the NFL ranks after nearly three decades of coaching college football. Kwiatkowski joined Steve Sarkisian in Texas five years ago as the team’s defensive coordinator. After a rough first year, Kwiatkowski’s defenses never finished worse than 28th in the country in points allowed over the following four seasons. The Longhorns fielded the third-best scoring defense in 2024. Kwiatkowski was fired after his unit took a slight step back in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-71ed-d990-a1de-7def227c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports the Dolphins “have had trade talks with teams regarding” S Minkah Fitzpatrick.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7229-d89c-a1be-ffff3ec60000</link>
      <description>Fitzpatrick returned to Miami in 2025 as part of the deal that sent Jalen Ramsey to Pittsburgh. He appeared in 14 games, totaling six pass breakups and one interception. Fitzpatrick also added one sack and two fumble recoveries. The Dolphins have already made the decision to release Tyreek Hill and Bradley Chubb to save cap space. They will almost certainly take a deal to move Fitzpatrick if it gives them more ammunition in the draft. This is shaping up to be a true reset season for Miami.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7229-d89c-a1be-ffff3ec60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans offensive coordinator Brian Daboll said Cam Ward was a “big factor” in taking the Titans’ offensive coordinator job.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7275-d990-a1de-7e7fd9130000</link>
      <description>Daboll praised both Ward’s athleticism and accuracy when discussing the second-year passer. Ward occasionally flashed big-play potential as a rookie, but he spent most of his debut campaign missing passes and taking sacks. Defenses took him down behind the line of scrimmage a league-high 55 times. He completed just shy of 60 percent of his passes. Daboll has had success with young quarterbacks in the past. He coaxed a playoff berth out of Daniel Jones in 2022 and oversaw a handful of solid performances from Jaxson Dart in 2025 before the Giants canned him. Daboll has a tall order ahead of him, but quarterback has become a late-bloomer position in recent years, with Caleb Williams serving as the poster child for a post-rookie rebound. Titans fans will be hoping for a similar turnaround from Ward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7275-d990-a1de-7e7fd9130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams re-signed OT David Quessenberry to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7287-d629-a1bc-f29f51660000</link>
      <description>Quessenberry signed a one-year deal with the Rams last offseason to fill a backup role. He appeared in 13 regular season games, seeing most of his work on special teams. He will take on a similar role in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7287-d629-a1bc-f29f51660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers re-signed OT Nick Zakelj to a one-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72a7-d042-afbc-7ff799de0000</link>
      <description>Zakelj spent the 2025 season on San Francisco’s practice squad. He was called up for three games, seeing a handful of snaps on offense and special teams. Zakelj will be battling for a roster spot this summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72a7-d042-afbc-7ff799de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RG Wyatt Teller announced he will be leaving the team in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72dd-d89c-a1be-ffdfe82a0000</link>
      <description>Teller made a heartfelt post to the city of Cleveland and its fans on social media to say his goodbyes. All five starting offensive linemen for the Browns are set to hit free agency, and now at least one of them will not be back. At 31 years old, the three-time Pro Bowl guard should have plenty of suitors in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72dd-d89c-a1be-ffdfe82a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed said he “would love to come back” to the Seahawks next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7309-d629-a1bc-f31d28540000</link>
      <description>Shaheed is set to enter free agency this offseason after spending a half-season with the Seahawks. The 27-year-old was traded from the Saints to Seattle at the trade deadline and tallied 15 receptions for 188 yards in nine games for the Seahawks, adding three receptions for 78 yards in the playoffs. He most notably was a return specialist for the team, returning a kick for a touchdown to open the Seahawks’ Divisional Round win over the 49ers. When asked if he would consider a return, Shaheed said, “I kind of want to run it back. We just won the Super Bowl, so, you know, why not?” Though his offensive role was minimalized in Seattle’s offense, Shaheed has value as deep threat and return specialist. Expect him to generate much interest during free agency in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7309-d629-a1bc-f31d28540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports the Broncos are expected to hire Bills quarterbacks coach Ronald Curry as their wide receivers coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7377-d629-a1bc-f37f6a370000</link>
      <description>Curry also interviewed for the Broncos’ offensive coordinator vacancy and now lands in Denver as the wide receivers coach. He spent the past two seasons as the Bills’ quarterbacks coach, working with Josh Allen and company under Joe Brady. Curry previously worked as an offensive assistant under Sean Payton with the Saints earlier in his career, now returning to Payton’s staff to work with Courtland Sutton, Pat Bryant, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-7377-d629-a1bc-f37f6a370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson announced he will return for a 14th NFL season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72e5-d042-afbc-7ff714a20000</link>
      <description>Johnson told The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane the news on Thursday morning. The potential Hall of Famer missed the second half of the 2025 season with a Lisfranc injury, though it shouldn’t affect him for the upcoming season. The 2026 season will mark his first without offensive line coach Jeff Stoutland, who stepped down from the role at the end of the year. With Philly’s 2025 season going down as a bit of a dud, 2026 might be a one last ride situation for the veteran tackle. The hope is that a change at offensive coordinator revives the team’s explosive plays on the ground and through the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-72e5-d042-afbc-7ff714a20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
