<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Theo Johnson (shoulder) is not on New York’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fcb-d713-ad9e-7fdf88df0000</link>
      <description>Neither is Daniel Bellinger. Johnson will be a fringe TE1 this week against a beleaguered Bears defense. Bellinger’s playing time hasn’t been consistent enough to believe in him as more than a TE2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fcb-d713-ad9e-7fdf88df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants K Graham Gano (neck) won’t play in New York’s Week 10 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd1-d713-ad9e-7fd50fd90000</link>
      <description>He didn’t practice all week and is likely questionable for Week 11. Gano will yield way to Younghoe Koo at kicker in Week 10. Koo is a decent streamer against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd1-d713-ad9e-7fd50fd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints ruled out OT Taliese Fuaga (ankle) against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fc2-d713-ad9e-7fd6d1e50000</link>
      <description>The Saints’ depleted offensive line is in rough shape. Fuaga has a long way to go in his development, having allowed 22 quarterback pressures and three sacks this season, but downgrading to his backup, OT Asim Richards, won’t be any better. They face the Panthers this weekend, who field a solid defensive tackle unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fc2-d713-ad9e-7fd6d1e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB James Cook (ankle) is not on Buffalo’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d673-a39e-ffd5835e0000</link>
      <description>He’ll play and get his usual run after practicing in full. Ray Davis waiver-claimers in shallow leagues can move on for the moment if they have a better use of a roster spot out there, though it is possible Davis gets more run than usual if the game turns into a blowout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d673-a39e-ffd5835e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills EDGE Joey Bosa (wrist) is not on Buffalo’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd8-d713-ad9e-7fdc94410000</link>
      <description>Don’t be surprised if Bosa gets rested more often than usual this week against the Dolphins — the goal is for him to make it to the postseason healthy — but this wrist doesn’t seem to be a major impediment and he should be active for Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd8-d713-ad9e-7fdc94410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers DE Derrick Brown (elbow) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd6-d673-a39e-ffd7e8de0000</link>
      <description>Brown appeared on Thursday’s injury report as a limited participant on Thursday, but successfully practiced in full on Friday. The Panthers’ star defender should have a fruitful outing against an injury-depleted Saints offensive line missing OT Taliese Fuaga (ankle) and C/OG Erik McCoy, who is on injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd6-d673-a39e-ffd7e8de0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (groin/personal) is questionable to play in Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fda-d45b-affe-5fdeaf4b0000</link>
      <description>Listed only with a groin injury, Swift was limited on Wednesday and practiced in full on Thursday. He did not practice on Friday, but was shown with a non-injury-related personal listing alongside the groin issue. No word yet on whether the personal matter will impact his availability, but he was seemingly on track to play as of Thursday afternoon. Bears No. 2 RB Kyle Monangai could have a significant role once again this weekend. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fda-d45b-affe-5fdeaf4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Odunze (ankle/heel) is not on Chicago’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe3-d713-ad9e-7ff787c70000</link>
      <description>Good to go after a full practice, Odunze figures into the WR1/WR2 range against the Giants in Week 10. He thudded last week, but the overall shape of the passing game is very encouraging for Odunze. He should be started with confidence despite the dud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe3-d713-ad9e-7ff787c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (hip/groin) is not on Chicago’s final Week 10 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe4-d673-a39e-fff5ab0e0000</link>
      <description>As per usual, he was managed but will be good to go against the Giants in what is a good FLEX spot and could perhaps be interpreted as high as a WR3 role. The Giants defense is very generous, after all. Moore is coming off his best game of the season in Week 10 with a 4/72 receiving line, one rushing touchdown, and one passing touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fe4-d673-a39e-fff5ab0e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Kyle Monangai (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 10 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d1e7-a1fa-5fffcb480000</link>
      <description>Monangai kicked off the week with a limited practice session before upgrading to full on Thursday. He remained full on Friday. Teammate, RB D’Andre Swift, logged the same participation levels on Wednesday and Thursday, nursing a groin injury, but was absent on Friday, evidently due to a personal matter. He is questionable to play, which should yield another fantasy-friendly workload for Monangai. He is on the low-end RB2 spectrum, even if Swift is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5fd5-d1e7-a1fa-5fffcb480000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
