<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7964-d713-ad9e-7d7445d50000</link>
      <description>Bateman reportedly suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 10 against the Vikings. He was spotted in a boot after the game. Ravens head coach John Harbaugh told reports on Monday that Bateman will be okay, but he didn’t say whether or not the wideout would be able to suit up in Week 11. Our best guess as of Wednesday is that Bateman will miss at least one game. His absence could mean more 2TE sets for the Ravens, putting both Mark Andrews and Isaiah Likely on the field more often.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7964-d713-ad9e-7d7445d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports C.J. Stroud (concussion) did not practice Wednesday and is still experiencing symptoms.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7968-d45b-affe-7dfe1b430000</link>
      <description>Per Wilson, Davis Mills is prepping to start in Week 11 against the Titans. Mills drew the start last week and pulled off a miraculous comeback over the Jags. The Texans scored 26 unanswered points in the fourth quarter, punctuated by a 14-yard rushing touchdown with less than a minute left on the clock. His heroics likely won’t be needed this week. Even without Stroud, Houston should have no issues handling business versus the Titans. Mills will remain buried in the QB2 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7968-d45b-affe-7dfe1b430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPRC2’s Aaron Wilson reports Davis Mills is “prepping to start” in Week 11 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee82a10000</link>
      <description>C.J. Stroud is still experiencing concussion symptoms and remains in the league’s protocol. He did not practice Wednesday. Mills threw for 292 yards and two scores in an upset win over the Jags last week. He also ran for 30 yards and a game-winning touchdown. Mills won’t be asked to do nearly as much against the lowly Titans this week. He will slot in as a low-end QB2 for Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee82a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings coach Kevin O’Connell said J.J. McCarthy is not expected to be affected in practice this week after hitting his right hand on a helmet in Week 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796f-d45b-affe-7dff8ed10000</link>
      <description>McCarthy remains in line to play versus the Bears on Sunday. The young quarterback hit his hand on a helmet while following through on a pass. He didn’t miss any time during the game. O’Connell told reporters he will wear a bandage on his hand during Wednesday’s practice. The bandage will protect a bruise on his hand, preventing it from “festering.” Gross. Still, it sounds like this will be a non-story by the end of the week. After a disappointing showing versus the Ravens in Week 10, McCarthy will be relegated to the back of the QB2 ranks for his date with the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-796f-d45b-affe-7dff8ed10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings designated C Ryan Kelly (concussion) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7976-d673-a39e-fdf715ba0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings now have a 21-day window with which to observe Kelly in practice, so he is not guaranteed to suit up in Week 11 against the division-rival Bears. His designation is positive, regardless. Kelly “will wear a new helmet model today” and will also “likely use a Guardian Cap.” He was placed on injured reserve earlier this year after suffering his second recorded concussion of the season and the fifth of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7976-d673-a39e-fdf715ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans designated TE Cade Stover (foot) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7981-d45b-affe-7d97fe180000</link>
      <description>Stover was placed on injured reserve after suffering a foot fracture in Week 1. Before the injury, he caught 4-of-4 targets for 22 yards. The second-year tight end intrigued as a rookie, though he will likely be stuck behind veteran TE Dalton Schultz in the short term, if not the rest of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7981-d45b-affe-7d97fe180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos signed WR Lil’Jordan Humphrey off the Giants’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7988-d1e7-a1fa-7beaea5a0000</link>
      <description>Humphrey appeared in all 17 games for the Broncos in 2023 and 2024. He has been active for three games in New York this year, catching four passes for 55 yards. Schefter notes that Humphrey is likely to play in Week 11. His routes are likely to come at the expense of rookie Pat Bryant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7988-d1e7-a1fa-7beaea5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons OL Storm Norton reverted to injured reserve with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-798c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee725e0000</link>
      <description>Norton underwent surgery to correct his ankle issue in late August and was thusly placed on injured reserve. His 21-day practice window was activated in Week 8, but the team has determined he is not yet ready to retake the field. His reversion to injured reserve means he will not play in 2025. Falcons head coach Raheem Morris recently gave a non-answer when asked if Norton had suffered a setback. The Falcons signed S Jammie Robinson to the practice squad and designated LB Malik Verdon to return from the non-football injury (NFI) list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-798c-d1e7-a1fa-7bee725e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rico Dowdle (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-798f-d1e7-a1fa-7befe71d0000</link>
      <description>Dowdle got Wednesday off last week as well. He was cleared from the injury report on Friday. The Panthers loaded him up with touches in Week 10. Dowdle ran 18 times for 53 yards and a touchdown. He also caught three passes for 10 yards. His DNP today is likely nothing to worry about. Assuming he suits up in Week 11, Dowdle will remain in the RB1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-798f-d1e7-a1fa-7befe71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt LaFleur said WR Romeo Doubs (chest) “should be good to go” for Week 11 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7990-d673-a39e-fd911e540000</link>
      <description>Great news. Even if Doubs takes the day off or rests on Wednesday, we expect him to practice in some capacity on Thursday and ultimately play on Sunday. Assuming this is indeed the case, the Packers’ X-wide receiver can be started as a WR3 against the Giants this weekend. He is averaging a career-best 1.70 yards per route run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7990-d673-a39e-fd911e540000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
