<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed LB Ochaun Mathis, WR Jamaal Pritchett, DB Samuel Womack, OL Liam Fornadel, and DE Paschal Ekeji to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b3-d56e-afff-f6fbfb2a0000</link>
      <description>Mathis, a 2023 sixth-rounder of the Rams, has played in 17 NFL games and 107 defensive snaps and has five tackles and a quarterback hit, as well as a forced fumble. He did play heavily on special teams in New England, so he offers some roster versatility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b3-d56e-afff-f6fbfb2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes “staffing changes” could happen in Baltimore.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b8-d35e-a1bf-d5fa58990000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are reportedly letting the emotions of their loss to Pittsburgh on Sunday night die down still, but it’s possible that Harbaugh and/or his coordinators could still be let go later this week. Josina Anderson reported that Ravens OC Todd Monken had been a name of interest for the Clemson offensive coordinator job and that “some staff changes are coming relatively soon” for the Ravens. That can only mean that we must #StayTuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b8-d35e-a1bf-d5fa58990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested permission to interview Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94cf-dc7a-af9b-dfffb3640000</link>
      <description>They’re the second team to add the Colts DC to their interview list, after the Titans. Anarumo appears to have rejuvenated his reputation after being fired in Cincinnati after 2024 in a hurry. The Colts finished 23rd in yards allowed and 21st in points allowed, with their best finish in any category being allowing only 3.9 rushing yards per attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94cf-dc7a-af9b-dfffb3640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed LB Austin Ajiake to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94d7-d968-a19b-dcf770780000</link>
      <description>An exclusive rights free agent, Ajiake had 32 tackles and played 70 percent of the Colts special teams snaps this year. He also saw some sparse time at linebacker, with 157 defensive snaps over 16 games. The Colts also agreed to terms with RB Ulysses Bentley IV, CB Wyett Ekeler, DE Viliami Fehoko Jr., G LaDarius Henderson, QB Seth Henigan, T Bayron Matos, C Jimmy Morrissey, TE Sean McKeon, S Trey Washington, WR Coleman Owen, DT Tim Smith, G Bill Murray, DE Durell Nchami, S Ben Nikkel, WR Eli Pancol and G Josh Sills on reserve/future contracts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94d7-d968-a19b-dcf770780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed WR Ja’Corey Brooks, CB Tre Hawkins, DE D.J. Johnson, WR Jacoby Jones, DE TJ Maguranyanga, S Rob McDaniel, T Tim McKay, CB Darius Rush, CB Car’lin Vigers, G Sala Aumavae-Laulu and DT Ricky Barber to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94db-dc7a-af9b-dfffa1f70000</link>
      <description>In case you’re wondering, it’s not former Texans/Ravens wideout Jacoby Jones, but a wholly different Jacoby Jones who came out of UCF as an undrafted free agent in 2025. This Jones ran a 4.68s 40-yard-dash and is more of a special teamer who hangs around the roster. Glad we could clear that up for you. And us. But mainly you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94db-dc7a-af9b-dfffa1f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens signed CB Amani Oruwariye to a reserve/futures contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94f5-d56e-afff-f6fd7bc70000</link>
      <description>The former Lions starter has bounced around between the Jaguars, Cowboys, and Ravens the last three seasons. He’ll be cornerback depth for Baltimore in 2026. The Ravens also signed T Gerad Christian-Lichtenhan, WR Cornelius Johnson, DT David Olajiga, G Jared Penning, DB Marquise Robinson, DE Kaimon Rucker and RB Lucas Scott to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94f5-d56e-afff-f6fd7bc70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins requested an interview with Chargers assistant GM Chad Alexander for their general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9502-d968-a19b-ddf334e60000</link>
      <description>Alexander, who came over from the Jets to join former Ravens charge Joe Hortiz, interviewed for the Raiders and Jaguars jobs in the 2025 offseason. The Dolphins continue to grow their general manager interview pool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9502-d968-a19b-ddf334e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested permission to interview Ravens OC Todd Monken for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-950b-d56e-afff-f7eb8caa0000</link>
      <description>It’s probably a little more surprising than it would have been at this time last year, as Monken’s offense struggled while Lamar Jackson dealt with injuries. Still, Monken has a good reputation as an offensive play-caller and the Browns would definitely seem to be leaning in the direction of either a CEO coach or offensive mind so they could retain DC Jim Schwartz. The Ravens finished 11th in offensive DVOA despite Jackson’s injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-950b-d56e-afff-f7eb8caa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested to interview 49ers DC Robert Saleh for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9512-dc7a-af9b-dfbf40370000</link>
      <description>It’s the first request for Saleh this year. For a brief shining moment ahead of the firing of Jaguars GM Trent Baalke, Saleh was the favorite there in 2025 after interviewing well. He also interviewed for the Cowboys vacancy in the 2025 offseason. The 49ers have been besieged with defensive injuries in 2025, losing stars Nick Bosa and Fred Warner for most of the season, but have been respectable in spite of that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9512-dc7a-af9b-dfbf40370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals requested permission to interview Dolphins DC Anthony Weaver for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9516-d35e-a1bf-d5d658a30000</link>
      <description>It is Weaver’s second request of the cycle after he drew one from the Falcons yesterday. Miami’s defensive coordinator has been a finalist for the Saints, Commanders, and Falcons over the past couple of offseasons. Weaver certainly seems worthy of a chance to be a head coach at this point. We’ll see if he can become a favorite for anyone else this offseason. The Dolphins finished 24th in defensive DVOA last year with a skeleton crew defensive backs room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9516-d35e-a1bf-d5d658a30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
