<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 21:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed RB Jeff Wilson, formerly of the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-952c-d05a-adda-bfaeb74b0000</link>
      <description>Wilson, 29, has spent the last 2.5 seasons in Miami after being dealt to the Dolphins during the 2022 trade deadline. Since then, the veteran back has struggled with injuries and an inability to find consistent playing time in a Dolphins backfield that has been ripe with young, explosive talent. Wilson’s signing comes after the 49ers lost Isaac Guerendo (shoulder) for"a few weeks” and rookie Jordan James to a broken finger. Both running backs could have a chance to be ready for the start of the season, but they’ll be cutting it close. Wilson spent five seasons playing with the Niners in Kyle Shanahan’s system and can provide a sense of familiarity to the backfield. Wilson rushed for 57 scoreless yards on 16 carries last season and shouldn’t be viewed as a permanent fixture on the 49ers’ roster once Guerendo and James are able to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-952c-d05a-adda-bfaeb74b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden caught two of three targets for 29 yards in the Bears’ preseason game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9552-d90d-a5bd-b75b9b790000</link>
      <description>The second-round rookie saw early work with the second-team offense and led all Bears pass-catchers with three targets during his limited time on the field. His most notable play came on a third and 13, when he converted a first down on a 16-yard reception. Burden is expected to contribute early in three-receiver sets for the Bears, but may struggle to earn significant targets as long as D.J. Moore and Rome Odunze are healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9552-d90d-a5bd-b75b9b790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcasters covering the Bears’ preseason Week 1 game against the Dolphins said the team is taking CB Jaylon Johnson’s (leg) health, “day by day, week by week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9562-df63-a199-dd6bfe800000</link>
      <description>The Bears reportedly have “no concerns” about the injury, due to Johnson’s rigorous rehab, but the team representative avoided directly answering the broadcaster’s question regarding Johnson’s Week 1 availability. Johnson’s health is worth following closely. The Bears will have an extremely difficult time covering Justin Jefferson if Johnson is not on the field come Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9562-df63-a199-dd6bfe800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker III (undisclosed) did not practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9563-df63-a199-dd6b52b70000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports that Seahawks coaches were unavailable for comment after practice. Walker was sidelined by a sore foot earlier in training camp. Zach Charbonnet is one of fantasy football’s most valuable bench stashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9563-df63-a199-dd6b52b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed RB Brittain Brown, formerly of the Seahawks, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9584-df63-a199-ddaf88470000</link>
      <description>The Bears need extra depth with Roschon Johnson sidelined by a foot injury. Brown has not played an offensive snap in the NFL. He last contributed on special teams with the Raiders in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9584-df63-a199-ddaf88470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions signed RB Deon Jackson, formerly of the Jets, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-958d-d45c-a7fc-979f75d70000</link>
      <description>The Lions also signed OG Gunner Britton, OG Keaton Sutherland, TE Gunnar Oakes, and correspondingly placed OT Justin Herron, OL Colby Sorsdal and TE Kenny Yeboah on season-ending injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-958d-d45c-a7fc-979f75d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said WR Konata Mumpfield (ankle) won’t miss any time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-959a-d05a-adda-bf9a08160000</link>
      <description>Great news. Mumpfield earned McVay’s praise with his “smart and conscientious” play last week. It will be difficult for him to make his way onto the re-draft radar this year but he is a name to know for dynasty leagues. McVay adds that RB Ronnie Rivers (ribs) and TE Anthony Torres (ankle) will both miss “a little bit of time.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-959a-d05a-adda-bf9a08160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colston Loveland caught 1-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 1 game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a5-d05a-adda-bfa7e2950000</link>
      <description>Loveland blocked for a moment before shucking off his defender and running a delayed route. He turned upfield after securing the pass and absorbed contact in his surgically repaired right shoulder. He promisingly hopped up after the tackle and appeared no worse for wear. He remains a low-end TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a5-d05a-adda-bfa7e2950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai rushed six times for 30 yards and returned one kickoff for 22 yards in the Bears’ preseason Week 1 game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a9-d05a-adda-bfab7f440000</link>
      <description>Monangai had the first two drives all to himself and played all but one snap on the third. He rotated in and out through drives four and five. Monangai ran well, forcing two missed tackles on the ground. The No. 3 running back role behind D’Andre Swift and Roschon Johnson (foot) appears to be his.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95a9-d05a-adda-bfab7f440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Stephen Holder said Colts CB Kenny Moore II “seemed to be in pretty intense pain” after suffering an apparent knee injury on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95b4-d90d-a5bd-b7ff97bc0000</link>
      <description>That’s bad. Moore is the secondary’s lynchpin defender, lining up on the perimeter in base formations and covering the slot in nickel. Losing him for an extended time period would make the Colts’ secondary one to target in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-95b4-d90d-a5bd-b7ff97bc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
