<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/ribs) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb17-def2-abdb-df775d5b0000</link>
      <description>Jennings often plays through injuries when he is able to practice in a limited capacity. He did so earlier this year, practicing only on Friday in Week 2 and went on to catch 5-of-10 targets for 89 yards and one touchdown. Situations can change quickly, but for now, fantasy managers should expect Jennings to play in Week 6 against the Buccaneers, operating as his team’s No. 1 wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb17-def2-abdb-df775d5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared DT Jalen Carter (heel) inactive for Week 6 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb24-def2-abdb-df6579080000</link>
      <description>Carter was added to the injury report yesterday, so his absence is hardly surprising. The Eagles’ defense is a talented unit overall, but losing one of the best defensive linemen in football is a big deal. The Giants will likely attack the Eagles’ interior defensive line via an aggressive rushing attack. The Eagles also declared LG Landon Dickerson, TE Grant Calcaterra, CB Mac McWilliams and WR Xavier Gipson inactive for Week 6 against the Giants. On the plus side, LB Nakobe Dean (knee) will make his 2025 debut tonight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb24-def2-abdb-df6579080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Giants declared WR Darius Slayton, LB Demetrius Flannigan-Fowles, LB Swayze Bozeman, OT James Hudson III, OL Evan Neal, DL Elijah Garcia and QB Jameis Winston inactive for Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb2f-d94a-a79d-cb2f832f0000</link>
      <description>The Giants are expected to rely on two-tight end sets with Malik Nabers (knee) out for the year, and Slayton sidelined in the short term. TE Daniel Bellinger led the team with 52 receiving yards while fellow TE Theo Johnson scored the passing game’s only two touchdowns last week. Both players should again be involved early and often, though RB Cam Skattebo will likely function as the engine of the offense against an Eagles defensive front missing DT Jalen Carter (heel).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb2f-d94a-a79d-cb2f832f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb27-dd4c-afb9-efe7bbf40000</link>
      <description>Awuzie is now on the wrong side of questionable. CB Marlon Humphrey’s calf injury and S Kyle Hamilton’s groin injury are evidently progressing, though. Hamilton’s full participation puts him firmly on track to play in Week 6 against the Rams. The Ravens have been a fantasy-friendly unit thus far. Improved health would go a long way toward reversing course. LB Roquan Smith (hamstring) also remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb27-dd4c-afb9-efe7bbf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR Zay Flowers (shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb36-d94a-a79d-cb3f0c150000</link>
      <description>Flowers’ continued participation puts him on track to suit up, though playing through injury while catching passes from a backup quarterback is hardly a recipe for success. Flowers snagged a WR33 finish last week against the Texans. The Ravens face the Rams’ stout defense this week, keeping Flowers stuck in WR3 land, assuming he is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb36-d94a-a79d-cb3f0c150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Tutu Atwell (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb44-dd4c-afb9-efc5c2ef0000</link>
      <description>A mid-week addition to the injury report is never good. This all but guarantees that Atwell strained his hamstring in practice. Fantasy managers should expect to be without the field-stretching wide receiver this week, as the Rams take on the Ravens in Week 6. WR Jordan Whittington should hog No. 3 duties this week, though he will likely only be viable in DFS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb44-dd4c-afb9-efc5c2ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caf9-d94a-a79d-cbfd96110000</link>
      <description>Higbee and backup TE Colby Parkinson (concussion) were both limited today. Getting one or more back for the Rams’ Week 6 game against the Ravens would be helpful for Matthew Stafford’s fantasy prospects, though neither tight end could reliably be started as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-caf9-d94a-a79d-cbfd96110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Brock Bowers (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb4c-dd4c-afb9-efcd895d0000</link>
      <description>Bowers has now missed four straight practices and appears to be heading toward his second missed game. On the plus side, Raiders No. 2 TE Michael Mayer (concussion) continues to practice in full. He should handle starting duties with Bowers expectedly sidelined against the Titans and can be started as a streaming TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb4c-dd4c-afb9-efcd895d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence (quad) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb50-dd4c-afb9-efd1daa20000</link>
      <description>Lawrence’s potential return would significantly improve the Seahawks’ odds of slowing the Jaguars’ capable rushing attack. Unfortunately, S Julian Love (hamstring) and CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) remain sidelined and CB Riq Woolen (concussion) remains limited, indicating he failed to progress to the next phase of the NFL’s concussion protocol today. Seahawks OLB Derick Hall (oblique) is not expected to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb50-dd4c-afb9-efd1daa20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Chris Godwin (fibula) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb47-d94a-a79d-cb4fd3290000</link>
      <description>Godwin’s new fibula listing is concerning. The veteran wide receiver fractured his fibula when he dislocated his ankle last year, but the team had been listing him with an ankle designation up until last week. It is entirely possible that this is just precautionary, or even some sort of clerical error, but it is also possible that he suffered a re-injury. Hopefully, he resumes practicing on Friday. In the meantime, make a backup plan. The official injury report later confirmed that Godwin did not practice on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cb47-d94a-a79d-cb4fd3290000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
