<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL competition committee co-chairman Rich McKay said the committee has received zero requests to ban the tush push thus far this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87a2-d89c-a1be-afff08a90000</link>
      <description>Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts fumbled on a tush push attempt in Philadelphia’s 24-15, Week 13 loss to the Bears. He told reporters after the game that it is “becoming tougher and tougher” to run the play. Teams are having more success against it, defensively, than they did previously, while others have begun successfully running it themselves. Several teams turned to using it with tight ends, most notably Seahawks TE AJ Barner moonlighted as a tush push quarterback this season. Barner picked up one touchdown and nine first downs on 11 rushing attempts across the full NFL season. Connor Heyward (Steelers) and Cade Stover (Texans) also ran the play a non-trivial amount of times in 2025. It is still possible for teams to submit a ban proposal, but at this point, McKay does not “envision it” happening this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87a2-d89c-a1be-afff08a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins reports that “the Cowboys are “in talks” with K Brandon Aubrey about a long-term contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87cb-d990-a1de-efcfed280000</link>
      <description>Aubrey’s agent, Todd France, and the Cowboys have been in talks “for some time,” and Cowboys owner Stephen Jones confirmed that the two sides have been exchanging contract offers. Jones is seemingly intent on keeping Aubrey, saying the Cowboys will “tender him before the deadline” if they have to. Aubrey has earned Pro Bowl honors in each of the last three seasons. He was a first-team All-Pro in 2023 and was a second-team All-Pro in 2024 and 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-87cb-d990-a1de-efcfed280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Seahawks plan to sign WR Jaxon Smith-Njigba and CB Devon Witherspoon to contract extensions this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8788-d89c-a1be-afdf244f0000</link>
      <description>Smith-Njigba led the NFL with 1,793 receiving yards en route to Offensive Player of the Year, first-team All-Pro and Pro Bowl honors this season. He turned 24 years old earlier this month and believes he deserves to be the highest-paid wide receiver in the NFL. Smith-Njigba’s teammate, and fellow 2023 first-round draftee, Witherspoon also took home Pro Bowl and second-team All-Pro honors this year. Witherspoon should end up being handsomely paid as well, though it is unclear whether he is a candidate to reset the positional market. ESPN’s Brady Henderson notes that the Seahawks can exercise a fifth-year option on both contracts by May 1, giving all involved extra time to negotiate long-term deals if need be. Were the Seahawks to make Smith-Njigba the NFL’s highest-paid wide receiver, the contract would average more than $40 million per year in new money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8788-d89c-a1be-afdf244f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dallas Morning News’ Calvin Watkins believes that if the Cowboys use the franchise tag on WR George Pickens, there is a “strong possibility he will not report to the offseason programs.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8806-d89c-a1be-afdf60c30000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys are currently expected to use the franchise tag on Pickens. While a tag-and-trade scenario is possible, Watkins adds that “both sides have mutual interest in the star receiver returning.” Star players have had contentious negotiations with the Cowboys’ front office in recent seasons, including QB Dak Prescott, WR CeeDee Lamb and EDGE Micah Parsons, who was ultimately traded to the Packers. A speedy resolution would allow Pickens to join his teammates for offseason training without injury-related contract concerns looming overhead. And a more typical Cowboys resolution would leave us questioning if Pickens will even be on the team in August, putting a black cloud over his potential fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8806-d89c-a1be-afdf60c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Colts and Daniel Jones have been in discussions to sign a multi-year deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8abd-d042-afbc-ffff31bf0000</link>
      <description>We last heard that the two sides planned to speak soon. Now, as we prepare for combine week in Indianapolis, Pelissero reports the two sides have begun discussions and that a multi-year deal is on the table. There’s mutual interest on both sides to get a deal done, but Pelissero said any hold up in a deal will likely center around a number that “makes sense” for a multi-year deal. Jones suffered a leg injury late in the season that was followed by a torn Achilles in Week 14. Prior to going down, Jones was playing some of the best ball of his career, throwing for 3101-19-8 while completing 68.0 percent of his passes. If they are unable to reach a deal before the franchise tag deadline, it’s possible the Colts will tag Jones to buy themselves more time to get a deal in place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8abd-d042-afbc-ffff31bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essentially Sports’ Tony Pauline reports the “overwhelming belief” from people he has spoken to is that the Dolphins favor signing free agent QB Malik Willis.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b35-d990-a1de-ef7f7fa40000</link>
      <description>It’s not a typical source for us, but what Pauline is reporting aligns with the already widely-held belief that newly minted head coach Jeff Hafley and general manager Jon-Eric Sullivan, who were previously with the Packers, would pursue Willis in free agency. Pauline also notes that many believe Willis will ultimately sign with the Cardinals, who are expected to move on from Kyler Murray. Willis had a solid two-year stint with the Packers and flashed in limited action. So much so, that he’s expected to sign a multi-year deal this offseason and be the unquestioned QB1 for a team in 2026. Willis threw for 972-60-0 on 89 pass attempts in two seasons with the Packers while adding another 42-261-3 on the ground. Wherever he signs, his next team will hope the tremendous improvement he showed in a small sample size will translate into long-term success for him and their organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b35-d990-a1de-ef7f7fa40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essentially Sports’ Tony Pauline reports Dolphins OC Bobby Slowik “is a big fan of Quinn Ewers.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b49-d89c-a1be-afdf24e20000</link>
      <description>According to Pauline, Ewers could be the Dolphins’ preferred option at QB in 2026 if the team is unable to sign Malik Willis this offseason. Ewers threw for 622-3-3 in four games with the Dolphins last season while making three starts. The rookie seventh-rounder was also sacked eight times on just 31 pressures and fumbled the ball three times. Slowik and the Dolphins could have limited options available to them to improve their QB room this offseason, so it wouldn’t be surprising if Ewers did work his way into the starting lineup if the Fins are unable to land their preferred option at QB in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b49-d89c-a1be-afdf24e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports the Jets “would like to sign Breece Hall to an extension” this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b5c-d629-a1bc-bb5d72ae0000</link>
      <description>Cimini notes that this would be the ideal situation for the Jets, while also pointing out that Hall has “been dropping hints for months that he might want to move on” from Gang Green. Hall’s impending free agency includes a handful of scenarios that could play out. While he could re-sign with the Jets outright, it’s also possible the team lets him walk, uses the franchise tag to keep him in place and potentially buy time for a long-term deal or a trade, or they could use the transition tag which allows Hall to seek other deals while giving the Jets the right of first refusal to match any offer Hall may receive. Hall would be a coveted running back on the open market, and has bell cow back traits that allow him to stay on the field for all three downs. He’ll only be 25 at the start of this season, and has appeared in 16 or more games in each of the last three seasons since tearing his ACL as a rookie in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b5c-d629-a1bc-bb5d72ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones said the team will place the franchise tag on George Pickens some time next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b81-d990-a1de-efcff4850000</link>
      <description>All signs have pointed to the Cowboys tagging Pickens before the deadline to do so, but whether that results in him staying with the team on a long-term deal remains in question. Jones said the team thinks “the world” of Pickens and wants him to stay a Cowboy, but declined to comment on when an extension could get done. Pickens enjoyed a career year in 2025, catching 93 passes for 1,429 yards and nine touchdowns — all career-highs. His pairing with CeeDee Lamb made for one of the most dynamic receiver duos in the league, but for the right price, it’s possible the Cowboys opt to tag and then trade Pickens for draft picks to improve their roster elsewhere. We’ll have a better sense on where things are headed after Pickens is tagged, but things could be setting up for a long offseason of negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8b81-d990-a1de-efcff4850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Falcons plan to use the franchise tag on TE Kyle Pitts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8ba6-d629-a1bc-bbbf69d30000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, the plan “is to work out a long-term deal” rather than force Pitts to play on the tag. If he does play on the tag, the veteran tight end would receive a guaranteed $15 million next season. Pitts had his best season as a pro in 2025, posting career-highs in receptions (88) and receiving touchdowns (5) while also totaling 928 receiving yards. The 25-year-old playmaker struggled to live up to the lofty expectations he set as a rookie in 2021 when he went for 68-1026-1, but his breakout performance last season made him a player the new regime hopes to hang out to for the foreseeable future. Pitts and the Falcons now have until July to hammer out a new contract before playing on the tag becomes a real possibility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8ba6-d629-a1bc-bbbf69d30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
