<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons requested permission to interview 49ers director of scouting and football operations Josh Williams for their “president of football” position.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9483-d56e-afff-f6ebe1cb0000</link>
      <description>“President of football” being a very silly term aside, reporters have made it clear that the Falcons want to check the box on this job before they get to their GM and head-coaching vacancies. Williams has already been requested for the Dolphins GM position and was a finalist for the Jaguars GM position last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9483-d56e-afff-f6ebe1cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets coach Aaron Glenn, asked if Justin Fields would be back in 2026, said “he’s under contract.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9488-d35e-a1bf-d5ca02c50000</link>
      <description>So, probably not then. Fields enters year two of a two-year contract as either a trade possibility or a candidate for release. The trade would save more cap space for the Jets, so we’d expect them to pursue that avenue. Fields would still be a fairly good backup quarterback option for most teams even if he hasn’t delivered great results as a starter. The 2021 first-rounder turns 27 in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9488-d35e-a1bf-d5ca02c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said he doesn’t anticipate any changes to his coaching staff in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-948c-d968-a19b-dcfd73510000</link>
      <description>In other words, embattled DC Al Golden has survived. This seemed impossible in November, when the Bengals were putting up numbers that generated WOAT discussion in the field of defensive performance. Things did turn around a bit towards the end of the season. We can’t say we’re surprised that the Bengals retained Golden, because they are reluctant to make major changes to a fault, but it is definitely a bold move by Taylor to attach his coaching future to what happened to this defense in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-948c-d968-a19b-dcfd73510000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs waived QB Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9493-d968-a19b-dcf37d230000</link>
      <description>Buechele was signed off the Bills practice squad ahead of Week 18 and completed 7-of-14 passes for 88 yards against the Raiders in a game that neither team seemed to want to win. His reward was being waived. The Chiefs also signed LB Kam Arnold, DT Marcus Harris, WR Jimmy Holiday and T Matt Waletzko to reserve/future deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9493-d968-a19b-dcf37d230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears designated CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b1-dc7a-af9b-dfbf90480000</link>
      <description>His 21-day practice window is open, though this is pretty clearly a four-day runway to get him ready for Saturday. Gordon has played just three games this year, Weeks 6 and 7, as well as Week 13, while struggling through a long-term injury. If healthy, he’d be a huge addition. The key words there are “if healthy.” The Bears also opened OT Braxton Jones’ 21-day window, though he might only make the roster as a backup at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b1-dc7a-af9b-dfbf90480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets signed LB Ochaun Mathis, WR Jamaal Pritchett, DB Samuel Womack, OL Liam Fornadel, and DE Paschal Ekeji to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b3-d56e-afff-f6fbfb2a0000</link>
      <description>Mathis, a 2023 sixth-rounder of the Rams, has played in 17 NFL games and 107 defensive snaps and has five tackles and a quarterback hit, as well as a forced fumble. He did play heavily on special teams in New England, so he offers some roster versatility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b3-d56e-afff-f6fbfb2a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo believes “staffing changes” could happen in Baltimore.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b8-d35e-a1bf-d5fa58990000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are reportedly letting the emotions of their loss to Pittsburgh on Sunday night die down still, but it’s possible that Harbaugh and/or his coordinators could still be let go later this week. Josina Anderson reported that Ravens OC Todd Monken had been a name of interest for the Clemson offensive coordinator job and that “some staff changes are coming relatively soon” for the Ravens. That can only mean that we must #StayTuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94b8-d35e-a1bf-d5fa58990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants requested permission to interview Colts DC Lou Anarumo for their head-coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94cf-dc7a-af9b-dfffb3640000</link>
      <description>They’re the second team to add the Colts DC to their interview list, after the Titans. Anarumo appears to have rejuvenated his reputation after being fired in Cincinnati after 2024 in a hurry. The Colts finished 23rd in yards allowed and 21st in points allowed, with their best finish in any category being allowing only 3.9 rushing yards per attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94cf-dc7a-af9b-dfffb3640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts signed LB Austin Ajiake to a one-year contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94d7-d968-a19b-dcf770780000</link>
      <description>An exclusive rights free agent, Ajiake had 32 tackles and played 70 percent of the Colts special teams snaps this year. He also saw some sparse time at linebacker, with 157 defensive snaps over 16 games. The Colts also agreed to terms with RB Ulysses Bentley IV, CB Wyett Ekeler, DE Viliami Fehoko Jr., G LaDarius Henderson, QB Seth Henigan, T Bayron Matos, C Jimmy Morrissey, TE Sean McKeon, S Trey Washington, WR Coleman Owen, DT Tim Smith, G Bill Murray, DE Durell Nchami, S Ben Nikkel, WR Eli Pancol and G Josh Sills on reserve/future contracts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94d7-d968-a19b-dcf770780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed WR Ja’Corey Brooks, CB Tre Hawkins, DE D.J. Johnson, WR Jacoby Jones, DE TJ Maguranyanga, S Rob McDaniel, T Tim McKay, CB Darius Rush, CB Car’lin Vigers, G Sala Aumavae-Laulu and DT Ricky Barber to reserve/future contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94db-dc7a-af9b-dfffa1f70000</link>
      <description>In case you’re wondering, it’s not former Texans/Ravens wideout Jacoby Jones, but a wholly different Jacoby Jones who came out of UCF as an undrafted free agent in 2025. This Jones ran a 4.68s 40-yard-dash and is more of a special teamer who hangs around the roster. Glad we could clear that up for you. And us. But mainly you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-94db-dc7a-af9b-dfffa1f70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
