<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:08:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Hurts completed 24-of-33 passes for 283 yards, one touchdown and an interception in the Eagles’ 34-17, Week 6 loss to the Giants, adding seven carries for 13 yards and a second score.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc2a-d94a-a79d-cd2faa720000</link>
      <description>Hurts’ 283 yards passing were a new season high for the second time in five days, but it would be inaccurate to say he had a great night slinging it. He missed DeVonta Smith on a wide-open, should-have-been 89-yard score, and tossed a ghastly red zone interception as the Eagles were trying to mount a second half comeback. Under pressure, Hurts made the wrong read and failed to see CB Cor’Dale Flott jumping the route. Hurts was lucky it wasn’t a pick-six, though Flott still managed to return it 68 yards. The “passing” score Hurts did convert was more of a Dallas Goedert rushing touchdown. Hurts’ ground score, naturally, came via “tush push.” Mediocre as a passer of late as his rushing production has decreased over the past two weeks, Hurts does not have a bounce-back Week 7 spot in a Minnesota road trip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc2a-d94a-a79d-cd2faa720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Goedert caught 9-of-11 targets for 110 yards and a touchdown in the Eagles’ Week 6 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc2f-db72-a199-fe6ff3f50000</link>
      <description>The catches, targets and yards were all new season highs, though the touchdown was Goedert’s fifth in the past four games. Although it goes in the books as a three-yard receiving score, it was really more of a Goedert rushing touchdown on a broken trick play. With Jalen Hurts struggling to get his chemistry on track with A.J. Brown and DeVonta Smith, Goedert for whatever reason has been the beneficiary. Who knows if the Eagles actually want that to continue, but then again, it’s one of the only things working. Healthy and in the midst of one of the more productive stretches of his career, Goedert will be an easy TE1 for Week 7 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc2f-db72-a199-fe6ff3f50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley rushed 12 times for 58 yards in the Eagles’ Week 6 loss to the Giants, adding two receptions for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc35-dd4c-afb9-eff54f6b0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a 30-yard dud against the Broncos, Barkley bettered that on the Eagles’ first two plays from scrimmage, churning up 31 yards on two carries. So needless to say, it was surprising when he was shut down for the rest of the evening by a highly-suspect Giants run defense. It didn’t help that the G-Men were leading 13-3 after 10 minutes. Having now failed to clear 60 yards rushing in four straight games, Barkley is in a certified slump. For Week 7, he will be facing a Vikings defense more vulnerable on the ground than through the air, but that was also true of the Giants. This is just a struggling offense right now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc35-dd4c-afb9-eff54f6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.J. Brown caught 6-of-9 targets for 80 yards in the Eagles’ Week 6 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc39-dd4c-afb9-eff90dfe0000</link>
      <description>Brown’s six receptions tied a season high, while his 80 yards were his second most. He also notched a 30-yard reception, just his second of the year. All decent enough developments, but these shouldn’t be notable milestones for a superstar wideout. This is a struggling offense right now, and AJB is bearing the brunt of it. Jalen Hurts seems more comfortable throwing to Dallas Goedert and DeVonta Smith. Although it’s tempting to think that could be some kind of reaction to Brown’s moaning about not getting the ball, the reality is that Brown faces the toughest coverage and is the toughest target to hit for a quarterback currently struggling through the air. Things don’t figure to get a whole lot better against Brian Flores’ pass defense in Week 7, but perhaps Philly can burn gambling Flores on some of his riskier calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc39-dd4c-afb9-eff90dfe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVonta Smith caught 4-of-5 targets for 49 yards in the Eagles’ Week 6 loss to the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc3e-def2-abdb-dd7f01970000</link>
      <description>That’s already a disappointing statline before you learn Jalen Hurts missed Smith for what should have been a walk-in, 89-yard touchdown. It’s just been that kind of year for Philadelphia’s passing game. Smith also appeared to tweak his left leg, but he received minimal medical attention and was never announced with an injury. If he’s sore tomorrow, he will still have nine more days to rest up for Week 7 against the Vikings. A secondary target in an offense struggling for big plays through the air, Smith is more of a WR3 than WR2 until further notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc3e-def2-abdb-dd7f01970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 6-of-7 targets for 84 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc40-db72-a199-fe4b6cd00000</link>
      <description>Robinson’s 84 yards were his most since Week 2 and second most of the season. He finally had a big day in Malik Nabers’ absence. His touchdown was a 35-yarder where Jaxson Dart got outside the pocket, improvised, and found Robinson. The wideout then broke a tackle near the goal line to secure the six points. The Giants are trying to limit their passing volume as Dart learns the NFL game — and keeps calling his own number as a rusher — but Robinson will continue to see the most of it. He’s more of a top-40 option than true WR3 ahead of Week 7 against the Broncos, but Robinson can be justified in most fantasy lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc40-db72-a199-fe4b6cd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 2-of-4 targets for 27 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc43-d94a-a79d-cd4f613b0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a two-score Week 5 and generating some fantasy buzz, Johnson had a quiet night in a huge Giants upset victory. One of his missed connections was a rough third down drop. Despite the recent scoring binge (three TDs between Weeks 4-5), Johnson has still yet to surpass 34 yards receiving. He’s established a bare-minimum floor but hasn’t really hinted at a ceiling ahead of Week 7 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc43-d94a-a79d-cd4f613b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyrone Tracy rushed four times for six yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc46-dd4c-afb9-efc73a3c0000</link>
      <description>Active for the first time since Week 3 as the G-Men pulled off a stunning upset victory, Tracy got out-touched 21-4 by Cam Skattebo, who generated 110 yards from scrimmage and three touchdowns. Pro Football Focus charted Tracy as playing just 21 snaps to Skattebo’s 49. Four touches is probably Tracy’s absolute floor, but it’s tough to say he’s a 1B back at this time. Skattebo has taken over the backfield, and Tracy is a second-tier contingency back as a fumbler in an offense that would be wary of giving him big workloads in the event of a Skattebo injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc46-dd4c-afb9-efc73a3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil’Jordan Humphrey caught 4-of-8 targets for 55 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc49-db72-a199-fe4b3ae60000</link>
      <description>Elevated from the practice squad with Darius Slayton sidelined with a hamstring injury, 27-year-old journeyman Humphrey somehow matched a career high with his eight looks. Several of them came in the end zone, where Humphrey unfortunately committed a drop. He also drew a defensive holding call. We’re sure the Giants were happy with the effort from a role player on short notice, but this could easily be the last time all year you hear Humphrey’s name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc49-db72-a199-fe4b3ae60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalin Hyatt caught 3-of-5 targets for 17 yards in the Giants’ Week 6 win over the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc4c-def2-abdb-dd6d66320000</link>
      <description>Yet to catch a pass on three targets this season coming into this evening, Hyatt got more run with Darius Slayton (hamstring) sidelined. Unfortunately, he got out-targeted 8-5 by practice squad elevation Lil’Jordan Humphrey. Hyatt also had something of an end zone drop that thankfully resulted in a DPI call that set the Giants up for a one-yard Cam Skattebo touchdown. In theory a big-play threat who could be a little livelier down the stretch as this offense perks up with Jaxson Dart under center, the reality is Hyatt seems extremely unlikely to ever make re-draft fantasy noise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-cc4c-def2-abdb-dd6d66320000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
