<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers re-signed LS J.J. Jansen to a one-year deal.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</link>
      <description>The long-time snapper of snaps longer than the average snap will enter his age-40 season with the Panthers in 2026. Jansen has played in every single game of Panthers football since signing with the club as a UDFA in 2009. He has recovered one fumble and made one Pro Bowl. He also has snapped many, many balls a moderate distance away from his person in an attempt to set up some good punts and kicks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cee-d990-a1de-6ceed25d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Vic Tafur believes “it seems like the 49ers have big plans for second-year player Jordan James.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</link>
      <description>It’s an interesting assertion because James rarely played this year, starting the season with a wrist injury and eventually playing only three offensive snaps in three active regular season games. However, James did close out the Divisional Round loss to the Seahawks with six carries for 28 yards and it appears he could seize the No. 2 role behind Christian McCaffrey if Brian Robinson walks in free agency. Isaac Guerendo, per Tafur, “seems like an easy cut” if Robinson returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d629-a1bc-fcffab340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis believes Mac Jones “checks more boxes for what the Vikings are looking for” than the other potentially available quarterbacks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d01-d042-afbc-7dd3eeb60000</link>
      <description>Yes, we are again banging the drum that the 49ers may get an offer they can’t refuse for Jones, who has only $1 million in guaranteed salary in 2026 and could be a major upgrade for the Vikings over J.J. McCarthy. Lewis believes the 49ers will “drive a hard bargain” for Jones. As has been rumored for a bit, it would likely take a Day 2 pick for the 49ers to move on from Jones, and perhaps a second-rounder rather than a third-rounder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d01-d042-afbc-7dd3eeb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reports the Vikings “removed most of [their] over-the-middle passing concepts throughout the season” to keep J.J. McCarthy’s line of sight “simple.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d09-d89c-a1be-efdfab780000</link>
      <description>The depths of the McCarthy struggles last year were obvious, but the fact that the Vikings didn’t even trust him to do some fairly remedial work adds another layer to just how fractured this offense was. It’s almost impossible to imagine McCarthy winning a starting job against whoever the Vikings bring in this offseason. In fact, with Kwesi Adofo-Mensah fired, it’s probably not far-fetched to suggest that McCarthy could be available in a trade if another team still believes in him. If he stays in Minnesota, McCarthy is an easy fantasy football fade in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d09-d89c-a1be-efdfab780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s Albert Breer believes Jim Schwartz could come back as the Eagles defensive coordinator in 2027.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d1f-d990-a1de-6d5f649d0000</link>
      <description>Schwartz, who resigned from the Browns defensive coordinator job in early February after Todd Monken was named head coach, is set to take the year off with all defensive coordinator chairs filled. Vic Fangio appears to be very “year to year” with the Eagles at this point and contemplated stepping down this offseason. Schwartz’s deal with the Browns has a club option for 2027 that may require compensation in return, but Breer believes he will be the “belle of the defensive coaches’ ball” in 2027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d1f-d990-a1de-6d5f649d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Enquirer’s Kelsey Conway reports the Bengals will gather information from other teams about Trey Hendrickson’s market at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</link>
      <description>The Bengals have left open the option to trade Hendrickson through the franchise tag, but that seems like a really unrealistic scenario on paper. Hendrickson would, after being tagged back-to-back years, be guaranteed a $30.2 million salary in 2026. He could simply sign the tag and likely do better for himself than he would on the free market. This feels a lot like the Vikings trying to drum up a market for Sam Darnold in a tag-and-trade last year — if a team can’t afford to tag the player and simply keep him, it’s hard to believe that a trade will come to fruition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d2d-d042-afbc-7dffa8420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec believes Tyler Linderbaum “appears primed” to eclipse Creed Humphrey as the league’s highest-paid center in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d89c-a1be-efffca0a0000</link>
      <description>Linderbaum is expected to have a strong market, in other words. The two natural landing spots will be a return to Baltimore and a reunion with coach John Harbaugh in New York, though neither are exactly flush with cap space. Linderbaum has posted PFF grades above 74.6 in all four of his seasons and is a strong run blocker despite being undersized. He’ll turn 26 in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6cfb-d89c-a1be-efffca0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec reports the Ravens have made “no progress” in their efforts to extend Isaiah Likely.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d3e-d990-a1de-6d7e88ff0000</link>
      <description>When the Ravens surprisingly re-upped Mark Andrews in-season, it seemed to point to the idea that Likely could leave in free agency. This report only accentuates that. Turning 26 in April, Likely would seem to be one of the few free agent tight ends (perhaps alongside Chig Okonkwo) with any real starter upside. Zrebiec believes “he should do quite well” in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d3e-d990-a1de-6d7e88ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Josh Kendall believes it’s “hard to imagine” the Falcons will be able to bring back Tyler Allgeier.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d42-d042-afbc-7dd2635d0000</link>
      <description>Allgeier will probably be one of the highest-regarded backs on the market, and Kendall notes that the Falcons can’t afford to give him starting running back money behind Bijan Robinson. Allgeier could wind up in a terrific fantasy situation this year — the Chiefs and Texans (our speculation) are two rooms he could step into as the lead back easily with real upside — and could find himself in the RB2 tier in the right landing spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d42-d042-afbc-7dd2635d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt believes the Jets could release Justin Fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d4e-d89c-a1be-efdf54210000</link>
      <description>Fields would incur a $22 million dead cap hit and save the Jets only $1 million against the cap if released, and yet Rosenblatt still believes that is a likely scenario because the Jets are not lacking for cap space. Fields would likely find backup work somewhere if released, but the Jets runout appears likely to have been his final chance to cut it as a starter in the NFL. Rosenblatt also notes that it’s unlikely any team would trade for Fields at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-6d4e-d89c-a1be-efdf54210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
