<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 01:29:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots RB Terrell Jennings (knee) is active for Week 11 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fa2-d45b-affe-7fb6a4cc0000</link>
      <description>Jennings will give it a go as the Patriots’ short-yardage back, though he is tough to trust as more than a touchdown-dependent FLEX. The Patriots declared DT Joshua Farmer, G Caedan Wallace, QB Tommy DeVito, RB Rhamondre Stevenson, LB Christian Elliss, TE Austin Hooper and WR Kayshon Boutte inactive for Week 11 against the Jets. Stevenson will miss his third straight game with a toe injury, while Boutte will miss his second straight game with a hamstring injury. Last week, rookie WR Kyle Williams scored a 72-yard touchdown by catching one of his two targets. He should be rostered where available, but he makes for a zero-floor, boom-bust FLEX starter this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fa2-d45b-affe-7fb6a4cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars TE Brenton Strange (hip) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9d-d713-ad9e-7fdd0aa60000</link>
      <description>Strange is recovering from a ligament tear in his hip, suffered back in early October. His Week 11 availability remains fluid, but his continued participation is promising. The Jaguars’ wide receiver corps is banged up and underperforming. Should Strange retake the field, ready for a full complement of snaps, he has a chance to quickly return TE1 value, operating as a featured pass catcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7f9d-d713-ad9e-7fdd0aa60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7faf-d673-a39e-ffbf30850000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Mid-week downgrades are rarely a good sign. Horton may have suffered a setback and should not be expected to take the field in Week 11. In the meantime, new Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed will continue to carve out a role against the Rams this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7faf-d673-a39e-ffbf30850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers head coach Kyle Shanahan confirmed WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) will play in Week 11 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fb1-d713-ad9e-7ff51cca0000</link>
      <description>Earlier today, Pearsall told reporters that he is once again feeling like himself, though it should be noted that he remained limited at Thursday’s practice. That said, yesterday, Shanahan said that the medical staff declared Pearsall “healthy and good to go.” The 49ers’ perimeter wide receiver ranked third among NFL wide receivers with 281 receiving yards in Weeks 1-3. If he has fully regained his form, he should graduate from fantasy WR3 status to WR2 status fairly quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fb1-d713-ad9e-7ff51cca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Bam Knight (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fb2-d673-a39e-ffb374790000</link>
      <description>This backfield is a mess. Three players touched the ball, with Knight (11) leading the way. That said, backup RB Emari Demercado totaled 104 yards on just seven touches, so expecting Knight to remain the lead back could be foolhardy. Unless Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon reveals his intended positional usage, neither Knight nor Demercado can be trusted as anything more than shaky FLEX options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fb2-d673-a39e-ffb374790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders WR Tyler Lockett (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fc5-d45b-affe-7fd716090000</link>
      <description>The 33-year-old wide receiver has a balky knee. Since Lockett mostly functions as a target thief, mildly infringing upon the Raiders’ intriguing, youthful fantasy assets, fantasy managers should keep an eye on this one. Lockett is on track to play, but if he were to miss Week 11 against the Cowboys on Monday night, WR Tre Tucker could work his way onto the FLEX radar, while TE Brock Bowers and RB Ashton Jeanty steal the show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fc5-d45b-affe-7fd716090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fbd-d45b-affe-7fbffbc60000</link>
      <description>Adams leads the NFL with nine receiving touchdowns. Were the Rams to limit him at all in-game, they would likely keep him on the field in scoring position, which mostly preserves his fantasy-scoring ceiling. It would be great to see him practice in full on Friday. For now, treat him as a high-upside WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fbd-d45b-affe-7fbffbc60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Jets head coach Aaron Glenn is expected to keep his job beyond the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fc6-d673-a39e-ffd79f230000</link>
      <description>Rapoport weaved the news into a segment where he explains that the Jets “next move” is to find a franchise quarterback by using the 2026 and 2027 NFL Draft picks haul that the team acquired before this season’s trade deadline. Rapoport indicates that a franchise quarterback could be found via the draft or by trading away picks. While Rapoport’s phrasing suggests the Jets plan to acquire a franchise quarterback this offseason, it is worth noting that the segment was backdropped by a graphic showing two first-round picks and two-round picks in 2026, plus three first-round picks and one second-round pick in 2027. Rapoport narrates by saying “Glenn is expected to be there” with GM Darren Mougey, “making those picks.” Given the Jets’ 2025 failures under Glenn, we assume the first-time head coach does not actually have guaranteed job security through 2027, though Rapoport’s phrasing leaves room for interpretation. Expect Glenn to get another shot in 2026 at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fc6-d673-a39e-ffd79f230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp (hamstring/wrist) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fd0-d713-ad9e-7fd428ac0000</link>
      <description>Kupp now has two full practice sessions under his belt, albeit while swapping out his recent heel injury for a new wrist injury. The 32-year-old faces his former Rams squad this weekend and surely hopes to produce a fine stat line against them. Kupp is an WR3/4 for his revenge game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fd0-d713-ad9e-7fd428ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fd0-d45b-affe-7fd633370000</link>
      <description>Barner has been practicing in full since last Friday, which is a great sign. The Seahawks could be forced into a faster pace and a more pass-heavy game plan than in previous weeks, taking on the Rams this weekend. Barner is back on the streaming TE1 radar in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-7fd0-d45b-affe-7fd633370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
