<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:13:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 2-of-3 targets for 41 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 13 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd4d-db57-afda-df7f699a0000</link>
      <description>Slayton got the Giants on the scoreboard with a 30-yard catch-and-run touchdown in which he simply out-ran five defenders to the paint following a simple inside curl route, marking his first touchdown of the season. He would add only one other reception for 11 yards the rest of the game as rookie quarterback Jaxson Dart fed 16 combined targets to Wan’Dale Robinson and Theo Johnson. Slayton remains a shaky weekly fantasy bet that managers won’t need to worry about starting as the team heads to their Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd4d-db57-afda-df7f699a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theo Johnson caught 3-of-8 targets for 29 yards in the Giants’ Week 13 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd52-d6c4-abfb-df53b53d0000</link>
      <description>Johnson was first on the scene following a hard hit by Christian Elliss down the sideline on a Dart scramble in the first quarter, sparking a gathering of bodies near the New England bench. Unfortunately for fantasy managers, that would go down as his top contribution on the field while catching only three of his eight targets, the final incompletion of which occurred on the team’s final play from scrimmage with under a minute to play. He remains an integral part of the offense but will need to find the end zone at greater frequency before he is regarded as anything more than a top end TE2 in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd52-d6c4-abfb-df53b53d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan’Dale Robinson caught 7-of-8 targets for 34 yards in the Giants’ Week 13 loss to the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd55-d6c4-abfb-df57a5350000</link>
      <description>Robinson has seen his involvement in the offense ebb and flow as the quarterback situation has undergone multiple changes in New York this season, tasked with a more robust route tree with both Russell Wilson and Jameis Winston under center while transitioning back a short area monster to serve as a security blanket for rookie Jaxson Dart. His fantasy returns have obviously been more suppressed with Dart considering that shift in role, leaving fantasy managers with a diminishing asset in all but deep PPR leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd55-d6c4-abfb-df57a5350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Maye completed 24-of-31 passes for 282 yards and two touchdowns in the Patriots’ 33-15, Week 13 win over the Giants, adding 12 yards on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd58-d90e-a9da-df5f631c0000</link>
      <description>Chants of “MVP, MVP” rang through Foxboro at multiple points in the game as the Patriots made easy work of their former playoff rivals. Maye was denied piercing 300 yards through the air for the second consecutive game after a 30-yard touchdown throw to tight end Hunter Henry was called back for offsetting penalties late in the fourth quarter, but he looked every bit of an MVP candidate in this one. His poise in the pocket, arm strength, and decision making chops were on full display, highlighted by a 33-yard dime to the corner of the end zone to rookie Kyle Williams in the second quarter to give the team a commanding 24-7 lead. The Patriots head to their bye with the top record in the league at a sparkling 11-2, now winners of 10 straight, before a second meeting with the division rival Bills in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd58-d90e-a9da-df5f631c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreVeyon Henderson rushed 11 times for 67 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants, adding 19 yards on three receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6a-d90e-a9da-df6fc3850000</link>
      <description>The 14 touches trailed backfield mate Rhamondre Stevenson by one in an easy victory, intimating that the latter will continue to be utilized in conjunction with the electric rookie for the remainder of the season, regardless of the former’s exploits without Stevenson in the lineup earlier this season. Henderson continues to carry the greater per-touch upside but will see a muted ceiling while operating in a near-even timeshare. Stevenson gained 40 yards on 12 totes while adding 40 yards on three receptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6a-d90e-a9da-df6fc3850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Henry caught 4-of-6 targets for 73 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6e-db57-afda-df7ef14e0000</link>
      <description>Henry led the team in receiving on a night quarterback Drake Maye attempted only 31 passes due to positive game script throughout, aided by a 94-yard punt return touchdown from Marcus Jones. His fantasy day could have been much bigger had a 30-yard touchdown grab in the fourth quarter not been called back by offsetting penalties. That pass would have also pushed Maye over 300 yards through the air for the first time in his career. Henry remains a back end TE1 but will head to his bye in Week 14 before a rematch with the division rival Bills in Week 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd6e-db57-afda-df7ef14e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte caught 4-of-5 targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd71-d82c-a79a-fff5de6e0000</link>
      <description>Boutte showcased the preseason work he put in with quarterback Drake Maye with his three-yard touchdown in the first quarter, a beautifully placed fade against man coverage to the back corner of the end zone. He would not see his number called frequently from there on out considering the low total pass volume from the Patriots, highlighting his status as a true touchdown-or-bust fantasy option while the other skill position players remain healthy. His next chance to return usable counting stats comes in Week 15 against the Bills following the team’s Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd71-d82c-a79a-fff5de6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Williams caught his only target for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd75-d82c-a79a-fff502a50000</link>
      <description>The electric rookie made the most of his lone target, reeling in a 33-yard dime from Drake Maye on an over-the-shoulder catch down the sideline in the end zone to extend the team’s lead to 24-7. It was not the first time the downfield threat made a big play, but also highlights his status as a boom-or-bust fantasy asset unless there is an injury ahead of him on the depth chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd75-d82c-a79a-fff502a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMario Douglas caught all three targets for 33 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd77-d90e-a9da-df7f8d630000</link>
      <description>The diminutive receiver made the most of the opportunities he received but remains unlikely to see significant weekly volume, keeping him from legitimate consideration in fantasy circles for the time being. That said, he could be busier against the nickel-heavy Bills defense in Week 15 following the team’s Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd77-d90e-a9da-df7f8d630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefon Diggs caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Patriots’ Week 13 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd79-d82c-a79a-fffd8c700000</link>
      <description>The modest target total was primarily a product of extremely positive game script following a 94-yard punt return touchdown by Marcus Jones in the first quarter, which the team would add to before the first frame was complete. They would eventually take a 30-7 lead into the break, muting the offensive production from all skill position players in the second half. Diggs continues to operate as one of many primary contributors in an offense built around packaged mismatches, meaning he is unlikely to return elite fantasy ceiling without an injury to another skill position player. Up next for Diggs is a matchup against one of his former teams when the Patriots take on the Bills following their Week 14 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-dd79-d82c-a79a-fffd8c700000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
