<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93b5-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9f910000</link>
      <description>Johnson sustained a Linsfranc fracture in mid-November but could suit up for Wild Card Weekend, according to the Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane. “Johnson has made progress in his recovery, but still has to test his right foot before the team makes a decision on his availability for Sunday’s wild card game vs. the 49ers,” McLane said. The team’s offense fell apart with Johnson sidelined as they finished the season 3-4. The Eagles are now 18-28 in games Johnson hasn’t played during his 13-year NFL career. His presence would go a long way in helping the Philly offense find its footing in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93b5-dc7a-af9b-dfbf9f910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants general manager Joe Schoen said potential head coaching hires are “excited” about QB Jaxson Dart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93cc-d968-a19b-dbfd2f590000</link>
      <description>“From the people I’ve talked to, the consensus is that there are a lot of potential head-coaching candidates that are excited about the opportunity here because of Jaxson Dart,” Schoen said when asked about what might be appealing about the Giants head coaching vacancy after the team parted ways with Brian Daboll this season. Dart’s physicality as a runner and his refusal to run out of bounds or slide to avoid a major hit was a major concern throughout the season, as Dart suffered several brain injuries. But he was solid as a passer, completing nearly 64 percent of his pass attempts for 15 touchdowns and five interceptions over 14 games. Dart will be at the center of whatever comes next for the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93cc-d968-a19b-dbfd2f590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Charlotte Carrol reports Giants QB Russell Wilson did not tell the team about a hamstring injury he sustained in Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93f3-d35e-a1bf-d7f33e8c0000</link>
      <description>Wilson, 37, suffered what he described as a Grade 2 hamstring injury ahead of New York’s Week 2 game against the Cowboys. He said he felt he could not inform the team of the injury and kept it under wraps before throwing for 450 yards and three touchdowns against the Cowboys. “I couldn’t tell anybody,” Wilson said. “I had to go and play on it just because I knew the circumstances. I had to play on it, no matter what. I actually ended up going to the Dallas Mavericks’ facility, training. And, you know, just kept it quiet, just trying to get treatment on it and just knowing that I probably couldn’t run from the goal line to the 10-yard line if I wanted to, but I feel like, you know, I got to play that game.” Wilson lost the starting gig to Jaxson Dart, as expected, and will likely play elsewhere in 2026. Wilson said he wants to continue playing into his age-38 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-93f3-d35e-a1bf-d7f33e8c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers OG Chandler Zavala (calf) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9433-d968-a19b-dcf393280000</link>
      <description>Zavala could return from a lengthy absence for the Panthers’ Wild Card game against the Rams if he’s able to practice in the coming days. His presence would be a boon for a Carolina offense that very much wants to be run heavy, as they were when they upset the Rams in late November. Zavala’s injury status will be one to monitor ahead of the Wild Card weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9433-d968-a19b-dcf393280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Commanders and offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury mutually parted ways.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-943e-d56e-afff-f6fee1750000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury didn’t have much chance of making it to a third season at the head of Washington’s offense after the team collapsed in 2025 with Jayden Daniels missing much of the regular season with multiple injuries. Pelissero claims Kingsbury, the former Cardinals head coach, “has head coaching interest and otherwise will have multiple OC options.” Washington’s offense in 2025 was somehow 16th in EPA per play despite Daniels’ injuries (and his poor play when healthy). They were ninth in offensive success rate and 12th in yards per play, ahead of postseason teams like the Broncos, Panthers, Eagles, Chargers, Jaguars, and Steelers. The Commanders will likely hire an OC with experience getting the most out of duel-threat quarterbacks like Daniels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-943e-d56e-afff-f6fee1750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders fired defensive coordinator Joe Whitt, Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9447-d56e-afff-f6efeff50000</link>
      <description>The Commanders also parted ways with offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury after a disastrous 2025 season. Whitt, coaching one of the least talented defenses in the NFL, saw his unit get run over on the ground and through the air. Only three defenses gave up more yards per play, and only the Cardinals allowed more first downs in 2025. Washington allowed the second highest EPA per play under Whitt in 2025, and a mere three teams gave up a higher passing success rate. A first-time defensive coordinator in Washington, Whitt is not a sure thing to land another DC job in the offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9447-d56e-afff-f6efeff50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports the Giants and Titans are expected to interview former Commanders offensive coordinator Kliff Kingsbury for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-944d-d968-a19b-dcfdbf020000</link>
      <description>Kingsbury’s work with young quarterbacks is certainly a selling point for both the Giants and Titans after Kingsbury’s success with Jayden Daniels in 2024. Kingsbury’s Washington offense was surprisingly efficient in 2025 despite the team missing Daniels for much of the regular season. Washington’s offense in 2025 was somehow 16th in EPA per play. They were ninth in offensive success rate and 12th in yards per play, ahead of postseason teams like the Broncos, Panthers, Eagles, Chargers, Jaguars, and Steelers. Kingsbury would be a boon for either Jaxson Dart or Cam Ward in 2026 and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-944d-d968-a19b-dcfdbf020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Field Yates reports the Falcons and QB Kirk Cousins agreed to a “modified” final two years of Cousins’ contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-945e-dc7a-af9b-dfff39e30000</link>
      <description>The adjustments mean Cousins could stick around Atlanta for another year or two depending on what the Falcons want to do at the QB position in 2026 and beyond. Cousins, 37, showed signs of life in the season’s final month after Michael Penix was placed on injured reserve with a knee injury. He had multiple touchdowns in three of his final four games and had two games of more than 230 passing yards in the run-first Falcons offense. The contract modification could also make Cousins a trade candidate if the Falcons choose to stick with Penix as the starter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-945e-dc7a-af9b-dfff39e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos defensive coordinator Vance Joseph is expected to interview with the Giants, Raiders, Titans, and Cardinals for those teams’ head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9470-d56e-afff-f6f8f2570000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter confirmed these teams’ interest in Joseph after he coached one of the NFL’s most dominant defenses in recent memory. Over the past two seasons the Broncos have allowed the league’s lowest offensive success rate and the third lowest EPA per play. Joseph would look to revamp the defenses of any one of these teams; all of them rank among the NFL’s worst units.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9470-d56e-afff-f6f8f2570000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
