<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Nick Bosa (knee) suffered a season-ending torn ACL in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ac-d1b3-a5dd-73fdbd8a0000</link>
      <description>The 49ers had optimism last night, but this is a devastating blow. It is the same knee he initially tore the ACL in during the 2020 season. San Francisco was getting by with Bosa and some blitz packages, but now has no obvious source of pressure on the roster. Bryce Huff could be elevated beyond his situational role as the 49ers try to pick up the pieces on defense. It’s a major downgrade for their D/ST and will make their playoff climb a little steeper, even at 3-0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ac-d1b3-a5dd-73fdbd8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said they’re “evaluating everything” when asked about who will be the starting quarterback on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72b4-dfde-a1bd-7ebd6d840000</link>
      <description>It is the second time in three weeks that Daboll hasn’t really offered much of an endorsement for Russell Wilson, although he did manage a 400-yard effort against the Cowboys in Week 2. It seems like Jaxson Dart will get his chance sooner rather than later regardless of what happens this week, with the team clearly spiraling at 0-3 and Daboll needing some way to manufacture some job security. Whenever he’s elevated, Dart will need to blow the NFL away for Daboll and Joe Schoen to have any shot of keeping their jobs. The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes that “after listening to Daboll’s entire presser, they have to be making a QB change and he’s just not ready to announce it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72b4-dfde-a1bd-7ebd6d840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce has entered concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72bd-d1b3-a5dd-73fdc0000000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Pierce left Week 3’s win over the Titans with a concussion. The veteran receiver will now need to clear protocol if he hopes to play in Week 4 against the Rams, but his recent concussion history suggests he’ll miss at least one game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72bd-d1b3-a5dd-73fdc0000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports CeeDee Lamb “could miss 3-4 weeks with a high left ankle sprain.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72c5-d6a5-adff-f6c5cb910000</link>
      <description>Numerous reports continue to come in on Lamb’s ankle. In less than 24 hours, we have gone from Lamb saying he could “absolutely” play in Week 4 to the team now expecting him to miss 3-4 weeks, which always felt like the most likely outcome regardless of Lamb’s optimism. NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport later reported that the Cowboys don’t plan to place Lamb on injured reserve in case he can return inside the four games players on IR are required to miss, but it sounds like this is trending toward being a multi-week absence. George Pickens and Jake Ferguson stand to benefit the most from Lamb’s absence, with Pickens profiling as a WR2 and Ferguson a fringe TE1 in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72c5-d6a5-adff-f6c5cb910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers TE Ja’Tavion Sanders (foot) was spotted in a walking boot after Sunday’s win.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72d7-d1b3-a5dd-73f78d9f0000</link>
      <description>He was still wearing it as of Monday, despite saying that X-Rays were fine on Sunday. This will be a situation to monitor. The Panthers have been run-heavy, but Sanders hauled in 7-of-9 targets in Week 2 when they threw 55 times and would figure to be one of the team’s main pass-catchers at this point. The Panthers should update his status at some point in the next few days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72d7-d1b3-a5dd-73f78d9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RT Zach Tom (oblique) left Week 3’s game against the Browns and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72e7-d93f-ad9d-7ae707a10000</link>
      <description>He played just one snap in what was an aggravation of a previous injury that held him out of Week 2. Both Anthony Belton and Darian Kinnard got work against the Browns in what was a disappointing loss. The fact that this was a re-aggravation does make it sound like Tom may be sidelined for more than just a week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72e7-d93f-ad9d-7ae707a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers LG Aaron Banks (groin) left Green Bay’s Week 3 game against the Browns and did not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72e9-dfde-a1bd-7eedea300000</link>
      <description>He played 31 snaps before leaving at halftime, which kicked Jordan Morgan inside and got Green Bay’s other right tackles on the field to replace the similarly-departed Tom. We wouldn’t be surprised if Banks spent some time on the injury report this week at the very least. Green Bay’s offensive line injuries helped contribute to a disappointing loss against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72e9-dfde-a1bd-7eedea300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn said Jayden Daniels (knee) is still day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ef-d1b3-a5dd-73ff31980000</link>
      <description>Quinn will provide another update on Wednesday when the Commanders take the field for their first practice of the week. The team has played Daniels’ availability somewhat close to the vest, calling him “truly day-to-day” last week, only to eventually rule him out before the weekend after he failed to practice all week. We don’t fully know the severity of Daniels’ injury, leaving us to trust what the team tells us while we monitor injury reports from afar. Daniels’ practice status will be one to watch when the first report is released on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ef-d1b3-a5dd-73ff31980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kris Rhim believes the Chargers may be forced to “lean on” Omarion Hampton in a way they “didn’t anticipate in 2025.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ee-d6a5-adff-f6ef52840000</link>
      <description>With Najee Harris seemingly done for the season with an Achilles tear, the Chargers did not rotate Hampton out of the game often in Week 3. Backup Hassan Haskins played just seven offensive snaps, and did not receive a carry on any of them, while Hampton played 68 of 86 snaps. The Chargers may sign a third back off their practice squad this week, but it stands to reason that they may not be rotating Hampton out very often despite Greg Roman’s insistence that they’d do so in Week 1. The story quotes Jim Harbaugh as saying that Hampton has “picked it up and taken it on his shoulders. We’re really lucky to have him.” Bottom line: Fantasy managers who dealt with Hampton’s ugly first two weeks may be in for a dream runout if he can stay healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72ee-d6a5-adff-f6ef52840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders placed S Will Harris (fibula) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72f4-d6a5-adff-f6f5eb050000</link>
      <description>We don’t know how much time Harris is expected to miss, but the stint on injured reserve will require him to miss a minimum of four games. The Commanders already signed veteran safety Darnell Savage to provide added depth to the secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-72f4-d6a5-adff-f6f5eb050000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
