<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:02:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed RT Abraham Lucas to a three-year, $46 million contract extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-154a-de13-afdd-57cb70ff0000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo, Lucas can also earn more money via incentives. He was set for a contract year before inking the long-term deal. The former third-round pick had a solid rookie season but has since seen his career bogged down by injuries. Lucas has appeared in just 13 games over the past two seasons after taking the field for 16 starts in 2022. Lucas’s deal is relatively affordable for a starting tackle, with the incentives likely giving Lucas a chance to improve both his play and his salary over the next few seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-154a-de13-afdd-57cb70ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed K Matt Prater to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1589-de13-afdd-57cb43770000</link>
      <description>Tyler Bass is dealing with a groin injury and was limited in Wednesday’s practice. Prater will be called up from the practice squad if Bass can’t suit up for Week 1. Prater went 6-of-6 on his field goal tries with the Cardinals in 2024 before missing the remainder of the season with a torn meniscus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1589-de13-afdd-57cb43770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1590-dbe3-a9bb-35d3951a0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Brian Daboll said Thomas looked good yesterday during his limited session. It’s possible his DNP today is just maintenance or a precaution, but it’s still an ominous start to the season for Russell Wilson’s blindside protector. Jordan Hudson would enter the starting lineup if Thomas is unable to suit up for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1590-dbe3-a9bb-35d3951a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said offensive coordinator Mike Kafka will take over play-calling duties for the 2025 season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ab-db7b-a5dd-b5af81b20000</link>
      <description>The Giants rolled out a disastrous offense with Daboll calling the plays in 2024 and finished 31st in the league in points per game. They were far better off with Kafka calling plays in 2023, when they finished... 30th in points per game. Kafka called plays for the G-Men during the preseason this year, foreshadowing his return to the role. Quarterback talent has ultimately been the issue on offense, regardless of who has been calling the shots over the past couple of seasons. The Giants are hoping to solve that issue with Russell Wilson under center. If Wilson stumbles, the turn to rookie Jaxson Dart could be quicker than expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15ab-db7b-a5dd-b5af81b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins TE Darren Waller (hip) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15af-db7b-a5dd-b5af02720000</link>
      <description>Waller has now missed both of the Dolphins’ Week 1 practices. He still has a chance to turn things around by practicing tomorrow, but at this point, he should be considered a long shot to play against the Colts this weekend. If active, he would be difficult to rank as a top-24 option, positionally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15af-db7b-a5dd-b5af02720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b4-d332-a1fd-97b6c0df0000</link>
      <description>Kirk was set to play in both two- and three-wide receiver sets, as the Texans’ No. 2 wide receiver. The WR pecking order is murky behind Kirk. Day 3 rookies, WR Jayden Higgins and WR Jaylin Noel, won the Nos. 3 and 4 WR roles in camp, but late-August reports suggest Higgins could split time with WR Xavier Hutchinson. None of the backups offer a reliable floor, though Higgins is likely the best bet to return moderate FLEX value. New OC Nick Caley, a former Rams passing game coordinator, is expected to use three WRs frequently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b4-d332-a1fd-97b6c0df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (groin) returned to practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b8-de13-afdd-57fbfd390000</link>
      <description>The news puts Benford, the Bills’ No. 1 CB, on track to play in Week 1 against the Ravens. Fill-in No. 2 CB Tre’Davious White (groin) remains sidelined. The Bills’ first-round rookie CB Maxwell Hairston (knee) is eligible to return from injured reserve after four games. Stud slot CB Taron Johnson could kick outside in base formations, but the Ravens could go big-play hunting by keeping three WRs on the field while targeting the Bills’ chosen perimeter backup coverage defender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15b8-de13-afdd-57fbfd390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Keon Coleman (groin) was seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15c5-d332-a1fd-97f7878e0000</link>
      <description>Coleman was a surprise addition to yesterday’s injury report as a limited participant. We do not yet know his participation level for today’s practice, but the fact that he is able to continue practicing in any capacity is a good sign for his Week 1 availability. He is a boom/bust WR4/5 for the Bills’ Sunday Night Football bout with the Ravens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15c5-d332-a1fd-97f7878e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills WR Elijah Moore (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5c4350000</link>
      <description>Although Moore is just 25 years old, his erratic participation and performances have seemingly been ever-present for fantasy managers in football’s modern era. We do not know why he was sidelined today, but the official injury report should clarify things. He dealt with an ambiguous leg issue in July. Moore is not worth rostering at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15d5-db7b-a5dd-b5d5c4350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens TE Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15de-de13-afdd-57df5dab0000</link>
      <description>Likely appears to be highly unlikely to play in Week 1 against the Bills. He underwent surgery to correct a foot fracture on August 1st and has been sidelined ever since. Mark Andrews should command a healthy target share. Ravens FB Patrick Ricard (calf) has been sidelined since August 14th and likewise appears to be unlikely to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-15de-de13-afdd-57df5dab0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
