<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks OT Charles Cross (finger) participated in team drills on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d31b-dbe3-a9bb-f35bdf930000</link>
      <description>The occasion marks Cross’ first full-contact practice participation since late July. ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports that this “puts him ahead of [head coach Mike] Macdonald’s initial timeline and serves as an obvious indication he’ll be play[ing] in the opener.” It’s great news for Sam Darnold, who has the 49ers’ pass rush on tap in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d31b-dbe3-a9bb-f35bdf930000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans released TE Dalton Keene.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3af-de13-afdc-d7ef6b7f0000</link>
      <description>The Texans released Keene (hamstring) and waived WR Xavier Johnson (hand) from injured reserve with injury settlements. Both moves are in relation to cutdown day, coming up next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3af-de13-afdc-d7ef6b7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exhibit’s Josina Anderson reports the Vikings are “not likely” to trade for Panthers WR Adam Thielen “at this point.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3cc-de13-afdc-d7cf7ccc0000</link>
      <description>That makes two national reporters who have pumped the brakes on a potential Thielen-Vikings reunion. Both Anderson and The Athletic’s Dianna Russini highlighted the potential deal’s financial speed bumps while also stopping short of fully ruling out the trade between the two teams at some point. If the Panthers are willing to take on some of Thielen’s contract to facilitate the trade, the Vikings might be willing to make the move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3cc-de13-afdc-d7cf7ccc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals LB Demetrius Knight Jr. left practice early after suffering a “lower extremity injury” on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d361-dbe3-a9bb-f373f2250000</link>
      <description>The Bengals spent a second-round pick on Knight this offseason, and the rookie was penciled in as the team’s co-starter alongside LB Logan Wilson. The Bengals’ defense is already talent-deficient and EDGE Trey Hendrickson’s contract dispute has not yet been resolved. Bengals LB Oren Burks is Knight’s primary competition for the starting role and has had a strong camp. The injury could push the rookie into a backup role to begin the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d361-dbe3-a9bb-f373f2250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 8-of-13 for 143 yards and one touchdown and rushed once for 18 yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d46a-dbe3-a9bb-f47b823e0000</link>
      <description>Mahomes looked good, distributing the ball effectively across his receiving corps. The run game took over on the first drive once the offense entered the red zone, with Kareem Hunt getting the ball on first down before Isiah Pacheco found the end zone from two yards out on second. Mahomes notably targeted rookie RB Brashard Smith twice on the drive. Smith dropped a would-be first-down pass on 2nd-and-10 but Mahomes went back to him three plays later and the two connected for a 12-yard gain. Mahomes then led the offense to a field goal on the second drive by linking up with Tyquan Thornton for 58 yards. He made it a point to get the remaining starters involved on the third drive, which he capped off with a touchdown pass thrown to Rashee Rice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d46a-dbe3-a9bb-f47b823e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 2-of-2 targets for 13 yards and one touchdown in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3c5-dbe3-a9bb-f3d719320000</link>
      <description>Rice nearly hauled in a long pass from Patrick Mahomes on the second play from scrimmage but CB Nahshon Wright interfered, resulting in both defensive pass interference and face mask penalties. Rice scored on the Chiefs’ third drive, gaining handsy separation on an end zone fade. He’s a risky pick due to the potential suspension but when on-field, he makes a strong case for WR1 consideration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d3c5-dbe3-a9bb-f3d719320000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed three times for 21 yards and one touchdown in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d47e-db7b-a5dd-f47e0a8e0000</link>
      <description>Pacheco surrendered the Chiefs’ first touch inside the Bears’ five-yard line to Kareem Hunt, but Hunt gained just one yard and Pacheco punched it in on the following play. Pacheco looked like his normal, hard-running, speedy self in this one. Hunt’s red zone involvement is unideal but Pacheco could return RB2 value via his seventh-round ADP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d47e-db7b-a5dd-f47e0a8e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed three times for 15 yards and caught 0-of-1 targets in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d477-dbe3-a9bb-f4779f180000</link>
      <description>Hunt subbed in on the first drive, once the offense got past the Bears’ five-yard line. He immediately got the ball on an inside run but gained just one yard and was yanked in favor of Isiah Pacheco, who promptly scored from two yards out. Securing the scoring position role is likely Hunt’s path to weekly fantasy relevance. He currently profiles as a recommended bench stash with flex-potential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d477-dbe3-a9bb-f4779f180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 2-of-3 targets for 32 yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d483-de13-afdc-d6cb123c0000</link>
      <description>Kelce earned a target on the second drive and recorded his first catch on the third. The veteran tight end remains efficient at age-35, though the Chiefs clearly worked on distributing the ball as much as possible here. Kelce is once again a TE1 entering the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d483-de13-afdc-d6cb123c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 1-of-1 targets for nine yards in the Chiefs’ preseason Week 3 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d487-de13-afdc-d6cf6c910000</link>
      <description>The Chiefs focused on divvying up looks to all involved early on. Both Worthy and Travis Kelce touched the ball for the first time on the Chiefs’ third drive. Worthy looked like his typically elusive self in this one, and profiles as a high-upside WR3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-d487-de13-afdc-d6cf6c910000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
