<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd0-deb1-a39b-2dde354e0000</link>
      <description>Pearsall attempted to play through the knee issue in Week 4 but quickly re-aggravated the injury. He has been out ever since. A DNP to open the week suggests Pearsall will miss another game because of the lingering injury. Jauan Jennings and Kendrick Bourne will again operate as the team’s top wideouts. Jennings turned four catches into 31 yards while Bourne was held to 14 yards on two grabs. Fantasy managers can treat Jennings as a WR3 while Bourne is falling into the WR5 ranks ahead of San Francisco’s matchup with the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd0-deb1-a39b-2dde354e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd5-dab4-a3fb-9ff51db20000</link>
      <description>Purdy returned to practice last week for some limited work. The team still chose to sit him for their matchup with the Falcons. Head coach Kyle Shanahan said on Monday it would be “a reach” for him to play this week, though he didn’t rule Purdy out entirely. We are fully expecting to see Mac Jones under center this week. Jones has been a competent QB2 for fantasy purposes across his four starts. He will stay in that range for a tough road game against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dd5-dab4-a3fb-9ff51db20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. McCarthy (ankle) is questionable for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ddb-deb1-a39b-2ddf02c50000</link>
      <description>Head coach Kevin O’Connell has already announced Carson Wentz as the starter, so McCarthy would only be available for backup duties if he is active. We expect the QB2 role to go to Max Brosmer versus the Chargers. McCarthy will continue to rehab his ankle injury for now, getting the mini-bye from Thursday to next Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ddb-deb1-a39b-2ddf02c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Darrisaw (knee) is questionable for Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dde-d5d8-a3ff-fdffd9d70000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw was a surprise addition to the injury report on Wednesday. He was listed as a DNP and hit with the questionable tag. A late-week DNP, especially on a short week, is an ominous sign for a player. Justin Skule would likely take his place in the lineup if Darrisaw can’t suit up versus LA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0dde-d5d8-a3ff-fdffd9d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Jacobs (calf) was limited in practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0deb-d5d8-a3ff-fdeb1e5c0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs played through the calf issue and an illness in Week 7. He ceded six carries to Emanuel Wilson and logged just 13 rushes of his own but saved the day for fantasy managers with a pair of touchdowns. His workload should increase as he puts the calf issue behind him. Per usual, Jacobs is an RB1 heading into his Week 8 matchup with the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0deb-d5d8-a3ff-fdeb1e5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dontayvion Wicks (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ded-d5d8-a3ff-fdedc3130000</link>
      <description>Wicks played through an ankle issue last week but only managed one catch for five yards. With another injury on his ledger, the Packers could rest him for a week to make sure things don’t get worse. Christian Watson remained limited in practice while working his way back from the torn ACL he suffered late in the 2024 season. He has been designated to return from injured reserve and is close to making his 2025 debut. He could take Wicks’ place in the lineup this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0ded-d5d8-a3ff-fdedc3130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (hamstring) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e05-deb1-a39b-2f0fb09d0000</link>
      <description>Brown lands on the Eagles’ injury report as a non-participant due to a hamstring injury to open the week. The 28-year-old has had an up-and-down role to start the season in the low-volume Philly offense, but remains the team’s top wideout. This could be the same hamstring issue Brown dealt with before the season though the severity is unclear. Fantasy managers should stay tuned for the rest of the week; if Brown can squeeze in a limited practice, his chances to play Week 8 against the Giants will increase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e05-deb1-a39b-2f0fb09d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (calf) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e09-deb1-a39b-2f0fcfc00000</link>
      <description>Goedert was listed as a limited participant to open the week, dealing with a calf issue. He dealt with a knee issue earlier in the season, though he scored a touchdown in four straight games after returning from the injury. Goedert was at least able to practice which makes us believe this is not a serious issue. He is in the low-end TE1 mix for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e09-deb1-a39b-2f0fcfc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LB Jeremiah Trotter Jr. (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e10-deb1-a39b-2f1e00590000</link>
      <description>Trotter left the Eagles’ Week 7 game against the Vikings with the injury. EDGE Azeez Ojulari (hamstring), C Cam Jurgens (knee), and CB Adoree’ Jackson (concussion) also all left in Week 7 and did not participate in Wednesday’s practice. The Eagles defense and offensive line turn to depth options with all four players question marks for Week 8 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e10-deb1-a39b-2f1e00590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Daniel Bellinger (neck) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e18-d5d8-a3ff-ff799fe60000</link>
      <description>Bellinger was listed as a limited participant to open the week with a neck issue. The 25-year-old has become a viable target in the Giants offense with Malik Nabers out, catching a 44-yard touchdown in Week 7 against the Broncos. He is still trending to play Week 8 against the Eagles, but Theo Johnson enters the TE1 ranks if Bellinger misses time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-0e18-d5d8-a3ff-ff799fe60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
