<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers OT Tristan Wirfs (knee) is questionable for Tampa Bay’s Week 4 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86fe-d95b-addb-eefeb7e40000</link>
      <description>This has been the rumored return week for Wirfs for some time and Bucs coach Todd Bowles said things were trending in the right direction. Tampa will likely bookend him with Graham Barton, leaving them with question marks only on the interior of the line against Philadelphia’s Jordan Davis and Jalen Carter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86fe-d95b-addb-eefeb7e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans placed RB Kalel Mullings (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8702-d95b-addb-ef465a260000</link>
      <description>Mullings, who has not appeared in an offensive snap this year in two appearances, will miss at least the next four weeks. He may come back to the Titans later in the season with Tennessee looking to figure out what he can be for them in the future, but it’s hard to imagine he gets more than a committee role behind Tony Pollard and Tyjae Spears at this point. He’s not a must-keep in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8702-d95b-addb-ef465a260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (concussion) will not play in Indianapolis’ Week 4 game against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8705-d6e9-af9d-8f9535480000</link>
      <description>He did not practice all week and will enter Week 5 on the questionable line. Adonai Mitchell will get a role in the Colts offense this week and isn’t a terrible flier in deep leagues given Los Angeles’ cornerback play to this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8705-d6e9-af9d-8f9535480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he has not decided if Isaiah Likely (foot) will play in Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86fe-d95b-addb-eefe418b0000</link>
      <description>Speaking after Friday’s practice, Harbaugh said likely “looked really good,” but didn’t want to rush to commit to his fourth-year tight end returning in Week 4 against the Chiefs. Likely has logged just one week of practice, as Harbaugh pointed out to justify the possibility of sitting him one more week. Whether or not Likely plays in Week 4 should bear any weight on fantasy managers’ roster decisions. Until we see how he looks and how the team utilizes him, he’ll be hard to trust as anything more than a dart throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-86fe-d95b-addb-eefe418b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (calf) is questionable for Carolina’s Week 4 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8708-deb6-a7fd-d7df5cbe0000</link>
      <description>McMillan logged limited practices in back-to-back days after missing Wednesday’s session. Dave Canales said “we’ve got to see how he wakes up tomorrow” when asked about the ramp-up period. It sounds like McMillan is truly questionable to play in Week 4. If he misses the game, Carolina could go extremely run-heavy against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8708-deb6-a7fd-d7df5cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots HC Mike Vrabel said DC Terrell Williams has been diagnosed with prostate cancer.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-870b-deb6-a7fd-d7df09330000</link>
      <description>Williams has been away from the team since mid-September and will remain away for the time being, per Vrabel. The long-time defensive coach is in his first season with the Patriots and also spent time with Vrabel during his stint in Tennessee. Vrabel said Williams is undergoing treatment and is figuring out “the best plan of attack” to allow him to heal and return to the field. We wish him the best in his recovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-870b-deb6-a7fd-d7df09330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said Rhamondre Stevenson won’t see a playing time cut for his fumbles in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8710-deb6-a7fd-d7df2bd40000</link>
      <description>TreVeyon Henderson managers, welcome to despair. Stevenson looks like a good bet to remain head of the committee in New England, at least for this week. It seems like Vrabel simply views Stevenson’s skill set as a must for his team in spite of how much more shifty his rookie second-round back is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8710-deb6-a7fd-d7df2bd40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is questionable for New England’s Week 4 game against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8718-dca3-a9fb-bf995e9a0000</link>
      <description>Jordan Schultz reported that Gonzalez is expected to make his season debut this week. Gonzalez has missed the first three weeks with a hamstring injury that sidelined him all preseason. We’d put him on the optimistic side of questionable for this battle against Tet McMil— uh, Xavier Leg — uh, Hunter Renfrow and the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8718-dca3-a9fb-bf995e9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Conklin (elbow) is questionable for Week 4 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8712-deb6-a7fd-d7df9a1c0000</link>
      <description>Conklin missed Week 2 with an eye injury and Week 3 with the same elbow injury he is currently trying to play through this week. The veteran tackle was limited in practice throughout the week, but the same could be said of his practices leading up to Week 3. It’s safe to assume he is truly questionable for Sunday. If he’s unable to play, Cornelius Lucas would likely draw the start in his absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8712-deb6-a7fd-d7df9a1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) will not play in Week 4 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8724-d6e9-af9d-8fb4ede20000</link>
      <description>Latham will now miss his third-straight game with a hip injury, but head coach Brian Callahan said the second-year tackle doesn’t need any surgery, but rather some rest and rehab. Now set to enter a third-straight week of rest, we’ll hope that Latham, who the team opted to keep off injured reserve, will be able to get right in time for Week 5’s game against the Cardinals. Backup RT John Ojukwu is expected to start in Latham’s absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8724-d6e9-af9d-8fb4ede20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
