<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:53:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that the Cowboys will play in “the NFL’s first-ever regular-season game next season in Rio de Janeiro.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3053-d355-a5bd-bf57c9540000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys’ opponent has not yet been revealed. This is the second international game to be announced today. The 49ers will also play the Rams in Melbourne, Australia next season. The Chiefs and Chargers notably played in São Paulo, Brazil in Week 1 of 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3053-d355-a5bd-bf57c9540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots LB Robert Spillane (ankle) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ff9-d89c-a1be-afff8c300000</link>
      <description>Spillane resumed practicing today after sitting out on Wednesday. He missed Weeks 14-18 with the same ankle injury, but managed to return for postseason play. Spillane aggravated the injury in the AFC Championship Game, yet remained confident that he would play in Super Bowl LX against the Seahawks. Today’s return is a good sign. Unfortunately, Patriots LB Harold Landry (knee) was downgraded today after logging a limited session on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2ff9-d89c-a1be-afff8c300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks S Nick Emmanwori (ankle) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d042-afbc-7dff11c90000</link>
      <description>Seahawks head coach Mike Macdonald told reporters earlier today that he is “confident” Emmanwori will play in Super Bowl LX against the Patriots. Shortly thereafter, ESPN’s Jeff Darlington said that Emmanwori underwent imaging on the injured ankle and, in a poorly worded report, indicated that Emmanwori avoided a high-ankle sprain. The rookie safety notably suffered a high-ankle sprain in the same ankle back in Week 1, causing him to miss Weeks 2-4. Hopefully, Emmanwori resumes practicing tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-303f-d042-afbc-7dff11c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks QB Sam Darnold (oblique) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3063-d89c-a1be-bfff852c0000</link>
      <description>This is great news. A report from this afternoon indicated that Darnold would again participate in a limited capacity, as he has done since injuring his oblique during the Seahawks’ final Divisional Round practice. Darnold is ready to go for Super Bowl LX against the Patriots. Seahawks LT Charles Cross (foot) remains limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3063-d89c-a1be-bfff852c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hired Lou Esposito as their new defensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3083-d89c-a1be-bfdff8d00000</link>
      <description>This will be Esposito’s first time coaching in the NFL. Esposito spent the last two seasons coaching Michigan’s defensive line. From 2017-2023, he served as Western Michigan’s defensive coordinator and defensive line coach. He spent time coaching at smaller schools like Davenport and Ferris State before that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3083-d89c-a1be-bfdff8d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myles Garrett was named Defensive Player of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3071-d355-a5bd-bf753d7e0000</link>
      <description>Garrett totaled 23 sacks this season, setting a new NFL record along the way. He notably won Defensive Player of the Year in 2023 as well, following a 14-sack season. The nine-year veteran has astonishingly totaled double-digit sack tallies in all but his 2017 rookie season. The 30-year-old defensive end deservedly signed a four-year contract, averaging $40 million per year last offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-3071-d355-a5bd-bf753d7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos OLB Nik Bonitto underwent a cleanup procedure on his wrist.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-308a-d629-a1bc-b09f02750000</link>
      <description>Per the Denver Post’s Luca Evans, Bonitto injured his wrist by “slamming the ground” moments after the Broncos’ Week 2 loss to the Colts. He then played the rest of the season with a large club on his right hand. Despite the issue, Bonitto still totaled 17 sacks this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-308a-d629-a1bc-b09f02750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan was named Offensive Rookie of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30c1-d042-afbc-7dd390310000</link>
      <description>McMillan caught 70-of-120 targets for 1,014 yards and seven touchdowns this season, leading all NFL rookies in the latter two categories. The Panthers’ promising youngster proved himself as an NFL-ready No. 1 wide receiver. He is primed for another big outing in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30c1-d042-afbc-7dd390310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Thuney was named Protector of the Year.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd91e60000</link>
      <description>Thuney wins the NFL’s inaugural offensive linemen award in his first season with the Bears, who acquired him in exchange for a 2026 fourth-round draft pick in March 2025. Although the left tackle position remains one of the most important positions in football, Thuney, a left guard, winning the award proves that Protector of the Year will not simply be handed to the NFL’s best left tackle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-30cc-d629-a1bc-b0dd91e60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
