<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 4-of-5 targets for 54 yards in the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b63-d45b-affe-7ff7b6460000</link>
      <description>Ertz delivers the prototypical tight end receiving line in this one, with his lone incomplete target sailing far over his head via a downfield opportunity on the Commanders’ first drive. Fill-in starting QB Marcus Mariota may have simply been trying for a defensive pass interference call. Ertz remains a TE1 against the Dolphins in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b63-d45b-affe-7ff7b6460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 3-of-4 targets for 34 yards in the 49ers’ Week 10 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b63-d713-ad9e-6f77d99c0000</link>
      <description>He was the only 49ers player to have more than two targets besides George Kittle, Jauan Jennings, and Christian McCaffrey. Robinson played just 29 snaps as they favored letting Luke Farrell and Kyle Juszczyk play in bigger personnel. He’s not really on the fantasy radar at this point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b63-d713-ad9e-6f77d99c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Bourne caught his only target for 19 yards in the 49ers’ Week 10 loss to the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d713-ad9e-6f75d2060000</link>
      <description>We miss the Mac Jones/Kendrick Bourne friendship. Since going for 142 yards in back-to-back games in Week 5 and Week 6, Bourne has managed a total of 111 yards in four games, with just nine targets. If you were holding on to him hoping that Mac Jones would eventually get back to his main man, you can let go of those dreams. It looks like it will take injuries to make that happen again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d713-ad9e-6f75d2060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treylon Burks caught 3-of-3 targets for 58 yards in the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b60-d713-ad9e-6f746bb00000</link>
      <description>Burks astonishingly led the Commanders in receiving yards this week. His performance was highlighted by hauling in a deep, contested catch along the left sideline for 38 yards. Across two 2025 appearances, he has now caught 4-of-4 targets for 75 yards. Boasting tight end-esque size and athleticism, Burks is sauntering toward waiver wire consideration. Burks notably out-snapped Commanders rookie WR Jaylin Lane 21-15. Lane caught 1-of-1 targets for 41 yards. The Commanders face the Dolphins in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b60-d713-ad9e-6f746bb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed 11 times for 30 yards in the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b64-d45b-affe-7ff6a3a00000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt’s Week 10 showing marks his sixth sub-40-yard rushing outing. The run-centric back is struggling to produce on his own, but the Commanders also continue to fall into pass-heavy game scripts. Things were briefly looking up on the sixth drive, when he touched the ball on five of the first seven plays, before being subbed out when the offense was on the Lions’ five-yard line on third down. On the next play, Commanders QB Marcus Mariota lined up in the shotgun, snapped the ball and patty-caked it into WR Deebo Samuel’s hands, who had been sent in motion pre-snap. The play gained just one yard, but the Commanders successfully went back to Samuel on a flat route in the end zone on fourth down. Croskey-Merrit was later brought in for a two-point conversion attempt, but he was stood up by Lions LB Jack Campbell. RB Chris Rodriguez notably suffered a shoulder injury this afternoon, and the Commanders face the Dolphins’ league-worst run defense in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b64-d45b-affe-7ff6a3a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rodriguez rushed six times for 16 yards and one touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 10 loss to the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d1e7-a1fa-7beffab80000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez out-snapped Jacory Croskey-Merritt 17-4 in the first half before hurting his shoulder after logging one snap in the third quarter. He was initially labeled as questionable to return, but never retook the field. While Croskey-Merritt has continued to disappoint, Rodriguez hardly played better, averaging 2.7 yards per carry. His touchdown was an easy one-yard scamper off the left tackle on the Commanders’ fourth drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b65-d1e7-a1fa-7beffab80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Harrison, Jr. caught 3-of-12 targets for 33 yards and a touchdown in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b85-d673-a39e-ef95218f0000</link>
      <description>Harrison nearly came down with another touchdown on an inefficient outing against Seattle’s stingy secondary. Twenty-five of Jacoby Brissett’s 44 pass attempts went to Harrison and Trey McBride, a good formula for weekly fantasy upside. Harrison has 22 targets over his past two games; he had a career day last time the Cards played in Week 8 against Dallas. Brissett’s play — and the increased pass volume of the Arizona offense with Kyler Murray benched — makes MHJ a weekly top-12 fantasy option. That should continue in Week 11 against a weak Niners defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b85-d673-a39e-ef95218f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emari Demercado had four rushes for 64 yards in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding three catches for 40 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8a-d673-a39e-ef9be93c0000</link>
      <description>When Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon said the team’s backfield usage in Week 10 would be “similar but not the same,” he meant it. Demercado, a week after functioning as the main rushing back, took on the pass-catching role against the Seahawks. He ran 22 routes on the day to 19 routes for Bam Knight, who had one grab for five yards. Demercado remains the most explosive backfield option for the Cardinals, though Trey Benson’s return to the lineup — which could come as soon as Week 11 against the 49ers — would make Demercado little more than a bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8a-d673-a39e-ef9be93c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacoby Brissett completed 22-of-42 attempts for 258 yards and two touchdowns in the Cardinals’ Week 10 loss against the Seahawks, adding four rushes for 31 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8f-d673-a39e-ef9f4f150000</link>
      <description>Brissett lost not one but two fumbles for Seattle touchdowns early in the game as the Seahawks built a 35-0 lead in the middle of the second quarter. The game functionally over, Brissett and the Cardinals shifted into pass-heavy comeback mode, leading to 56 Brissett drop backs. He targeted Marvin Harrison Jr. (12 targets) and Trey McBride (13 targets) relentlessly, especially in the red zone. Brissett nearly had a third and a fourth touchdown in furious second half drives after a series of Seattle miscues. Brissett continues to make McBride a league-winning tight end play and puts MHJ in the weekly top-12 wideout conversation. He’ll be a reasonable streamer in Week 11 against an injury-marred Niners defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b8f-d673-a39e-ef9f4f150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught both of his targets for 74 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 10 win against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</link>
      <description>Kupp, returning from a hamstring injury that kept him sidelined in Week 9, had an electric 67-yard catch and run in the second quarter before the Seahawks shut down the passing offense up 35-0 on the hapless Cards. Kupp ran a route on 10 of Sam Darnold’s 13 drop backs on the day. He should hold some PPR value coming down the stretch of the regular season. Kupp will be a top-36 play in Week 11 against a vulnerable Niners secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6b94-d673-a39e-ef956d470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
