<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marquez Valdes-Scantling caught 5-of-7 targets for 34 yards in the Steelers’ Week 18 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c80-dc7a-af9b-cfbfac6e0000</link>
      <description>Scantling was wide open for what would have been a 30-plus yard gain, but Aaron Rodgers overthrew the pass. The wideout was able to haul in a decent amount of targets, but the yardage leaves a lot to be desired. MVS will be a secondary option at best for the Wild Card Round bout against the Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c80-dc7a-af9b-cfbfac6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Loop made 1-of-2 field goals and all three extra-point attempts in the Ravens’ Week 18 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c8a-d968-a19b-dcfb7fff0000</link>
      <description>Loop has been one of the best kickers in football even as a rookie, but his season ends on a dour note as he missed what would have been a game-winning field goal with no time remaining. The 24-year-old shouldn’t have any issues with job security to open 2026 even with the miss, and he’ll be worthy of fantasy consideration in leagues that still employ kickers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c8a-d968-a19b-dcfb7fff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 3-of-5 passes for 51 yards in the Steelers’ Week 18 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c96-d35e-a1bf-cdd6fa100000</link>
      <description>Freiermuth did most of his damage on a 31-yard connection with Aaron Rodgers that set up a Kenneth Gainwell touchdown. The 27-year-old has been routinely catching around three passes a game for the majority of the season, and he likely will see a similar amount of targets against the Texans next Monday in the Wild Card Round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8c96-d35e-a1bf-cdd6fa100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns fired coach Kevin Stefanski.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-84a7-d56e-afff-e6ef88660000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter had the report Monday morning. The move comes on the heels of multiple weekend missives, including one from Schefter himself, that the Browns planned to move on from their coach of six years. The 43-year-old two-time Coach of the Year will still have a chance to be a head coach next year as he’ll likely be one of the top names in this offseason’s coaching carousel, especially given his offensive-minded background. Stefanski won 11 games twice in his first four years with the Browns, but is out after going 7-26 over the last two years. GM Andrew Berry will remain in place and lead the search for a new head coach, according to a statement from Browns owners Dee and Jimmy Haslam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-84a7-d56e-afff-e6ef88660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals to retain head coach Zac Taylor and GM Duke Tobin next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eae-d56e-afff-eeeebb280000</link>
      <description>Following an emphatic report from NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport over the weekend that Taylor was going nowhere, the Bengals announced that they’re sticking with the 42-year-old coach Monday morning. Taylor, who took the franchise to its third Super Bowl appearance in 2021 and first since 1988, has also overseen the team nosedive in the last three seasons. Cincinnati hasn’t made the playoffs in three years, with significant injuries to quarterback Joe Burrow impacting two of those seasons. The Bengals defense allowed 492 points this year, the most in franchise history, after moving on from defensive coordinator Lou Anarumo last offseason. Taylor’s contract reportedly runs through the 2027 season, giving him job security that it is difficult to say he’s earned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eae-d56e-afff-eeeebb280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants to retain GM Joe Schoen next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ec0-dc7a-af9b-cfffef7f0000</link>
      <description>The Giants are 22-45-1 in four seasons under Schoen, which includes one playoff appearance and one playoff victory. According to a report from the New York Post’s Ryan Dunleavy, Schoen will lead the search for hiring a new coach, his second with the Giants. Around this time last year, Giants owner John Mara gave his coach Brian Daboll and Schoen a vote of confidence with the implication being that if the Giants had another bad season, both would be looking for new jobs. Daboll didn’t make it past Week 10 as he was fired with a 2-8 record, but somehow Schoen remains. Landing Malik Nabers, Theo Johnson, Tyrone Tracy, Abdul Carter, Jaxson Dart and Cam Skattebo in the last two drafts has bought him more time, however misguided that might be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ec0-dc7a-af9b-cfffef7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is expected to play against the Panthers in the Wild Card round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eea-d56e-afff-eeea25e00000</link>
      <description>Adams hasn’t played since he re-aggravated his hamstring injury in Week 15 against the Lions. The 33-year-old receiver enjoyed one of his best seasons, catching 14 touchdowns from Matthew Stafford in 14 games. The Rams tried to recreate Adams in the aggregate, using tight ends and depth receivers in his spot over the last few weeks. Stafford and McVay have to be thrilled that Adams is coming back for the playoff game against the Panthers, a team that beat the Rams in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eea-d56e-afff-eeea25e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders fired coach Pete Carroll.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ef4-d968-a19b-def54eb80000</link>
      <description>Of all of Monday’s firings, this one will go down as the most inevitable, as well as the most necessary. Although inarguably one of the greatest football coaches in American history, Carroll proved out of ideas as the literal oldest head coach in NFL history. His plan to “run back” his final 9-8 Seahawks campaigns with Geno Smith was dead on arrival, with an archaic offensive approach somehow proving incapable of getting the ball to the likes of Brock Bowers and Jakobi Meyers. Things were even worse along the offensive line, where Carroll curiously never placed much emphasis even during his most successful seasons in Seattle. There are bigger problems than Carroll with this franchise — who exactly is in charge, for instance — but he was not going to be the solution in 2026. The Silver and Black will be hiring their fifth full-time head coach since moving to Nevada in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ef4-d968-a19b-def54eb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers told reporters if his body doesn’t feel right, he won’t play in Week 1 next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8efc-d968-a19b-defd9e440000</link>
      <description>Nabers is recovering from surgery on his ACL and meniscus. The 22-year-old receiver told reporters Monday, “My target date is when my body feels good to get out there and I can continue to be who I am.” As for Week 1, Nabers said, “If my body doesn’t feel right (Week 1) then I’m not going to play.” Previous reports expected him to be good to go for the start of the 2026 season, though Nabers has at least introduced the possibility that his return might take longer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8efc-d968-a19b-defd9e440000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
