<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 20:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said Tyjae Spears will miss a few weeks with a high-ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94b2-d90d-a5bd-b6fbca400000</link>
      <description>Spears’ preseason is now over, as the third-year back will look to get right before Week 1 when the Titans visit the Broncos. Spears exited Saturday’s preseason game against the Buccaneers on a cart after totaling 12 yards from scrimmage on four touches. Tony Pollard will likely serve in a three-down role throughout the duration of Spears’ absence, but as far as the preseason is concerned, Julius Chestnut and Kalel Mullings will stand to see increased workloads over the final two preseason games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94b2-d90d-a5bd-b6fbca400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said the team needs “to give Sean Tucker the ball more.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d2-d90d-a5bd-b6db27850000</link>
      <description>Been there, heard that. Bowles echoed a similar sentiment last season after he unexpectedly broke out for 14-136-1 on the ground while adding another 3-56-1 through the air in Week 6 against the Saints. The end result was Tucker rushing 34 times for 165 yards and one touchdown over the final 11 games of the season. It’s worth pointing out, however, that Tucker could see an increased role after Rachaad White exited yesterday’s preseason game with a groin injury, but there’s little reason at this time to believe Tucker would see enough opportunities to make him fantasy relevant when all three backs are healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d2-d90d-a5bd-b6db27850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Matthew Stafford (back) will return to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d8-df63-a199-ddfbef7d0000</link>
      <description>It was reported late last week that Stafford could practice on Monday if his workout before Saturday’s preseason game went well. Stafford reportedly threw 60-plus passes in the workout and looked good, paving the way for a return to the field on Monday. Stafford will have just under four weeks to ramp things up for Week 1 when the Rams play host to the Texans. While it sounds like he’s trending in the right direction, it will be worth monitoring reports out of camp to see if his back responds well to the recovery and epidural he received to help mitigate the issue. If for some reason Stafford can’t play in the season opener, Jimmy Garoppolo would be the favorite to open Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d8-df63-a199-ddfbef7d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said L’Jarius Sneed (knee) is close to returning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94f3-d90d-a5bd-b6fbe1440000</link>
      <description>Callahan wouldn’t provide a timeline for Sneed’s return, but it’s encouraging news for the veteran corner who has been on the PUP list all of camp. Sneed had a cleanup procedure for his knee back in May. He appeared in just five games for the Titans last season due to a quad injury, and said in June that he was as “healthy as [he’s] been.” Sneed, 28, signed a four-year, $76.4 million contract with the Titans last offseason and is expected to play a key role for a secondary that ranked ninth in YPA allowed last season. At some point, we would expect to receive word on whether or not the Titans anticipate Sneed being ready for Week 1 against the Broncos, but with nearly a month to go, Callahan may play it close to the vest a bit longer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94f3-d90d-a5bd-b6fbe1440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said Rachaad White (groin) will undergo further tests.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9512-d05a-adda-bf9237070000</link>
      <description>White ran six times for 28 yards before exiting Saturday’s win over the Titans. The fourth-year back entered training camp firmly as the RB2 on Tampa Bay’s depth chart, and is already at risk of losing additional work in the passing game to Bucky Irving. Should White’s absence stretch into the regular season, Sean Tucker would stand to see an increased workload behind Irving, but Irving remains the only back to bet on for guaranteed double-digit touches in this offense. We’ll check back in on White’s availability when we receive an update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9512-d05a-adda-bf9237070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed RB Jeff Wilson, formerly of the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-952c-d05a-adda-bfaeb74b0000</link>
      <description>Wilson, 29, has spent the last 2.5 seasons in Miami after being dealt to the Dolphins during the 2022 trade deadline. Since then, the veteran back has struggled with injuries and an inability to find consistent playing time in a Dolphins backfield that has been ripe with young, explosive talent. Wilson’s signing comes after the 49ers lost Isaac Guerendo (shoulder) for"a few weeks” and rookie Jordan James to a broken finger. Both running backs could have a chance to be ready for the start of the season, but they’ll be cutting it close. Wilson spent five seasons playing with the Niners in Kyle Shanahan’s system and can provide a sense of familiarity to the backfield. Wilson rushed for 57 scoreless yards on 16 carries last season and shouldn’t be viewed as a permanent fixture on the 49ers’ roster once Guerendo and James are able to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-952c-d05a-adda-bfaeb74b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luther Burden caught two of three targets for 29 yards in the Bears’ preseason game against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9552-d90d-a5bd-b75b9b790000</link>
      <description>The second-round rookie saw early work with the second-team offense and led all Bears pass-catchers with three targets during his limited time on the field. His most notable play came on a third and 13, when he converted a first down on a 16-yard reception. Burden is expected to contribute early in three-receiver sets for the Bears, but may struggle to earn significant targets as long as D.J. Moore and Rome Odunze are healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9552-d90d-a5bd-b75b9b790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcasters covering the Bears’ preseason Week 1 game against the Dolphins said the team is taking CB Jaylon Johnson’s (leg) health, “day by day, week by week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9562-df63-a199-dd6bfe800000</link>
      <description>The Bears reportedly have “no concerns” about the injury, due to Johnson’s rigorous rehab, but the team representative avoided directly answering the broadcaster’s question regarding Johnson’s Week 1 availability. Johnson’s health is worth following closely. The Bears will have an extremely difficult time covering Justin Jefferson if Johnson is not on the field come Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9562-df63-a199-dd6bfe800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker III (undisclosed) did not practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9563-df63-a199-dd6b52b70000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Brady Henderson reports that Seahawks coaches were unavailable for comment after practice. Walker was sidelined by a sore foot earlier in training camp. Zach Charbonnet is one of fantasy football’s most valuable bench stashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9563-df63-a199-dd6b52b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears signed RB Brittain Brown, formerly of the Seahawks, to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9584-df63-a199-ddaf88470000</link>
      <description>The Bears need extra depth with Roschon Johnson sidelined by a foot injury. Brown has not played an offensive snap in the NFL. He last contributed on special teams with the Raiders in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9584-df63-a199-ddaf88470000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
