<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns Beat Reporter reports LB Jeremiah Owusu-Koramoah is “doubtful to ever to return to the field.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-826a-d990-a1de-ee6e116d0000</link>
      <description>Owusu-Koramoah suffered a terrifying neck injury in 2024 and missed the entirety of the 2025 season while recovering from the injury. It now appears as if his days of playing competitive football are done. It’s an unfortunate situation for the former Pro Bowl linebacker but he at least appears to have recovered from the injury enough to lead a normal life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-826a-d990-a1de-ee6e116d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLKY Louisville reports Vikings WR Rondale Moore has passed away at the age of 25.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8305-d89c-a1be-afdf1dbb0000</link>
      <description>Moore passed away Saturday in New Albany, Ind. The Vikings have confirmed his death. Devastatingly, the New Albany police chief said Moore is believed to have taken his own life, but an autopsy has been scheduled for Sunday. The 25-year-old spent the 2025 season on Minnesota’s injured reserve after doing the same for the Falcons in 2024. The No. 49 overall pick of the 2021 draft, Moore was a high school and college sensation despite his 5-foot-7 frame. His NFL career was sadly beset by injury, but he still caught 135 passes across 39 games, and was a factor on special teams. Our thoughts are with Moore’s family, friends, and teammates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8305-d89c-a1be-afdf1dbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports Alabama QB Ty Simpson will throw at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85ad-d629-a1bc-b5bd431a0000</link>
      <description>Simpson will be looking to shore up the QB2 ranking in the class. The Alabama quarterback came out of nowhere last year with a conference-leading 473 attempts for 3,567 yards, 28 touchdowns, and five interceptions. Simpson had thrown just 50 passes in his first three seasons as Tuscaloosa. Scouts will want to get as deep of a look as they can at Simpson, so it makes plenty of sense for him to throw at the combine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85ad-d629-a1bc-b5bd431a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Michael DiRocco believes Brian Thomas Jr.'s stats “may not reach what they were in 2024.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85b4-d042-afbc-fdf659e50000</link>
      <description>Rest assured that Thomas will be “a key piece of head coach Liam Cohen’s offense,” but DiRocco seems to believe that Thomas’ complementary role will endure in 2026. DiRocco also notes that Thomas looked uncomfortable in training camp, setting the scene for an ugly early-season run. Thomas has had plenty of trade buzz from the outside this offseason, but a trade probably relies on another team evaluating him at his 2024 level rather than his 2025 level. If he remains in Jacksonville, it’s hard to count on him as more than a WR3 pick in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85b4-d042-afbc-fdf659e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini believes the Cardinals could be a “potential suitor” for RB Breece Hall.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85cf-d629-a1bc-b5df04b70000</link>
      <description>Cimini connects these dots through new head coach Mike LaFleur, who coached Hall with the Jets. Arizona’s backfield is in a major state of flux after all of last season’s backs (James Conner, Trey Benson, Zonovan Knight) suffered season-ending injuries. It’s a vacuum where Hall would make sense. Cimini believes the Jets would like to extend Hall before he hits the open market, but may wind up using the franchise or transition tags instead — or on the way to — a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85cf-d629-a1bc-b5df04b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kris Rhim believes the Chargers could “make a push” to sign Ravens C Tyler Linderbaum in free agency.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85d5-d629-a1bc-b5dd63c60000</link>
      <description>The Chargers do not often dip outside of GM Joe Hortiz’s preferred free agency lanes, but Rhim speculates it might be different for the former Ravens center who Hortiz helped draft in 2022. The Chargers definitely have a need at the position as Bradley Bozeman has been outclassed the last few years. Linderbaum would do a lot to help fix an interior line that has just never come together. But this does rely on the Chargers doing something they haven’t really done under Hortiz yet: spending big in free agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85d5-d629-a1bc-b5dd63c60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes “it’s reasonable” to think George Kittle (Achilles) could return in Week 5 “or so.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85fe-d629-a1bc-b5ffa7d80000</link>
      <description>Wagoner’s long piece on Kittle’s injury is rooted in the idea that Kittle’s Achilles tear was “clean” and “happened high up by his soleus,” meaning the blood flow wasn’t as poor as it could be during the recovery. Kittle did not entirely rule out the idea of being ready for Week 1. We’d be surprised if a tight end entering his age-33 season was ready for Week 1, but we’ve learned not to count out any wild physical feats from Kittle. This timeline makes him a little more interesting in 2026 best ball, at the very least.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-85fe-d629-a1bc-b5ffa7d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Nick Kosmider expects the Broncos to “explore multiple other options” before attempting to re-sign J.K. Dobbins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8612-d629-a1bc-b61f0c5b0000</link>
      <description>As well as Dobbins played, this makes plenty of sense. The Broncos stumbled into him in post-draft free agency — he was no primary target — and he (as usual) missed a huge chunk of last season with an injury. With the Russell Wilson cap hold gone, the Broncos could be a sneaky threat for the bigger-name running backs in free agency in 2026. Kosmider does say it would not be “shocking” if Dobbins eventually comes back, but he’s not a priority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8612-d629-a1bc-b61f0c5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos hired John Morton as their new pass game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-86fe-d629-a1bc-b6ff8e2d0000</link>
      <description>Morton served as the Broncos’ pass game coordinator in 2023 and 2024 before accepting the Lions’ offensive coordinator role in 2025. He was relieved of play-calling duties in-season last year and fired in early January. The Broncos then brought him aboard as an offensive consultant for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-86fe-d629-a1bc-b6ff8e2d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders hired Mario Jeberaeel as their new run game coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8709-d042-afbc-ffdb55c90000</link>
      <description>Jeberaeel has coached in the NFL for five seasons, spending the last two seasons with the Jaguars and the three before that with the Falcons. He got started with the latter team as a diversity coaching intern and offensive line coach in 2021. He served as the assistant offensive line coach in 2022 before becoming a special projects coach on defense. The Jaguars hired him as an assistant outside linebackers coach in 2024. He spent 2025 working as a defensive assistant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-8709-d042-afbc-ffdb55c90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
