<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) has cleared protocol and will be activated from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a797-d82c-a79a-b797ac400000</link>
      <description>Ward sustained his concussion in pre-game warmups ahead of Week 6’s game with the Cardinals. His return should give the Colts a lot of versatility at cornerback as they can now boast a triumvirate of Sauce Gardner, Ward, and Kenny Moore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a797-d82c-a79a-b797ac400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Gabriel (concussion) practiced on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a79b-d82c-a79a-b79f70120000</link>
      <description>His return won’t impact any of the plans for Week 12, with Shedeur Sanders likely to start. Gabriel is still in the early stages of clearing concussion protocol, but his return on Friday is a good sign that he’ll be ready for Week 13 if the Browns choose to go back in that direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a79b-d82c-a79a-b79f70120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Mike Gesiciki (pectoral/IR) is questionable for Cincinnati’s Week 12 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a1-d413-ad9f-b7fd7e330000</link>
      <description>He was practicing in full all week, so the questionable tag leads us to believe the Bengals probably want to get Gesicki into game shape before activating him. Or, perhaps, it’s one of the most optimistic questionable tags of the week. If Gesicki does play, he and Noah Fant will cannibalize each other’s opportunities and leave neither of them as a sure-fire TE1, which is a shame because this Patriots outfit is a pass funnel that could support a mid-range TE1 finish from someone who actually got a full snap allotment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a1-d413-ad9f-b7fd7e330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kayshon Boutte (hamstring) will play in Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a5-db57-afda-f7b713f40000</link>
      <description>Boutte has missed the last two games with a hamstring injury he suffered in Week 9 against the Falcons, but the Patriots’ WR2 will be ready to go this week. Boutte gets a juicy Week 12 matchup against a Bengals defense that has struggled all season to slow down opposing passing attacks, which could bode well for Boutte in his return. Boutte has caught four or more passes in just two games this season, and profiles as a boom-or-bust WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a5-db57-afda-f7b713f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhamondre Stevenson (toe) is expected to play in Week 12 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a6-d90e-a9da-bfaf1bda0000</link>
      <description>The last thing fantasy managers who are rostering TreVeyon Henderson need is to worry about how Stevenson may eat into the rookie’s workload, but that concern is about to become very real in Week 12. While Henderson’s last two weeks have been highly productive on the ground (33-209-4), he’ll now face the possibility of Stevenson working into the mix. Stevenson was averaging 16.0 touches per game in his last three games before going down, and will likely be a safe bet for double-digit touches once he returns. Despite this, his highly-inefficient play will make him a risky bet as anything more than an RB3. He’s finished as a top-24 PPR back just three times this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a6-d90e-a9da-bfaf1bda0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) is not on Cleveland’s final Week 12 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a4-d82c-a79a-b7b4ccb80000</link>
      <description>Back-to-back DNPs would have put most players in a dicey situation to play, but the Browns trust their veteran tight end. His return will cut into Harold Fannin’s usage and keep both players off the high-TE2 borderline in a game where we’re expecting Shedeur Sanders to struggle against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a4-d82c-a79a-b7b4ccb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) won’t play in Cincinnati’s Week 12 game against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a9-d413-ad9f-b7fd04000000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson will miss his third-straight week with the injury, and has not practiced since the lead-up to Week 8’s game against the Jets. The Bengals will continue to be one of the defenses who turn WR3s into WR2s and TE2s into TE1s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7a9-d413-ad9f-b7fd04000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans WR Elic Ayomanor (hamstring) will not play in Tennessee’s Week 12 game against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc094d0000</link>
      <description>We’ll never get to see if his receiving line would have been 3/28 or 4/24 now. Van Jefferson and Chimere Dike look to be the main two receivers for an offense lacking any fantasy-football worthy juice at home against one of the best defenses in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7ac-d82c-a79a-b7bc094d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers coach Mike Tomlin said Aaron Rodgers (wrist) is questionable for Pittsburgh’s Week 12 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7bc-d90e-a9da-bfbfab0a0000</link>
      <description>“We’ll see where the weekend leads us,” Tomlin continued. Rodgers was limited on Thursday and Friday practices and was seen with a brace and wrap on his left wrist. It does seem to be trending towards Rodgers playing, but the chance of re-injury is a factor to consider before firing him up as a superflex QB2 in a good matchup. Mason Rudolph would start if Rodgers cannot go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7bc-d90e-a9da-bfbfab0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Rashod Bateman (ankle) could return in Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7bf-d82c-a79a-b7bfadb60000</link>
      <description>Bateman will be out for Week 12’s game against the Jets, but Harbaugh is hopeful they can get his 1.8 receptions per game for this season back in the lineup in Week 13 against the Bengals. DeAndre Hopkins figures to operate as the Ravens’ WR2 opposite Zay Flowers, but he can be avoided outside of deeper leagues after catching one pass for 11 yards in Week 11 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-a7bf-d82c-a79a-b7bfadb60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
