<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 16:53:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs S Deon Bush suffered a torn Achilles in Saturday’s preseason loss to the Cardinals and is out for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9431-d45c-a7fc-963b21120000</link>
      <description>The veteran safety exited in the second quarter of Saturday’s preseason game and had to be carted from the field. Bush has played almost exclusively on special teams since first joining the Chiefs in 2022 and has registered just 21 tackles in 24 games over that span. Still, his injury is a brutal reminder of the reality of preseason games as players battle for roster spots. Bush will be placed on injured reserve, ending his season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9431-d45c-a7fc-963b21120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blake Corum rushed nine times for 32 yards and two touchdowns in the Rams’ 31-21 preseason win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9437-df63-a199-dd3f4a7f0000</link>
      <description>Corum made the start as the Rams sat their starters for the first preseason game of the season. He averaged just 3.6 yards per carry, with his longest run on the afternoon coming on a nine-yard scamper, but he did manage to find the end zone on runs of two and four yards. Corum is only in his second season but is already battling for playing time with rookie fourth-rounder Jarquez Hunter. Their performances will be worth watching as they head into their next preseason game on Saturday against the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9437-df63-a199-dd3f4a7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RJ Harvey rushed seven times for 25 yards in the Broncos’ 30-9 preseason win over the 49ers, adding one catch for four additional yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-943d-d05a-adda-bebf1da00000</link>
      <description>After being listed as the RB5 on the team’s first preseason depth chart, Harvey surprisingly opened with the starters and handled every rush attempt while running with the first team unit. Head coach Sean Payton said after the game that Harvey will “continue to get work” with the starters, but also noted that other backs will also get their chance to play with the starters in next week’s preseason game against the Cardinals. Harvey being listed as the RB5 never should have been viewed as a negative for his long-term outlook this season. He still sounds like the favorite to split backfield duties alongside J.K. Dobbins, who did not play a snap in Saturday’s win over the Niners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-943d-d05a-adda-bebf1da00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Kevin Seifert reports Rondale Moore is expected to miss the season with a “pretty significant” left knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9452-d90d-a5bd-b65b24d00000</link>
      <description>It’s another brutal blow for Moore, who missed all of the 2024 season due to a dislocated right knee injury. Moore exited after the first play of the Vikings’ preseason game against the Texans on a tackle that head coach Kevin O’Connell said had “a lot of the characteristics” of the now-banned hip drop tackle. We’ll likely get official confirmation on Moore’s injury early in the week, but for now, it sounds like the former second-rounder will miss a second consecutive season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9452-d90d-a5bd-b65b24d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said James Cook “was not willing to play” in Saturday’s preseason game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-946c-d05a-adda-beee0e9d0000</link>
      <description>After a weeklong hold-in at training camp, Cook’s decision to sit out of Saturday’s preseason game was to be expected. His participation in pregame warmups, while in full uniform, gave the illusion of a player who was going to play, but that ultimately did not come to fruition. Cook continues to seek a contract extension from the Bills ahead of his final season, and reportedly had “a good conversation” with McDermott before the game. That said, this remains a wait-and-see situation, with no end in sight for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-946c-d05a-adda-beee0e9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets WR Allen Lazard was seen wearing an arm sling after Saturday’s preseason game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9472-d45c-a7fc-967a30ef0000</link>
      <description>Head coach Aaron Glenn said Lazard is dealing with a right shoulder injury and will undergo further testing to determine the severity of his injury. Lazard caught two passes for 17 yards in Saturday’s contest and is expected to serve as the Jets’ WR2 this season alongside Garrett Wilson. The team is hopeful that Lazard’s injury is nothing more than a bruise, but we should have an update soon. Even if it is a minor injury, Lazard doesn’t come with much fantasy upside in a Jets offense that’s expected to be among the most run-heavy in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9472-d45c-a7fc-967a30ef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletics’ Zac Jackson says “the Browns absolutely might keep all four quarterbacks” entering Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9499-d05a-adda-be9b9e250000</link>
      <description>This comes just days after Shedeur Sanders impressed in his preseason debut against the Panthers. While keeping four quarterbacks would be unconventional, the Browns’ quarterback room is anything but stable. Joe Flacco is preparing for what may be his final season. Meanwhile, Kenny Pickett is injured and has proven unreliable as a starter, while Sanders, along with fellow rookie Dillon Gabriel, who is also dealing with an injury, has a lot to prove. Sanders’ performance on Friday could earn him increased reps with the first or second-string offense if Pickett and Gabriel are unable to practice this week, which could also lead to him seeing a significant amount of snaps in Saturday’s preseason game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9499-d05a-adda-be9b9e250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said Tyjae Spears will miss a few weeks with a high-ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94b2-d90d-a5bd-b6fbca400000</link>
      <description>Spears’ preseason is now over, as the third-year back will look to get right before Week 1 when the Titans visit the Broncos. Spears exited Saturday’s preseason game against the Buccaneers on a cart after totaling 12 yards from scrimmage on four touches. Tony Pollard will likely serve in a three-down role throughout the duration of Spears’ absence, but as far as the preseason is concerned, Julius Chestnut and Kalel Mullings will stand to see increased workloads over the final two preseason games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94b2-d90d-a5bd-b6fbca400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles said the team needs “to give Sean Tucker the ball more.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d2-d90d-a5bd-b6db27850000</link>
      <description>Been there, heard that. Bowles echoed a similar sentiment last season after he unexpectedly broke out for 14-136-1 on the ground while adding another 3-56-1 through the air in Week 6 against the Saints. The end result was Tucker rushing 34 times for 165 yards and one touchdown over the final 11 games of the season. It’s worth pointing out, however, that Tucker could see an increased role after Rachaad White exited yesterday’s preseason game with a groin injury, but there’s little reason at this time to believe Tucker would see enough opportunities to make him fantasy relevant when all three backs are healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d2-d90d-a5bd-b6db27850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Matthew Stafford (back) will return to practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d8-df63-a199-ddfbef7d0000</link>
      <description>It was reported late last week that Stafford could practice on Monday if his workout before Saturday’s preseason game went well. Stafford reportedly threw 60-plus passes in the workout and looked good, paving the way for a return to the field on Monday. Stafford will have just under four weeks to ramp things up for Week 1 when the Rams play host to the Texans. While it sounds like he’s trending in the right direction, it will be worth monitoring reports out of camp to see if his back responds well to the recovery and epidural he received to help mitigate the issue. If for some reason Stafford can’t play in the season opener, Jimmy Garoppolo would be the favorite to open Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-94d8-df63-a199-ddfbef7d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
